Chapter 1278: Dog Tail Life Extending Ferret

Boom!

A loud sound was heard in the fate reversing refinement sub formation.

Flood Extremity was no longer surprised, after taking a glance, he looked away.

During this period, the Gu formation's pillar of light had shrunken by fifty percent.

"This Gu formation is quite interesting." Right at this time, a voice entered Flood Extremity's ears.

"Who is it?!" Flood Extremity was shocked, his Gu Immortal aura burst out as he prepared to use his powerful methods.

"Little one, don't be afraid, and don't make a move." The voice said again.

At this moment, Flood Extremity could not move.

He felt like he was in a frozen river.

This person was powerful beyond imagination. He was a rank seven Gu Immortal, one of Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities, but he could not react before he was suppressed completely!

"You are the descendant of master, as long as you do not attack me, I will not eat you. Hehehe." The voice said again.

Next, Flood Extremity saw a huge, hill-like beast revealing its figure in front of him.

This was a four legged beast with purple fur.

It looked like a ferret.

It was covered in shiny purple fur, its eyes were shining with a purple crystal-like color.

The most eye catching thing was its tail.

This was not a ferret tail, but a dog tail.

A giant ferret with a dog tail?

Flood Extremity was stunned, before he thought of an existence.

Indeed, at the next moment, South Desolation Immortal's letter came from an information path Gu worm in his immortal aperture — he could not leave now, this giant beast was sent here to help, it would deal with any enemy who dares to obstruct Longevity Heaven!

"You, you are the dog tail life extending ferret? Ancestor Giant Sun's steed?" Flood Extremity stammered.

The giant beast nodded before opening its mouth, speaking: "Stop calling me a steed, I have my own name too. I am Mao Li Qiu, you can call me Grandpa Mao."

"Mao, Grandpa Mao!" At the other end, Black Extremity was also tongue-tied, he was still in great shock.

"Okay, forget about this Gu formation. Let's go to Reverse Flow River and retrieve Ma Hong Yun and that love Gu!" The dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, slashed with its claws.

Intense winds blew, countless Gu worm auras were exposed, forming an immortal killer move.

The fate reversing refinement sub formation that Black Extremity had created with much difficulty broke apart, turning into rubble.

"This?!" Black Extremity's eyes almost popped out.

"Stop stammering, is it very fun to disrupt my sleep? Quickly finish this business, your Grandpa Mao has to go back to sleep!"

The giant ferret, Mao Li Qiu, said this as it breathed out deeply.

This breath flew rapidly, tying up Flood Extremity and Black Extremity.

The giant ferret jumped and its huge body flew into the sky.

Beside it, Black Extremity and Flood Extremity were pulled along by the special breath, going towards Reverse Flow River.

"What is going on?" The sudden change in Reverse Flow River affected all of the Gu Immortals in it.

After an intense change, the entirety of Reverse Flow River calmed down, the river water became smooth flowing and had small ripples in it.

"Reverse Flow River went back to normal?" Fang Yuan's eyes shone brightly, he felt the pressure intensifying in the river.

There was a large amount of junk unable to move on their own, they were washed down by Reverse Flow River.

Seeing this, at once, many Gu Immortals chose to go downstream and leave Reverse Flow River by getting to the end.

This was the only way to get out of Reverse Flow River.

"The situation is not looking good." Fang Yuan had not found Ying Wu Xie and gang, he continued moving forward.

In the sky, Bi Chen Tian and the other Central Continent Gu Immortals were looking down at Reverse Flow River.

These people were originally trying to swim forward, but Reverse Flow River kept returning to normal as the sub formation was destroyed.

Bi Chen Tian saw that this was not going well, he could continue, but the other Gu Immortals could not, they went downstream and left Reverse Flow River, flying towards the sky after they got out.

But this way, they became outsiders, any methods used on Reverse Flow River would be reflected back at them.

Bi Chen Tian soon found Fang Yuan, who was inside Reverse Flow River.

"Our fight can be disregarded, as long as you hand over affection Immortal Gu." Bi Chen Tian spoke to Fang Yuan.

"This is the rank seven Gu Immortal who could fight evenly with Lord Bi Chen Tian? How did he cultivate?" The other Central Continent Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan with shock and curiosity.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, he ignored Bi Chen Tian.

One of the Central Continent Gu Immortals flew into a rage: "Such audacity! You dare to disrespect Lord Bi Chen Tian!"

Bi Chen Tian snorted coldly: "You think I can do nothing to you if you hide inside the river?"

"Before I get washed away, you should worry about yourselves. This is not Central Continent." Fang Yuan replied fearlessly.

Bi Chen Tian's key concern was pointed out, his face turned cold as he ignored Fang Yuan, he started to move in the upstream direction.

Fang Yuan was a small matter. What was important was Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun.

Because the dog tail life extending ferret destroyed the sub formation, the complex situation at the surface of the river became easily observable now.

The junk was all swept away, only some Gu Immortals were left in the river.

Mu Ling Lan, Zhao Lian Yun, and Ma Hong Yun were at the front.

The second group were Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Purple Mountain True Monarch, and Lady Wan Shou.

The third group was rank eight Gu Immortal Wei Ling Yang, as well as some other Central Continent Gu Immortals.

The fourth group was Ying Wu Xie and gang, as well as some Snowy Mountain peak lords.

And the fifth group was Fang Yuan alone. When he was swept into Reverse Flow River, he was too far from Snowy Mountain blessed land, thus, he had fallen to the back of the river, even though he tried to swim upstream, the others were also working hard.

Honestly speaking, the situation was quite interesting.

"Quick, swim forward!" Mu Ling Lan looked at Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch who were close behind, he spoke anxiously.

The floating mound earlier was already swept away, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun had to swim forward to avoid getting captured by Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

The second group of Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch were chasing after Ma Hong Yun to capture him.

The third group including Wei Ling Yang also did not want to give up. As long as they stalled Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Purple Mountain True Monarch, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun would have the chance to go downstream and the crisis would be resolved.

Ying Wu Xie and the Snowy Mountain demonic path Gu Immortals also had the same idea as Wei Ling Yang, they were at the back but there was still hope.

"Quickly look, to the back!" Hei Lou Lan suddenly alerted.

Ying Wu Xie turned back and looked, his heart jumped: "He actually chased us to this place!"

This river was calm now, there was no junk left, everyone's field of vision was clear, thus Ying Wu Xie easily saw Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan still did not know about Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Even though he could see Old Ancestor Xue Hu at this position.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was a miniman, he was the size of a thumb and was sitting on Old Ancestor Xue Hu's shoulder, it was hard to see him clearly.

Fang Yuan had no idea what happened in Snowy Mountain blessed land. Even though he met Bi Chen Tian, he had only understood that a battle of rank eights happened here, as for who had the advantage, would Bi Chen Tian tell him?

Thus, Fang Yuan had always thought that killing Ying Wu Xie and gang would resolve his crisis regarding Shadow Sect.

Therefore, after seeing Ying Wu Xie, his eyes shone as he swam even more quickly towards Ying Wu Xie.

"He is our enemy?" A snowy mountain peak lord sneered at Fang Yuan: "Let's work together and kill him! Outside, the situation is complex with countless Gu Immortal methods available. But here, he is all alone, he is just one person!"

Once he said that, the Gu Immortals were ready to attack.

Ying Wu Xie was moved too.

If they could kill Fang Yuan now, and obtain his sovereign immortal body, it would be a great opportunity.

"However... the sovereign immortal body is not easy to deal with. I should meet up with Lord Purple first. Our main body is still in the dream realm after all!" Ying Wu Xie thought about it and decided to play safe.

"Come with us, we will meet up with Ancestor Xue Hu. He is not important, our biggest enemy is Central Continent." Ying Wu Xie did not expose Fang Yuan's foundation, he successfully diverted the attention of the Snowy Mountain Gu Immortals.

"That's right, let's meet with old ancestor!" Snowy Mountain's peak lords could not go downstream now.

Because a rank eight Central Continent Gu Immortal was in the sky. Once they left Reverse Flow River, they would need to face off against a rank eight Gu Immortal, they had to stay in Reverse Flow River for now.

But soon, they realized that it was not easy to stay in Reverse Flow River.

In this special environment, if they could not move forward, the river would push them backwards.

In the past, Ren Zu had failed in Reverse Flow River, he had failed at the final step before success.

Nobody thought that they could achieve what Ren Zu did. But in this situation, every wave of Gu Immortals had their own reasons to remain in Reverse Flow River!

"Ma Hong Yun... you cannot escape." Old Ancestor Xue Hu had a cold gaze as Lady Wan Shou smiled continuously.

"Quick, quick. They are catching up." Mu Ling Lan and Ma Hong Yun dragged Zhao Lian Yun along from either side.

"Fairy Lian Yun, hang on, we are going to reach soon!" Wei Ling Yang shouted.

Ying Wu Xie was behind them, waiting to strike. He felt a headache regarding Fang Yuan at the back, he needed to move forward more quickly, to fight for more time later.

"Ying Wu Xie!" Fang Yuan was shortening his distance with Ying Wu Xie.

Soon, the first person to be unable to persevere appeared.

It was one of Snowy Mountain's peak lords.

He had used up all his stamina, he floated backwards with a pale expression.

Fang Yuan avoided him.

Now was not the time for that, if he stopped for a moment, he would be pushed backwards as well, even if he killed the enemy, his progress would be greatly affected.

"Be careful!" In the sky, Bi Chen Tian shouted.

"I finally caught up. You little rats." Old Ancestor Xue Hu was already right behind Zhao Lian Yun's group.

Zhao Lian Yun knew that she had no strength left, if this continued, she would only burden Ma Hong Yun.

She gave Ma Hong Yun one last affectionate look, she suddenly mustered her strength and broke free from his grasp, swimming towards Old Ancestor Xue Hu instead.

Chapter 1279: Fervently Approaching Death!

"Mu Ling Lan!" Behind Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Wei Ling Yang shouted angrily.

Mu Ling Lan was already resolved, he gritted his teeth, moving even more quickly than Zhao Lian Yun, he pushed the weak Zhao Lian Yun into Ma Hong Yun's arms.

"You have to live well!"

Saying this, he turned around and grabbed Old Ancestor Xue Hu's waist.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu struggled intensely, but he still stop moving forward and was pushed away by the river.

The danger for Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun was averted.

"Quick, quickly go!" Ma Hong Yun held onto Zhao Lian Yun as his heart beat rapidly.

"Meddlesome fool!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu hated Mu Ling Lan to the core, he kicked Mu Ling Lan's chest several times in the water.

His dao marks far surpassed Mu Ling Lan's.

Mu Ling Lan was rank seven, how could he possible match him?

Soon, his bones were broken, he was spitting out blood, dying the water red.

More than ten breaths of time later, Mu Ling Lan could not take it anymore, he stopped breathing as he lost his life.

Seeing that their companion had died like this, the Central Continent Gu Immortals were all anguished.

"Mu Ling Lan, Central Continent will remember your sacrifice, Heavenly Court will remember it!" Wei Ling Yang called out, charging at Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was stalled by Mu Ling Lan, he had fallen behind to the third group.

He was immediately attacked by the furious and upset Central Continent Gu Immortals.

"Xue Hu!" Lady Wan Shou was worried about her husband, she quickly went to help him.

Both sides fought for a while, they were pushed backwards and quickly encountered Ying Wu Xie and the others, who were the fourth group.

As a result, a large number of Gu Immortals were fighting in this river, it was a chaotic scene.

Bi Chen Tian and the rest were watching in shock.

Grand Gu Immortals had lost their sagely demeanor, they were fighting in the water like brutish mortals.

But it was too late for Bi Chen Tian to interfere now.

Soon, blood dyed the surroundings as many Gu Immortal corpses flowed down the river.

"Ying Wu Xie!" Fang Yuan joined the group, he had finally arrived.

"Where is our lord?" Ying Wu Xie finally found Old Ancestor Xue Hu amidst the chaos, he asked this loudly.

"Upstream!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu answered.

It turned out that while Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Mu Ling Lan were fighting, Purple Mountain True Monarch had swam upstream to capture Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

Precisely because of this, Old Ancestor Xue Hu could fight with the Central Continent Gu Immortals, this was his plan to obstruct the enemies.

Ying Wu Xie got his answer and quickly swam with Hei Lou Lan and the rest, away from the fighting as he went towards Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Fang Yuan called out: "Ying Wu Xie, where are you going?"

Ying Wu Xie sighed, saying: "Tai Bai Yun Sheng."

"All of you leave first!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted, he charged at Fang Yuan with a resolute expression of someone disregarding death.

Fang Yuan was obstructed.

Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing managed to escape.

Bam bam bam!

Fang Yuan's attacks were powerful, Tai Bai Yun Sheng soon had broken bones and fractures.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng was resolved, he stalled Fang Yuan and grabbed onto him, he even used his teeth to bite and head to slam.

Fang Yuan could not break free for a period of time.

In this urgent situation, he exclaimed: "Old Bai, do you still remember Imperial Court blessed land?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was stunned, he exposed a flaw.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a ruthless light, his fingers pierced into Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes without mercy.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was heavily injured, blood was pouring out of his eyes.

Fang Yuan used this chance to unleash the finishing blow as Tai Bai Yun Sheng stopped moving entirely.

He was dead.

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan shrugged off Tai Bai Yun Sheng's corpse as he continued to swim, chasing after Ying Wu Xie.

During this period, the groups with Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Wei Ling Yang were engaged in fierce battle, they had finally separated as both sides suffered great losses.

Bi Chen Tian looked at Reverse Flow River from above, he could see the situation clearly.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were still at the lead.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was at the second position.

Ying Wu Xie and the other two were the third.

Fang Yuan was fourth.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou were the fifth.

Wei Ling Yang and the other Central Continent Gu Immortals were sixth.

Bi Chen Tian was anxious, the Central Continent immortals were in an extremely disadvantageous position.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were in front, but there was no longer anyone protecting them.

The second placed Purple Mountain True Monarch was an enemy, while Ying Wu Xie and gang were vicious members of Shadow Sect. The fifth placed Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou were also out of the question.

Without any choice, Bi Chen Tian could only approach Fang Yuan.

"You just need to protect the lives of those two in front, you will obtain the friendship of Central Continent and Heavenly Court!!"

"You can request anything, do you want Immortal Gu or cultivation resources, will my great Central Continent not be able to satisfy you?"

"As long as you help to protect Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun!"

"This again..." Fang Yuan heard this and sighed internally.

He thought of Imperial Court blessed land.

Back then, he had to make a choice too. If he chose to save Ma Hong Yun, it would have been extremely profitable for him!

And now, the situation was quite similar to back then in Imperial Court blessed land.

But Fang Yuan remained silent, he only continued swimming. He was bent on eliminating Ying Wu Xie and gang now, forget about Ma Hong Yun, he could bugger off.

But what followed was a long stalemate.

The further one traveled up Reverse Flow River, the harder it was to keep going.

Stamina and dao marks were secondary, it was a test of one's will.

"Lady Xiao Yun, we need to persevere, I believe that there will be a chance!" Ma Hong Yun continued to speak, encouraging Zhao Lian Yun.

The river water was icy cold, but inside Ma Hong Yun's embrace, Zhao Lian Yun felt immeasurable warmth.

This warmth was a huge driving force for her, she gritted her teeth and persevered on.

Behind them was Purple Mountain True Monarch.

"Ma Hong Yun! Zhao Lian Yun! Hehe! As long as I catch you, I will be able to restrain Old Ancestor Xue Hu. At that point, I will get him to deal with Southern Border's super dream realm." Purple Mountain True Monarch was planning deeply.

"Protect Lord Purple!" Ying Wu Xie was worried.

"Dear, dear, wake up!" Something happened to Old Ancestor Xue Hu's group.

Lady Wan Shou had fainted. She was heavily injured in the battle, after enduring and persisting for a while, she fainted.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was flustered.

He gritted his teeth and stopped swimming, he carried Lady Wan Shou as Reverse Flow River swept them away.

Wei Ling Yang allowed him to leave, they wanted to have one less competitor.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu quickly left Reverse Flow River, he used his Gu Immortal methods to stabilize Lady Wan Shou's condition.

Bi Chen Tian was nervous, he could not deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu alone. The Gu Immortals around him, without any Immortal Gu Houses, could not interfere in a rank eight fight!

"I will kill you first!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu carefully placed the unconscious Lady Wan Shou in his immortal aperture.

Next, he charged at Bi Chen Tian.

He was the number one person in Northern Plains' demonic path, he was a ruthless person, how could he give up this chance to deal with these weakened opponents?

"It's only death at worst." Bi Chen Tian was resolved to die, he neither evaded nor dodged.

But right when the two rank eights were about to fight, they felt an intensely strong aura.

The hill-like dog tailed purple ferret carried Flood Extremity and Black Extremity, as they arrived at the bank of Reverse Flow River.

Chapter 1280: Perseverance

Outside Reverse Flow River.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu wanted to kill Bi Chen Tian, but at this moment, the dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, appeared.

"Why is this ferret here? Doesn't it stay inside its cave all the time?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu was surprised.

This ferret had a huge origin, it was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's steed. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had subdued it in his later years, his motive was clearly to find a lifespan extension method.

The dog tail life extending ferret's dao marks were very numerous and mystical.

As it grew older, the dog tail would shrink as its lifespan decreased. When its lifespan nears its end, the tail would vanish.

Thus, whenever it sensed that its life was ending, it would devour an immemorial desolate beast dog. After consuming it, the dog tail life extending ferret would gain the lifespan of this immemorial desolate beast dog, its tail would grow out and it would continue living.

Precisely so, even after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable died, the dog tail life extending ferret still lived until now.

This giant ferret was enlightened by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it gained intelligence and learned to use Gu worms and even immortal killer moves.

It was an immemorial desolate beast to begin with, now that it had wisdom and could use Immortal Gu and other methods, it had unfathomably deep strength.

Even Old Ancestor Xue Hu was wary of it.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu had wanted to deal with Bi Chen Tian, but with the dog tail life extending ferret's appearance, he discarded this plan.

"To think that Mao Li Qiu would save me!" Bi Chen Tian let out a breath of air, he relaxed slightly.

He also knew about the dog tail life extending ferret.

Immemorial desolate beasts of this level were too famous. It was like Central Continent's Huo Kong, or that Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng, they were unique existences, their battle strength was at the peak of rank eight!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu quickly focused his gaze on the two Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals accompanying the dog tail life extending ferret.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's gaze focused on Black Extremity.

He chuckled coldly: "As expected, Sun Ming Lu, you are a member of Longevity Heaven! To think that Longevity Heaven had targeted me since so long ago."

He had already made a guess earlier, now that he saw Black Extremity, it was confirmed.

Black Extremity greeted Old Ancestor Xue Hu respectfully: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu, we meet again. I am one of Longevity Heaven's Eight Extremities, Black Extremity, Sun Ming Lu is simply a name I use when I travel in Northern Plains."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu chuckled coldly again, but he did not attack.

Because Black Extremity was beside the dog tail life extending ferret.

It was not like Old Ancestor Xue Hu feared Mao Li Qiu, but he knew that the crux of this issue was not the three of them, it was the events in Reverse Flow River.

With the situation in Reverse Flow River unconfirmed, it was not time to fight, a third party would benefit if he did.

After Black Extremity and Old Ancestor Xue Hu exchanged greetings, their gazes became fixed on Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

"Grandpa Mao, the two at the front are our targets!" Black Extremity reminded the dog tail life extending ferret.

Bi Chen Tian frowned slightly.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's cold laughter became even colder.

But Mao Li Qiu nonchalantly curled its lips, its beast face made a very human-like expression: "No rush! Wait for them to decide a victor. We are outside Reverse Flow River, we can use Gu worms but we cannot affect the river itself. Any method used on Reverse Flow River will be reflected back upon us, why would I waste my effort? Reverse Flow River would only lose some water when it reflects an attack, this river is huge, how long would it take to dry out this river? I would not do something so time consuming and pointless!"

Saying this, it paused before saying: "Don't worry, these people can't continue for long. The further they swim, the more it tests their will. Hehe, they are swimming in Reverse Flow River, any thoughts of persevering in this river would be reversed by the river, any sort of determination would waver, they would eventually be washed away by the river."

The three rank eight existences were wary of each other, they did not fight.

Outside the river, there was a deadlock, the Gu Immortals thus looked towards Reverse Flow River.

Inside the river.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were still at the lead.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was second, he was inching closer to them.

Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, and Hei Lou Lan were third.

Next was Fang Yuan.

The fifth position was originally Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou, but earlier, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had given up the contest for the sake of his unconscious wife, he went outside the river.

Thus, the fifth position went to Heavenly Court's rank eight rule path Gu Immortal Wei Ling Yang, and several Central Continent Gu Immortals.

Purple Mountain True Monarch moved with all four limbs, flapping his thin wings at times.

Ma and Zhao were already close by.

"I need to persevere and capture these two, I will be able to control Old Ancestor Xue Hu and deal with Central Continent!"

Purple Mountain True Monarch was filled with determination.

Reverse Flow River's water continued to assault the will in his mind.

He shrugged his head, trying to get rid of his hesitation.

"Ninety thousand years ago, heaven's will attacked. I deduced with all my effort and found a trace of hope for survival. By sealing myself, I turned into a purple-gold rock. But to think that heaven's will would still harm me and I would go into a crazy state at times."

"These last hundred thousand years, I woke up many times and experienced great danger, I only escaped from danger and survived with Shadow Sect's help."

"Right now, my main body refined sovereign immortal aperture, but it was stolen from us."

"My main body is stuck in the dream realm, being in great danger."

"The great Shadow Sect is just a shadow of its past, I cannot fail in this situation, I need to persevere, I need to capture Zhao and Ma."

"I am about to succeed!"

Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes were shining, he was extremely close to the two.

"Oh no, Purple Mountain True Monarch is about to reach Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun!" The Central Continent Gu Immortals were shocked.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Ying Wu Xie had expressions filled with joy.

"What do we do?" Flood Extremity shouted.

"Nothing!" Mao Li Qiu rolled its eyes: "Unless they come out."

"Ah——!" But at this moment, Purple Mountain True Monarch suddenly grabbed his head as he screamed, he struggled intensely as he showed intense pain on his face.

"What is going on?"

"What happened?"

The immortals were perplexed.

"At this very moment, damn it!" Ying Wu Xie internally cursed heaven's will.

At the crucial moment, Purple Mountain True Monarch fell into madness, he went downstream with the currents.

Thankfully, Ying Wu Xie and gang were following Purple Mountain True Monarch as insurance if he went crazy, he quickly grabbed Purple Mountain True Monarch as the four swam upstream together.

Thus, Ma and Zhao escaped from the dangerous situation, they were still in first place.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had fallen behind, becoming second place with Ying Wu Xie and gang.

Third was Fang Yuan.

And fourth was Wei Ling Yang and his Central Continent Gu Immortals.

"Lord Wei Ling Yang, it all depends on you now!" Bi Chen Tian was overjoyed.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals also started cheering.

It was good news to Central Continent that something happened to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Especially those Gu Immortals who did not know Fang Yuan, they felt that right now, only Central Continent's rank eight Wei Ling Yang was left, even though he was in last place, he could still win!

Wei Ling Yang was gritting his teeth.

The difficulty of swimming was rising, and more importantly, the Reverse Flow River was affecting his every thought.

Any thoughts of persevering and swimming ahead would be obstructed by Reverse Flow River.

Many thoughts were washed away, but there was one thought that was rooted in Wei Ling Yang's mind!

"I need to persevere!"

"I am the only hope left in Central Continent, if we capture Ma Hong Yun and save Zhao Lian Yun, we will be able to return victorious."

"I cannot fail!"

"Central Continent's pride, Heavenly Court's honor, they cannot be lost because of me!!"

Wei Ling Yang swam ahead stably without any hesitation.

The Gu Immortals around him also followed.

These Gu Immortals formed the biggest force in Reverse Flow River, it was eye-catching.

Even the dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, said: "Oh? It seems that Central Continent has a huge advantage. Hmph, Heavenly Court still likes meddling so much, this will not do, Ma Hong Yun is a Northern Plainsman!"

Bi Chen Tian frowned.

He looked at Mao Li Qiu, and Old Ancestor Xue Hu whose face was cold as ice, he was worried: "Even if Wei Ling Yang defeats the competitors and obtains Ma and Zhao, what will happen after he leaves Reverse Flow River?"

Bi Chen Tian thought from all angles, he could not find a way to escape, he could only continue watching.

Time passed by the seconds and minutes.

The situation was still the same in Reverse Flow River.

Ma and Zhao were first.

Ying Wu Xie and gang were second.

Fang Yuan was third.

And Wei Ling Yang and the other Central Continent Gu Immortals were fourth.

The positions did not change, but their mutual distances had evidently shrunk.

"Oh? These people have all lasted until now, strange, why are there so many outstanding people here?" The dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, quipped: "As expected, the great era is coming, in an era which would create a venerable, a great number of geniuses and talented individuals would emerge like a tide."

Bi Chen Tian's eyes were shining too.

He was assessing the Central Continent Gu Immortals, and memorizing their faces.

These people had firm determination, if they grew without any accidents, they surely would be important pillars of each sect!

"Persevere! The mission of protecting Fairy Lian Yun is in my hands, I cannot give up!" Bu Zhen Zi frowned.

"Just like refining Gu, no matter how tough it is, or how unpredictable the results, as long as I persevere, I will be rewarded." Yu Yi Ye Zi encouraged himself.

Shi Zheng Yi had an angry expression: "Lord Mu Ling Lan was sacrificed to protect Fairy Lian Yun, how can I back down? Work harder! Shi Zheng Yi! For the sake of love and justice, you cannot back down!!"

Fang Yuan was expressionless, he stared ahead at Ying Wu Xie: "Such a close relationship, that rank eight miniman Gu Immortal who went crazy must be a member of Shadow Sect. I must kill him, I must eliminate them all! Inside Reverse Flow River, it is the best opportunity for me to eliminate these threats once and for all!"

Chapter 1281: Washed Away

Reverse Flow River flowed silently.

The further they went ahead, the calmer the river surface.

However, to the swimmers, Reverse Flow River was like a torrential tide, it defied all thoughts of traveling ahead.

Destruction of the body was not scary, destruction of thoughts and the mind was scary.

In the past, even Ren Zu failed in Reverse Flow River. These Gu Immortals were doing the same thing as Ren Zu now.

"Damn it, I cannot continue anymore!" At the next moment, Yu Yi Ye Zi reached his limits, he could not continue anymore, he was washed away by the tides.

And the second Central Continent Gu Immortal, followed by the third.

Shi Zheng Yi gave it his all, but he failed and was washed away by Reverse Flow River.

Bu Zhen Zi was unwilling, but he could only float away.

Bi Chen Tian and the rest were showing ugly expressions as each Central Continent Gu Immortal got eliminated.

Not long after, out of the Central Continent Gu Immortals, only rank eight Wei Ling Yang was left.

Being able to reach rank eight, he truly had shocking willpower!

Wei Ling Yang showed the foundation of a rank eight great expert.

As for those Gu Immortals who were washed away, they were all gathered by Bi Chen Tian and went back to the group, they were not obstructed by Old Ancestor Xue Hu, or the dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu.

"Why is it that our Gu Immortals were all swept away, but these random people are still inside the river?" Some Central Continent Gu Immortals were very unhappy towards Ying Wu Xie's gang and Fang Yuan.

"At merely rank six, their willpower is truly shocking. But we were all defeated, they will fail soon." A Central Continent Gu Immortal who was just swept out of the river said.

But they did not managed to see Fang Yuan or Ying Wu Xie fail, before a situation occurred around Ma Hong Yun.

Ma Hong Yun, who was swimming forward, choked on the river water as he was nearly swept away.

"Be careful!" Bi Chen Tian couldn't help but call out.

Ying Wu Xie was overjoyed, but soon, Ma Hong Yun continued to swim forward, moving his arms.

It was just a scare.

"It's that girl, hehe, her willpower is shocking too." Mao Li Qiu could see the subtle details.

At the crucial moment, Zhao Lian Yun had helped Ma Hong Yun and stabilized his condition.

The truth was, after Reverse Flow River went back to normal, the river surface became smooth, it did not challenge one's physical stamina as much. Especially towards the upstream, the river became more shallow, but its reflective power against willpower and mental energy became stronger.

"Hong Yun, we cannot be separated anymore."

"Do you know, in order to be with you again, how much have I experienced, how much hardship have I gone through, and how much I have lost?"

Zhao Lian Yun had lost her voice and could not speak, but at this moment, she had no such energy anyway.

Her aged body was unleashing strength that even Zhao Lian Yun could not believe she had.

Zhao Lian Yun had forgotten about her stamina and age, she was purely wanting to be together with Ma Hong Yun.

Even if they were swimming for their lives, and could not even look at each other.

Even if she could not speak, and danger was right behind them.

"No matter how bad the situation is, I need to persevere. Every minute and second that I spend with him, fighting alongside him, regardless of the situation, I have never been so blissful!"

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun continued moving forward, even though they were slow, the situation was stabilizing.

It was just a scare.

Bi Chen Tian and the other Central Continent Gu Immortals, and even Flood Extremity and Black Extremity, were having their hearts shake from the shock.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu snorted coldly, he did not conceal his disappointment.

The immortals watched Reverse Flow River, every action caused deep emotions to form in their hearts.

Even though some of them were rank eight existences, and even though the rank six and seven Gu Immortals were experts among those with the same cultivation level, elites of their regions.

"Even my immortal zombie body is feeling tired?" Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was on his head, pulling Ying Wu Xie's hair, he was causing a din as he cried or laughed at times.

"I am just a split soul of the main body, I have not lived for a long time."

"But since coming to life, I knew that I had my own responsibilities!"

"Right now, Lord Purple is crazy, I cannot ignore him, he might choke to death in the river, I am Shadow Sect's only hope."

"Even if I die from exhaustion here, I cannot give up. Only by capturing Zhao Lian Yun and Ma Hong Yun can I stall for time until Lord Purple awakens again!"

His duty was making Ying Wu Xie persevere.

Bai Ning Bing gritted her teeth, her chest was pumping up and down.

"Hehehe," she even laughed lightly, her face was distorted, excitement was in her eyes.

"Exciting!"

"This is truly exciting!"

"In Reverse Flow River, I have experienced a new type of excitement never felt before, this is the road that Ren Zu once walked on!"

"Interesting, this is simply too interesting!!"

"Even if I fail, this trip was worth it. Even if I die, this life was worth it!"

Hei Lou Lan was filled with anger.

"How can I stop here?"

"Mother, I have not avenged you yet!"

"I have not killed that man with my own hands yet!"

"Argh!"

"I need to persevere..."

Hei Lou Lan was trembling, she was showing indomitable willpower.

However, as time passed, some people could not persevere.

"Will my excitement end here?"

"I... have not... taken revenge yet..."

Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan were out of energy, they were washed away.

But their safety was ensured, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was already waiting for them outside.

This way, there were only six people left in Reverse Flow River.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were still at first place.

Ying Wu Xie and the crazy Purple Mountain True Monarch were second.

Fang Yuan was third.

Wei Ling Yang was fourth.

"There is still hope!" Right now, Old Ancestor Xue Hu's hopes were all on Ying Wu Xie.

As long as Ying Wu Xie captured Ma and Zhao, Old Ancestor Xue Hu's side would gain the initiative, they would be able to threaten Bi Chen Tian and the others, as well as Longevity Heaven's dog tail life extending ferret.

But if Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were swept away, then everyone would have a chance, a huge battle would occur, it was unclear who would win. It would depend on their strength and also luck.

"Lord Wei Ling Yang, it will depend on you now." Bi Chen Tian thought, he clenched his fists that were full of sweat.

The dog tail life extending ferret was laughing.

Its eyes were staring at the river, thinking of something.

"Ah! The glory of Heavenly Court..." A moment later, Wei Ling Yang sighed out loud as he reached his limits, despite his unwillingness, he was washed away by Reverse Flow River.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were shocked, they were completely stunned.

Someone screamed in disbelief: "How can this be? Lord Wei Ling Yang is a rank eight Gu Immortal, how could he lose to these people?"

"Swimming in Reverse Flow River has nothing to do with cultivation level, it depends on your willpower." Someone explained.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were silent, did this mean that the great rank eight Central Continent Gu Immortal, Wei Ling Yang's willpower, was inferior to these people?

Bi Chen Tian slowly spoke: "Don't forget, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun had rested on the floating mound earlier, according to the information, they even had fruits to eat, when Reverse Flow River engulfed everything, they were at the front, the Gu Immortals behind them also went through many struggles, their stamina and willpower were greatly expended."

The Central Continent Gu Immortals finally realized.

"That's true."

"Even though Lord Wei Ling Yang lost, if they had the same starting point, he would definitely be the victor!"

Because of Bi Chen Tian's words, the Central Continent Gu Immortals' morale stabilized.

Bi Chen Tian was expressionless, his mood was heavy.

"What do we do now?" Bi Chen Tian was hesitant.

The Central Continent group had a huge disadvantage.

The wise choice was to retreat and preserve their strength. They could go to black heaven and try to meet with Myriad Tidal Dragon, using the Immortal Gu House to see if they could turn this around.

There was a third option, it was to stay here and contest for Ma and Zhao with Old Ancestor Xue Hu and the dog tail life extending ferret.

"We should discuss this after Wei Ling Yang returns." This was a huge matter, Bi Chen Tian could not make the decision, he was not the leader, Wei Ling Yang was.

But while they were waiting, another change occurred in Reverse Flow River.

"I... will not give in!" Ying Wu Xie bellowed as he raised his head, but Reverse Flow River engulfed him as he was swept away.

"Is it finally ending! Ying Wu Xie, die!!" Fang Yuan screamed internally, he was waiting for this moment all along.

He collided heavily with Ying Wu Xie.

Both sides were fighting in the water, they stopped advancing.

This way, Fang Yuan and Ying Wu Xie, as well as Purple Mountain True Monarch, could not help but be washed downstream by Reverse Flow River.

Sovereign immortal body versus the strength path immortal zombie.

Undeniably, Ying Wu Xie was at a disadvantage, he was quickly beaten until he suffered bone fractures by Fang Yuan's punches and kicks.

But the immortal zombie body was dead to begin with, its only weakness was the brain. Even the heart was not a weakness.

Fang Yuan had become an immortal zombie for some time, he naturally knew this, but Ying Wu Xie was defending his head, he disregarded the rest of his body and only protected his skull.

Undeniably, this was a wise decision.

Once he stalled for time and Fang Yuan was swept out of Reverse Flow River, Ying Wu Xie would counterattack.

Don't forget, Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, and Old Ancestor Xue Hu were already outside the river.

Among everyone here, Fang Yuan was the only one who was truly alone.

He was racing against time!

Fang Yuan wanted to kill Ying Wu Xie and Purple Mountain True Monarch before they got out of Reverse Flow River.

While Ying Wu Xie was stalling for time, trying to survive.

Fang Yuan was not able to do anything to Ying Wu Xie at the moment.

Chapter 1282: Surpassing Ren Zu?

The most important reason was: Fighting in water greatly affected Fang Yuan's ability to attack consecutively.

Because he needed to breathe outside the water at certain intervals.

In this aspect, Fang Yuan was inferior to the dead Mu Ling Lan. He was a water path Gu Immortal, he had special water path dao marks that allowed him to breathe underwater.

On the other hand, the immortal zombie did not need to breathe, as it was dead to begin with.

"Hmph!" Fang Yuan could not attack successfully, he changed his target towards Purple Mountain True Monarch, who was in Ying Wu Xie's arms.

Ying Wu Xie was worried about Purple Mountain True Monarch's safety, he wanted to try and save him.

But Fang Yuan changed his target again, poking at Ying Wu Xie's eyes.

This was a vicious move.

As long as he succeeded, Fang Yuan would be able to stab into Ying Wu Xie's brain and end his life for good.

Ying Wu Xie's heart was jumping, it was too late to defend himself, he fell into despair.

However, a change occurred right at this moment.

Purple Mountain True Monarch suddenly stood up and charged at Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan had the initiative, he could easily defend himself. He grabbed Purple Mountain True Monarch and tried to squeeze his fist and kill Purple Mountain True Monarch.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch had unfathomable capabilities, and was a wisdom path Gu Immortal with deep wisdom path dao mark accumulation, Fang Yuan felt like he was grabbing an eel, it was so slippery, Purple Mountain True Monarch somehow managed to squeeze himself out of his fist.

Purple Mountain True Monarch escaped Fang Yuan's demonic clutches, he moved agilely in the water, his wings gave him more mobility, Fang Yuan actually missed all of his attacks.

Next, Purple Mountain True Monarch flew to Ying Wu Xie and grabbed his shirt, swimming desperately and managing to get free from Fang Yuan.

Ying Wu Xie was shocked and overjoyed, seeing Purple Mountain True Monarch regain clarity in his eyes, he knew that at this crucial moment of life and death, Purple Mountain True Monarch had regained his senses!

"This is great!" Ying Wu Xie was overjoyed, with Purple Mountain True Monarch now clear-headed, they could capture Ma and Zhao again.

"Quickly leave!" Purple Mountain True Monarch carried Ying Wu Xie as they moved downstream, rapidly escaping.

He was tiny but he had great strength.

"Lord Purple!" Ying Wu Xie understood something immediately, as soon, Purple Mountain True Monarch fell into insanity once again.

"Oh!' Ying Wu Xie sighed deeply, he knew why Purple Mountain True Monarch wanted to retreat, because his condition was not stable.

Because of Purple Mountain True Monarch, Fang Yuan could not eliminate Ying Wu Xie.

Furthermore, he was lagging behind.

He was far from Ma and Zhao.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu had an unhappy expression.

Because Ying Wu Xie and Purple Mountain True Monarch left, only three people were left in Reverse Flow River.

They were Ma Hong Yun, Zhao Lian Yun, and Fang Yuan.

"Who is this? He is a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, but he dares to foil my plan?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu had deep killing intent towards Fang Yuan.

Hei Lou Lan was already standing beside Old Ancestor Xue Hu, hearing Old Ancestor Xue Hu's words, her heart jumped.

Fang Yuan clearly had deep enmity with Ying Wu Xie, she had to answer this question now.

Hei Lou Lan was a member of Shadow Sect, at this moment, she could not expose Fang Yuan's true identity, but thankfully, he had another identity, so she said: "He is Liu Guan Yi."

"Liu Guan Yi? The demonic path Gu Immortal who killed Ye Lui Qun Xing and cultivates ancient sword dragon transformation?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu was stunned before replying.

He knew about Liu Guan Yi.

Even though he was refining Gu in Snowy Mountain, he still paid attention to the situation in Northern Plains.

Because the rank eight Gu Immortals in Northern Plains were all obstacles for him in refining Fortune Rivalling Heaven. As for Liu Guan Yi, and Chu Du, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was not too concerned about them.

But to think that this insignificant character was actually foiling his plan at this moment.

"Hahaha, luck is truly on our side." The dog tail life extending ferret laughed loudly, waves of noise billowed.

Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang had gathered together, Central Continent's Gu Immortals waited solemnly. They had chosen to stay and wait for a chance.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing stood together.

The three parties were all at the starting point, waiting for Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun to be swept away.

"Fairy Lian Yun, Ma Hong Yun, you can come out now, even if us Gu Immortals of Central Continent have to sacrifice our lives, we will defend you." Wei Ling Yang called out.

"Laughable! You Central Continent fellows want to snatch them from me, Grandpa Mao?!" The dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, was furious and spoke in displeasure.

Black Extremity was worried that Mao Li Qiu's scary appearance would frighten Ma Hong Yun, he quickly added: "Ma Hong Yun, you are acknowledged by fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu and have Giant Sun's bloodline, you are a member of Longevity Heaven. Longevity Heaven is the origin of our bloodline, it is the grotto-heaven of Ancestor Giant Sun. We are here to bring you home."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu snorted, pressuring Fang Yuan: "Liu Guan Yi, if you can capture Ma and Zhao, I will allow you to become the third peak lord of Snowy Mountain. I, Xue Hu, am one to hold my word, you can rest assured. If you succeed, I will back you up, your future cultivation journey will be smooth sailing."

Hearing this, the other Gu Immortals started to look at Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan lost the chance to kill Ying Wu Xie.

There was no other way.

He had tried his best.

But the foundation of rank eight was immense, the advantage of the strength path immortal zombie body in Reverse Flow River and most importantly, Purple Mountain True Monarch's moment of clarity, pushed him towards the abyss of failure.

"I failed again!"

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth.

The situation was horrible for him. Out of the three rank eight existences outside the river, he could only join Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

But Old Ancestor Xue Hu was with the members of Shadow Sect.

"If I leave Reverse Flow River, these three rank eights will attack me. My speed cannot match Hui Feng Zi, even with myriad self and familiar face, the hope of escaping from them is likely very slim."

Fang Yuan was very clear on his current situation.

"However, if I can capture Ma and Zhao, I will have the best bargaining chips. Central Continent and Longevity Heaven will be willing to transact, not to mention Old Ancestor Xue Hu as well, by then, I could use them to help eliminate Shadow Sect!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan stared at Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

He swam upstream, charging towards the two of them.

Ma and Zhao saw Fang Yuan's movement, they were the only ones ahead of him now, his animosity was obvious.

Ma and Zhao could only grit their teeth and continue swimming.

"Persevere!"

"I have just escaped from Snowy Mountain, I cannot be captured again!"

"There is also Lady Xiao Yun, she became like this because of me, I need to save her!!"

"Thus, I need to persevere."

"Ma Hong Yun, you can do it, work hard!"

Ma Hong Yun gritted his teeth, he desperately swam, even though he was very tired, he had strong driving force in his heart.

Fang Yuan's speed was faster than Ma and Zhao.

But because he had fought with Ying Wu Xie earlier, he was pushed back by Reverse Flow River for some time.

Thus, Ma and Zhao were very safe, unless they could not hold on anymore.

As time passed, this mystical competition was reaching its end.

Outside the river, large numbers of Gu Immortals were observing the three people in Reverse Flow River.

"Hmm?" At this time, Zhao Lian Yun's expression suddenly changed.

While swimming, her legs had touched the ground.

Next, she subconsciously stepped on the ground and stood up from Reverse Flow River, her head and shoulders was exposed above the water.

This change made both her and Ma Hong Yun extremely joyful.

"How could this happen?" Flood Extremity was extremely shocked.

The dog tail life extending ferret yawned: "Are you ignorant! Upstream in Reverse Flow River, it gets shallower and shallower, did you people not read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>? Back then, Ren Zu wanted to walk out of Reverse Flow River, he failed at the last step."

"So it is like this!" Mao Li Qiu spoke loudly, the Central Continent Gu Immortals finally realized it.

"Unknowingly, the two of them have already reached the end."

"Look, they are only a hundred steps away from the shore."

"Does this mean Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun will be able to break the record and achieve what Ren Zu could not do, forcefully getting out of Reverse Flow River from the front?!"

"That might not be, Ren Zu had swam from the bottom of the river, Ma and Zhao had a much easier time."

"Even so, this is a grand feat!"

"That's right, their willpower is simply shocking!!"

The Gu Immortals were all discussing this.

Even Mao Li Qiu was moved: "This is true, Ma Hong Yun is really something! He might be able to charge out of Reverse Flow River. Hehe."

Black Extremity and Flood Extremity looked at each other, the former said arrogantly: "As expected of the person chosen by fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan was still swimming, trying to reach them, when Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were already walking in Reverse Flow River.

Almost all the Gu Immortals were looking at Ma and Zhao.

The immortals wanted to know if these two could break the record of human history, and in a sense, surpass Ren Zu and walk out of Reverse Flow River from the front!

One step at a time.

Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun supported each other, as they walked forward shakily but with determination.

They were extremely tired, their bodies were numb, but they still persevered.

Almost every step, their bodies would shake like tree branches in the wind. It would not be strange if any of them fainted at the very next moment.

But in this condition, they continued to advance.

This situation created a huge impact on these immortals' hearts.

"What sort of willpower is this!"

"Is this the power of love?"

"The two of them are supporting each other through thick and thin, and are walking side by side. Regardless of the result, I feel deep admiration towards the two of them."

The river water's turbulence gradually stopped, as Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun finally approached the end of the river, everyone held their breaths in anticipation.

Chapter 1283: Immemorial Secrets of Reverse Flow River

"Am I going to fail..." Fang Yuan was still swimming, seeing this, his heart sank: "No, until the final moment, I still have a chance, I cannot give up!"

"The final step!" Bi Chen Tian cried out.

The immortals did not dare to breathe loudly, they were nervous, staring at this grand moment.

"Grandpa Mao, get ready to save Ma Hong Yun, we will fight for them the moment they get out!" Black Extremity transmitted, reminding the dog tail life extending ferret.

But the latter replied: "No need."

"Grandpa Mao, what do you mean?" Black Extremity was anxious.

Because now, Ma Hong Yun was holding Zhao Lian Yun's hand, taking the final step.

His left leg was still in Reverse Flow River, but right now, the river water was not even at the sole of his left foot. Meanwhile, his right foot was already in the air, about to step out of the river.

At this moment, nobody could stop Ma Hong Yun, unless Zhao Lian Yun went crazy or if Ma Hong Yun gave up.

But none of these happened.

Ma Hong Yun took a step forward!

Ping.

With a soft sound, water splattered.

He stepped on water.

"Why is there water?" Ma Hong Yun was stunned, Zhao Lian Yun was also dazed.

They saw clearly that when Ma Hong Yun took the final step, the river water also moved forward by a little.

Thus, Ma Hong Yun was still in Reverse Flow River.

"How can this be?" Ma Hong Yun could not believe it, he gritted his teeth and took a second step.

This time, a similar thing happened, Reverse Flow River moved ahead again, causing him to remain in the river.

The immortals were shocked.

How could Reverse Flow River do this?

This was simply too shameless!

"Hahaha!" Mao Li Qiu suddenly laughed out loud: "This is too fun, this is too fun! Look at your faces, hahaha, this is too funny, too funny."

The immortals' expressions changed.

Black Extremity understood something after recalling Mao Li Qiu's earlier words, he realized at once that Mao Li Qiu was sure Ma Hong Yun could not step out of Reverse Flow River, that was why it was so calm and did not try to snatch them.

"Grandpa Mao, what is going on?" Flood Extremity was impatient, he asked curiously.

"Hahaha, you fools, look at your faces!" Mao Li Qiu was laughing as his claws slammed on the ground, he was extremely overjoyed.

"Reverse Flow River itself is like this!"

"It has upstream and downstream parts, but it is impossible to try and forcefully leave the river from upstream. Because Reverse Flow River has no end. Every step you take at the final stretch of the river would just create a new extension of the river."

"During the immemorial era, Ren Zu wanted to save his son, but fate Gu dictated the life and death of all beings. How can a dead person have a second life? That was against the rules of heaven and earth, thus, wisdom Gu did not tell Ren Zu that there was such a mystical aspect in Reverse Flow River."

"Hahaha, this is too funny, to think that we would encounter something so funny!"

Mao Li Qiu said this as it laughed maniacally, it even rolled on the ground, patting its tummy.

The immortals' expressions completely changed.

This was an immemorial secret.

Everyone was hearing it for the first time.

"This means that in the legends, wisdom Gu entrapped Ren Zu?"

"Ren Zu failed at the final step, but the truth is there was no final step. Because Reverse Flow River is endless to begin with."

"This is a scheme. Wisdom Gu specially set this trap!"

"Wait, does that mean that Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun are trapped inside Reverse Flow River forever?"

Someone said that and reminded everyone.

The immortals turned their gazes towards Reverse Flow River.

But this time, they paid no attention to Ma and Zhao, they were looking at Fang Yuan who was not far behind.

Fang Yuan!

He did not give up. As a result of his perseverance, there was a huge opportunity now!

"This Liu Guan Yi was not swept away, he is still persevering, he is very close to Ma and Zhao now!"

"That means with his speed, he can definitely catch up to Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun?"

"Liu Guan Yi has immense battle strength, the battle earlier states everything. He had fought Lord Bi Chen Tian evenly in Reverse Flow River!"

The other Gu Immortals were all eliminated!

Only Fang Yuan, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were left.

Right now, even if the Gu Immortals outside Reverse Flow River wanted to catch up to them, there was no time. And more importantly, they were all eliminated, all of their mental energy regarding swimming upstream had been consumed, they had no determination to swim in Reverse Flow River anymore for this period of time.

"Damn it, the only hope now is that Liu Guan Yi will overly exert himself?" Bi Chen Tian thought about it, his forehead was full of sweat.

He suddenly reminded Ma and Zhao, "Walk slowly, don't rush, as long as you maintain your current speed, you can stay in Reverse Flow River!"

Bi Chen Tian had fought with Fang Yuan, he knew about Fang Yuan's immense strength when fighting in Reverse Flow River!

On this point, Ying Wu Xie, who had just escaped from Reverse Flow River, could prove it with his injuries. He had Purple Mountain True Monarch's help and was an immortal zombie, but he was still one step away from dying.

Thus, with Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun on Central Continent's side, they should avoid meeting with Fang Yuan.

They needed to stall for time until Fang Yuan could no longer persevere.

This was Central Continent's only hope of victory!

But Fang Yuan continued moving ahead, he was not fast, but compared to the turtle-like speed of Ma and Zhao, he was like a rocket.

Not long after, he also stood on the riverbed, he was just a hundred steps away from Ma and Zhao.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu suddenly spoke: "Very good, Liu Guan Yi, capture the two of them, you can ask for any request from me. Right now, you are wanted by both Liu tribe and Ye Lui tribe, but if you hand them to me, I will be your ally! Anyone who tries to deal with you will have to face me, Xue Hu!"

Wei Ling Yang was stunned, he also spoke: "Liu Guan Yi, we are Central Continent's ten great sects, as well as Heavenly Court's members. If you can protect them, you can join Central Continent, we can modify your immortal aperture and let you adapt to Central Continent's heaven and earth qi! You will become a true Central Continent Gu Immortal! After this merit, Central Continent will not disappoint you, whatever Old Ancestor Xue Hu can give you, we can give you several times that, or even tens of times as many benefits to you."

"Hmph! Liu Guan Yi, even though you do not have the Huang Jin bloodline, as long as you protect both Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, and hand them to Longevity Heaven, we can make an exception and allow you to become our external supreme elder! Joining Longevity Heaven will grant you unthinkable benefits. You will be in Northern Plains' righteous path and not demonic path. Not only will you no longer be wanted by anyone, all the Huang Jin tribes will welcome you." Flood Extremity also said in response.

Chapter 1284: Ma Hong Yun's Death

This was indeed a funny situation.

All three sides gave Fang Yuan attractive offers.

Fang Yuan's position was too advantageous, if he succeeded in this attempt, regardless of which side he joined, he would gain great benefits.

However, Fang Yuan did not respond.

He had no spare energy to speak.

He stepped on the riverbed as he stood up and walked ahead.

He knew that talking was pointless, only by capturing Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun could he qualify to make conditions and negotiate with the three forces outside.

The distance was shrinking.

The people outside Reverse Flow River were watching Fang Yuan's movements, some were speaking and trying to raise their offers.

But there was something strange.

Nobody said anything to threaten Fang Yuan!

Because everyone knew that Fang Yuan's public identity, Liu Guan Yi, was someone who could kill Ye Lui Qun Xing, he had outstanding battle strength and even dared to offend Liu tribe, he was a vicious and lawless person. Threatening such a person would only have negative consequences.

"I must live, I want to be together with Hong Yun!" Zhao Lian Yun sobbed, she chanted in her heart, every step was difficult for her, she was inching forward slowly.

"I am here, I am right here. Don't be afraid, Xiao Yun, I will protect you..." Ma Hong Yun was pale as paper, he was holding Zhao Lian Yun's arm as his vision turned dark, every step he took, he felt an assault of intense dizziness, he felt that he would collapse at any moment.

"Where are you two going?" Fang Yuan's voice came from behind Ma Hong Yun.

Ma and Zhao shook, they turned around.

Fang Yuan's hands were already on the shoulders of both Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

"No—!" At this moment, Ma Hong Yun shouted loudly, pushing Zhao Lian Yun away as he charged at Fang Yuan.

But how could Fang Yuan allow Ma Hong Yun to succeed?

Earlier, he failed to deal with Ying Wu Xie and Purple Mountain True Monarch, Fang Yuan was already furious. Dealing with Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, a mortal and a false immortal, it was too easy.

After some dazzling moves that made Ma Hong Yun's head spin, the two were subdued by Fang Yuan in turn, they were carried in each of his arms, unable to move.

Ma and Zhao reacted, struggling intensely. But at this moment, Fang Yuan's cold voice spoke: "Move and I will kill the person you love!"

Instantly, Ma and Zhao shuddered, they looked at Fang Yuan with immense fear.

Fang Yuan's words targeted their greatest weakness.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, he carried these two captives as he walked forward.

In this dangerous situation, Fang Yuan had finally found a way to survive.

He looked outside the river, saying: "We can negotiate now!"

"Hahaha, lad, you are quite good. You are like me back in the day, we can talk it through!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu laughed.

"Don't be rash, Central Continent can satisfy your needs." Wei Ling Yang also said.

"Boring." Mao Li Qiu pouted, lying on the ground as it wagged its tail, relaxing.

Black Extremity smiled bitterly: "Liu Guan Yi, just tell us what you want... hmm!"

At this moment, a change occurred.

Ma Hong Yun suddenly stopped breathing!

He was dead!!

The immortals were shocked, there was pure silence.

At once, even Fang Yuan was shocked.

"I did not exert any strength. Oh wait, Ma Hong Yun died of exhaustion! He carried Zhao Lian Yun as they traveled in the river, he was completely overexerting himself, surpassing his limits. Eventually, not only was he out of stamina, he was also drained of mental energy. After I caught him, his body relaxed and he died immediately."

Fang Yuan quickly understood.

This change caught him off guard.

Ma Hong Yun was dead!

The immortals gasped.

"Damn it! Liu Guan Yi, you actually killed him, I will tear your bones and tendons out, I will make sure you die a terrible death!!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu fell into a rage, he screamed loudly as his eyes turned red.

Ma Hong Yun died, the effect of Fortune Rivalling Heaven also completely dissipated.

Only a living Ma Hong Yun had value as an immortal material. A dead Ma Hong Yun was just a rank five Gu Master corpse.

This was why Lady Wan Shou had been keeping Ma Hong Yun alive and did not kill him before trying to refine the Gu.

Like the spring dream fruit tree, luck path immortal materials also had a special trait, if it was a living luck path immortal material, it had to be alive. Refining the luck path Immortal Gu would require a living refinement in that case.

"Ma Hong Yun..." Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang were downcast.

"Little worm, you actually killed Ma Hong Yun, you squeezed him to death!!" Mao Li Qiu shouted even more loudly than Old Ancestor Xue Hu, it was furious and bared its sharp fangs, it was agitated and its hair was standing, it was ready to pounce to devour Fang Yuan alive.

"Ma Hong Yun actually died?! Never mind, I still have Zhao Lian Yun." Fang Yuan held in his shock.

Zhao Lian Yun was covered in tears.

"Hong Yun!"

"Hong Yun—!"

The person she loved had died right in front of her.

Unparalleled grief and sadness assaulted her and overwhelmed her like a tsunami!

But she could not scream, she could not shout, she was unable to emit any sound.

She could only scream in her heart and cry!

She had spent so much effort to reach this step, she had just reunited with Ma Hong Yun, when they were separated for good.

What was Zhao Lian Yun going to do now?

Her tears flowed like a river, the pain was engraved in her soul, extreme grief was causing her to tremble intensely.

"Oh no." Fang Yuan quickly made a move, wanting to knock out Zhao Lian Yun.

It was to prevent Zhao Lian Yun from dying on the spot as well from grief.

However, right when Fang Yuan was about to hit Zhao Lian Yun's neck, a blue light burst out from Zhao Lian Yun's body.

Rank nine love Immortal Gu!

At the most critical moment, it displayed its might again.

"This aura... rank nine love Gu?! Wait, aren't Gu worms unable to be used in Reverse Flow River?" Flood Extremity called out.

Mao Li Qiu rolled its eyes: "Are you stupid? How can anything be absolute in this world? Reverse Flow River is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it is filled with dao marks, preventing Gu worms from being used. But if it is a rank nine Immortal Gu, they are not dao marks but fragments of the Great Dao. And a fragment of the Great Dao cannot be suppressed by Reverse Flow River's dao marks, the Immortal Gu's power can be used."

"Save him, save him, even if I have to sacrifice my life!" Zhao Lian Yun was overjoyed, she screamed in her heart.

But love Immortal Gu could not be controlled, the blue light brought Zhao Lian Yun into the sky, escaping Reverse Flow River. It then went to Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian, the speed was simply too fast to react to.

Meanwhile, Ma Hong Yun's corpse remained.

Fang Yuan was holding onto it.

Even though Ma Hong Yun died, his soul was still in his body.

But Old Ancestor Xue Hu lost all interest in this corpse already. If reviving Ma Hong Yun would help, Lady Wan Shou would not have used this difficult living refinement method.

Mao Li Qiu was staring at Fang Yuan, ready to attack.

Fang Yuan had grasped the chance earlier, but to think that this sudden change would cause Fang Yuan to fall into even bigger danger than before.

"Such a mishap, it is definitely heaven's will!"

Instantly, Fang Yuan understood.

He had fallen into Reverse Flow River, his Immortal Gu were ineffective, after such a long time passed, heaven's will had already started its plotting.

He was first swept into Reverse Flow River, followed by the events of Purple Mountain True Monarch and Ying Wu Xie, and finally, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

Heaven's will!

Fang Yuan raised his head.

At this moment, he was completely trapped.

Not just Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Mao Li Qiu, and Central Continent's Gu Immortals, even heaven's will was everywhere, trying desperately to eliminate this biggest uncontrollable factor!

"A desperate situation... then, what should I do?"

Fang Yuan's mouth was dry.

But from start to finish, he was expressionless.

He could not think of a way, just Old Ancestor Xue Hu alone was an enemy Fang Yuan could not face.

That giant purple ferret was unfathomable, it was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's steed!

Not to mention the other Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan had no way, he could only continue moving in Reverse Flow River.

The clamoring of the Gu Immortals around him continued.

"Liu Guan Yi, you cannot escape death today."

"You committed so much evil, you have done yourself in today, the fact that you are in this state is truly heaven's judgment!"

"Kill him, we need to kill him, he actually foiled our plans!"

"Do you know that you killed someone you could not touch. You will die for sure today!!"

"Howl—!" The dog tail life extending ferret howled, sound waves resounded endlessly, if not for Reverse Flow River, it would have attacked Fang Yuan already.

"I have no choice now... if Reverse Flow River sweeps me out, with my current methods, there is little chance of escaping." Fang Yuan was completely stumped.

He could only continue moving forward in Reverse Flow River.

Step by step.

He was at the front already, every step he took, Reverse Flow River would move forward by a bit, causing Fang Yuan to stay in the river forever.

Reverse Flow River had no end.

This was a form of despair.

But Fang Yuan did not feel anything.

"In my life, I have experienced too many instances of despair." Fang Yuan sighed internally.

His gaze was clear, he was still expressionless.

"In the current situation, I can only wait for the three sides to fight, I will then be able to escape. I can only persevere in this river." Fang Yuan thought.

Step by step.

Time passed, the Gu Immortals who were waiting for Fang Yuan to be swept out became frustrated.

"Is he going to stop?"

"What's the point of moving forward in Reverse Flow River? You will still die."

"Come out you coward! I will kill you with one slap!"

"It is hopeless now, Liu Guan Yi, suiciding is the only way you can retain your honor."

Some Gu Immortals were laughing, some were watching coldly.

In their opinion, Fang Yuan was just struggling futilely.

Chapter 1285: Fang Yuan's Perseverance!

"If you think that there will be a chance to escape when we fight, you can forget about it. Today, I only have one target, that is you. Do you know how much of a price I've paid to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu? You foiled my cultivation plan, you are the person I hate most in my life. If I do not kill you, I will never be appeased!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu looked at Fang Yuan with deep hatred, his words were like an icy river pouring on Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan was still expressionless.

He was like a rock, a deaf person, anyone's words, be it threats or promises, had no effect on him.

As time passed, Fang Yuan continued to move forward.

Unknowingly, the growling of the dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, became softer.

This giant purple ferret's expression had changed.

It spoke in a weird and incredulous tone, looking at Fang Yuan: "No way..."

"What?" Black Extremity was confused.

At this moment, Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Bi Chen Tian, and Wei Ling Yang also had changes in their expressions.

They sensed something.

Soon, the other Gu Immortals present were stirred up, they quickly shouted.

"Hmm?"

"This is a Gu worm's aura? But it doesn't seem like it!"

"What Gu worm? Impossible, does he also have a rank nine Immortal Gu?"

"This is weird, this is not an Immortal Gu's aura, or rather, it is not complete, this is so strange!"

Suddenly, Yu Yi Ye Zi's eyes shined, he guessed the truth as he said: "This situation, he is refining Gu!"

A Gu Immortal immediately mocked: "How can that be? Refining Gu in Reverse Flow River?"

That was true.

Gu worms could not be used in Reverse Flow River, unless it was a rank nine Immortal Gu.

Even though Fang Yuan had wisdom Gu, it was inside Lang Ya blessed land, he could not use any Gu worms, not to mention refining Gu.

Fang Yuan also felt the change inside his body.

He was expressionless, but he was shocked on the inside: "It seems... I really am refining Gu? What is going on? Every step I take, the aura in my body strengthens. What is going on?"

Even though Fang Yuan did not understand it, he knew that this was a turning point!

The situation was at its worst, no matter what, Fang Yuan wanted to try.

He continued to move forward.

Step by step.

He walked steadily, he was expressionless, but it gave others a feeling of strength.

"Why does he show no expression?" A Gu Immortal suddenly asked.

The immortals finally reacted.

That was true.

Other than Fang Yuan, everyone else who had been in this situation had distorted expressions, they were in pain, or they were going crazy or sobbing.

But why was Fang Yuan expressionless from start to finish?

The immortals were silent.

They all knew that the person who asked this question actually was asking about something else.

And that was —

"Why is this Liu Guan Yi able to persevere for so long? Furthermore, he seems to be able to continue, it seems like he can persevere forever!"

How was it possible?

Everyone was eliminated, swept away by Reverse Flow River.

How could he remain here with so much remaining strength?

Why was it him?

Why was it him!

Nobody could answer that, the Gu Immortals were all silent.

A moment later, as Fang Yuan continued to advance, the Gu worm aura in his body continued to strength, it was at its peak.

Soon, from inside Fang Yuan's body to the outside, he started to shine in a bright pure white light.

"It really... it really became like this!" Mao Li Qiu saw this and his eyes were staring wide open, he was gaping, unable to believe the sight in front of him.

"Grandpa Mao, what is going on?" Black Extremity could not endure it, he asked.

"Sigh! At this point, there is no reason in me hiding it anymore." Mao Li Qiu sighed deeply, showing a defeated look on his face.

"There is an Immortal Gu nurturing inside his body. This Immortal Gu's name is Perseverance!" Mao Li Qiu said some shocking things.

"Perseverance Immortal Gu?!" Black Extremity was extremely shocked.

The other Gu Immortals were too.

"It is said in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> that perseverance Immortal Gu was the crucial Immortal Gu that could allow the user to conquer Reverse Flow River? Isn't it just a legend?" Yu Yi Ye Zi asked.

"No, it exists." Bi Chen Tian said, he was a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, he knew many ancient secrets.

"There was a person who had once owned it, that person was a former leader of Heavenly Court, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable!" Wei Ling Yang added.

"What?!" The immortals went into shock again.

"But we had never expected the refinement method of perseverance Immortal Gu to be like this. Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had never mentioned it." Bi Chen Tian sighed and shook his head.

"Of course he didn't. This is a shameful event in his life. Hehehe." Mao Li Qiu interjected, it was very interested in anything that would ruin Heavenly Court's reputation.

These words made Shi Zheng Yi shout: "Rubbish, how dare you slander the reputation of an Immortal Venerable?!"

Daring to yell at a legendary immemorial desolate beast, Shi Zheng Yi was truly courageous, many Central Continent Gu Immortals were worried for him.

Mao Li Qiu did not get angry: "Little boy, what do you know? Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable, even if they have high cultivation level, they are still human. Humans have emotions, they have flaws, they have weaknesses."

"Back then, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable charged through Reverse Flow River and was trapped inside, unable to escape. Eventually, he painstakingly traveled to the end of the river and refined perseverance Immortal Gu in his body. From then on, he conquered Reverse Flow River and became the first Reverse Flow River Lord in history."

"The first Reverse Flow River Lord?" Even Old Ancestor Xue Hu was shocked. This Reverse Flow River had been his for so long, he did not think there were such secrets.

"This means..." At once, the immortals' gazes landed on Fang Yuan.

Mao Li Qiu sighed, with his gaze fixed on Fang Yuan who was bathed in white light, he said helplessly: "That is true. At this rate, he will refine perseverance Immortal Gu and become the second Reverse Flow River Lord!"

The immortals were lost for words, they looked at Fang Yuan, who continued moving forward.

He was expressionless, no matter how many steps he took, Reverse Flow River was always still below his feet, as if fate was mocking and laughing at him.

But he continued walking.

He had traveled through five hundred years of experiences over his previous life, he did not know how much longer he would have to walk.

But he knew where he needed to go.

As if... nobody could stop him.

At least... inside this river, nobody could stop him.

In the five hundred years of his previous life.

Fang Yuan sat inside the bamboo house, he looked at the village, he looked at Qing Mao Mountain.

His fists were clenched, hope was displayed all over his young and tender face.

"It is time to give up the past."

"Transmigrating here is my greatest opportunity! Because here, I can attain eternal life."

"I have to make good use of this rare opportunity! Otherwise, how can I live with myself, how can I give up this chance?"

"Of course, right now, I need to improve the living conditions of me and my brother. Hehe, that little fellow..."

After the aperture awakening.

On the battle stage, Fang Yuan lowered his head, he was filled with shock and anger.

"I was set up!"

"Who set me up? Who does not want me to win in battle? The answer is obvious!"

"Brother, give up, you are not my match. Because of our differing aptitude, we are fated to be different." Gu Yue Fang Zheng said with glee and smugness in front of him.

Fang Yuan turned around and left, he was filled with determination.

"Since the village refuses to nurture me, since my aunt and uncle are purposely pushing me aside, what is the point of staying here?"

"If I stay here, will I be able to get stronger and gain eternal life?"

"Why don't I leave?"

Inside the caravan.

Gu Master Big Beard died, Fang Yuan stood in front of his grave.

The youngster was filled with tears, he sobbed: "Uncle Big Beard, rest in peace."

"Thank you for the final present."

"You said: When you were a child, you wanted to be a grand hero, like those legendary figures of the righteous path. When you were a youngster, you wanted to be a clan leader. When you were an adult, you were satisfied with becoming a clan elder. When you were a middle aged man, you were exiled from the clan, you felt that you could live by yourself just as well, you were satisfied with just raising your Gu worms and yourself."

"But I am not like this, I will not forgo my dreams just because of age."

"This world is too big, but we are all minor characters... I will work hard! I will definitely do my best!"

...

Childhood, adolescence, adulthood.

Qing Mao Mountain, caravan, he walked all along.

Middle age, old age, and eventually, lifespan Gu.

Southern Border, Western Desert, Eastern Sea, and Central Continent.

After his rebirth using Spring Autumn Cicada, Qing Mao Mountain, Three Kings blessed land, Hu Immortal blessed land, Imperial Court blessed land, Yi Tian Mountain, and Reverse Flow River!

Step by step, through difficulties and ordeals.

Bi Chen Tian frowned, he stared at Fang Yuan's figure, thinking: "What sort of willpower is this! Why does he persevere? What makes him persevere to this extent?"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu snorted coldly, solemness showed in his eyes, he no longer looked down on this rank seven Gu Immortal: "This means, there was Genesis Lotus three hundred thousand years ago, and now, there is Liu Guan Yi... the Reverse Flow River Lord."

Mao Li Qiu looked at the light on Fang Yuan's body, there was nothing it could do, it bore its fangs and scratched the ground with its claws, causing deep marks to form.

Bai Ning Bing's and Hei Lou Lan's eyelids were twitching, they were evidently moved.

Zhao Lian Yun had woken up, she looked at Ma Hong Yun's corpse, held in Fang Yuan's arm, her tears were flowing out.

She cried in her heart: "Hong Yun, Hong Yun, how could you leave me like this. Without you, I am all alone in this world. What is the point of living? Do you know, the perseverance of one person is so difficult!"

How difficult is the perseverance of one person?

All of the Gu Immortals here could answer that question.

Because among them, some persevered because of responsibility, some persevered because of hatred, some persevered because of excitement, and some persevered because of love...

And Fang Yuan's answer?

He was still expressionless, he continued to move forward relentlessly.

I had once screamed, gradually, I lost my voice.

I had once cried, gradually, I lost my tears.

I had once grieved, gradually, I became able to withstand everything.

I had once rejoiced, gradually, I became unmoved by the world.

And now!

All I have left is an expressionless face, my gaze is as tough as a monolith, only perseverance remains in my heart.

This is my own, an insignificant character, Fang Yuan's — Perseverance!

A dazzling light erupted out.

Perseverance Immortal Gu, at this moment, was refined successfully!!

Chapter 1286: Wisely Urging Old Ancestor Xue Hu

Perseverance Immortal Gu, at this moment, was refined successfully!

Outside Reverse Flow River, the immortals who saw this all fell into dead silence.

They watched as Reverse Flow River continued to flow slowly. A rank seven Gu Immortal, with the appearance of a young man wearing a long white robe, with long hair and deep dark eyes, was standing in the water, he was as free as the wind.

"He actually managed to refine perseverance Immortal Gu!" Bai Ning Bing muttered, having complex emotions.

"He actually did the same thing as Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable?" The Central Continent Gu Immortals could not believe this.

"Look guys, he is no longer moving forward, he is standing on the spot, Reverse Flow River is no longer sweeping him away!" Shi Zheng Yi pointed and shouted.

Fang Yuan shut his eyes, half his attention was inside his immortal aperture.

A brand new Immortal Gu had formed completely, appearing in his immortal aperture.

Perseverance Immortal Gu!

It was like a monolith, it was huge, at the size of a giant whale. The bottom was wide while the top was thin, it was squarish and metallic black, the sides were very straight. At one glance, it looked like a rock that could not be eroded by the sea in the span of ten thousand years, it was like a huge rock that could not be melted by magma over the ages.

It was really a very special Immortal Gu.

Because in terms of size, it was the largest Immortal Gu Fang Yuan had ever seen.

"Rank seven Immortal Gu..."

Fang Yuan could tell this Immortal Gu's rank from the aura it was emitting.

It was not rank eight, nor rank nine.

Fang Yuan was happy about this.

Having a higher rank Immortal Gu was not always better, this was something that every Gu Immortal knew.

Rank seven perseverance Immortal Gu best fit Fang Yuan's rank seven cultivation level.

"What is the food of this perseverance Immortal Gu? What effect does it have? How can I make use of it?" Questions appeared in Fang Yuan's head.

He did not think any further, he placed his focus on the outside world again.

Outside Reverse Flow River, the three rank eight Gu Immortals were still waiting to strike, the other Gu Immortals were also ready to attack any time.

"By owning perseverance Immortal Gu, I really conquered Reverse Flow River!" Fang Yuan soon found that Reverse Flow River was as obedient as a pet dog around him.

The immense pressure it gave him earlier had vanished.

Fang Yuan stood here without moving, Reverse Flow River no longer worked against him.

Not just that, Fang Yuan also found that he could use Gu worms freely in the river, he could even open his immortal aperture's entrance easily.

"Good!" Fang Yuan was excited, he first placed Ma Hong Yun's corpse in his immortal aperture.

Ma Hong Yun's soul was also inside Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

His soul contained the luck path true inheritance of all living being's luck, Fang Yuan paid attention to this. During Imperial Court blessed land, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were protected by the all living being's luck true inheritance, they had each gained a portion of the inheritance.

"Right now, Ma Hong Yun's soul is in my hands, the portion of all living being's luck that he has belongs to me. It is a pity Zhao Lian Yun had rank nine love Immortal Gu, I could not capture her."

In Fang Yuan's opinion, Ma Hong Yun's soul had great value, but his body was merely a Gu refinement material, even though it had gone through many living refinement attempts.

But Fang Yuan frowned slightly.

If he could capture Zhao Lian Yun, he might have been able to use her and negotiate with the Gu Immortals outside.

But earlier, Zhao Lian Yun had escaped from danger due to love Immortal Gu, she had returned to Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang.

"Northern Plains' Liu Guan Yi, to think that this battle would establish your fame." Wei Ling Yang sighed.

"I want you to die, I want you to die!" Zhao Lian Yun screamed in a shrill voice, her gaze towards Fang Yuan was filled with hatred and grudge.

The love she had for Ma Hong Yun became hatred for Fang Yuan!

"Liu Guan Yi, even if you become the Reverse Flow River Lord, so what?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu smiled coldly.

"Lad, you are quite capable. But this is it, you killed Ma Hong Yun, you caused me to fail before even trying. Walk out of Reverse Flow River and let me kill you in one slap, I will let you off without much pain! Howl!" Grandpa Mao said with a ruthless expression.

"Damn it." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth secretly.

He was the only person in Reverse Flow River now, but the situation did not turn around for him.

He was trapped inside Reverse Flow River.

Even though he refined perseverance Immortal Gu and conquered Reverse Flow River, he could not gain the initiative and escape with his life.

Especially after killing Ma Hong Yun and losing Zhao Lian Yun, Fang Yuan was in a passive state.

"Three rank eight Gu Immortals, many experts, as well as heaven's will..." Fang Yuan looked around, he was trapped. Refining perseverance Immortal Gu made him the target of everyone now, he had attracted too much attention.

"Huff!"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu suddenly breathed out, he grunted as he spat out a mouthful of cold air.

The cold air soon landed on Reverse Flow River, the water was still flowing slowly, the surface of the river was flickering with light as the cold air was reflected back at him.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu dodged it, staring at the river water as he laughed: "Liu Guan Yi, you foiled my plans, if you surrender now and hand over Reverse Flow River, I can spare your life, you can become my slave. But if you insist on resisting us, I will make sure you cannot die even if you want to!"

Saying this, he spat out more cold air, attacking Reverse Flow River.

Reverse Flow River continued to reflect all of the attacks back, but Old Ancestor Xue Hu dodged them all, he continued threatening: "Liu Guan Yi, you can forget about it if you want to use Reverse Flow River to protect yourself. Reverse Flow River is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it has immense might, but it is not a living being, reflecting attacks consumes its water. Eventually, the river will dry up, by then, you will die."

As Old Ancestor Xue Hu continued to attack, Reverse Flow River started being expended, even though only traces of the water were used, eventually, it would run out.

But Fang Yuan retorted: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu, you are the number one rank eight Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, how can you not know that Central Continent's Gu Immortals were the ones who foiled your Gu refinement plan? Furthermore, Longevity Heaven's trap might also be involved. I just happened to be here due to a coincidence, are you ignoring these great enemies and targeting an insignificant character like me?"

As he said this, Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang became extremely alert, they moved back by a bit.

Mao Li Qiu pouted: "This lad is good at sowing discord."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu stared slightly in surprise: "Liu Guan Yi, you seem to be forgetting that the Reverse Flow River under your feet belonged to me. You stole my secluded domain of heaven and earth, you are an enemy of mine. You caused the death of Ma Hong Yun and ruined my hope, if I do not kill you, my anger will not be appeased!"

Fang Yuan quickly said: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu, we are both Northern Plainsmen. Among everyone present, this ferret is from Longevity Heaven, while these Central Continent Gu Immortals are all from the ten great ancient sects or Heavenly Court. They are all righteous path, only we are in the demonic path. Righteous path and demonic path cannot intermingle, we can work together."

"Yes, I took away Reverse Flow River and by chance became the Reverse Flow River Lord. But we can cooperate, I can lend Reverse Flow River to you, with my help, Reverse Flow River will be much more useful to you now."

"Yes, I killed Ma Hong Yun, but everyone knows that I did not intend to do that. I only held him lightly and Ma Hong Yun died. He was completely worn out, he was mentally exhausted, or maybe he suffered too big of a shock and could not endure it. Without me, he was going to die anyway, I was merely implicated."

"Now that he is dead, Fortune Rivalling Heaven's effect vanished, I can understand that you want to seek revenge with me. But you need to undergo tribulation, will killing me and venting your anger help you pass the tribulation?"

Saying this, Fang Yuan shook his head, he continued: "Not just that, your tribulation might even become more dangerous. Because of how vast Reverse Flow River is, you will exert a lot of effort in draining its water, and yet, you cannot refine Fortune Rivalling Heaven to deal with your tribulation."

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu, you have a family, you are a grand overlord, the number one demonic path overlord in Northern Plains. If you die from tribulation, or even if you are just heavily injured, all of your enemies, and the righteous paths of Northern Plains and Central Continent, will be overjoyed. At the same time, Lady Wan Shou would grieve."

"Even though Snowy Mountain blessed land was destroyed and this refinement failed, as long as you are around, you can build another Snowy Mountain blessed land. If the refinement fails, you can snatch resources from others and get enough materials to refine Gu again."

"These righteous path Gu Immortals have ill intentions, we can take them down!"

"I, Liu Guan Yi, am a demonic path member of Northern Plains, I am willing to cooperate with you to achieve our grand ambitions!!"

Fang Yuan spoke with confidence and assurance, he had a glib tongue.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu heard these words and felt that Fang Yuan was not so detestable anymore!

Because what he said was right, even though Old Ancestor Xue Hu was furious, he had not lost his reasoning yet. Furthermore, Fang Yuan was considering him and putting himself in his perspective while making plans.

How could Old Ancestor Xue Hu not be moved?

He was a rank eight Gu Immortal, even after this major setback, his ambitions had not wavered. He was still going to refine Gu later, where would he get the materials?

Old Ancestor Xue Hu subconsciously looked towards Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang, as well as the dog tail life extending ferret.

Seeing Old Ancestor Xue Hu's gaze, Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian became nervous, while Mao Li Qiu felt offended, his hair stood on end as he opened his mouth, revealing his sharp fangs to Old Ancestor Xue Hu, not showing any weakness.

"This fellow is still as crafty as ever!" Ying Wu Xie was frustrated.

If this was earlier, he might encourage Old Ancestor Xue Hu to cooperate with Fang Yuan. After all, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body was the fruit of Shadow Sect's efforts after a hundred thousand years, it could not be lost.

But now, after being hunted down by Fang Yuan, and seeing him conquer Reverse Flow River, Ying Wu Xie's wariness towards Fang Yuan had reached an extreme level.

If there was a chance, Ying Wu Xie would definitely kill Fang Yuan, and eliminate this terrifying foe!

But Ying Wu Xie did not speak.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had fallen into deep sleep in his hands.

When he awakened, he would regain clarity for some time.

Currently, Ying Wu Xie had to keep a low profile, it would be best if everyone forgot about him.

This was Shadow Sect's weakest moment.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals were also like this, even though they got back Zhao Lian Yun, they did not dare to retreat easily. If they did, they might attract unwanted attention and become everyone's targets.

The situation was in a deadlock.

It was quite peculiar.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Shadow Sect, Central Continent's Gu Immortals, Longevity Heaven, Fang Yuan, none of them dared to make a move, they had their own considerations and perspective, and most importantly, none of them had overwhelming strength that could suppress the situation.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's attitude became the crucial thing now.

Everyone stared at him.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu thought for a moment and suddenly said, "Sure, we can make an alliance!"

Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

Chapter 1287: Myriad Self Second Style!

Seeing that Fang Yuan was about to successfully convince Old Ancestor Xue Hu, be it Central Continent or Longevity Heaven, their expressions all changed.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was the number one rank eight in Northern Plains' demonic path, if he fought with his full strength, he could definitely bring Fang Yuan away even against the dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu, Bi Chen Tian, and Wei Ling Yang.

However, Old Ancestor Xue Hu gave Fang Yuan very strict alliance agreement rules.

Fang Yuan's joy vanished, according to this alliance agreement, he was not an equal ally of Old Ancestor Xue Hu, he was a slave!

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu, such an alliance agreement... are you joking?" Fang Yuan's expression was ugly.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu started to laugh: "Of course I am not!"

"Liu Guan Yi, didn't you analyze this thoroughly earlier? Among the people present, only we are from the demonic path, we are natural allies."

"You killed Ye Lui Qun Xing, you killed a Liu tribe Gu Immortal and plundered their resources, are you going to hand yourself in to Longevity Heaven?"

"Or will you leave your homeland and go to Central Continent? And be the lackey of the ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court?"

"I am your only option."

Saying this, he paused before looking at Ying Wu Xie: "You know, I have my own difficulties. I have an agreement with these people, but it seems that you are enemies too. I cannot offend another rank eight existence just because of a rank seven Gu Immortal and Reverse Flow River, right?"

Ying Wu Xie's heart jumped.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was indeed trying to convince Fang Yuan, but he was also probing Shadow Sect's and Purple Mountain True Monarch's background.

After all, everyone saw that Purple Mountain True Monarch went crazy.

If this Purple Mountain True Monarch was truly crazy and unable to control himself, Old Ancestor Xue Hu might attack them. After all, killing a crazy rank eight Gu Immortal would grant enough benefits that would move Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Furthermore, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had failed the Gu refinement and Snowy Mountain blessed land was destroyed, all of his investments were wasted.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was a demonic path overlord, he was not easy to fool.

His words earlier had truly moved Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

But Old Ancestor Xue Hu had his own schemes and plans, he used Fang Yuan's words to deal with him in return.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's words were filled with suspicion and probing.

But Fang Yuan knew that he could not cooperate with Mao Li Qiu or Wei Ling Yang.

Longevity Heaven was defensive in regard to its descendants, Fang Yuan killed Ye Lui Qun Xing, he offended the Huang Jin tribes, and after killing Ma Hong Yun, going to Longevity Heaven was courting death.

On the other hand, he could not go to Central Continent.

Even though he had methods to defend against wisdom path, they could not be relied upon. Normally, he was relying on the isolation of being inside an immortal aperture or the Southern Border super Gu formation to defend himself from the deductions of Central Continent's Gu Immortals.

If he went to Central Continent, Heavenly Court's Fairy Zi Wei would know about it, by then, his identity would be exposed, he would be put on trial. After all, he was listed on the Demon Judgment Board.

As for Shadow Sect, because of sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it was even more impossible.

Thus, among everyone here, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was Fang Yuan's only choice.

But now, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had stated that he could help Fang Yuan, but Fang Yuan had to accept these conditions. If he did, he would be signing a slavery agreement, he would become Old Ancestor Xue Hu's slave.

"If you agree, I will ensure your safety. If you do not, I will attack Reverse Flow River, you will die here today, there is no other option." Old Ancestor Xue Hu was domineering, he stared at Fang Yuan fixedly, forcing him to make a decision.

Fang Yuan had a struggling and hesitant expression: "Let me think!"

"I will give you three breaths of time." Old Ancestor Xue Hu had a cold expression, he breathed out cold air as he gave Fang Yuan three breaths of time to consider.

It was truly merciless!

Fang Yuan smiled, he knew that he could not deceive Old Ancestor Xue Hu, there was no way to stall for time, he stopped acting: "Then, Old Ancestor, I will have to see your methods."

"Hahaha." Old Ancestor Xue Hu laughed loudly, he had a ruthless expression: "I knew it, how can someone who is qualified to be the Reverse Flow River Lord submit to others so easily? Therefore, I will beat you until you beg for mercy!"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was happy to have this prey, he seemed to be unwilling to kill Fang Yuan.

But who knew if this was his plot?

Old Ancestor Xue Hu attacked, waves of cold air assaulted, unceasingly with grand might.

Reverse Flow River's water was raging, reflecting Xue Hu's attacks, while consuming the river water.

Fang Yuan did not move, it was still too early to affect him, even though he was bound to lose, because he could only take attacks passively and could not counterattack.

"I need to find a way to get out of this predicament and escape with my life."

Fang Yuan smiled, looking at Central Continent's group: "Guests from Central Continent, what are you waiting for? Do you want Northern Plains' Gu Immortals to collaborate and take care of you?"

Wei Ling Yang's and Bi Chen Tian's hearts jumped.

Zhao Lian Yun cried out shrilly: "Murderer! You should worry about yourself! I will only leave after I see you die right in front of me!"

The other Central Continent Gu Immortals were silent, they looked at the two rank eight Gu Immortals.

But Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian did not move, they were like statues, not making a response.

Fang Yuan was about to speak to the dog tail life extending ferret.

Mao Li Qiu suddenly laughed: "Little boy, no need to say anymore, sowing discord is pointless. I am right here, even if Xue Hu doesn't want to kill you, I will kill you!"

Saying this, it attacked.

It spat out traces of purple aura, it was like mist that was reflected by Reverse Flow River, intensifying Reverse Flow River's expenditure.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly on the inside, these rank eight existences, be they human or beast, were astute, words could not cause them to waver.

"It seems that I can only rely on myself now."

"The new move that I created is powerful, but in front of four, no, five rank eight existences, it will be too difficult to escape."

Five rank eight existences, they were Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Mao Li Qiu, Bi Chen Tian, Wei Ling Yang, and the crazed Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Fang Yuan looked at the water below his feet, he actually went into a daze for a moment.

The attacks outside the river were powerful and unceasing, incredible might could be felt.

But Fang Yuan had no regard for the surroundings, because in his current state, an inspiration had formed in his mind.

Activating an Immortal Gu, the river water below his feet started to create ripples according to his will.

"It seems that if I continue activating perseverance Immortal Gu, I will be the Reverse Flow River Lord. Inside this river, I can use other Immortal Gu as well!"

Earlier, he had tried to use strength path Immortal Gu Pulling Water.

Under the effect of Pulling Water, Fang Yuan found that he could move Reverse Flow River just like any other river or stream.

But with just this, Fang Yuan could not leave the place.

Pulling water Immortal Gu was just rank six, it could move rivers and bodies of water, but it moved very slowly, trying to escape with this was impossible.

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu seems to have a way to make use of Reverse Flow River and create a formation, why can't I do the same? I am the Reverse Flow River Lord, I have perseverance Immortal Gu, I can freely manipulate this river. Or maybe, I can form an immortal killer move..."

This idea appeared in Fang Yuan's mind and began to take root deeply.

Perseverance Immortal Gu allowed Fang Yuan to get Reverse Flow River's compliance, and pulling water Immortal Gu could manipulate rivers and water. This was the basis of an immortal killer move.

Adding more Gu worms to form a complete immortal killer move, it seemed... that it was nothing too hard.

Fang Yuan felt that he could do it!

This was not a random guess.

It was his attainment level!

Fang Yuan had incredible attainment levels, one of them was water path.

He had just become a water path grandmaster.

After adding more water path Gu worms in, he quickly compiled this immortal killer move.

But it was not enough.

"Not enough... strength!" Fang Yuan realized.

The framework, the skeleton of the killer move was created, the wings were spread, but he lacked the crucial muscles for strength. Just two Immortal Gu were not enough.

Then he would add more!

Fang Yuan first thought of strength path.

Myriad self!

His most familiar technique, and also a unique immortal killer move that he had created after rebirth.

A solution was found.

Strength path grandmaster attainment level and water path grandmaster attainment level, they allowed him to naturally reach success.

But wait!

Fang Yuan suddenly thought of an unrelated immortal killer move.

This killer move came from Ye Lui Qun Xing, he used star fragments to create a powerful killer move, it was like Fang Yuan trying to use Reverse Flow River, they were using external forces!

And now, he even had the blood vessels.

Skeleton, muscles, wings, and blood vessels, he had them all.

Fang Yuan actually created an immortal killer move in this short period of time.

"This is myriad self second style." Fang Yuan's eyes were shining brilliantly.

Chapter 1288: Practising the Killer Move

With sufficient attainment level, Fang Yuan created an immortal killer move on the spot.

Because he used myriad self killer move as the foundation, Fang Yuan named this move myriad self second style.

But because this move was just created, it was far from being usable.

Bam bam bam!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu and the dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu, these two rank eight existences continued to attack Reverse Flow River, causing huge ripples in the water, countless attacks were reflected as the water level started to fall.

Fang Yuan's actions had gone past their bottom line. And because he was unwilling to give up, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Mao Li Qiu were expending their energy to attack Reverse Flow River, in order to kill Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked at the river water, thinking: "At this rate, I still have a lot of time."

His heart eased slightly.

Reverse Flow River was a secluded domain of heaven and earth indeed, it endured the attacks of two rank eight existences, only falling a little in water level.

Of course, a reason was that Xue Hu and Mao Li Qiu did not use their full strength.

They were wary of each other, and Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian were together with the other Central Continent Gu Immortals, awaiting their chance. These people restrained each other, they guarded against each other, how could they use their full strength on Fang Yuan?

Because of this complex situation, a lot of pressure was lifted off Fang Yuan, he could test his killer move without rushing.

The first activation.

Fang Yuan was careful.

First was perseverance Immortal Gu, it had been expending red date immortal essence to allow Fang Yuan to move freely in Reverse Flow River, remaining unrestricted by the secluded domain of heaven and earth.

Next were a large number of water path mortal Gu, they flew up in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture, surrounding the huge perseverance Immortal Gu as they moved in the air.

Soon, large amounts of water vapor rose, as faint blue light appeared in them.

But soon, this blue light vanished, some of it had even turned red, the originally ice-cold water vapor had turned warmer.

"I failed." Fang Yuan immediately stopped.

The scene in front of him was out of his expectations.

This was not what he wanted.

He stopped his immortal essence expenditure, crack crack, large numbers of water path mortal Gu exploded, destroyed on the spot.

Fang Yuan calmed down and started to think.

According to his planning, there should be blue light shining as the water vapor became colder, why was there red light and warmer temperature?

Fang Yuan deduced in his mind, soon, because of his wisdom path attainment level, he found the source of the problem.

It was because he had used two conflicting water path mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan immediately changed one of them, in Reverse Flow River, he could open his immortal aperture and connect to treasure yellow heaven to purchase water path mortal Gu easily.

After modifying the entire immortal killer move, Fang Yuan tried to activate it again for the second time.

Perseverance Immortal Gu was still in use.

The surrounding water path mortal Gu started to rise and fly around it.

First was water vapor and blue light, he soon passed this stage as Fang Yuan used Immortal Gu Pulling Water.

Rank six strength path Immortal Gu Pulling Water.

This was the second core of the immortal killer move.

The first core was undeniably rank seven perseverance Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was careful.

While activating perseverance Immortal Gu, he activated Pulling Water, it was a very risky thing.

If he could not manage it well, these two Immortal Gu might interfere and cause harm to each other, they might even get destroyed.

Testing immortal killer moves was not just risky to the Gu Immortal, the Immortal Gu and mortal Gu involved were also in danger. And because Immortal Gu themselves were fragments of the Great Dao, when they suffered a backlash, the damage was much more severe.

Fang Yuan was very vigilant, he was quickly rewarded for it.

He met with difficulty.

Although pulling water Immortal Gu was activated and its mystical power was used, it could not integrate into the framework of the move.

"What is the problem?"

Fang Yuan stopped.

A lot of water path mortal Gu were destroyed.

Experimenting with immortal killer moves had a price.

A complete and effective immortal killer move needed conceptualization and experimentation, the Gu Immortal needed to put in a lot of effort and resources.

As the attacks in the outside world continued, Fang Yuan ignored them, he had the sovereign immortal body, his thoughts were produced rapidly as they moved around and collided.

With his wisdom path grandmaster attainment level, wisdom path dao marks, as well as wisdom path methods, his deductions were progressing rapidly.

It was faster this time!

In just a few breaths of time, Fang Yuan found the problem.

The powers of perseverance Immortal Gu and pulling water Immortal Gu could not fuse together, it was because the quantity and types of water path mortal Gu were not appropriate. These mortal Gu were the bridge between the two Immortal Gu, they had the effect of linking them.

Fang Yuan thought about it, he reduced a portion of some water path mortal Gu and while increasing others, at the same time, he added in new water path mortal Gu.

The third activation.

This time, it was smooth sailing, he successfully fused pulling water Immortal Gu into the killer move.

The moment he succeeded, there were waves forming in the Reverse Flow River water below him.

It was finally starting to work!

But he was still far from reaching his goal.

Fang Yuan did not rest, he could not waste time in this situation, he continued experimenting, activating the immortal killer move, his aura strengthened and weakened at times, flickering continuously.

"What is Liu Guan Yi doing?"

"Gu worm auras are appearing on his body from time to time, it looks like he is experimenting with an immortal killer move?"

Other than Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Mao Li Qiu, the other Gu Immortals were just watching.

Every time Fang Yuan experimented with his immortal killer move, the Gu worm auras would leak, it could not be concealed from the Gu Immortals.

If he wanted to conceal the auras, he needed a special immortal killer move.

These types of immortal killer moves were very rare, like Fang Yuan's dark assassination, it was among these immortal killer moves.

Fang Yuan reached his limits in conceptualized myriad self second style, he could not consider adding aura concealment to it.

But it did not matter.

Gu worm auras alone could not determine the types of Gu worms.

Furthermore, he had just created myriad self second style, it was complex and used many different Gu, it was not possible for them to find out its flaws by watching.

Fourth time, fifth time...

Fang Yuan continued to activate the immortal killer move, sometimes he made great progress, while sometimes, because of some adjustments, he backtracked by several steps.

Fang Yuan was not dejected, he persevered on without any expression.

"He is really testing an immortal killer move."

"Hehehe, is this Liu Guan Yi an idiot? Creating an immortal killer move on the spot, does he think he is an Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable?"

"Even if he creates an immortal killer move, I want to see if he can use it to deal with all of us?"

The Gu Immortals watching all commented on Fang Yuan's naivety and mocked him in disdain.

If immortal killer moves were so easy to create, would they still be immortal killer moves?

But soon, some of their expressions changed.

They found that some mystical changes were occurring in Reverse Flow River.

"Twenty-first try."

Fang Yuan stretched out his arm, grabbing towards at river below his feet.

"Rise." At the same time, he muttered lightly.

Bam.

A soft sound occurred as a huge ball appeared on the river surface near him.

This ball was completely made of Reverse Flow River's water, after rising, it burst as water splattered everywhere.

The killer move activation failed!

Fang Yuan's nose was bleeding as two streams of blood flowed down.

"His immortal killer move has effect on Reverse Flow River?" Yu Yi Ye Zi saw this and his eyes shined with sharp light.

"No, more accurately speaking, he is using Reverse Flow River to create an immortal killer move!" Bu Zhen Zi said.

"Hmph, laughable." Black Extremity smiled coldly: "Back then, I used Reverse Flow River to create the sub and main fate reversing refinement formation, it used up several years of my time. Liu Guan Yi, even if you are the Reverse Flow River Lord, you are simply too arrogant, you think you can create an immortal killer move using it in such a short amount of time?"

Evidently, none of the Gu Immortals here thought highly of Fang Yuan's chances.

But soon, Fang Yuan started his testing again.

Pew!

This time, a small mound appeared on the river surface near him.

The mound quickly collapsed as the water doused Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's expression turned pale, his body wavered, not only did he have a nosebleed, even his ears were bleeding.

"I failed again, Man as Before!" At the next moment, he was completely healed.

"I should find the reason for the failure. It seems that a small problem occurred at the final juncture..." Fang Yuan fell into deep contemplation.

Chapter 1289: Reverse Flow Protection Seal

A moment later, Fang Yuan opened his eyes, activating the killer move again.

This time, a segment of Reverse Flow River's water was moved by him, causing huge waves.

The immortals' expressions changed.

Even Old Ancestor Xue Hu's attacks stopped.

But at the next moment, Old Ancestor Xue Hu shouted loudly and erupted with even stronger attacks.

"This is so hard. Because I added in many Gu worms of different types, many problems occurred. But this is already my current limit. To create a concise version, I will need years to deduce, or an increase in my attainment level once again."

Fang Yuan knew that this myriad self second style had too many Gu worms involved, it was too complex and had many issues to deal with.

While Fang Yuan was sighing at the difficult progress, the other Gu Immortals were filled with shock.

Even though they did not speak, their gazes were flickering.

"Liu Guan Yi, this fellow..."

"Such fast progress! He could really mobilize Reverse Flow River."

"Unbelievable! Is he really human? He could achieve such progress in this short period of time."

"No, there is no way he can succeed. How can he really create an immortal killer move in such a short amount of time?"

Undeniably, Fang Yuan's rapid advancement had broken the common sense of these immortals.

They had never seen a person create an immortal killer move in such a short period of time and gain such rapid improvements through experimentation.

But right now, they were seeing it live.

Fang Yuan continued.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu and the dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, subconsciously increased their attacking power.

But Reverse Flow River was too huge, even after their endless attacks, they consumed less than five percent of the entire river.

"Once more! Rise." Fang Yuan had a serious expression, he grabbed at the air towards the river below him as he called out.

This time, the entirety of Reverse Flow River was affected, it was like a long dragon awakening from its slumber, it started to stretch its entire body freely.

"How could this happen?!" Someone cried out subconsciously.

The entirety of Reverse Flow River started to fly in the sky like a rising dragon, ready to soar and roam the five regions and nine heavens.

"Wishful thinking!" Old Ancestor Xue Hu shouted, slamming with his palms as an icy light shot out towards Reverse Flow River.

Reverse Flow River was hit and reflected it, the icy light seemed to have collided into a mirror, it was sent right back at him, in the blink of an eye, all of the vast surrounding grassland turned into an icy plain.

Frost energy permeated, the sky was snowing, the temperature was falling.

Strong winds blew intensely, the entire world seemed to have changed colors.

This was the power of a rank eight!

Fang Yuan could not help but feel shocked.

He was temporarily safe in Reverse Flow River, and the other Gu Immortals were protected by their rank eight existences.

Ying Wu Xie was covered in cold sweat, Purple Mountain True Monarch had awakened again at the crucial moment, if not for him, Ying Wu Xie and the rest would not have survived.

"We will leave." Purple Mountain True Monarch said.

"But this..." Ying Wu Xie hesitated, but Purple Mountain True Monarch waved his hand and several rings of light appeared, capturing Ying Wu Xie and gang, sending them towards the sky.

To think that Shadow Sect was the first to retreat.

Purple Mountain True Monarch left rapidly without saying a word, the Gu Immortals present were stunned.

"Lord, that is the sovereign immortal aperture..." Ying Wu Xie was anxious, he transmitted to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

"Don't worry, I have already deduced that he won't die! He can definitely escape." Purple Mountain True Monarch said confidently.

Ying Wu Xie was not very convinced of Purple Mountain True Monarch's words, but he could not express his doubts.

But at the next moment, he saw that all of Reverse Flow River started to glow in a bright blue light.

Blue light flickered like rumbling clouds or raging currents.

The immortals' gazes were all attracted to it.

Fang Yuan stood in the middle, great winds were blowing, causing his hair and sleeves to flutter in the sky.

His eyes were eerie, he said softly: "Rise."

Instantly, the river water surged and the immortals could hear the sounds of the waves, it resembled the roaring of a thousand men, the scene was domineering and grand.

Immediately after, the blue light condensed, Reverse Flow River shrank, it became a tiny dot in an instant.

The huge Reverse Flow River vanished, it condensed towards Fang Yuan and turned into a light blue colored robe.

This long robe had wide sleeves, it was white like snow. On the surface of the robe, there was slow flowing water, it was the same appearance as Reverse Flow River earlier.

Not just that, the surface of the white robe had faint mist surrounding it. There was also a strip of light that was deep azure, it was curvy and wavy, resembling a long sash, it coiled around Fang Yuan's arms, the back of his neck, and around his waist again.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self Second Style — Reverse Flow Protection Seal, had been successfully activated at this moment!

"He succeeded?!"

"Impossible!"

"He actually used Reverse Flow River to create a new immortal killer move in this short time?"

The immortals saw this and became tongue-tied, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was staring fiercely: "I refuse to believe this!"

He thrusted with his palms in Fang Yuan's direction.

Immediately, an icy light shot out at incredible speed towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was prepared to face it.

The icy light landed on his body, but it was fully blocked by reverse flow protection seal.

Reverse flow protection seal flickered as the terrifying icy light was reflected back at its creator, Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

"Success!" Fang Yuan's heart was jumping, it gradually calmed down.

Even though the immortal killer move was activated successfully, he needed to test it.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's attack confirmed that Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal was incredibly powerful!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu dodged the icy light, his expression turned ruthless and harsh as he looked at Fang Yuan.

"Let me try." Mao Li Qiu shouted.

Its body vanished on the spot, at the next moment, it appeared behind Fang Yuan.

Its ruthless claws were raised and they landed harshly.

Boom!

A loud sound could be heard, Fang Yuan flew out like a cannonball that was shot out.

His field of vision changed, Fang Yuan had landed on the ground a breath of time later.

Next, with a loud explosion, a huge crater was formed on the icy ground.

Under everyone's watchful gazes, Fang Yuan slowly stood up in the deep crater, he was expressionless and his body was intact, there was not even a graze on his skin!

Reverse flow protection seal had turned into a snow-white robe with an azure sash, there were almost no changes to it, but the mist on the surface of the robe had dissipated to a large extent. If one observed closely, the snow-white robe seemed to be covered in a layer of dust, it was no longer as bright as before.

Mao Li Qiu looked at Fang Yuan before turning to look at its claws.

Its right paw was covered in blood, its flesh was exposed now!

Fang Yuan suffered no injuries, while Mao Li Qiu was quite severely injured.

"Gasp..." Sounds could be heard coming from the Gu Immortals present.

"What immortal killer move is this? Even Mao Li Qiu suffered a loss!!"

Seeing this, even Bi Chen Tian's eyes were twitching rapidly.

"He actually did it!" Black Extremity was speechless, his expression was of utter shock.

"Even an immemorial desolate beast's physical attack was reflected back?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu frowned deeply.

"How can this be?" Ying Wu Xie, who was far away in the sky, saw this and felt like he was dreaming.

There had never been a case where a rank eight Gu Immortal attacked a rank seven Gu Immortal and resulted in the rank seven Gu Immortal being unharmed, while the rank eight Gu Immortal was actually injured!

Rank eight and rank seven, the former always suppressed the latter.

In the last few thousand years, Feng Jiu Ge was the sole monster who had overwhelming talent, he was unparalleled and could battle rank eight existences.

But now, after Fang Yuan created myriad self second style, and successfully used it, Feng Jiu Ge no longer held this title alone.

From now on, this supreme glory was shared with another person.

Liu Guan Yi!

"Central's Feng Jiu Ge, North's Liu Guan Yi..." Bu Zhen Zi muttered in a daze.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu smiled lightly: "Lad, I underestimated you after all."

His arms were behind his back, he stopped attacking.

But Mao Li Qiu was furious: "Little lad, you are courting death, you dared to make me lose face!!"

The immemorial desolate beast attacked Fang Yuan furiously.

Fang Yuan was not its match, he was slammed away like a rubber ball.

But after dozens of blows, Fang Yuan was unharmed, he still had a pristine air, but Mao Li Qiu was panting roughly, bleeding profusely.

Every one of its attacks was reflected back at itself.

Mao Li Qiu was staring furiously, thinking: "This lad is a porcupine, I'm hurting myself, since when did Northern Plains have such a monster?"

Fang Yuan saw that Mao Li Qiu was at a loss against him and laughed, charging at the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were like frightened birds, they dispersed at once.

The two Central Continent rank eights stayed and attacked Fang Yuan.

But it was no use!

Reverse flow protection seal was reflecting their attacks back at them, they landed on Mao Li Qiu, who was chasing after him.

Mao Li Qiu was suffering greatly, so angry it was about to blow up, it spat out a vast amount of purple light, its attack engulfed an enormous surrounding range.

This attack caused a huge battle.

The situation became chaotic, the Gu Immortals of all three sides were attacking.

This was the last thing Ying Wu Xie saw.

He was in deep admiration towards Purple Mountain True Monarch's decision of retreating.

At the same time, he understood: After this battle, Liu Guan Yi's name would spread throughout the five regions, it would shock the world, his reputation would rival Feng Jiu Ge!

More than ten days later, a figure in a sorry state passed the regional wall, arriving at Eastern Sea.

It was Fang Yuan.

"I finally got free from that crazy animal." Fang Yuan sighed deeply.

More than ten days ago, Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Central Continent's Gu Immortals, and Longevity Heaven engaged in fierce combat, they fought with all they had.

Fang Yuan managed to escape from this chaotic battle, but Mao Li Qiu refused to stop chasing him.

Fang Yuan was not Mao Li Qiu's match, but after he entered Northern Plains' regional wall, Mao Li Qiu could only watch helplessly.

It was a wild beast born in Northern Plains, it was restricted by the regional wall.

Fang Yuan managed to escape from these pursuers.

"Time to go back to Southern Border." Fang Yuan did not stay, he flew into the clouds.

Chapter 1290: Truce Between Shadow Sect and Fang Yuan?

On the dark stone wall, eerie flames were burning.

The flames were not big, they were like fireflies or lanterns in size.

They were green flames that were cold and icy, the pale flames reflected on the faces of Purple Mountain True Monarch, Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, and Hei Lou Lan.

Being the first to leave the Reverse Flow River battle, they were brought here by Purple Mountain True Monarch.

But after that, Purple Mountain True Monarch returned to a state of insanity.

Looking at Purple Mountain True Monarch, who was nibbling on his toes, Bai Ning Bing sneered at Ying Wu Xie: "This is your plan? This is the rank eight great expert who will kill Fang Yuan?"

In this trip to Snowy Mountain blessed land, even though Ying Wu Xie saved Purple Mountain True Monarch, he lost a lot, Shi Nu and Tai Bai Yun Sheng died in battle.

Hei Lou Lan was silent.

This rank eight Gu Immortal was unreliable.

But due to Shadow Sect's alliance agreement, Hei Lou Lan kept quiet.

Ying Wu Xie was mocked by Bai Ning Bing, but his expression remained the same.

After so many setbacks, he had gained a disposition of being calm no matter the situation.

He slowly spoke: "I underestimated Fang Yuan, to think that he would refine perseverance Immortal Gu and become the Reverse Flow River Lord. No wonder heaven's will chose him as a tool. This person can only be killed, he cannot be defeated."

Ying Wu Xie praised Fang Yuan without hesitation.

Even though they were enemies, Ying Wu Xie had an open mind, he admitted that Fang Yuan had both the advantage and superior strength.

Bai Ning Bing snorted coldly, thinking about the scene where Fang Yuan conquered Reverse Flow River, she no longer said anything.

In the tiny cave, only Purple Mountain True Monarch's screaming echoed throughout the place.

A moment later, Purple Mountain True Monarch stopped shouting, his tiny body shook before he stood up calmly.

He straightened his back, clarity returning to his eyes.

"Lord, you are awake!" Ying Wu Xie was overjoyed, he quickly got closer.

Purple Mountain True Monarch held his forehead, feeling pain in his head, his expression was distorting from the pain.

"Earlier in Reverse Flow River, I forced myself to awaken, thus it was only for a moment. But now is different, I have quite some time left. How long has it been? How did the battle end?"

"It has already been half a month. Fang Yuan escaped Northern Plains through the regional wall, I assume he entered Eastern Sea. After all, he has some foundation in Eastern Sea. As for the battle, the result has yet to be determined. Central Continent's Gu Immortals wanted to leave, but Old Ancestor Xue Hu pursued them, during the dangerous situation, an Immortal Gu House descended from the sky, as both parties went to fight in white heaven." Ying Wu Xie answered.

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "This time, Central Continent's Gu Immortals will likely lose, in the past, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable chose Northern Plains as his domain, how could he not make arrangements here? For example, none of Longevity Heaven's rank eight Gu Immortals have shown up yet."

"Lord, what do we do from now on?" Ying Wu Xie asked.

He was once in charge of Shadow Sect, now that Purple Mountain True Monarch woke up, this rank eight great expert was naturally going to lead Shadow Sect, Ying Wu Xie had to step down.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was about to speak when the sound of winds echoed in this cave.

Next, the eerie fire on the cave walls started flickering intensely, as if a strong wind was blowing.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's gaze flickered: "I arranged this cave as one of our escape methods. These eerie fires were nurtured by me to create a natural Gu formation, it allows us to defend against deductions from others. When I was insane, how many times did they flicker?"

"A hundred and seven times." Bai Ning Bing said plainly.

"I am afraid Fang Yuan's deductions are included in this. His investigative killer move can use the profundities of luck path and find our locations. Even inside an immortal aperture, we cannot hide from him." Ying Wu Xie said grimly.

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "Fang Yuan is indeed worthy of being the person nurtured by heaven's will, as the crucial key to deal with our Shadow Sect. This person is very daring and has incredible talent, his willpower is unparalleled, he is truly an absolute genius seen once in ten thousand years."

Purple of Shadow Sect actually gave Fang Yuan such a high evaluation.

But the three Gu Immortals present were silent, they agreed with Purple Mountain True Monarch's words.

Purple Mountain True Monarch continued: "And now, our plan is to reach a truce with Fang Yuan."

These were shocking words.

"What, a truce?" Ying Wu Xie and the rest were shocked.

"Is that very strange?" Purple Mountain True Monarch looked at the three.

He was very clear of the current situation. When he woke up, Ying Wu Xie had used information path methods to inform Purple Mountain True Monarch of everything he knew.

"You are all too young, you know too little. Our biggest enemy now is not Fang Yuan but Heavenly Court." Purple Mountain True Monarch shook his head, looking at Ying Wu Xie: "Do you think rescuing our main body's soul is easy? Other than the super Gu formation in Southern Border, and that giant dream realm, I can assure you that when we strike, Heavenly Court will interfere! Like on Yi Tian Mountain, they used Heaven Overseeing Tower and attempted to thwart our plan. Or like this time, when they went to Snowy Mountain blessed land to save Ma Hong Yun."

Ying Wu Xie's expression was grim: "Lord, I considered that before, but our main body is in great danger, he is trapped by the dream realm and is being consumed by it, that's why I was so anxious..."

"That is exactly why we need to cooperate with Fang Yuan." Purple Mountain True Monarch added.

"Firstly, Fang Yuan's strength is already extraordinary, that immortal killer move alone can stand up to rank eight Gu Immortals."

"Secondly, Fang Yuan is a complete otherworldly demon, he is listed on the Demon Judgment Board, and is a common enemy of Heavenly Court."

"Finally, cooperating is a win-win situation for us. Our Shadow Sect has huge amounts of cultivation resources, while he has the killer move to unravel dreams, he can help us conquer the giant dream realm and save our main body's soul."

Ying Wu Xie frowned deeply, he cast aside his personal emotions and tried to consider the possibility of this.

But soon, he expressed his worries: "Fang Yuan is scheming and vicious, he thinks of us as huge threats, he wants to eliminate us all. Now that he is the Reverse Flow River Lord, he is already able to contest with rank eight existences. We desperately need methods to unravel dreams, while he needs cultivation resources less urgently. It is hard for us to cooperate."

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "You are completely right, but do you know about the biggest flaw of the sovereign immortal body?"

"What do you mean? You mean the non-conflicting dao marks of the sovereign immortal body?" Ying Wu Xie asked in confusion.

"Of course not. Non-conflicting dao marks are the sovereign immortal body's biggest advantage, far surpassing the weaknesses that they bring. What I mean is that hidden problem!" Purple Mountain True Monarch shook his head.

"There is an important hidden problem?" Ying Wu Xie was shocked.

"Our original plan was to refine a rank ten sovereign immortal fetus Gu. Only rank ten sovereign immortal fetus Gu can be considered perfect without any flaws. But evidently, we only refined a rank nine version, that huge drawback has not shown itself yet, but it will force Fang Yuan to cooperate with us regardless." Purple Mountain True Monarch said.

The sovereign immortal body had a major flaw!

As for what flaw it was that made Purple Mountain True Monarch so certain that it would restrict Fang Yuan?

Ying Wu Xie and the rest were curious, but Purple Mountain True Monarch did not answer it.

At the same time, Purple Mountain True Monarch had his own questions and suspicions.

"Strange."

"From Ying Wu Xie's information, our sect refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu very hurriedly. It is not like our original plan."

"What is the reason that made our main body act so urgently?"

"It seems that alongside getting in contact with Fang Yuan, I need to make a trip to the River of Time!"

Eastern Sea.

Above the blue sea, Fang Yuan rapidly moved through the white clouds, his target was Southern Border.

"Happening again!" While flying, Fang Yuan's expression changed.

He could sense that the power of Dark Limit on him was rapidly consumed. This consumption was so fast that it was going to be used up soon.

Evidently, a great expert was deducing matters about him.

When he saw that no one was around, Fang Yuan quickly placed his immortal aperture.

After entering the immortal aperture, isolating him from the outside world, and preventing the deduction of the other party, Fang Yuan's danger of getting exposed was alleviated.

Fang Yuan sighed.

After the battle of Reverse Flow River, he was met with countless deductions.

Liu Guan Yi's identity became extremely famous.

Not just Northern Plains and Central Continent, even Eastern Sea, Southern Border, and Western Desert Gu Immortals were very curious about Liu Guan Yi, they wanted to deduce more information about him.

Liu Guan Yi was a fake identity, but he was still Fang Yuan.

This way, Fang Yuan endured all of the pressure.

Even with dark limit Immortal Gu, he had to constantly stop and hide inside his immortal aperture.

Along the way, Fang Yuan met with about four to five hundred deductions.

This greatly interfered with his traveling, he had to constantly stop, and resulted in him still being in Eastern Sea now.

With his usual speed, he would be in Southern Border already.

"If not for dark limit Immortal Gu, the situation would be worse."

"However, it is to be expected that I created such a huge commotion. After all, people are putting me in the same class as Feng Jiu Ge."

"When I destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and Imperial Court blessed land, I had Shadow Sect's help and felt no pressure, but now I do. It seems that getting an immortal killer move to deal with these deductions is necessary."

Fang Yuan was a wisdom path grandmaster, deducing an immortal killer move was not impossible. But it would not be as easy as creating reverse flow protection seal.

After all, when deducing reverse flow protection seal, there were many elements involved other than his water path attainment level.

Most importantly, he had the appropriate Immortal Gu along with a strong foundation, thus he met with no problems.

But currently, the Immortal Gu that suited this was Dark Limit, it was not wisdom path but dark path instead.

Fang Yuan's dark path attainment level was not outstanding.

Chapter 1291: Huge Assets

While evading deductions, Fang Yuan did not waste time, he inspected his immortal aperture.

Five regions, nine heavens.

The sizes were incredible, beyond this world's common sense.

335000km2 of space was already shockingly huge, nobody would believe it if they heard of it.

But now, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had exceeded 335000km2 of space already.

This was because he had been slaughtering Gu Immortals and annexing their immortal apertures recently.

Because of the sovereign immortal body's special characteristics, Fang Yuan could completely annex other people's blessed lands and absorb all their dao marks without any wastage.

These immortal apertures added up to create many unique areas in the sovereign immortal aperture.

These areas were mainly managed by land spirits, Fang Yuan could save a lot of effort. They were like tiny pearls scattered all over the five regions and nine heavens.

"I have incredible amounts of space path resources. Normal Gu Immortals try by all means possible to expand their immortal apertures, but I have so much space that I have yet to develop."

Fang Yuan was satisfied with this, on the other hand, regarding the time path resources, he had a different feeling.

The sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time had slowed a lot.

It was one-to-sixty earlier, this was simply unmatched!

But now, it was below normal standards.

This was something he had no other way to deal with.

Before Fang Yuan changed his cultivation method, in order to stall calamities and tribulations, he had to do this.

He used the time path methods in Hei Fan's true inheritance to slow the time in his immortal aperture, with fewer time path resources now, Fang Yuan's immortal essence production fell greatly, not just that, all of his gains in his other resources also fell.

Thinking over it in detail.

Inside Mini Central Continent, there was the blood zhi forest, and mirror willows, they were from Hu Immortal blessed land. Other than these, there was a small jade light pit.

This small jade light pit had light path mortal Gu in it, the quantity was large.

This was created in his immortal aperture after Fang Yuan took reference from the jade light pit resource point of Northern Plains' Liu tribe.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan ransacked the jade light pit and took away all of the light path mortal Gu in it.

A portion of the light path Gu worms were placed into the aurora lights in the nine heavens, but the rest could not be sold easily.

Fang Yuan thus created a small jade light pit to temporarily store these light path mortal Gu.

Of course, this small jade light pit could not compare with the genuine article. The latter was a true resource point, it had a lot of light path dao marks and any insect group placed in it would become Gu over time. But the former was only created by Fang Yuan haphazardly to store his light path Gu worms, it had no production capabilities.

Mini Central Continent had the least development among the five mini regions.

Mini Northern Plains was at a higher level.

Mini Northern Plains had flat terrain that was mostly covered in snow and ice, becoming an icy plain.

But snow and ice were not its only features.

Closer to Eastern Sea, there was a shallow green beach, pieces of rocks were piled together to form a special lake. The aquatic plants inside were growing well, as spirit snakes lived in it.

This shallow beach was the blessed land of transformation path Gu Immortal Han Dong, after Fang Yuan annexed it, even the pinkish red spirit snake land spirit was moved over and managed the area for him.

Nearer to Western Desert, there was a bone burial field.

There was a mountain of skeletons here of all types, collarbones, skulls, leg bones, even those from flying animals, there were lots of immortal materials that were very valuable.

This bone burial field was the bone burial field that Fang Yuan took from Liu tribe.

After killing Liu tribe Gu Immortal Liu Yong, he moved this bone burial field directly into his immortal aperture.

Thus, he had this resource point that could generate bone path Gu worms.

"But compared to the original bone burial field, my bone burial field may have a lot of bones, but the bone path dao marks cannot match the original. In the original bone burial field, even the surrounding soil had bone path dao marks. Liu tribe can rebuild their bone burial field with no problems."

Fang Yuan knew this deeply.

Of course, Fang Yuan had already taken eighty percent of this bone burial field, the most valuable thing were these bones.

The remaining twenty percent was the soil terrain, Liu tribe could rebuild their bone burial field, but to regain its former scale, they would need to expend a lot of resources.

And closer to Central Continent.

This was a sparse grassland with all sorts of wildflowers and grass, there were mainly blood sickle grass and red axe flowers.

These were from Hu Immortal blessed land too.

This grassland was huge, surpassing Han Dong blessed land. There were some pink flower rabbits, fox groups, water wolf groups, earth skin boar groups, poison beard wolf groups, and others, there was even a shark fin wolf and a desolate beast giant horned sheep, they were living in this grassland.

Mini Western Desert had the highest temperature.

Because most of the fire path dao marks were gathered here, the soil was sandy.

There were three main resource points here.

The first were the eerie fire dragon python dens, there were a lot of them in a particular area.

The second was the the sand gull soil beach.

It produced sand gull soil.

Sand gull soil was a Gu material, it was also the food of connect luck Immortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan did not have connect luck Immortal Gu anymore, sand gull soil was now a resource sold to help Fang Yuan earn immortal essence stones.

At the center of the sand gull soil, there was the dead egg of the worldly sand gull. It was filled with cracks, there were several small holes on it, as transparent egg white flowed out of the cracks slowly. Using the life essence in this egg, one could turn ordinary sand into sand gull soil.

The third was the rotten black swamp. This was formed when Fang Yuan went through tribulation, it was filled with dark path dao marks. Fang Yuan had already modified it to become a dark path Gu worm resource point now, but because it had just been made, its production was low.

Other than these three resource points, there were two blessed lands.

One was an earth path blessed land resembling a rotting swamp, there were five desolate beast mud monsters inside, and all sorts of earth path mortal Gu, it was managed by the small mudman land spirit.

The other was Liu Yong's enslavement path blessed land, there were more than twenty dog desolate beasts in it. These desolate beasts were all purchased in treasure yellow heaven by Fang Yuan. This was because Liu Yong blessed land's ownership requirement was to have twenty hound type desolate beasts. Among those were his six bone armor hounds. The entire blessed land was managed by a black hound land spirit.

Mini Eastern Sea's development was about the same as Mini Western Desert.

Wu Yi Hai's blessed land was here.

This was a sea that was well managed by Wu Yi Hai, there were three ancient desolate beast horned divine tortoises, a huge field of ancient desolate plant silent corals, and six desolate beast white letter blue feather seagulls, managed by the sea turtle land spirit.

Other than that, there was the original dragonfish group and two desolate beast dragonfish, air bubble fish group, as well as some rare literature carps and some oil water. There were large numbers of blue jade carps, blood jade carps, and an ancient desolate beast hidden room oyster (obtained in the turbulent flow sea area).

There was another blood lake, it had a large amount of desolate beast blood and Gu Immortal blood, Fang Yuan had once placed blood asset Immortal Gu here to recover.

Right now, blood asset Immortal Gu had fully recovered, but this blood lake remained.

In the five mini regions, Mini Southern Border was the richest.

Five Light Mountain, Immortal Succession Mountain, Heaven Sealing Mountain and others, for a total of more than ten mountains here.

Stalactite cave, regretful spider group, a small number of rockmen, a huge forest with musical trees, tea streams, and qi death birds singing.

There was a Become Dragon Mound, Fang Yuan had used pulling mountain Immortal Gu to move it into his immortal aperture from Northern Plains.

And in the nine heavens.

A small field of aurora lights were in Mini Orange Heaven. There were a lot of floating flowing light fruits in the aurora lights, and because he had obtained a lot of light path Gu worms from the jade light pit, the scale of the aurora lights and flowing light fruits expanded greatly on its original foundation.

And in Mini Yellow Heaven, there was a small gold fragment current.

In Mini Azure Heaven, there was a lot of pill azure incense, this was the food of change soul Immortal Gu. There was a heavenly crystal storage pool, it came from Hei Fan grotto-heaven and had no use for now.

Mini Black Heaven had the walking meat tree, Mini White Heaven had multicolored overlord flowers, three ancient remnant heavenly dogs, one ancient eagle hound, and seven desolate beast eagle hounds.

Mini Purple Heaven had the upper extreme heavenly eagle, although it had only desolate beast strength. More than eighty eagle nests were floating here. These were the loot from attacking Iron Eagle blessed land. The original eagle nest had already been fully eaten by the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

In Mini Blue Heaven, there was a lot of cloud soil, on top of them were the arrow bamboo forest, a star fragment grass field, and an infant falling star hound. The two desolate beast spinefin star dragonfish had already been sold, during the battle to defend Hei Fan grotto-heaven.

There was also a meteorite pit that produced stellar fire Gu and falling meteor Gu. After killing Ye Lui Qun Xing and obtaining his blessed land, Fang Yuan also placed it here, it was a floating island filled with star fragments, the star core land spirit was managing it.

There were also some blessed lands scattered around, and some other desolate beasts and desolate plants, there was no need to discuss them in detail.

As for Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, they were in Lang Ya blessed land.

Reverse Flow River was temporarily placed in Mini Eastern Sea by Fang Yuan.

As for Gu worms —

Rank nine wisdom Gu was in Lang Ya blessed land. Sovereign immortal fetus Gu had already been used, it would not be counted.

Rank eight Immortal Gu: Attitude, Wisdom Sword, Years Flow Like Water (sealed).

Rank seven Immortal Gu: Sword Eyebrows, Wave Sword, Flying Sword, Sword Escape, Calamity Beckoning (with Chu Du), Year, After, Dragon Breath, Affection, Perseverance.

Rank six Immortal Gu: Unravel Mystery, Woman's Heart, Blood Asset, Dark Limit, Dog Shit Luck, Change Form, Strength Qi, Self Strength, Flying Bear Strength, Pulling Mountain, Pulling Water, Landscape as Before, Man as Before, Star Eyes, Spring Autumn Cicada (contains heaven's will, stored in the immortal zombie body), Bone Spike, Perceivable Dao.

The mortal Gu were of all different types, they will be skipped.

Hei Cheng's dark arrow Immortal Gu had self-detonated, Fang Yuan did not obtain it.

In terms of captives, there was Fang Zheng (in Lang Ya blessed land), Hei Cheng (intact body), Ma Hong Yun's soul, Liu Yong's soul, Ye Lui Qun Xing's soul. As for Shi Nu's soul, Fang Yuan did not obtain it. Shadow Sect had incredible attainment in soul path, Fang Yuan could not stop the soul from dissipating even though he captured it.

As for the rest, like Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul, the featherman Gu Immortal's soul, the Eastern Sea Gu Immortals' souls, they were all sold to Lang Ya land spirit for sect contribution points. They were probably absorbed by Dang Hun Mountain and made into guts Gu by now.

There was also the featherman Gu Immortal slave Zhou Zhong, he was sent to Western Desert by Fang Yuan to establish another plan.

Huge assets!

This was Fang Yuan's current portfolio, it was no exaggeration.

In total, even though he was rank seven, he could fully rival ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals in assets.

Just those secluded domains of heaven and earth were incredibly valuable. And his Gu worms were plentiful, the number shockingly high!

Look at Gu Immortal Hei Fan, he was a rank eight Gu Immortal. how many Immortal Gu did he have?

But many Immortal Gu would create the problem of feeding them.

Fang Yuan was still at this stage, trying to provide food for his Immortal Gu.

The rank six and seven Immortal Gu were basically fine. The problems were attitude Gu and wisdom sword Immortal Gu, these two rank eight Immortal Gu.

The new perseverance Gu that he obtained fed on Reverse Flow River's water, Fang Yuan could easily feed it. Affection Gu fed on the same thing as love Gu, hope and fear, Fang Yuan could easily resolve that, he bought a large number of hope Gu and fear Gu from treasure yellow heaven.

For Fang Yuan, developing his immortal aperture was not the main point now.

As long as he slaughtered Gu Immortals and annexed their immortal apertures, his immortal aperture's foundation would continue to grow.

He was facing the problem of insufficient immortal essence.

Pursuing Ying Wu Xie and gang, the Reverse Flow River battle, and escaping from Mao Li Qiu, Fang Yuan expended a lot of immortal essence.

This caused his red date immortal essence storage to fall to a critical level.

"Originally, with my time path resources, the rate of time was fast, my immortal aperture produced a lot of red date immortal essence."

"But after using my time path methods, the immortal aperture's time is close to the five regions' time, I can only replenish my immortal essence through transactions."

Reverse flow protection seal used a lot of the Gu Immortal's mental energy and immortal essence.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan was a rank seven Gu Immortal now, if he was still using green grape immortal essence, he would have ran out of them.

Without red date immortal essence, Fang Yuan did not have much confidence.

While resting, he sold all of the desolate beast corpses in treasure yellow heaven.

These desolate beast corpses were immortal materials of high quantity. Fang Yuan had exterminated these desolate beast groups while he was pursuing Ying Wu Xie in Earth Trench.

Among them were a group of nightmare demonic colts, if these dream path immortal materials were sold in treasure yellow heaven, a huge commotion would arise, many Gu Immortals would fight for them.

But Fang Yuan kept all of these nightmare demonic colt corpses with him, he had better use for them.

After resting for a while, he made several transactions.

After subtracting the transaction fees of treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan earned a lot of immortal essence stones.

One immortal essence stone could convert to one bead of green grape immortal essence.

Fang Yuan was a rank seven Gu Immortal, using a hundred immortal essence stones would create one bead of red date immortal essence.

While he was replenishing his red date immortal essence stockpile, he received some information.

"This is a letter from Sixth Hair."

Fang Yuan felt strange.

After checking it, he felt shocked: "Shadow Sect wants to negotiate a truce with me, they even want us to work together?"

Author's Note: Collating Fang Yuan's assets was too tiring!

Chapter 1292: Attitude Gu's Problem

Fang Yuan's gaze was flickering.

Shadow Sect's letter was out of his expectations.

But thinking about it, it was completely logical.

In the battle of Reverse Flow River, even though Fang Yuan did not obtain a lot of cultivation resources, his battle strength rose drastically, he was at the level of the strongest person under rank eight, on par with Feng Jiu Ge.

The increase in his battle strength gave rise to his heightened status.

Actually, before this letter, he also received others.

Like the one from Chu Du. Chu Du spoke very politely in the letter, congratulating Fang Yuan for his victory and expressing regret at not being there. Next, he talked about his own situation, Chu Sect was now Chu tribe, and the supreme elders were now all external supreme elders. The disciples of Chu Du were his god-children now, and finally, Chu Du talked about his own difficulties, because he created a tribe and became part of the righteous path, he had to expel Fang Yuan from Chu Sect. This was not his own wish, he was forced to do so.

There was also one from the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics. Other than congratulating Fang Yuan, they invited him enthusiastically to explore Crazed Demon Cave. They said: Even if Northern Plains did not welcome him, Crazed Demon Cave would always be his home. These words were very mushy, it showed their brand new attitude towards him.

Regarding Longevity Heaven, they were putting up arrest warrants for Fang Yuan. After all, he killed Ma Hong Yun.

However, Liu tribe and Ye Lui tribe, who were pursuing Fang Yuan earlier, had quietened down.

Fang Yuan's battle strength shocked them completely. They quickly recalled the members they sent out to find him.

Instead, they were afraid that Fang Yuan would take revenge on them. After all, Fang Yuan's strength was incredibly famous in Northern Plains now, well beyond Chu Du.

"And now, Shadow Sect has sent a letter seeking cooperation. Hehe."

"Shadow Sect has a rank eight Gu Immortal, but he has a major weakness, he becomes insane at times." Fang Yuan thought about it, he had fought Purple Mountain True Monarch in Reverse Flow River, he learned something about his condition.

Actually, if Fang Yuan did not refine perseverance Gu and create the immortal killer move reverse flow protection seal, he would have likely lost in the battle of Reverse Flow River, he would have fallen into Ying Wu Xie's trap.

All along, Shadow Sect's remnant forces were Fang Yuan's biggest threat. Heaven's will set an arrangement using Fang Yuan to steal sovereign immortal fetus Gu, causing Fang Yuan and Shadow Sect to have unresolvable enmity.

If Shadow Sect wanted to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu again, they would follow a method similar to what Old Ancestor Xue Hu was using to refine Fortune Rivalling Heaven, he used Ma Hong Yun as the main material for the Gu refinement.

If Fang Yuan ended up in Shadow Sect's hands, he would not escape that fate, he would be used as the immortal material for that Gu refinement, he would be better off dead.

But now, Fang Yuan's strength grew to a point where he could stand up to rank eight Gu Immortals, thus, Shadow Sect sought cooperation with him.

This difference in attitude made Fang Yuan sigh deeply.

Reverse flow protection seal was like a weaker Immortal Gu House, he could be unscathed against rank eights, this gave Fang Yuan a lot of confidence.

"But cooperating with Shadow Sect is like walking on a tightrope!"

Even though Sixth Hair was saying the truth, and the reasons he gave were legitimate, there were indeed benefits to all of them if they cooperated. Disregarding anything else, just the soul path trap in Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body, and the secret of the sovereign immortal body, could be settled if they cooperated.

However, Fang Yuan could not trust Shadow Sect!

It was still the same problem.

Fang Yuan and Shadow Sect could not trust each other.

They were mortal enemies, how could they easily turn into allies?

Even if they were rational people who prioritized benefits, the basis of cooperation between Gu Immortals was not a person's reputation, but their information path methods instead.

However, Fang Yuan was lacking in information path, this was his weakness. And Shadow Sect possessed powerful information path methods.

Spectral Soul was a great grandmaster in all paths, ignoring everything else, just looking at Zombie Alliance and the organization 'Defy' in Central Continent, they had used very powerful information path methods. Any organization was built upon the basis of alliance agreements.

Fang Yuan could not trust Shadow Sect and did not dare to. If by cooperating, he was plotted against by them using information path methods, he would be an idiot.

However, Fang Yuan did not reject them.

He sent back a letter to probe Shadow Sect's sincerity. In the letter, he listed a request — Give me attitude Gu directly if you want to cooperate.

Speaking of which, even though Fang Yuan had been using attitude Gu all along, it was not his, it was borrowed from Hei Lou Lan.

Back then, when lending the Immortal Gu, both sides had an agreement, there was a time when he needed to return it.

If he went past the time limit, Fang Yuan would not be able to use attitude Gu. That was because Hei Lou Lan's will was inside attitude Gu, not Fang Yuan's.

And now, there was little time until the deadline.

Attitude Gu was a legendary Gu worm that could be used with mental energy alone, it had outstanding effects with relatively low costs. Ever since Fang Yuan obtained it, he had passed many difficulties with its huge help. Even though attitude Gu had no offensive methods, it was legendary in the support aspect, it had unlimited uses.

Without attitude Gu, the influence on Fang Yuan would be huge.

Firstly, familiar face would be unusable. Even though Fang Yuan could use his transformation path grandmaster attainment level to redesign this immortal killer move, without that rank eight core, the entire immortal killer move would weaken severely. The chance of getting exposed when he pretended to be Wu Yi Hai would be huge, it was very dangerous.

"If I can use this opportunity to resolve attitude Gu's problem, that would be best." Fang Yuan was feeling somewhat hopeful.

It was about time, Fang Yuan used dark limit Immortal Gu to increase its effect on him.

Next, he stored his immortal aperture and set off.

Towards the southwest direction.

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

Inside the hall, Fairy Zi Wei sat as she used her immortal killer move.

Her entire body was emitting faint purple smoke from all of her pores.

She was using wisdom path methods to deduce.

Soon after, Fairy Zi Wei's forehead was full of sweat as she opened her eyes.

"I have already used seven killer moves, but I could not deduce the location of our Gu Immortals." Fairy Zi Wei sighed.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals attacked Northern Plains, after the battle of Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan fled the scene as Central Continent fought against Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Longevity Heaven in an intense battle.

Central Continent wanted to reinforce them and send help.

But this first batch of Central Continent Gu Immortals had gone missing in black heaven. Fairy Zi Wei could not deduce their locations, how could she save them? There was nowhere to send these reinforcements to!

Duke Long beside her opened his eyes.

He was still very weak, he was thin and frail like an old man.

"It seems that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made many arrangements in Northern Plains, have you deduced Liu Guan Yi's location?" Duke Long asked.

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head: "He seems to have defensive methods to resist wisdom path deductions, but they are not strong. However, we know too little about him. If we had some crucial information, he would be exposed to us."

Duke Long heard this and nodded, after a while, he spoke: "So be it, continue deducing the location of our Gu Immortals, as well as Liu Guan Yi. Also, send me to Hidden Dragon Cave."

Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan sighed helplessly, he had to place his immortal aperture down again.

Liu Guan Yi was famous in all five regions, Dark Limit's power was constantly being consumed on Fang Yuan's body, at a rapid rate.

To maintain his secret, Fang Yuan had to stop many times.

His immortal aperture's entrance opened, he drew in large amounts of heaven and earth qi.

The sovereign immortal body could absorb heaven and earth qi from all five regions.

Ordinary Gu Immortals could only absorb the heaven and earth qi of their region, if they placed their aperture in other regions, even though they could absorb it forcefully, because of the differing heaven and earth qi, their immortal apertures would shake and many resources would be destroyed.

Right now, the sovereign immortal aperture had too many resources, along with desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts. Each time he absorbed heaven and earth qi, the commotion was huge, it was like a typhoon occurring.

Especially after he obtained Reverse Flow River, this secluded domain of heaven and earth had a heavy burden on the immortal aperture.

Chapter 1293: Thoughts of Trading Gu

It was fine if Reverse Flow River was outside, but if it stayed in the immortal aperture for long, it would consume a lot of heaven and earth qi. Once he lacked heaven and earth qi, his immortal aperture would be unstable.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to constantly place his immortal aperture outside to absorb heaven and earth qi and replenish it.

After he finished his absorption, Fang Yuan closed his immortal aperture's entrance.

Arriving at Reverse Flow River, he held an immortal zombie body.

It was his original body.

He tossed the immortal zombie into Reverse Flow River.

The immortal zombie body flowed along it.

Using perseverance Immortal Gu and Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan made his experiments, he used all of the methods he could think of.

However, it was pointless.

"As expected."

"The immortal zombie body's soul path dao marks cannot be destroyed or suppressed by Reverse Flow River. After all, these are soul path dao marks, not Immortal Gu."

"Rank one to eight Immortal Gu cannot be used in Reverse Flow River. But dao marks still work. It is like before, before I conquered Reverse Flow River, my dao marks still defended me. Thus, rank eight Gu Immortals were the strongest in that river."

Fang Yuan continued to analyze and think about his failed experiment.

He wanted to use Reverse Flow River to resolve his soul path trap, it was impossible.

Fang Yuan was not disheartened, in fact, he had expected this before trying it.

He placed the immortal zombie body back inside Heaven Sealing Mountain, using the Gu formation to seal it again.

Next, he refined Gu.

A nightmare demonic colt corpse was in front of him.

Fang Yuan's fingers moved like blades, golden light shone as he move them.

The golden light entered the nightmare demonic colt's body and vanished. The nightmare demonic colt's front leg was cut off.

There was no blood.

These nightmare demonic colts died in battle, Fang Yuan asked his immortal aperture's land spirits to process these materials first. The blood had been drained and kept elsewhere.

Fang Yuan lifted the leg and immediately tore it away.

Next, he breathed out fire and started to process this leg.

Three days later, the leg was finally melted into a dark purple liquid.

Fang Yuan continued to throw in Gu worms to refine Gu.

Over a dozen steps took up only fifteen minutes.

The dark purple liquid exploded, as a hundred dream path mortal Gu flew around chaotically in the sky.

But Fang Yuan willed and they quickly went back to Fang Yuan's side.

A hundred dream path mortal Gu!

This was only a leg of this nightmare demonic colt.

Processing this immortal material took the most time. This step took three days. The rest of the steps only took less than an hour.

Such efficiency was very high, it was a clear contrast to Fang Yuan refining Gu in his dream realm previously.

In the dream realm, Fang Yuan had to collect dream path Gu materials before refining Gu. There was a risk in entering the dream, he even sometimes had to use the immortal killer move, unravel dream, to pass the dream realm. Refining dream path mortal Gu but using immortal killer moves, the cost was very high.

But now, Fang Yuan had these nightmare demonic colts, refining these dream path mortal Gu was no longer like before.

"It is like earlier, when I used the spring dream fruit to refine mortal Gu, the efficiency was great."

"Actually, my Gu refinement method can be improved. Like the cutting method earlier, I used metal path methods, it was not the best, some of the dream path dao marks were consumed. When processing immortal materials, I can try other methods to see if there is a better way."

While he was refining Gu, Sixth Hair sent another letter.

Using Lang Ya blessed land, Sixth Hair was already the middleman between Fang Yuan and Purple Mountain True Monarch.

In the letter, Purple Mountain True Monarch did not give in, he said bluntly: If Fang Yuan wanted to control attitude Gu, he would need to cooperate first. As long as they worked together, attitude Gu would be his. This time, Shadow Sect even mentioned the sovereign immortal aperture's drawback, as for what it was, they did not say it.

"Rank eight Gu Immortals are truly hard to deal with."

"Drawback? Is Shadow Sect lying, or is it true?"

This information had a huge impact on Fang Yuan.

But soon, he calmed down.

He had gone through many difficulties, this scheme or threat was nothing to him.

"It seems I can only work hard myself."

Fang Yuan sent a letter, he bargained and continued negotiating with Shadow Sect.

But he had already realized that Shadow Sect would not give attitude Gu to him before cooperating.

Fang Yuan started to design a new immortal killer move.

He wanted to use this immortal killer move to refine attitude Gu.

He was soon met with a problem, the reason was that even though he had many Immortal Gu, they were not suitable for this purpose.

It was not like the creation of reverse flow protection seal.

Fang Yuan had pulling water Immortal Gu and perseverance Immortal Gu, they were suitable as the two cores of this immortal killer move.

But now, Fang Yuan's other Immortal Gu were not especially useful for refining attitude Gu, they had limited connection to it and a lot of mortal Gu were needed.

"If only there is a chance to trade Gu."

This thought appeared in Fang Yuan's mind and rooted itself deeply.

Trading Immortal Gu!

Fang Yuan had too many Immortal Gu now, it was shocking.

But in fact, a portion of the Immortal Gu were not suitable for him, or rather, they did not have much use for the time being.

Wisdom Sword, Years Flow Like Water, even though they were not usable now, they were rank eight, Fang Yuan would not exchange them.

Fang Yuan did not have many sword path dao marks, his sword path attainment level was ordinary as well, but Sword Eyebrows, Wave Sword, and Sword Escape, these sword path Immortal Gu sustained a portion of his battle strength, he could not lose them.

Looking over the situation, change soul Immortal Gu could be traded.

Woman's Heart was poison path, it had little use as well.

Flying bear strength Immortal Gu was strength path, but Fang Yuan used ancient sword dragon transformation, this Immortal Gu was not useful.

There was also bone spike Immortal Gu, it was completely irrelevant to Fang Yuan's current circumstances.

Perceivable dao Immortal Gu could inspect dao marks, it had a mystical use, but to Fang Yuan, it was not very useful, he had to weigh up its value later.

All in all, Woman's Heart, Flying Bear Strength, and Bone Spike, these three Immortal Gu had little use to Fang Yuan, if they could be traded for other Immortal Gu, that would be best.

But trading Gu, how difficult was that?

During the five regions chaotic war, it was very common. But now, there were few opportunities for Gu Immortals to undergo high end trading sessions.

This way, Fang Yuan continued to travel and stop.

He wanted to go faster, but it was too difficult.

Along the way, when placing his immortal aperture, he refined dream path mortal Gu and deduced immortal killer moves, attempting to refine attitude Gu to make it his own.

This time, as Fang Yuan stored his immortal aperture and prepared to set off, his expression suddenly changed, he noticed traces of Gu Immortals fighting.

Chapter 1294: Reappearance of Chu Ying

"We're finally past the regional wall." Ying Wu Xie let out a breath of air, looking at the sea, he felt mentally fatigued.

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing, who were beside him, were in no better condition.

After leaving Northern Plains, Shadow Sect's group left for Eastern Sea. They did not have the sovereign immortal body, each time they passed the regional wall, it was a huge test.

Thankfully, they were all powerful and were elites among Gu Immortals. Even though their immortal apertures were damaged, they did not die.

They were not leaving urgently.

After entering Eastern Sea, they chose a random island.

On this nameless island, Ying Wu Xie directed Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan to start arranging a refinement path Gu formation.

The Gu formation succeeded in activation, Ying Wu Xie came to the center and took out the purple gold rock, processing this immortal material.

As for Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan, they were outside the Gu formation, standing to defend against any intruders.

Not long after, the purple gold rock melted as the miniman Gu Immortal, Purple Mountain, True Monarch woke up again.

He was a rank eight Gu Immortal, if he wanted to cross the five regions, he would normally have to use black heaven or white heaven. But now, the parts of black heaven and white heaven above Northern Plains were influenced by Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace, it was controlled by Longevity Heaven.

Shadow Sect's group were not going to enter a trap. The outcome of Central Continent's Gu Immortals were displayed to them.

Shadow Sect had deep foundation, Purple Mountain True Monarch went into hibernation again as a purple gold rock formed around his body.

His aura was completely concealed, his vitality was indiscernible, he was just like a dead object.

Using such incredible methods, Ying Wu Xie brought Purple Mountain True Monarch through the regional walls and arrived in Eastern Sea.

The thin layer of purple gold rock was easily refined by Ying Wu Xie, who had the right method, it was way easier than the time when Lady Wan Shou had to process it.

"Eastern Sea..." Purple Mountain True Monarch woke up and sighed as he looked at the vast sea area.

Under his lead, Shadow Sect's group first dismantled the Gu formation and stored its components, wiping all traces of it.

Then, the four Gu Immortals started to use the ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel.

A moment later, they arrived in the turbulent flow sea area.

Purple Mountain True Monarch led the way, none of the sea currents could pose as obstacles.

Soon, Shadow Sect's group arrived at the center of the turbulent flow sea area.

"Hmm? Where is the tributary of the River of Time?" Unable to find the thing they needed, Ying Wu Xie asked this in confusion.

"Don't tell me this tributary of the River of Time is already gone, it is at the fringe of the turbulent flows?" Hei Lou Lan guessed.

After some investigation, Purple Mountain True Monarch found some clues.

"That tributary of the River of Time has been taken away by someone." He said grimly.

"How can that be? Who did it? Is it Fang Yuan?" Ying Wu Xie first thought of Fang Yuan.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch shook his head: "This method should not be his. It is someone else, forget about it. Since we cannot use this tributary of the River of Time, we will go to the next location, there is a tributary of the River of Time there too."

Shadow Sect's group left the turbulent flow sea area again.

Elsewhere in Eastern Sea.

There was a vast sea and sky.

Above the sea, a life and death battle was unfolding.

"Quickly leave, I was hit by his lightning soul needle, he can sense my location, I cannot escape, I cannot implicate you." Immortal Hua Die lay in a man's arms, speaking weakly.

This woman was dressed in a raiment, her sleeves were fluttering, she wore light pink. Her eyes were showing signs of weakness, blood was flowing out of the corner of her mouth, her injuries were severe.

Especially on her skin, there were tiny sparks shining at times, it was the sign of the immortal killer move lightning soul needle's effect.

"No." The male Gu Immortal rejected unhesitantly.

He had broad shoulders and a thin waist, he wore a suit of battle armor, and even though he was covered in injuries, his valiance could not be concealed.

"How can I abandon you? If I escape now, how can I face Lord Miao Ming Shen?" Even though he said that, when he looked towards Immortal Hua Die, there was love in his eyes.

He was Feng Jiang.

Feng Jiang, Immortal Hua Die, Gui Qi Ye, these three were subordinates of the Eastern Sea space path expert Miao Ming Shen.

Miao Ming Shen wanted to find a tributary of the River of Time in the turbulent flow sea area, thus these three Gu Immortals would take turns to guard the turbulent flow sea area. When they saw any Gu Immortals approaching the turbulent flow sea area, they would talk to them and ask for their help.

"Then you lovebirds can die together!" There was only one person in pursuit, he had rank seven cultivation level.

He was named Ge Wen, he wore a blue robe and had tough, dry skin, like tree bark. His eyes were shining with red light, his teeth were sharp, he had a sinister expression.

This person was quite a senior and had some reputation in Eastern Sea.

He was a lightning path grandmaster, but once when he was using an immortal killer move, he failed and suffered a backlash, leading to him having no choice but to become an immortal zombie.

Even so, he had outstanding battle strength, he possessed two Immortal Gu, the rank six Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang were forced to flee.

"Hand over the year cycle powder, you two are quite daring to snatch my immortal material. If you hand it over, I might leave you a proper corpse!" Ge Wen chuckled as he approached with overwhelming demonic aura.

Immortal Hua Die was anxious: "We found this year cycle powder first, how can it be yours?"

"I have been here for half a month already, but the moment I looked away, you two took it!" Ge Wen growled.

Immortal Hua Die was incensed: "Lord Miao Ming Shen found this year cycle powder three years ago and set a Gu formation here. Once every few months, I would come there and take care of it. No matter how you distort the facts, you cannot change them."

Immortal Hua Die said the truth, Ge Wen stopped denying it, his expression turned grim: "Hmph, you have a sharp tongue, you will be the first one I kill."

"Demonic scoundrel, don't be cocky!"

At this moment, there was a clear voice that resounded in their ears.

"Who?" Ge Wen's expression changed, he shouted.

The moment he said that, the sea level rose up like a small mound.

Next, from within the 'mound', a fierce beast charged out, causing winds to blow and water the splatter.

A blue scaled sea dragon appeared before the three immortals, speaking: "Demon, hand over your life!"

The three immortals saw this and understood that this blue scaled sea dragon was a Gu Immortal's transformation.

Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang were happy and shocked.

Ge Wen was furious: "Why are you a busybody! Take my killer move."

Saying this, he breathed in deeply, spitting at his right palm.

He did not spit out saliva, of course, it was an egg-sized flash of lightning.

The lightning entered Ge Wen's right palm and exploded into a beam of lightning that shot out from his palm.

The blue scaled sea dragon did not dodge, it opened its mouth towards the approaching beam of lightning.

Dragon's breath!

Ge Wen saw this and laughed in his mind: "My move can last for several minutes, while dragon breath needs to be used breath by breath, how can he last?"

But the blue scaled sea dragon's breath did not end!

The dragon's breath was like a beam of water colliding with the beam of lightning, next, the powerful dragon breath smashed through the lightning pillar.

In a few breath's time, it got to Ge Wen.

"How can this be? What dragon breath is this?!" Ge Wen showed disbelief and shock on his face.

He quickly dodged.

But the blue scaled sea dragon turned around and its dragon breath continued to sweep the battlefield.

Ge Wen frowned deeply, grunting: "You guys are lucky, I will spare you this time!"

Saying this, he retreated, turning into a flash of lightning with incredible speed.

The blue scaled sea dragon did not give chase, it watched as Ge Wen left.

"He wants to return to the Gu formation, a lot of the year cycle powder is left." Immortal Hua Die pointed out Ge Wen's plan.

Feng Jiang placed Immortal Hua Die down and cupped his fists at the blue scaled sea dragon: "Virtuous friend, you defeated the powerful foe, we will not forget the gratitude of saving our lives. I would like to know your esteemed name!"

The blue scaled sea dragon suddenly transformed into an ordinary looking Gu Immortal, he smiled: "I am Chu Ying, Fairy Hua Die, have you been well?"

Immortal Hua Die was surprised and joyful: "To think that you are Chu Ying!"

Seeing Feng Jiang's gaze, Immortal Hua Die explained: "It was thanks to Chu Ying that we found that tributary of the River of Time in the turbulent flow sea area. He was the reason Lord Miao Ming Shen could take away that tributary of the River of Time."

Chapter 1295: Eastern Sea Trading Convention

"So there was such a connection!" Hearing Immortal Hua Die's words, Feng Jiang's expression turned to joy, his suspicions were dispelled.

This Chu Ying was naturally Fang Yuan in disguise.

After he stored his immortal aperture, he found that there were traces of Gu Immortals fighting in the sea areas around him.

Out of curiosity, he followed the traces and wanted to see if there were some gains for him. In the end, he found that Immortal Hua Die and another person (Feng Jiang) were being pursued by an enemy.

And the pursuer was a rank seven immortal zombie. At this point, such a person was a weakling to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had helped Immortal Hua Die some time ago, he wanted to get in contact with the space path Gu Immortal expert, Miao Ming Shen, who was behind Immortal Hua Die.

This person knew of a method to enter and explore the blue dragon whale.

And this blue dragon whale was not ordinary either, it was nurtured by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable and awakened its immortal aperture, it possessed a huge treasury.

It was like the dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu of Northern Plains.

But the blue dragon whale's wisdom was not enhanced, it could only swim freely in the ocean according to its instincts.

Not only did Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable awaken its immortal aperture, he also used an immortal killer move on its body. Thus, this blue dragon whale had almost no predators or dangers.

The blue dragon whale was mild in temperament and posed no danger, but its defensive power rendered all of those who wanted to harm it helpless.

This was the style of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

According to a secret rumor in the five hundred years of his previous life, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had left a true inheritance in the blue dragon whale's body.

Fang Yuan remembered that Miao Ming Shen had explored the world inside the blue dragon whale many times. However, even though he had gains each time, he did not obtain the true inheritance from start to finish.

Fang Yuan naturally cared about this. Thus, when he saw Immortal Hua Die being pursued, he realized that this was a rare chance, he could express goodwill to Miao Ming Shen again.

Thus, he intervened and chased the lightning path immortal zombie Ge Wen away.

He did not transform into an ancient sword dragon.

The ancient sword dragon form could not be used openly now.

Because Liu Guan Yi had used it to kill Ye Lui Qun Xing in Northern Plains.

Right now, Liu Guan Yi was the Reverse Flow River Lord that was able to go unscathed against rank eights. His reputation was renowned all over the world, almost everyone knew of him.

Countless people were interested in Liu Guan Yi, they tried to deduce his origins.

The fact that Liu Guan Yi possessed an ancient sword dragon transformation was known to all.

Thus, once Fang Yuan used the ancient sword dragon transformation, other Gu Immortals would immediately think of Liu Guan Yi.

This was the burden of reputation.

Even though Fang Yuan could not use ancient sword dragon transformation, he had change form Immortal Gu, he could turn into countless things in this world at will.

Thus, he transformed into the blue scaled sea dragon that was exclusive to Eastern Sea.

This was also an ancient desolate beast.

But its might could not rival the ancient sword dragon.

However, Fang Yuan's dragon breath Immortal Gu could still be used.

Worth mentioning was that the dragon breath of the blue scaled sea dragon was also used breath by breath. Earlier, he could defeat the lightning path immortal zombie Ge Wen because Fang Yuan had used perseverance Immortal Gu at the same time.

Rank seven perseverance Immortal Gu, after obtaining it, Fang Yuan had tried to learn more about its ability.

Gu Immortals nurture, use, and refine, these three aspects needed a lot of time and investment.

After being in Eastern Sea for several days, Fang Yuan had already understood some of the uses of perseverance Immortal Gu.

Other than conquering Reverse Flow River, perseverance Immortal Gu could allow other Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves to last for a longer time.

For example, the blue scaled sea dragon's breath.

If Fang Yuan used dragon breath Immortal Gu solely, it could not break away from the normal limits of dragon breath, it would be used breath by breath, it could only be increased in strength.

But if he used perseverance Immortal Gu along with the dragon breath, then the dragon breath would be used for a long time without stopping!

Of course, he could not sustain it for too long. Dragon breath had a huge burden on the throat, even real blue scaled sea dragons breathed it out breath by breath. This was the self-defense mechanism of lifeforms after a long process of evolution.

Thankfully, although that Ge Wen had some fame, he retreated wisely after a short battle with Fang Yuan, realizing that he was a strong opponent.

After all, demonic path Gu Immortals focused on profits.

"This friend is?" Fang Yuan looked at Immortal Hua Die.

"I am one of Lord Miao Ming Shen's subordinates, Feng Jiang. Lord Chu, you are my savior, I wonder how I can thank you." Feng Jiang immediately introduced himself, it was very passionate and filled with gratitude towards Fang Yuan.

"No need to thank me, it was just a helping hand. I met you two coincidentally, thus I stepped in. Even though I am a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea, I have been moving around recently, I cannot stand these demonic acts. I have this personality, and because Fairy Hua Die is an acquaintance, I had no reason not to help." Fang Yuan was very humble.

Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang heard these words and felt closer to Fang Yuan.

The three immortals talked for a while as Immortal Hua Die sighed: "It is a pity. There was so much year cycle powder, they are mostly in Ge Wen's hands now. Our efforts have been in vain. We should have made that Gu formation even more hidden."

Feng Jiang consoled: "Alright, Little Die, don't blame yourself. Eastern Sea is so big, but Ge Wen found this Gu formation so coincidentally. We are not skilled in formation path, this Gu formation is already the best that can be done. If we hide it even more deeply, we will need Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan smiled: "I have something to say, even though the year cycle powder is lost, your lives are preserved, this is hope. Don't be disheartened, there are losses and gains in life, aren't our lives just a cycle of losing and winning anyway."

Feng Jiang laughed: "Lord Chu speaks deeply, this is truly insightful."

Immortal Hua Die's brows were locked, she was sorrowful: "I understand this too, and at a different time, so be it if this year cycle powder was lost. But right now, Lord Miao Ming Shen is attending a trading convention, one of his Gu Immortal friends need this. Lord Miao Ming Shen has already agreed to his request, there are only a few days left until the convention, but the year cycle powder was taken away, what should we do?"

Hearing this, Feng Jiang's expression sank: "That's right, we are going to return empty handed. Even if Lord Miao Ming Shen does not blame us, we will be at fault, we failed in our task. And most importantly, we will cause Lord Miao Ming Shen's reputation to suffer, this is our fault!"

"Trading convention?" Fang Yuan was moved.

Earlier, he was thinking about trading away some of the unsuitable Immortal Gu that he had.

To think that this would come in such a timely manner, he actually encountered one of Eastern Sea's trading conventions.

Eastern Sea was the most abundant in resources out of the five regions, even Central Continent could not match it.

Eastern Sea Gu Immortals were usually more affluent.

This resulted in Eastern Sea's trading conventions to be very famous in the five regions, they involved high-end items and often, Gu Immortals would exchange Immortal Gu with each other.

Of course, this was not to say that the other four regions had no trading conventions. But they were too few of them, Fang Yuan could not join them either.

Only Eastern Sea's trading conventions served as his opportunity.

"I have Immortal Gu that I want to trade away, is it possible for me to join this trading convention?" Fang Yuan did not hide his intention, he asked directly.

Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang looked at each other, the former said: "This trading convention is very high class, we are not qualified to join it, nor do we have the rights to recommend others. But Lord Chu Ying is different, you are our benefactor. How about this, can you follow us to meet with our lord, and see what he says?"

"Alright." Fang Yuan nodded: "Shall we set off now?"

He was very rushed.

Because time was limited.

Dark Limit's power was dwindling as other Gu Immortals deduced matters about him.

Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang were a little hesitant, their mission to collect the year cycle powder had failed, they actually wanted Fang Yuan to help them take back the year cycle powder, but they could not ask it outright.

Actually, Fang Yuan was aware about their intentions, but during their conversation, he held the initiative of the topic and did not give them any chance to ask.

Right now, even though Fang Yuan could go unscathed against rank eight Gu Immortals.

There was a flaw, it could not be used openly.

Be it ancient sword dragon transformation or reverse flow protection seal, they could not be easily used. Once he did, he would have to consider how to keep them a secret.

If too many traces were leaked out, Fang Yuan's identities and secrets might get deduced.

By then, Wu Yi Hai's identity would be exposed too.

Fang Yuan had gone through so much to enter the super Gu formation and interact with the giant dream realm. If he lost this opportunity, it would be a terrible setback to his future cultivation.

Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang had no choice, they could only bring Fang Yuan away from here.

They really had no courage to ask him.

He had saved their lives, but they still wanted their benefactor to fight against a strong foe. They really had no face to ask him to do that.

The three immortals moved quickly without stopping.

But along the way, they talked and conversed a lot.

As a matter of fact, Immortal Hua Die had seen Fang Yuan twice and had a deep impression of him, but she was unclear about the background of this Chu Ying.

Fang Yuan knew about her intention to probe him, thus he gave her half-truths about his origin.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, he had stayed in Eastern Sea for some time. Thus, his words were not lies. Especially some small details and experiences that he had, they were realistic, these experiences resonated deeply with Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang.

How could Fang Yuan show a flaw here?

By the time they met Miao Ming Shen, Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang already had very good feelings towards this 'easygoing' rank seven secluded cultivator, Chu Ying.

But they did not know that Fang Yuan was the true demon. Compared to him, what was immortal zombie Ge Wen's act of snatching some year cycle powder?

Not long ago, Fang Yuan had taken Reverse Flow River directly from Old Ancestor Xue Hu!

Chapter 1296: Light Shine Fungi

Eastern Sea.

In an ordinary sea area, there was a nameless mountain, it was desolate and barren, there were only rocks and caves in it.

Several Gu Immortals descended from the sky.

Among them were Fang Yuan, Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang.

"To think that this trading convention would be held on such an empty island." Fang Yuan stepped on the island as he sighed to himself.

"Brother Chu, you might be unaware that large trading conventions like this usually have their locations decided several days before the meeting, to prevent others from having ill intentions." A Gu Immortal beside Fang Yuan said.

This male Gu Immortal was neither tall nor short, neither fat nor thin. In terms of appearance, he looked ordinary, only his flat and wide nose left a heavy impression on others.

This person was a famous rank seven space path Gu Immortal expert in Eastern Sea — Miao Ming Shen.

In terms of appearance, he was not outstanding, but after Fang Yuan interacted with him, even though it was a short time, he could feel that this person was impressive, his appearance was deceiving.

Fang Yuan had saved Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang under the identity of Chu Ying, learning about the trading convention.

Next, he followed Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang to meet Miao Ming Shen.

Miao Ming Shen had no hesitation as he agreed to Fang Yuan's request of joining the trading convention: "Friend, you have helped me twice, you are also the benefactor of Little Die and Little Feng. This is just a trading convention, how can I reject you? Please do grace us with your presence!"

He was a rank seven Gu Immortal expert, but Chu Ying was a secluded cultivator with no reputation. Yet Miao Ming Shen did not put on airs, he was very amiable. He spoke politely and warmly to others.

Thus, Fang Yuan and Miao Ming Shen came to attend the trading convention.

The four of them had just stepped onto the island when a Gu Immortal came out of a rock.

"Miao Ming Shen, you are here." A midget Gu Immortal with a big head and small body welcomed them.

"Haha, Tu Tou Tuo, long time no see!" Miao Ming Shen said warmly, he laughed as he quickly went up to the person.

"Come, let me introduce the two of you. This is a secluded cultivator of Eastern Sea, Chu Ying, this is a rare earth path grandmaster in Eastern Sea, Tu Tou Tuo." Miao Ming Shen said.

"Greetings to you." Fang Yuan was polite but his expression was stiff, he pretended to be a secluded cultivator who was not good at interacting with people, it was flawless.

Tu Tou Tuo looked at Fang Yuan with several glances, he smiled with his yellow teeth: "You received Miao Ming Shen's recommendation and are here for the first time? Haha, in the past, I also joined in after Miao Ming Shen's recommendation."

Tu Tou Tuo was also quite polite.

He thought: "Miao Ming Shen has good foresight, the people he invites are all talented experts. This Chu Ying looks unassuming and has no reputation, but since he has Miao Ming Shen's recommendation, he is not simple."

While thinking of that, Tu Tou Tuo said: "Follow me, I was the first to arrive, there is nothing much to do but wait now, we can create a space underground first."

"I will trouble Brother Tu. After all, this time, I am the host of the trading convention..." Miao Ming Shen said courteously.

"Haha, it is just an underground cave, it is nothing much. Come!" Tu Tou Tuo looked at Miao Ming Shen like an old friend, he grabbed his arm and led him underground.

Everywhere he went, the tough ground melted like flowing water, opening a wide path that extended underground.

Tu Tou Tuo and Miao Ming Shen walked ahead while Fang Yuan, Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die walked behind them.

Tu Tou Tuo and Miao Ming Shen talked along the way.

Miao Ming Shen had incredible interpersonal skills, Tu Tou Tuo was laughing as he talked, his laughter was reverberating in the cave.

Furthermore, Miao Ming Shen did not give the cold shoulder to Fang Yuan, he turned around to talk to Fang Yuan.

His words seemed ordinary, but they felt natural and did not make Fang Yuan feel like he was alone, or that he was neglected.

The underground cave was very ordinary, but it was wide enough.

There was a platform, and several chairs in front of it, they were huge. There were carvings on the chairs, they were fluid patterns. This showed Tu Tou Tuo's incredible skills, and the meticulous aspect that he had.

Fang Yuan counted, there were six chairs.

"It seems that this trading convention only had six people originally. Immortal Hua Die and Feng Jiang are not part of this, they will leave when the trading convention starts and guard the area." Fang Yuan guessed.

"There is a new member, I will add a chair." Tu Tou Tuo stomped lightly as a mound appeared on the ground, it started to rotate like a ball.

In the blink of an eye, a chair was carved out like it was made by an artisan.

Fang Yuan and the rest sat down while waiting for the other immortals.

Not long later, two Gu Immortals appeared.

The former was a girl, she looked like a child with two ponytail braids, her eyes were round and watery, but there was deep maturity in them.

She was Tong Hua.

A rank seven light path Gu Immortal famous in the north of Eastern Sea.

The latter was a male immortal. He had an aquiline nose, his gaze was dark and he wore a black robe, having messy hair.

He was Wu Ma Yang, a dark path Gu Immortal, having exemplary battle strength among rank seven Gu Immortals. His immortal killer move, dark arrow veil, had once defeated three rank seven Gu Immortals working together, this battle caused his reputation to surge in Eastern Sea for some time.

Tong Hua talked a lot, while Wu Ma Yang was uncommunicative.

The two sides continued to mingle, and under Miao Ming Shen's intentional guidance, the atmosphere became congenial.

Fifteen minutes later, a third Gu Immortal entered this space.

He was Gong Liang Bai, a wisdom path Gu Immortal who also cultivated wood path. Wisdom path was his main focus, but wisdom path Gu Immortals were few in numbers, especially those like Fang Yuan who possessed a complete wisdom path Gu Immortal true inheritance.

However, not only did Gong Liang Bai have a complete wisdom path true inheritance, he even had some achievements in his cultivation, even though he could not match the top three wisdom path experts, among lone immortals, he had a huge network and was willing to deduce for people in exchange for payment.

The saying goes: Jia Dan sits in twin polar, Hua An hides in Nan Gong, there is also Dragon Head Tortoise, living inside adversity sea.

This saying refers to the publicly recognized three most powerful wisdom path Gu Immortals in Eastern Sea currently.

Song Jia Dan, Hua An, they were righteous path members, they rarely deduced for lone immortals. And Dragon Head Tortoise was always inside adversity sea, his traces were hard to find, it was hard for people to seek help from him.

"Gong Liang Bai, after these trades, let's have a good talk. I have some things for you to deduce." While talking, Miao Ming Shen said.

"Is it that Liu Guan Yi? I have received many requests from others, they are all after this person." Gong Liang Bai said.

"Of course not." Miao Ming Shen denied.

Gong Liang Bai nodded: "Then that is fine. Speaking of which, I have already made five deductions, I failed each time. There are simply too few clues, and that Liu Guan Yi has methods to defend against deductions."

Fang Yuan listened by the side, his expression did not change, though he felt a little awkward.

This topic attracted everyone's attention.

Tu Tou Tuo shouted: "This Liu Guan Yi is so popular now, he is completely famous!"

"Anyone who can render rank eight Gu Immortals unable to deal with them as a rank seven will go down in history." Tong Hua sighed.

"Resisting rank eight with rank seven cultivation level, this is truly a goal to set." Miao Ming Shen smiled bitterly: "It is a pity that I've had no opportunity to befriend such a person."

Fang Yuan was sitting right beside him, hearing this, he said expressionlessly: "I heard that Liu Guan Yi could resist rank eights as a rank seven because he became the Reverse Flow River Lord. This Reverse Flow River is a secluded domain of heaven and earth, but how can it be so powerful as to leave rank eight existences without options?"

Thus, the immortals' topic of discussion turned from Liu Guan Yi to Reverse Flow River.

Fang Yuan had subtly changed the conversation's direction.

The Gu Immortals talked until night time.

When night appeared and the moon rose, the trading convention began.

The other two Gu Immortals also had arrived.

The trading convention officially began.

According to the rules set earlier, Tong Hua stood on the platform.

"This is a desolate plant, I found it when exploring a deep sea. That place was dark as an abyss, but I saw some light far away. When I found the source, I took several minutes to reach it. The place was like a paradise of light path. It was so dazzling with rays of light extending immeasurably far."

"Initially, I thought that it was light from the corals. But soon, I found some green fungus on the surface of the corals. This green fungus is a desolate plant seen all over that place, I named it light shine fungus, it contains light path dao marks and can emit strong light."

Tong Hua talked about her findings, and the process of her naming.

Fang Yuan was surprised, to think that he found something he wanted when the trading convention had just started.

Light shine fungi!

Chapter 1297: Divination Tortoise Shell Immortal Gu

Fang Yuan needed light.

He had first used aurora light, he had bought large numbers of dazzling light Gu to increase the aurora light in his immortal aperture. The more intense the aurora light, the more flowing light fruits could be formed. And rank eight attitude Gu fed on these fruits.

Light shine fungus was a type of desolate plant that provided light which was not like the multicolored aurora light.

But this was not absolute.

Humans had the highest intelligence, they were most skilled in adapting flexibly. There were methods to modify and graft plants in this world.

Wood path Gu Immortals excelled at this.

Each path has its own specialties, and wood path Gu Immortals were often skilled at managing immortal apertures.

Thus, if Fang Yuan brought in light shine fungi, he might be able to modify them in the future using wood path methods into aurora light shine fungi, it was possible.

Other than attitude Gu, there was wisdom sword Immortal Gu.

Wisdom sword Immortal Gu fed on multicolored overlord flowers.

If Fang Yuan wanted to plant multicolored overlord flowers on a large scale, he needed to fulfill three conditions. Illumination, sweet scents and pearl soil.

The latter two were easy to achieve, but illumination was hard.

Fang Yuan's immortal aperture had light path dao marks, and he had also annexed a light path blessed land, but it was far from Fang Yuan's goal.

If he used light shine fungi, he would be able to solve the problem of mass production of multicolored overlord flowers.

But there was an uncertainty in this.

Light shine fungi grew in the deep sea, could they still survive in other environments?

"This should not be a problem, after all, light shine fungus is a desolate plant."

"Even ignoring aurora lights, earlier, I plundered Liu tribe's jade light pit, I gained a lot of replenishment. Even though I am still not at the required standard, I am close."

"But multicolored overlord flowers are different, their scale is far from optimal. I have too few light path dao marks currently, and not all of my light path dao marks can gather at the multicolored overlord flowers. My other lifeforms need light too."

"Oh, that's right, I have transformation path dao marks, in crucial moments, I can convert them to light path dao marks temporarily."

While Fang Yuan was thinking, Tong Hua spoke: "I am willing to trade these desolate plant light shine fungi for storey building water elephants, three of them."

Once she said that, a Gu Immortal responded: "Storey building water elephants... I have a few, how many storeys do you want from the water elephants?"

Storey building water elephants were a special type of beast in Eastern Sea, they had varying sizes, with white tusks and blue skin. Water elephants with one storey buildings were like boats and had blue jade exoskeleton on their backs resembling buildings. Two storey building water elephants were larger, with two floors of blue jade exoskeleton on their backs.

Similarly, six storey building water elephants had wide backs and were like huge boats, they were desolate beasts. Seven storey building water elephants were ancient desolate beasts, and eight storey building water elephants were immemorial desolate beasts, they were extremely rare. Nine storey building water elephants did not exist.

Be it beasts or plants, or even variant humans, there were no rank nine versions of them. Among humans, there were only ten of them, rank nine Gu Venerables, they were unique among all lifeforms.

Tong Hua showed the scale of her light shine fungi and told the Gu Immortals that she wanted a total of three six storey building water elephants.

This was not expensive, it was very standard.

But that Gu Immortal frowned: "I only have one six storey building water elephant, the light shine fungi can be split up, would you like to trade?"

Tong Hua hesitated.

He might not be speaking the truth.

After considering it, Tong Hua nodded: "Then let's trade."

Thus, the first deal was made, both sides transacted quickly.

"I would like some light shine fungi, but I do not have storey building water elephants, do you accept immortal essence stones?" Fang Yuan asked.

Tong Hua shook her head, but she did not reject him entirely: "If there are no storey building water elephants, never mind. But my light shine fungi will be sold in treasure yellow heaven, you can buy them then."

In fact, Eastern Sea had mostly water path Gu Immortals.

And light shine fungi suited Eastern Sea Gu Immortals a lot. Like Wu Yi Hai for example, his immortal aperture was a sea.

Tong Hua was only testing the waters with this new discovery, seeing if she could gain benefits from it.

As for selling them for immortal essence stones, Tong Hua did not want that.

Because she did not know the market price.

This was a new finding, she was selling it for the first time, Tong Hua did not know its value.

However, she was very expectant about it.

Thus, she rejected Fang Yuan without hesitation. What if this light shine fungus was very popular in treasure yellow heaven, then wouldn't her sale price be at a loss now?

But if she sold it for too high of a price, the other party would not trade. Treasure yellow heaven was the best place for that.

Tong Hua did not want to sell it, Fang Yuan was helpless.

But he understood her.

This was a new desolate plant, she could use some methods to raise the prices later.

Even though this world's economy was not developed, Gu Immortals were astute people, they knew how to jack up prices.

Especially this light shine fungus, in the world, currently only Tong Hua had it.

If it were Fang Yuan, he would also elevate the price at the initial stage to earn a huge profit.

This light shine fungus was just a rank six desolate plant, once it was in the market for some time, people would research about it, and Tong Hua's monopoly would be gone.

After all, Eastern Sea was so big, light shine fungi would not grow in only one place.

Gu Immortals could create a method to seek out light shine fungi after some research. That would cause the supply of light shine fungi to rise sharply.

Seeing that no one else was interested, Tong Hua stepped down.

Next, the second Gu Immortal went up onto the platform.

This was the rule of the trading convention.

In each round, the Gu Immortals would go up in order that was decided earlier. They could only put up one resource each round.

This ensured relative fairness.

As for Fang Yuan, a newly joined member, he could also transact and go on the platform, but he was the last person.

"This is marrow sucking stone, rank seven immortal material, I want some thousand year floating wood." The Gu Immortal who went up expressed himself quickly, explaining his item.

Once he said that, he displayed it.

This marrow sucking stone was black and looked like an ordinary rock by the beach. But in fact, as long as a life form that had bone marrow got close to it, they would be sucked inside.

Thus, marrow sucking stone was known as a demon stone.

Demon stone was a name coined by mermen.

Mermen were a type of variant human, most mermen in the world lived in Eastern Sea.

Mermen could live underwater and breathe, when they met marrow sucking stones, they had suffered from them, thus, they feared and called them demon stones.

In Eastern Sea's history, there were some merman tribes who treated these demon stones as deities to worship.

But to Gu Immortals, this marrow sucking stone was just an immortal material.

This transaction was successful as well.

Thousand year floating wood might be rare in the market, but the Gu Immortals here were all affluent, otherwise, they would not have gathered for this trading convention.

Birds of a feather flock together, Gu Immortals who associated with Miao Ming Shen were not simple.

One could say, this small trading convention was a rare gathering of experts in Eastern Sea.

After the second Gu Immortal, Tu Tou Tuo went up.

"I have an ancient desolate beast queen toad. It can command all huge toads at rank six level and below. If raised well, it can nurture enslavement path Immortal Gu as well. Anyone interested?"

The queen toad had a lot of enslavement path dao marks.

But Tu Tou Tuo's transaction failed.

The fourth Gu Immortal: "I am looking for clues to qi sea. Anyone know how to find qi sea and how to get in? I am willing to pay a high price for relevant information."

It was also possible to trade information, but the Gu Immortals present stayed silent.

This transaction also failed.

Qi sea was a special and mysterious sea area in Eastern Sea.

The Gu Immortals present might be unsure of it, or some might know but did not want to trade.

The Gu Immortals went up one by one.

The first round was about to end.

Fang Yuan was the final one.

And Miao Ming Shen was second last.

He went up: "I have a rank seven divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu, anyone wants to trade?"

Fang Yuan heard this and his eyes shined!

Chapter 1298: Trading Gu

The trading convention was underway.

As the host of this trading convention, Miao Ming Shen originally was to be the final person to get on the stage.

But because Fang Yuan joined in, he became the last person.

Miao Ming Shen was now the second last to trade.

In this aspect, Fang Yuan could see Miao Ming Shen's great interpersonal skills.

Gu Immortals who got to trade first had the bigger advantage. Miao Ming Shen, as the final person, was expressing goodwill to everyone.

But he could not place Fang Yuan before him.

This was against the rules.

Newcomers had to be last.

If he went against this, everyone would be unhappy. After all, Miao Ming Shen was the host of this session, but what about the next?

Interpersonal skills were nothing much, it was just one's attitude when interacting with people.

Miao Ming Shen had a good grasp of this, he made the people that he interacted with feel friendly towards him.

However, Fang Yuan's mind was not on Miao Ming Shen, his gaze was shining as he looked at the Immortal Gu that Miao Ming Shen was holding —

Rank seven, divination tortoise shell Gu!

Fang Yuan was greatly enticed.

Why?

Because Fang Yuan had many methods that he could not use. Like ancient sword dragon transformation or reverse flow protection seal, if they were used, Fang Yuan had to make sure there were no survivors. Otherwise, intelligence on him would leak and Gu Immortals would be able to find out more information about him, he would be forced into a corner.

This was quite awkward, actually.

As Fang Yuan got stronger, the problems he created were getting bigger.

Shadow Sect, Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven... looking at his opponents and enemies, all of them were colossal forces.

Recently, he even made enemies with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, the number one rank eight in Northern Plains!

Thus, Fang Yuan was facing great pressure, he had not reached rank nine.

Only after reaching rank nine would Fang Yuan be able to announce his identity openly, nobody would be able to stop him.

Before reaching rank nine, even if Fang Yuan cultivated to rank eight, Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court could still find trouble with him.

Currently, rank seven Fang Yuan had to act with a low profile, he had to disguise himself and cultivate rapidly to accumulate strength.

"Becoming Wu Yi Hai has a weakness, or rather, I have a flaw..."

Fang Yuan could not fight when he was Wu Yi Hai.

Because he was not the real Wu Yi Hai!

After soul searching Wu Yi Hai, Fang Yuan found that Wu Yi Hai had three transformation killer moves. One was a coral form, one was a seagull form, and the third was a tortoise.

Earlier, during the battle in the regional wall, Wu Yi Hai had turned into a tortoise to defend himself.

Fang Yuan remembered clearly that it was a horned divine tortoise. An ancient desolate beast with a tough shell, it was top ten in that regard among Eastern Sea's ancient desolate beasts.

Actually, this could be seen from Wu Yi Hai's immortal aperture.

Wu Yi Hai's immortal aperture was a sea. There were three types of lifeforms inside, sea turtles and tortoises with the ancient desolate beast horned divine tortoise, corals with the ancient desolate plant silent coral, and seagulls with the desolate beast white letter blue feather seagull.

As a transformation path Gu Immortal, he would often raise the species that he transformed into.

Firstly, these lifeforms were resources that could help with his transformation path cultivation. Like the horned divine tortoise that Wu Yi Hai cultivated, if he needed any Immortal Gu in the future, he could kill these horned divine tortoises to refine it.

Secondly, transformation path Gu Immortals had to have a clear understanding of these lifeforms that they transformed into to raise their battle strength. Raising them in the immortal aperture would allow them to observe the lifeforms and eventually have realistic transformations with greater battle strength.

As for Fang Yuan, this was just a method.

Fang Yuan's transformation path attainment level was raised from dream realms and tribulations.

Once his attainment level rose, it would influence all these cultivation aspects, including this.

Thus, Fang Yuan saved a lot of trouble, he could skip a long time of observation and practice.

"If I can have this Immortal Gu, it would be very useful to me."

Fang Yuan became more enticed as he thought about it.

The divination tortoise was a wisdom path ancient desolate beast, it had one ability, to defend against deductions. Many Gu Immortals wanted to capture this ancient desolate beast, but using wisdom path methods to deduce its location was too difficult.

If Fang Yuan became a divination tortoise, it would help him greatly when traveling.

This, he concluded that this Immortal Gu was extremely useful.

Or rather — it was too useful!

For others, rank seven divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu might be useless. After all, it could only defend one's back. But if one wanted its deduction prevention ability, it was instead not as effective as other methods.

Thus, it had little use. Furthermore, why would a Gu Immortal face deductions all the time? Was everyone Liu Guan Yi?

Fang Yuan, however, was different.

He was extremely famous in the five regions now, even his fake identity was.

Furthermore, Fang Yuan could transform into a divination tortoise and use the transformation path dao marks, it was an immortal killer move. The ability to defend against deductions would be far stronger than using divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu alone.

Fang Yuan looked around, what made him happy was that these people were not very interested in the Immortal Gu.

Transactions of Immortal Gu were only done through exchange.

This was because Immortal Gu were unique, their value could not be determined easily. The value of Immortal Gu completely depended on the person. The same Immortal Gu could be a burden to someone, after all, the price of feeding Immortal Gu was huge, but to others, they would pursue it relentlessly, they would treat it like a treasure if they got it.

"Immortal Gu."

"To think that he is trading Immortal Gu in the first round."

The Gu Immortals sighed, they spoke softly, but they stayed on their seats, not moving.

Miao Ming Shen smiled.

He had anticipated this.

They were few transformation path Gu Immortals, among those present, Chu Ying was the only one. And even Chu Ying might not be very interested in this Immortal Gu.

Transformation path Gu Immortals usually cultivated two or three transformations, too many was pointless. Unless they had the essence of transformation path — change form Immortal Gu, it could allow them to turn into any form.

But Miao Ming Shen had his intentions in doing this.

He was the host of this trading convention. If news that an Immortal Gu trade had occurred in the first round got out, it would elevate the status of this trading convention, it would attract more Gu Immortals with greater wealth here.

"I am willing to trade for this Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan stood up from his seat.

At once, the Gu Immortals looked towards Fang Yuan with surprised expressions.

Miao Ming Shen was slightly dazed, before reacting and smiling even wider now.

"I wonder what you would like to trade for?" Fang Yuan asked.

Miao Ming Shen chuckled: "Chu Ying, this is your first trading convention, and you are my benefactor. How about this... I do not have much use for this Immortal Gu, we can trade anything."

This time, Fang Yuan was dazed, he did not expect Miao Ming Shen to list such an easy condition.

But even so, Immortal Gu transactions could only be done with Immortal Gu, other things were not usable.

Fang Yuan thought about it: "I have flying bear strength Immortal Gu..."

"Deal." Before Fang Yuan finished his words, Miao Ming Shen agreed without hesitation.

Fang Yuan could not help but look at Miao Ming Shen, realizing why this person was doing so well in Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world. He was a lone immortal, but he actually had several Gu Immortals that were so loyal to him!

But some things had to be stated clearly.

He smiled bitterly: "Friend, I am in admiration towards your intentions, but I have not finished my words, my flying bear strength Immortal Gu is only rank six."

Miao Ming Shen's expression changed.

The other immortals' expressions also turned grim, they looked at Fang Yuan with dark gazes.

Flying Bear Strength was a strength path Immortal Gu, while divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu was transformation path.

Strength path was declining, but transformation path was still popular and strong. Between the two, flying bear strength Immortal Gu was already less valuable than divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu.

And now, Flying Bear Strength was only rank six.

How could a rank six Immortal Gu and rank seven Immortal Gu be traded?

The value was completely different.

Chapter 1299: Another Trade

The difficulty of refining one rank six Immortal Gu was very different from refining a rank seven Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan wanted to use rank six flying bear strength Immortal Gu to exchange for rank seven divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu, if spoken nicely, he was dreaming, but to be blunt, he was simply too greedy, he was trying to take advantage.

This 'taking advantage' also gave a feeling of disdain.

Who did he think Miao Ming Shen was?

Was he easy to bully?

Or did he think the others were fools?

Thus, the Gu Immortals having grim expressions was understandable.

Fang Yuan smiled.

He saw these immortals' attitude and expressions, he knew why these people had a change of emotion.

But he still asked: "Will you exchange it?"

Miao Ming Shen smiled forcefully, but he nodded: "Yes! You have helped me twice, these will suffice."

The other Gu Immortals heard this and looked at Miao Ming Shen in a different light, their disdain towards Fang Yuan increased.

One of them even snorted coldly, expressing his unhappiness towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan suddenly laughed.

He said: "Everyone has said how incredible Lord Miao Ming Shen is, I was disbelieving, but after today, I completely agree. How can I take advantage of you? I will compensate you with something else, you will definitely be pleased!"

Saying this, Fang Yuan transmitted to Miao Ming Shen secretly.

Miao Ming Shen heard this and his expression changed, he became excited: "Chu Ying, are you serious?"

"Hahaha, let's do the deal now, you will know if it's true or false." Fang Yuan laughed again.

"Sorry, we need to do this transaction alone." Miao Ming Shen said as Fang Yuan followed him to leave the cave.

They went outside for the transaction, afterwards, the two returned with smiles on their faces.

Fang Yuan was relaxed, while Miao Ming Shen was smiling in a pleased manner.

The two were walking together closely, everyone could tell that their relationship had gotten closer.

After sitting down, Miao Ming Shen cupped his fists at Fang Yuan: "I owe you a third favor."

"Your demeanor is truly magnificent. This is merely a transaction, there is no favor." Fang Yuan was very polite.

These words made the Gu Immortals very perplexed.

At once, they started guessing: What did Chu Ying trade to make up for the difference, and make Miao Ming Shen so happy?

Miao Ming Shen sat down but Fang Yuan did not.

After this transaction, it was Fang Yuan's turn, he went on the platform.

The immortals looking at him had different gazes now, they were solemn and curious, with probing intentions.

At the same time, they were curious about what Fang Yuan was going to offer.

This was because they did not know Fang Yuan, he was a stranger.

According to Fang Yuan's offer, they would be able to guess some information about him. Like what immortal materials he had in abundance, they were often produced in their own blessed lands. This way, some intelligence could be deduced, like how developed Fang Yuan's immortal aperture was, and what types of dao marks he had inside.

If it were one or two damaged ancient desolate beast corpses, they were often the Gu Immortal's spoils of battle. If an ancient desolate beast reared in the immortal aperture died, the corpse would not be damaged. Such corpses would allow the immortals to assess Fang Yuan's battle strength as well.

Gu Immortals focused heavily on gathering intelligence.

On this aspect, information path Gu Immortals had the greatest advantage.

But what Fang Yuan took out shocked them.

"Everyone, take a look, this is a bone path rank six Immortal Gu, Bone Spike. I obtained it by chance, but I am not a bone path Gu Immortal, I want to trade with it, does anyone want this? As for what I want in return, I am like Lord Miao Ming Shen, I have no specific preference." Fang Yuan smiled.

"An Immortal Gu again."

"This is the first round, there are actually two Immortal Gu transactions."

"This Chu Ying is quite rich, he is a transformation path Gu Immortal but he had two Immortal Gu of other paths."

"The first transaction is done, but this one might not succeed. There are no bone path Gu Immortals here."

The Gu Immortals talked to each other secretly, they were close with one another.

"None?" Fang Yuan waited for a while, but no Gu Immortal spoke.

He felt no disappointment.

The rank seven Immortal Gu, Divination Tortoise Shell, was worth coming to this trading convention.

Just when Fang Yuan was about to step down, a voice said: "Wait, I think... we can trade with this Immortal Gu."

The immortals turned to look, it was Wu Ma Yang.

"Strange, he is a dark path Gu Immortal, why does he want a bone path Immortal Gu?" This question appeared in everyone's minds.

Bone spike Immortal Gu had no relation with dark path.

But if Wu Ma Yang had any immortal killer moves that needed bone spike Immortal Gu, then it was possible for him to want this Immortal Gu.

Everyone had their own secrets, even though the Gu Immortals were puzzled, they held in their questions and watched quietly.

"There is a Gu Immortal who wants bone spike Immortal Gu?" Fang Yuan was also curious.

He asked: "I wonder what you would like to trade with?"

Wu Ma Yang frowned, he hesitated a little before gritting his teeth: "I will trade this Immortal Gu."

He displayed this Immortal Gu.

It was a rank six Immortal Gu, on the same rank as bone spike Immortal Gu.

The Gu Immortals looked as someone cried out: "This is day Immortal Gu."

That's right, this was the rank six time path — day Gu!

Fang Yuan was stunned.

"I did not expect this, this trading convention was really worth it!" Fang Yuan rejoiced internally, but his expression was blank, he seemed to be in deep thought.

There was no need to think!

The moment Fang Yuan saw this Immortal Gu, he wanted it.

The reason?

Because he had Hei Fan's true inheritance, he had rank seven year Gu, after Immortal Gu, and Years Flow Like Water, as well as a bunch of time path immortal killer moves.

He remembered that in the true inheritance, Hei Fan had been talking about immortal level day Gu and month Gu non-stop.

He remembered those four immortal killer moves, days pass like years and the rest.

"If the inheritor can obtain immortal level day Gu or month Gu, these four immortal killer moves would not need to expend so many mortal day Gu and month Gu, the effect would even rise greatly."

These were the words recorded in Hei Fan's true inheritance.

Fang Yuan saw this and did not think much of them.

He was not overly ambitious, year Gu was enough to satisfy him.

But destiny was very mystical, when Fang Yuan had placed no attention on immortal level day Gu and month Gu, day Gu appeared right in front of him like this.

"Let's exchange it."

"Even though I am not familiar with time path, feeding bone spike Immortal Gu is certainly a burden."

Fang Yuan said.

"My day Gu consumes the water of the River of Time, it has no feeding problems. However, I cannot use this Immortal Gu, I might as well trade it for bone spike Immortal Gu, to add into my immortal killer moves." Wu Ma Yang said.

The two traded quickly.

The original wills inside the two Immortal Gu left as the other party's immortal essence entered.

The Gu Immortal's will inside the immortal essence was the true key to refining Gu.

In Earth's terms, wills were like a preset program to Gu worms.

Wills could think. Wild Gu worms had their own wills. Refining wild Immortal Gu was simply using the Gu Immortal's will together with immortal essence to erase the wild will.

Wild wills had the instinct to survive, they could not destroy themselves, thus, even though it was tough for Gu Immortals to refine Immortal Gu, it was not risky.

Other people's Immortal Gu were different.

A Gu Immortal's will was vastly different from wild will.

Trying with brute force to refine someone else's Immortal Gu would only destroy it. For example, Fang Yuan could recall his Immortal Gu with just a special will set inside them. Basically all Gu Immortals would not allow another person to refine their Immortal Gu directly.

Once that was happening, the will inside the Immortal Gu would destroy the Gu worm.

Unless wisdom path methods were used to suppress the Immortal Gu's will. But usually, it would be hard to suppress all of it in an instant. With a small flaw, the Immortal Gu would be destroyed.

Precisely because of this, even though Fang Yuan captured Hei Cheng, he did not obtain dark arrow Immortal Gu.

And because of this, even though Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan's alliance agreement was gone, he could not directly refine attitude Gu, it was a problem.

Chapter 1300: Refining Attitude Gu

"This particular trading convention is very different."

"That's right, it is truly not normal. In our usual trading conventions, even though there are Immortal Gu trades, they will not appear in the first round."

It was traditionally hard to trade Immortal Gu, most of the members in the trading convention had limited chances. Thus, they would usually put up the items which were unlikely to be traded to the end.

Thus, even if they wanted to trade away their Immortal Gu, the Gu Immortals would choose to do it in the last few rounds.

This was normal in trading conventions.

But this time, it was different.

Not only was there an Immortal Gu trade in the first round, it happened twice. And more importantly, both times succeeded!

And in these two transactions, Fang Yuan played a pivotal role.

Even though this was the first time he came to a trading convention, the Gu Immortals present did not dare to underestimate this newcomer, Chu Ying, anymore.

"We will start the second round now, Fairy Tong Hua, please." Miao Ming Shen said.

He was very happy.

The trading convention had just started and Immortal Gu were already traded, this result would help him a lot when he traveled over Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world.

Tong Hua went onto the platform, she wanted to trade another type of desolate beast.

"It seems that she is trying to develop her blessed land." Fang Yuan, who was sitting beside Miao Ming Shen, spoke to him.

Miao Ming Shen smiled: "Brother Chu, you might not know, but Fairy Tong Hua had just passed a tribulation recently."

"So that's it." Fang Yuan understood.

After a Gu Immortal passed a tribulation, their immortal aperture's resources would be greatly damaged, but they would gain a lot of dao marks too. These new dao marks would modify the immortal aperture's environment, causing it to be more accommodating to different types of resources.

Thus, Fairy Tong Hua tried to trade for all sorts of resources in this convention, planning to develop them in her immortal aperture.

"This Immortal Tong Hua is very affluent. Not only is her immortal aperture managed well, she also has a personal sea area, called rainbow aurora sea. Whenever it is dawn or dusk, aurora light shines above the sea area, weaving with the sky, it is extremely beautiful. This sea area is not far away. After the trading convention ends, Fairy Tong Hua will invite everyone to her sea area for a gathering. By then, Brother Chu can go with us." Miao Ming Shen said, giving Fang Yuan some information about Tong Hua.

Fang Yuan gained more understanding of her.

"Then I will thank you for a recommendation. To speak the truth, I am interested in her light shine fungus." Fang Yuan said directly.

"No problem, I can help you with that." Miao Ming Shen was someone who knew the best way to interact with someone, he gladly took on this task.

After the trading of Immortal Gu, his relationship with Fang Yuan improved greatly.

Fang Yuan knew why Miao Ming Shen's attitude had changed.

The reason was none other than — lifespan Gu!

What could interest Miao Ming Shen was undoubtedly lifespan Gu. Fang Yuan used a rank six Immortal Gu to trade for a rank seven Immortal Gu, and he even used a declining strength path Gu.

But Miao Ming Shen was very satisfied with the transaction. This was because Fang Yuan used a hundred years of lifespan Gu to make up for the difference.

Lifespan Gu was only a mortal Gu, but it was really rare.

Many Gu Immortals would keep them in their hands and refuse to trade them. They would keep these lifespan Gu for the time when they really needed it.

Miao Ming Shen's lifespan was not near its end, but he did not have a lot left.

Thus, he was looking for the tributary of the River of Time, he wanted to find some methods to extend lifespan.

In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, Miao Ming Shen had entered the blue dragon whale many times to look for the lifespan Gu inside.

Fang Yuan offered him lifespan Gu, why would Miao Ming Shen not be happy with it?

Furthermore, Fang Yuan took out a hunded years of lifespan Gu, what did that mean?

Miao Ming Shen was not dumb, he thought: This meant that Chu Ying had more lifespan Gu. Otherwise, why would he use them so 'unsparingly'?

Thus, Miao Ming Shen wanted to improve his relationship with Fang Yuan.

But he did not know that this was Fang Yuan's intention.

Fang Yuan's motives were deeper.

The blue dragon whale!

According to his previous life's information, Fang Yuan had a greater understanding of this opportunity than Miao Ming Shen currently.

The transactions continued.

During the second round, Gu Immortals went up one by one, and most of their transactions succeeded.

Soon, it was Fang Yuan's turn.

Immortal Gu Woman's Heart.

Fang Yuan was about to trade this rank six Immortal Gu away when his expression suddenly changed.

"Sorry, something happened, everyone, I need to leave early." Fang Yuan said.

The Gu Immortals were shocked.

This trading convention was a rare chance, to think that Fang Yuan was giving up now.

But the trading convention was not a restricted event, it was fine if Fang Yuan wanted to leave, they could not stop him.

"What happened? Do you need my help?" Miao Ming Shen sent Fang Yuan off.

"It is not a big matter, but it is urgent. This is such a waste, I am missing out on the trading convention!" Fang Yuan sighed.

Miao Ming Shen quickly said: "Don't worry, when such a trading convention happens again, I will inform you."

"I will thank you in advance, goodbye."

"See you again."

Fang Yuan flew off into the clouds, vanishing from sight.

Miao Ming Shen sighed, looking at Fang Yuan vanish, he turned around and went back into the cave.

While flying in the clouds, Fang Yuan's expression was ugly.

He had left earlier because a wisdom path great expert had suddenly tried to deduce his whereabouts.

The power from Dark Limit was almost used up, with this huge expenditure now, Fang Yuan was forced to leave the trading convention prematurely.

"Damn it, which Gu Immortal is deducing me? I wonder if they are deducing Fang Yuan or Liu Guan Yi?"

Fang Yuan felt some regret.

If he had some more time, he might have traded woman's heart Immortal Gu away.

Such opportunities were incredibly rare.

After one convention, many Gu Immortals would lay low for many years before wanting to trade again.

After he got to a safe distance, Fang Yuan used the new divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu, as well as change form Immortal Gu.

Immortal killer move — Divination Tortoise Transformation!

Transformation path killer moves were so simple and straightforward.

Because he lacked the help of mortal Gu, this killer move's effect was not outstanding. But because of change form Immortal Gu, this panacea, although the transformation had none of the battle strength from the divination tortoise, Fang Yuan could use it.

This divination tortoise transformation was to give Fang Yuan more time.

A while later, he found a safe environment and placed his immortal aperture.

For several days, he stayed inside the immortal aperture.

He started to think about how he could refine attitude Gu.

Even though he had two new Immortal Gu, they were not useful for refining attitude Gu.

Fang Yuan was helpless about this.

Maybe the third Gu for Woman's Heart could have been a suitable Immortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan missed this opportunity.

He needed to stay inside the immortal aperture for some time so that Dark Limit could be used again.

By then, the trading convention would be over.

"This means I can only borrow Immortal Gu from Lang Ya blessed land." Fang Yuan had a backup plan.

But this was a secondary method.

The best situation was for Fang Yuan to settle it himself.

Borrowing Immortal Gu was not a feasible plan.

If Fang Yuan used his own Immortal Gu to deduce an immortal killer move to refine attitude Gu, it would help him greatly, he could even fuse this immortal killer move into reverse flow protection seal.

Think about it, by then, Reverse Flow River would flow around Fang Yuan's body, and any Immortal Gu that flew inside would be refined by Fang Yuan. How tempting was that?

Fang Yuan had a long term goal regarding this.

But it was a pity, even though he joined the trading convention, he did not gain any progress in this aspect.

But thankfully, Lang Ya blessed land had no lack of refinement path Immortal Gu.

Through treasure yellow heaven, and after expending Lang Ya Sect contribution points, Fang Yuan borrowed some Immortal Gu.

A commotion occurred in treasure yellow heaven again, but Fang Yuan had no choice but to do this.

Using these refinement path Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan came up with an immortal killer move using Reverse Flow River to refine attitude Gu.

Fang Yuan purposely slowed his movement, half a month later, he successfully refined attitude Gu.

And now, he finally owned this legendary rank eight Immortal Gu.

Chapter 1301: Approach of the Great Era

Central Continent, Hidden Dragon Cave.

"Greetings to superior immortal from Heavenly Court." Two Gu Immortals knelt on the ground.

One old and one young.

A grandfather and a grandson.

They were Gu Immortals from Wind Cloud Manor.

The young Gu Immortal was Feng Chan Zi, while the elderly man was Old Man Bei Feng, with rank eight cultivation level. Among the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, he was famous, and without any mishaps, he would have become a member of Heavenly Court already.

It was not easy or normal to become a member of Heavenly Court.

Rank eight cultivation level was not enough, they had to be elites among rank eights. This standard had never been lowered since Heavenly Court was created. Heavenly Court did not waver in this aspect, too few was better than too many!

And this Old Man Bei Feng was now kneeling on the ground, expressing his reverence.

The person he was kneeling to was an extremely weak old man, he was shaking as if a gust of wind could blow him away.

But this old man was not ordinary, he had a huge origin, he left a deep mark in Heavenly Court's history.

He was — Duke Long!

"Get up, bring me inside." Duke Long said plainly.

"Yes." Old Man Bei Feng acknowledged.

A moment later, Duke Long came to the deepest part of Hidden Dragon Cave.

This was a deep earth trench, it was larger than the Earth Trench that Northern Plains' Zombie Alliance had.

It was possible to stuff thousands of cities into it easily.

Duke Long and Old Man Bei Feng were tiny like dust specks compared to it.

From their view, the entire Earth Trench was covered in darkness, this darkness was so deep that one could not see through it.

Rumble...!!

Suddenly, the entire Earth Trench started shaking intensely.

The two sides of the Earth Trench started to have falling rocks.

The earthquake caused incredible sound waves that would make people shell-shocked.

Old Man Bei Feng's expression changed, he quickly used the Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture. Suddenly, bright lights shone as countless auroras and flowing water weaved together dazzlingly.

There was actually a huge super Gu formation here!

In contrast to this Gu formation, the one that surrounded Southern Border's dream realm was just a kitten compared to an elephant.

Old Man Bei Feng controlled the Gu formation, his expression quickly changed as his forehead was covered in sweat.

"The commotion is so huge!" As a great rank eight Gu Immortal, he was actually feeling difficulty now.

This super Gu formation was suppressing a terrifying lifeform, Old Man Bei Feng could only barely deal with it using the super Gu formation.

"Hehehe, it seems that after so many years, you are still so lively. Di Zang Sheng." At this time, Duke Long spoke plainly.

"Roar!!!" At the next moment, an overwhelming dragon roar filled the entire Earth Trench.

The super Gu formation's aurora lights were dispersing, flowing water was disrupted.

Old Man Bei Feng's forehead was dripping with sweat, he thought: "This is after the super Gu formation's isolation, the volume is still so loud. If I have to face this Evil Dragon directly, I am afraid..."

Duke Long was unmoved, he assessed: "It seems your temper has not changed, you are still so feisty."

"Accursed old man!!" This time, a voice came from inside the Gu formation.

The voice was just as loud.

At the next moment, a huge dragon head appeared from within the aurora light and flowing water.

It was Evil Dragon — Di Zang Sheng!

This immemorial desolate beast had a huge origin, it was a legendary immemorial desolate beast created from endless hatred, anger, and grudges, all these negatives emotions in Central Continent's earth veins.

It was born of nature, because it was created from the collective negative emotions of humans, after it was born, it had intelligence that matched humans.

Initially, it could only roar and growl, but after learning, it could use hope Gu to awaken its aperture, it learned human language, and for some time, it turned into a human and tried to master Gu Immortal methods.

For some time, it wreaked havoc in Central Continent, it caused great distress and chaos in the world.

But eventually, it was suppressed by Duke Long.

It was suppressed for countless years.

But Heavenly Court could not kill it.

Because it was formed from the negative emotions of humans. As long as humanity still flourished, the Evil Dragon would continue to grow stronger every day. Even if its body was destroyed or completely decimated.

Soon, it would form from new earth veins, and continue to cause chaos in the world.

That was why Heavenly Court used a super Gu formation to suppress this Evil Dragon.

The people guarding the place were rotated from time to time. This time, Feng Chan Zi sold immortal materials for his own profits, he was punished to guard Hidden Dragon Cave. And his grandpa knew that he could not do this alone, so he gave up the chance to join Heavenly Court and came to look after this Evil Dragon.

After the Evil Dragon saw Duke Long, it became incredibly furious.

The meeting of enemies with filled with animosity.

"Why are you roaring and growling, you cannot escape from this prison." Duke Long said plainly.

Di Zang Sheng heard this and no longer raged, it laughed: "Hahaha, I almost forgot. Accursed old man, you are going to die soon. Your lifespan is reaching its limit, you only have one last chance of extending your life. Even lifespan Gu cannot save you. Haha, this is hilarious, so what if you suppressed me? I am alive, while you are dying."

Duke Long nodded: "You are right. Sometimes, I envy you, you have a long lifespan from birth, you innately have longevity. This might be the last time we meet, let me borrow ten years of life from you."

Saying this, Duke Long sucked in a breath.

Old Man Bei Feng was shocked to find out that as the guardian, he instantly lost control of this Gu formation.

Di Zang Sheng was suppressed by Duke Long, this super Gu formation was created by Duke Long personally.

Duke Long was the true owner of this super Gu formation!

"Roar!" Di Zang Sheng let out a painful cry.

Duke Long was still sucking.

Old Man Bei Feng could not tell what Duke Long was actually sucking.

It seemed to be a sort of life essence that could not be seen with the naked eye, it was forcefully extracted from Di Zang Sheng's body, sucked into Duke Long's own body.

"It seems that this super Gu formation is not purely for suppressing Di Zang Sheng, it has this kind of effect." Old Man Bei Feng had an epiphany.

During the process of sucking, Duke Long's body inflated like a balloon from its twig-like appearance. His pale yellow ragged face faded to a normal color. His pale white hair also turned dark.

He was hunchbacked earlier and had fragile bones that emitted cracking sounds, but it had straightened now.

Most evidently, the pair of horns on his head were originally shriveled like two lumps of meat, but now, they shined with a metallic luster, piercing towards the sky.

Bam.

His peak rank eight aura burst out like an invisible wall, pushing outwards.

Old Man Bei Feng took a step back uncontrollably, looking at Duke Long's majestic background, he had a sense of admiration in his heart.

In contrast to Duke Long was Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng.

It said in a hoarse voice: "Damned old man, that is merely ten years of lifespan. It's like I'm giving a pool of piss to you. Hahaha..."

It was still laughing, but it was very weak now.

Duke Long clenched his fists, saying nonchalantly: "Evil Dragon, you do not understand, how can I, Duke Long, fear death? I woke up this time to make up for my previous mistake. Ten years is more than enough."

"Enough for? What are you trying to do?" Evil Dragon asked.

"What else? The great era is coming." Duke Long said with deep meaning.

"Great era? Great era! Don't tell me, the earth veins will merge, the regional walls will vanish, and the five regions will become one... wait, accursed old man, don't go, tell me everything!" Di Zang Sheng shouted.

But Duke Long sneered, why would he care about a captive? He turned around and left Hidden Dragon Cave without any hesitation.

Southern Border.

A nameless place.

River water was surging.

This was a tributary of the River of Time!

Ying Wu Xie and the rest had been waiting by the riverside for a long time.

A figure emerged from the tributary of the River of Time.

"Quick! Let's quickly give lord a helping hand!" Ying Wu Xie saw this and shouted.

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing worked together beside him, activating the Gu formation.

Under the effect of the Gu formation, Purple Mountain True Monarch escaped from the tributary of the River of Time, he was like a drowning person, he barely managed to crawl ashore, he breathed roughly and was soaked to the bones.

"Purple Mountain True Monarch actually managed to return safely after entering the River of Time!" Bai Ning Bing was expressionless, but she was shocked on the inside.

"Lord, did you succeed?" Seeing Purple Mountain True Monarch regain his composure, Ying Wu Xie asked this.

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "I went into the red lotus and interacted with that will, my gains were phenomenal!"

"Is that so?" Ying Wu Xie was overjoyed.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch had a solemn expression: "I used Red Lotus' true inheritance to observe the past and future. Before Fang Yuan was reborn, our Shadow Sect had succeeded, we delayed the great era by five hundred years, we exterminated the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable before she matured, we even had Heavenly Court completely under our control! It is a pity that Fang Yuan changed everything. Shadow Sect cannot stop it anymore, the great era is coming!"

Ying Wu Xie had an extremely shocked expression.

Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan looked at each other, feeling puzzled.

The former asked coldly: "What is the great era?"

Ying Wu Xie breathed in deeply and answered: "The earth veins will merge, the regional walls will vanish, the five regions will become one, and Great Dream becomes venerable. This is the great era!"

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing were stunned.

At the same time.

Fang Yuan went back to Southern Border using Wu Yi Hai's appearance, he was back in Wu clan.

"I am finally back."

"This time, I must absorb the dream realm and go all-out in raising my attainment levels."

"There is enough time."

"After five hundred years, during the five regions chaotic war, I might become a great grandmaster of every path already. I am looking forward to it."

Chapter 1302: Divination Tortoise Transformation

Southern Border, Wu clan.

Fang Yuan entered Southern Border, using 'Wu Yi Hai''s appearance, he went all the way back to Wu clan's headquarters.

Knowing that he was back, Wu clan's current first supreme elder, Wu Yong, summoned him.

"Brother, these are the Immortal Gu that I borrowed from the clan, I am returning them now." Fang Yuan returned the Immortal Gu in his hands.

Wu Yong received them and smiled as he sat in the main seat: "Was your journey to Eastern Sea fruitful?"

Every Gu Immortal had their own secrets, especially someone with a special status like Wu Yi Hai, Wu Yong could not probe excessively. His question was really just small talk.

"I had great gains." Fang Yuan showed some joy on his face, it was very realistic.

"That is good." Wu Yong nodded.

He would not be able to imagine how great Fang Yuan's gains were.

After leaving Southern Border, Fang Yuan chased after Shadow Sect's remnant forces, even though he did not succeed in killing them, his gains were huge.

Not only did Fang Yuan obtain perseverance Immortal Gu and become the Reverse Flow River Lord, his battle strength surged and he could go unscathed against rank eight Gu Immortals. Liu Guan Yi's reputation was renowned in the entire world!

Furthermore, while returning, he participated in an Eastern Sea trading convention. He obtained divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu and rank six day Gu.

"Thank you for the concern, brother. I wonder when can I return to the Gu formation to cultivate? Please arrange it for me." Fang Yuan said with a polite and humble tone.

Wu Yong was very satisfied with Fang Yuan's performance.

These last days, he had control of Wu clan, because Fang Yuan backed down, there were few obstacles in Wu clan, he successfully took over the clan and obtained the highest authority.

Right now, Wu Yong was already different from when he first took over. He was more composed and grand, he gave off an indomitable aura, he had great authority.

He was very happy about Fang Yuan's attitude.

Clans were different from sects, bloodline was very important.

Wu Yi Hai's status in Wu clan made him very special among Wu clan's Gu Immortals. In terms of bloodline, he was solely inferior to Wu Yong, and was above everyone else.

Wu Yi Hai wanted to cultivate in seclusion, Wu Yong was sure to satisfy it.

Thus, he agreed: "Return to your residence and rest first. I will arrange this, in a few days, it will be ready."

"Thank you, brother, I will take my leave." Fang Yuan left after seeing that his objective was achieved.

He had a home in Wu clan.

When he first joined Wu clan, he was assigned by Wu clan to live on this Bear Mountain.

"Wu Yong is starting to be in control of Wu clan."

"Wu Yi Hai's identity is very sensitive, if he worked with an ambitious clan like Qiao clan, to create lots of problems, Wu Yong would have a huge headache."

"Thus, to play safe, Wu Yong would not let Wu Yi Hai roam around and make contributions for the clan, and increase his reputation."

Other Wu clan Gu Immortals were fine, but Wu Yi Hai was not.

Or rather, not for now.

Wu Du Xiu had just died, Wu Yong was in control of Wu clan but it was not a stable position.

Fang Yuan was very aware of Wu clan's situation.

He was not worried that he would be unable to return to the super Gu formation.

While staying on the mountain, he cultivated.

But his immortal aperture could not be placed down.

Not to mention opening the immortal aperture's entrance and taking in heaven and earth qi.

"My sovereign immortal aperture's foundation is too deep, each time it absorbs heaven and earth qi, the commotion is huge, winds would surge and clouds would move."

"But Reverse Flow River really consumes a lot of heaven and earth qi. It seems that I will need to go to Yi Tian Mountain later to take in heaven and earth qi, only by replenishing it will I sustain the sovereign immortal aperture and prevent my foundation from falling."

This was a form of burden.

But it was a good one.

Even though Wu Yong asked him to rest, Fang Yuan did not rest.

He continued to cultivate, he was fighting against time.

During this period, many Gu Immortals from the clan came to visit Wu Yi Hai, who had a special status, but Fang Yuan rejected them all.

This attitude made Wu Yong very pleased. He felt that Wu Yi Hai was not trying to interfere in the clan affairs. Thus, he gave Fang Yuan a lot of immortal materials under his own name. Not only was he trying to reward and appeal to him, he was also trying to gain reputation for 'being a caring brother'.

At the peak of the mountain, Fang Yuan, who was inside his huge house, had turned into a tortoise.

This tortoise was as large as a house, it was black and had a thick and tough shell, there were countless markings on its shell, it was difficult to observe but it had a certain order.

It was a divination tortoise.

This ancient desolate beast was associated with wisdom path, after transforming, Fang Yuan's transformation path dao marks turned into wisdom path.

With his wisdom path dao mark accumulation, there was a huge quantitative change.

With this foundation, Fang Yuan could use wisdom path deduction methods with greater efficiency. It was at least several times or even more than ten times that of before!

Simply divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu, in terms of the Gu worm itself, it could not compare to attitude Gu or wisdom sword Immortal Gu, even Flying Sword, Sword Escape, and Dragon Breath were better than it.

But regarding Fang Yuan, it was extremely useful!

Suddenly, a brilliant light shined in the divination tortoise's eyes.

"After ten or so days of hard work, I finally succeeded in deducing the killer move, divination tortoise transformation."

At Fang Yuan's will, he turned back to human.

Next, he tried to use the newly completed divination tortoise transformation killer move.

Once, twice, thrice...

After more than ten times, he finally finished making his adjustments.

A new divination tortoise transformation!

He added in a lot of transformation path mortal Gu, like tortoise head Gu, tortoise tail Gu, tortoise leg Gu, and others. There were also some wisdom path Gu worms, to increase the divination tortoise's ability to block deductions, until Fang Yuan reached his limits. There were also many defensive Gu worms.

Of course, there were only two cores.

One was rank seven divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu, the other was change form Immortal Gu.

The brand new divination tortoise was larger than before, it was lifelike like an actual ancient desolate beast divination tortoise.

Especially the tortoise shell, countless dao marks were weaved together in a criss-crossing fashion, there were an enormous number of them.

"Very good, I have reached my current limit." Fang Yuan experimented and felt very pleased.

This was all thanks to his wisdom path and transformation path grandmaster attainment levels.

Deducing these killer moves was as simple as drinking water.

Similar to the ancient sword dragon transformation, which combined transformation path and sword path. This divination tortoise transformation was the combination of transformation path and wisdom path.

And now, Fang Yuan had a new fighting method. It was not an incomplete version like before, this could be fully used in battle.

And most crucially, the killer moves ancient sword dragon transformation, reverse flow protection seal, and myriad self could not be used in battle, but this divination tortoise transformation covered the flaw, it solved Fang Yuan's current problem.

Fang Yuan stopped the transformation and rested to regain his mental energy.

He closed his eyes and his mind entered sovereign immortal aperture.

Landscape as Before!

The rank six Immortal Gu was used, targeting Reverse Flow River in the immortal aperture.

Red date immortal essence was expended rapidly, while Reverse Flow River started to produce river water under the power of Landscape as Before.

"The efficiency is too low." Fang Yuan sighed.

This was not his first experiment, he was quite disappointed.

Landscape as before Immortal Gu, even though it was effective on Reverse Flow River, the effect was mild.

This formed a clear contrast to Luo Po Valley and Dang Hun Mountain.

"Why is it that using Landscape as Before on Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley had such incredible effects, but on Reverse Flow River, it barely works?"

Fang Yuan was puzzled.

Was Reverse Flow River more special than the other two secluded domains of heaven and earth?

What other reasons were there?

If he could repair Reverse Flow River immediately, that would be great. He would have an unceasing supply of Reverse Flow River's water.

But reality was less than perfect for Fang Yuan.

"Wait! Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were once in the possession of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. And Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was the creator of sovereign immortal fetus Gu. Maybe... these two secluded domains of heaven and earth were modified by Shadow Sect, just like how Hei Lou Lan and the others could use Immortal Gu of other paths without being restricted by dao marks."

Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration.

His guess was right.

Not only did Shadow Sect have a method to allow Gu Immortals to cultivate other paths without facing conflicting dao marks, they could also modify secluded domains of heaven and earth, to allow Immortal Gu of certain paths to be very effective on the secluded domains of heaven and earth and not face conflicts from dao marks.

And time path Immortal Gu were fully effective on Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, they would not be resisted by the vast number of soul path dao marks in them.

This was because Landscape as Before and Man as Before belonged to Shadow Sect. They were passed to Tai Bai Yun Sheng through Purple Mountain True Monarch.

As for Reverse Flow River, Shadow Sect did not have it, they had no interest in this river either.

Thus, Reverse Flow River was not modified, when Fang Yuan used Landscape as Before on Reverse Flow River, it was weakened by its vast number of dao marks, and had little effect. And this was already because Fang Yuan was the Reverse Flow River Lord, otherwise, Landscape as Before's effect would be reflected upon him.

"Reverse Flow River lost a lot of water, the rank eight existences depleted a good amount. But thankfully, it is recovering, even though the speed is very slow."

"Can I use reverse flow protection seal to resist immemorial year beasts?"

Fang Yuan shook his head.

Using Reverse Flow River, he could at most defend himself. If an immemorial year beast tried to destroy the immortal aperture, he could do nothing against it.

He thought about this because Fang Yuan was concerned about the sealed rank eight Immortal Gu, Years Flow Like Water.

Even though his battle strength surged greatly, Fang Yuan was still unable to unseal Years Flow Like Water currently.

Like this, Fang Yuan cultivated silently, waiting for Wu Yong's arrangement for returning to the giant dream realm.

But a few days later, a minor mishap occurred.

Chapter 1303: Divination Tortoise's Power

Southern Border, Wu clan.

In the hall, Fang Yuan, Wu Yong, and another Gu Immortal were present.

He had a tall body, he wore a black and white coat, he had a long beard that extended downwards to his chest. His eyes were slim and long, a mysterious light was hidden in them, his body was covered in mist.

Wu clan Gu Immortal, Wu Yu Bo, a prideful person with peak rank seven battle strength, it was only slightly lower than Old Treeman Ba De.

"Gu Immortal Yan Huang challenged Yu Bo, the reality is that Xia clan is after Moon Bowl. This place produces moon path Gu worms, it is one of the most important resource points of our clan, we cannot lose." Wu Yong said.

"Since I am going, there is no need to worry. If I can defeat Yan Huang twice, I can win a third time." Wu Yu Bo said coldly.

Moon Bowl was not a bowl, it was a valley.

But this valley had a peculiar shape, resembling a bowl, and because it produced moon path Gu worms, people called it Moon Bowl.

Moon Bowl had a village in it.

But when Wu clan expanded, in order to take over Moon Bowl, they eradicated this village. There was a Gu Immortal in this village, he was known as Immortal Yan Huang.

Wu clan sent out Wu Yu Bo and defeated him. Immortal Yan Huang could not defeat them and had to escape in tears, abandoning his home.

Wu clan was a righteous path clan, they needed a proper reason to take over Moon Bowl, they could not kill Immortal Yan Huang directly.

This was the rules of the righteous path.

Immortal Yan Huang left with hatred, to take revenge, he hid his identity and practised his killer moves, but he still lost to Wu Yu Bo a second time.

After Wu clan learned of his whereabouts, they knew that this enmity was unresolvable, they gathered Gu Immortals to assassinate Immortal Yan Huang.

But at the crucial moment, Immortal Yan Huang was saved by an unknown force.

Wu clan wanted to pursue it, but at that time, Wu Du Xiu died, Wu clan was in chaos and Wu Yong had just taken over, he needed to suppress the situation. This gave Immortal Yan Huang some time to recover.

Until now, a few days ago, Immortal Yan Huang sent a challenge to Wu Yu Bo with Moon Bowl as the stake. Whoever wins would obtain Moon Bowl.

Wu clan was the number one super force in Southern Border, how could they not accept it?

But Wu Yong's worry was that Immortal Yan Huang was here after joining Xia clan, a super force, he was no longer all alone.

This meant that the mysterious force which helped Immortal Yan Huang earlier was undoubtedly Xia clan.

On the surface, this was Immortal Yan Huang challenging Wu Yu Bo. But the truth was, this matter was significant, it was the contest of two super forces.

This challenge had been spread widely, the attention of many Southern Border forces and Gu Immortal experts were drawn to it.

After Wu Du Xiu died, even though Wu clan was still the number one force, its reputation had fallen. Xia clan was the first challenger of Wu clan's dominance. If Wu clan lost this, the other clans would smell weakness and everyone would be tempted to target Wu clan, there would be huge problems.

This was Wu Yong's worry.

Immortal Yan Huang's open challenge was now the first hurdle of Wu Yong's rule.

"Yu Bo, don't be careless, you know how important this is for our clan." Wu Yong sighed: "That Yan Huang joined Xia clan, he is given aid by them, they must have ill intentions and be amply prepared this time if they are challenging you."

"First supreme elder, you only need to wait for good news." Wu Yu Bo had a nonchalant expression, he glanced at Fang Yuan and said: "In my opinion, we don't need to bring so many people. This Yan Huang is just a loser, I can easily capture him."

"We should play safe, my brother is skilled in three transformations, he is a rank seven expert, with him guarding you, I can rest assured." Wu Yong said.

Wu clan had a huge territory, even though there were many Wu clan Gu Immortals, they were split up in many places, they lacked manpower.

Originally, Wu Yong was planning to send Fang Yuan to the super Gu formation.

But now that this happened, Wu Yong had to send Fang Yuan to guard Wu Yu Bo. After all, Immortal Yan Huang was not alone, he was accompanied by Xia clan Gu Immortal Xia Qing Cang.

Fang Yuan had joined Wu clan, although he could reject this, there was no harm in going, Fang Yuan agreed.

This was a good task, he only needed to stay on guard, after it was over, the clan would reward him for the help.

Wu Yu Bo did not care, but Wu Yong insisted on it, he could not reject it.

This matter was decided, a few days later, Wu Yu Bo went to the designated location with Fang Yuan.

Over there, Xia Qing Cang and Immortal Yan Huang were waiting already.

Immortal Yan Huang looked like a middle aged Gu Immortal, he had a mature expression and ordinary appearance, after seeing Wu Yu Bo, his expression changed, he stared with wide opened eyes, like they were spewing fire.

But that Xia Qing Cang had a special disposition, his body stood tall and straight like a mountain peak. He had a square face and white hair. Especially his beard, it was tough like needles, his eyes were shining brightly.

"Wu Yu Bo, you destroyed my village and killed my descendants, I will return all this humiliation to you today!" Immortal Yan Huang growled.

Wu Yu Bo sneered: "Simply slander! I did that to find traces of blood path and uphold justice, eliminating evil for this world. You are not a righteous person, and you dare to smear me, you deserve death!!"

The two fought immediately.

Fang Yuan and Xia Qing Cang watched at the two ends of the battlefield, staying on guard for their respective Gu Immortals.

There was nothing to say, everyone knew the real reason, but the righteous path had to put a front of righteousness over their intentions.

Immortal Yan Huang was a fire and earth path dual cultivator, on one hand, his flames were like rising dragons, emitting tremendous heat. On the other hand, rocks were rumbling, there was a huge commotion.

Meanwhile, Wu Yu Bo cultivated water path, he moved like falling leaves, he was grand and swift ,there was grace in his actions. His body was covered in water vapor, there was drizzle from the sky, but the rain was able to dissolve all of Immortal Yan Huang's flames and rocks.

Evidently, Wu Yu Bo had the upper hand.

However, the battle had just started, both sides were probing, they had not used their Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves yet.

Fang Yuan watched as he investigated the surroundings, he was defending against Xia Qing Cang, in case he used any sneak attacks.

Xia Qing Cang seemed very relaxed, he looked at Fang Yuan at times, smiling when his gaze met with Fang Yuan's eyes.

This made Fang Yuan feel uneasy.

Xia Qing Cang was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he was famous in Southern Border, he was a high-level character.

The battle continued.

Both sides started to use Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves.

Immortal Yan Huang was always suppressed and pressured by Wu Yu Bo, the advantage the latter had was becoming clearer.

Victory was near, Fang Yuan did not dare to be careless. If he failed his job, he would be punished when he returned to the clan.

"Yan Huang, die. It is your honor to die from my signature killer move!" Wu Yu Bo had deep killing intent, a cold light was shining in his slim and long eyes.

He activated his immortal killer move, rain poured down as clouds gathered, dark winds were howling, the three fused together to form a ball-shaped cage capturing Immortal Yan Huang.

Immortal Yan Huang was trapped inside and could not leave, he was in a desperate situation, he was about to die.

Fang Yuan closely observed Xia Qing Cang, guarding against his intervention.

But Xia Qing Cang had a smile on his face, he watched casually, seemingly having no intention to interfere.

But at this time, Immortal Yan Huang suddenly laughed loudly, the aura of countless Gu worms appeared from his body, a bright light was shining from his body.

Immediately, the cage that trapped him broke apart.

"How can this be?!" Wu Yu Bo was shocked, he was caught off-guard, his signature killer move was broken, he immediately suffered huge injuries.

The lava under Immortal Yan Huang's feet gathered and formed a battlefield.

This was an immortal battlefield killer move.

Wu Yu Bo had a pale expression, he was trapped inside the battlefield.

The situation had turned around, Wu Yu Bo was in grave danger.

With this sudden change, Fang Yuan wanted to help, but Xia Qing Cang flew to him, warning him: "Wu Yi Hai, don't be the shame of Wu clan!"

Fang Yuan chuckled: "How can an outsider like you determine if our Wu clan is shameful?"

Saying this, he turned into a divination tortoise and charged into the lava battlefield.

Xia Qing Cang praised Fang Yuan's resolute decision internally, but he did not move slowly: "In that case, have a taste of my killer move, scattering mind!"

A wisdom path immortal killer move.

Xia Qing Cang used his signature killer move right away, it was a powerful method.

Any Gu Immortal hit with this would feel their mind wandering, there would be random thoughts colliding in their mind, their battle strength would be greatly affected, if they were careless, they would fall into confusion and be unable to help themselves.

Fang Yuan chuckled, he kept charging towards the battlefield killer move without caring.

"Fool!" Xia Qing Cang mocked coldly.

At the next moment, his scattering mind hit Fang Yuan, but it dissipated, while Fang Yuan was unscathed.

Xia Qing Cang's cold smile froze on his face.

"How can this be? This is... divination tortoise?" Xia Qing Cang finally recognized Fang Yuan's transformation, he had a bitter expression.

The divination tortoise was a wisdom path ancient desolate beast, it was skilled against the deductions of wisdom path Gu Immortals. This wisdom path killer move was created from the concept of deduction, it was completely countered by the divination tortoise.

Bam.

The battlefield killer move was broken by Fang Yuan as the divination tortoise entered, immediately saving Wu Yu Bo, who was in danger.

Xia Qing Cang was about to interfere, but Fang Yuan said: "Our Wu clan has lost, this battle is over, Moon Bowl is yours!"

After hearing this, Xia Qing Cang stopped.

Immortal Yan Huang wanted to attack, but Xia Qing Cang stopped him.

The former had no choice but to watch with hatred as his enemy escaped.

"Why did you let him go?" Immortal Yan Huang roared.

Xia Qing Cang looked at him coldly: "We have already won Moon Bowl, our objective has been met. It is not the time for you to kill Wu Yu Bo yet. Don't forget that you are an external supreme elder of Xia clan, you have to think about our clan's benefits first!"

This time, Xia clan had won, if they pursued this matter, Wu clan would fight back with force.

Xia clan did not want to be Wu clan's target and lose in the end, allowing the other forces to benefit.

Chapter 1304: Happily Getting Immortal Gu

The Wu clan rank seven Gu Immortal, Wu Yu Bo, lost to Immortal Yan Huang.

This matter was intentionally spread by Xia clan, soon, the whole of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world knew about it, everyone was moved!

"Wu Yu Bo is a rank seven expert, a famous battle strength of Wu clan, he lost to Immortal Yan Huang?"

"Immortal Yan Huang is not weak, now that he has Xia clan's help, it is not that hard to defeat Wu Yu Bo."

"Wu Yu Bo is arrogant and prideful, it is quite shocking that he lost to a person he defeated before."

"The important thing is that Immortal Yan Huang broke through Wu Yu Bo's signature killer move, this is impressive. Perhaps Xia clan's Xia Liu Pei helped him to deduce it."

Xia clan had a wisdom path Gu Immortal who was famous for being a deduction expert in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

It was Xia Liu Pei.

"This time, Wu clan lost face. Not only did Wu Yu Bo lose to Immortal Yan Huang, he even nearly lost his life. If not for Wu Yi Hai, who broke through the battlefield killer move, Wu Yu Bo would not have survived."

"Seriously?"

"Yes, all sorts of Gu worms have been passed around, they record the scene of that battle."

"Wu clan actually lost Moon Bowl, hehe, this is a huge joke."

"Well if we trace the origin, Wu clan had snatched Moon Bowl previously. This is what Wu clan deserves!"

"Hahaha, now that Wu Du Xiu is dead, Wu clan cannot keep its title of number one."

Losing Moon Bowl was not a problem for Wu clan, which had vast territory and wealth.

But Fang Yuan had intervened to destroy the battlefield killer move and save Wu Yu Bo, this made Wu clan fall into a passive spot.

This was the difference between righteous path and demonic path.

Fang Yuan had saved Wu Yu Bo, this was against the rules of the fight, Wu clan had lost face as a result.

And the problem was, there was hard evidence regarding this, they could not deny it.

Xia clan's wisdom path Gu Immortal Xia Qing Cang was the one guarding Immortal Yan Huang. He was a meticulous person and had used information path Immortal Gu to record the scene. They were targeting Wu clan, they naturally came prepared.

Wu clan had to admit their fault, after Fang Yuan returned with Wu Yu Bo, Wu Yong gave orders to punish Fang Yuan, because he had gone against the rules of the fight, he was punished to be secluded and had to compensate some immortal essence stones.

Fang Yuan had saved Wu Yu Bo, this was a merit. But for Wu clan, they had lost face, even though they saved a rank seven Gu Immortal, and it was much more important to them than face!

Fang Yuan had merit, but Wu Yong punished him.

But he had no grudges, he accepted his punishment and returned to Wu clan's headquarters, staying in his mountain and not leaving.

The incident of Moon Bowl was still escalating, the impact was increasing.

Wu Yu Bo was a prideful person, after losing to Immortal Yan Huang, he felt incredibly ashamed, he declared that he was going into secluded cultivation after returning, he would claim victory in the future.

Eve though Wu clan lost Moon Bowl valley and Wu Yong punished Fang Yuan, who broke the rules, Wu clan's reputation had unavoidably declined.

And most importantly, Xia clan's actions were an inspiration to the other super forces.

Righteous path and demonic path were different.

The righteous path had its own rules.

Xia clan used these rules, even though Wu clan lost Moon Bowl, they did not object.

Xia clan was special in Southern Border, and even among the five regions. Because this super force mainly cultivated light path and wisdom path. Even though wisdom path Gu Immortals were rare, Xia clan had five wisdom path Gu Immortals, and some of them were strong experts.

Among the wisdom path Gu Immortals of Southern Border, Xia clan was the domineering force, having a huge proportion of them.

It was not strange that Wu clan was plotted against by Xia clan.

The other forces saw Xia clan's success and were all moved, wanting to imitate them.

When Wu Du Xiu was alive, Wu clan was domineering, taking over resource points from others, expanding their territory, incidents like Moon Bowl were numerous. They had many enemies like Immortal Yan Huang.

This was what other forces could use to deal with Wu clan.

All sorts of intelligence was arriving, Wu Yong had an ominous sensation, he felt like a storm was brewing towards Wu clan.

As expected, after Moon Bowl, Luo clan approached Wu clan with similar reasons as Xia clan.

Next, Chi clan and Chai clan also attempted to get a share of Wu clan's inspiration cocoon cave and spring sun mountain range.

Wu Yong oversaw the situation from the base, deploying people outside, but Wu clan's territory was too big, they lacked manpower, they could only maintain the situation at best.

Wu clan was in trouble, Wu Yong had a huge headache, but his brother 'Wu Yi Hai' was living a comfortable life.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

"Let me go, please let me go. Ahh—!" Ma Hong Yun's soul screamed in pain.

But Fang Yuan ignored him, continuing to soul search him.

Ma Hong Yun's soul could not endure such torture, he quickly became very weak.

Guts Gu.

Fang Yuan used one Gu worm to replenish Ma Hong Yun's soul, before continuing his soul search.

"You evil fiend!!"

"Kill me, kill me..."

The intense pain in his soul made Ma Hong Yun unable to endure it, he continued to curse, scold, cry, and beg, but Fang Yuan was unmoved.

A moment later, he stopped.

Ma Hong Yun's soul was very diffuse, like mist that was about to vanish.

But next, Fang Yuan smashed one guts Gu and Ma Hong Yun's soul healed.

"I have finally excavated all of the luck path true inheritance that Ma Hong Yun had."

"But Zhao Lian Yun is not dead yet, I can still continue to keep Ma Hong Yun's soul, it has value. Hehehe."

Fang Yuan had killed Ma Hong Yun by accident in Reverse Flow River and obtained his soul.

These last days, he had been soul searching.

After confirming that he had fully excavated everything, Ma Hong Yun had no secrets in front of him anymore.

Fang Yuan thus obtained a portion of the all living being's luck true inheritance.

Self luck, all living being's luck, heaven and earth luck, these were Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's three true inheritances. Self luck was in Lang Ya blessed land, all living being's luck was in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and heaven and earth luck was in Longevity Heaven.

As Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed, and the all living being's luck true inheritance was destroyed as well.

However, back then, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were protected by the all living being's luck true inheritance, they each received a portion of it.

After so many events, Fang Yuan soul searched him and obtained this portion of the all living being's luck true inheritance.

"Thankfully, Old Ancestor Xue Hu wanted to use Ma Hong Yun to refine Fortune Rivalling Heaven and needed a healthy Ma Hong Yun, thus he did not do anything to his soul."

"When Ma Hong Yun left Imperial Court blessed land, he was captured by Shadow Sect's Qin Bai Sheng. Since he learned about the all living being's luck true inheritance, Shadow Sect also knows."

Fang Yuan analyzed, in this portion of the true inheritance, the greatest value was fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu's recipe!

Ma Hong Yun remembered the details.

This was the core essence of the all living being's luck true inheritance.

It was not strange.

It was because Ma Hong Yun knew of this Immortal Gu recipe that Old Ancestor Xue Hu learned of it after buying him, resulting in him having the intention to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

"Fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu..." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

According to this Immortal Gu recipe, even if he used up all of his wealth, he could not complete ten percent of the recipe's needs.

Unless he had a living Gu material like Ma Hong Yun, he could save a lot of precious refinement materials, Fang Yuan could barely give it a go.

But how would Fang Yuan dare to refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

This was a rank eight Immortal Gu!

Brazenly trying to refine a rank eight Immortal Gu, what would happen? Old Ancestor Xue Hu's outcome was an example.

This was the number one Gu Immortal with the highest battle strength in Northern Plains, but he was not doing well now. Not only did his refinement of Fortune Rivalling Heaven fail, he lost Reverse Flow River and Snowy Mountain blessed land, even his beloved wife Lady Wan Shou was injured.

"Even though I have a lot of assets now, and the sovereign immortal aperture's foundation can rival rank eight Gu Immortals, my immortal essence stone and red date immortal essence storage is low, and most importantly, I have few resources that are high in value."

This time, Fang Yuan chased after Ying Wu Xie, from Southern Border to Eastern Sea to Northern Plains, it consumed a lot of immortal essence. And inside Reverse Flow River, he created an immortal killer move. Reverse flow protection seal was the most costly immortal killer move that he had.

"The sovereign immortal aperture's production was incredible, but because I reduced the rate of time to stall calamities and tribulations, the efficiency fell drastically."

"Even though I am still earning profits, my expenditure is huge too. Especially the feeding of Immortal Gu, wisdom sword Immortal Gu and attitude Gu have not had their feeding settled yet, I still need more funds for them."

Fang Yuan wanted to solve the problem of food, he also needed to store immortal essence for emergencies, his current situation was quite awkward.

A while ago, he had to pay immortal essence stones for saving Wu Yu Bo against the rules, it added to his problems.

"Slowing the rate of time causes my immortal aperture to produce more slowly. This way, I can only expand production to emphasize on quantity instead."

"But what resources do I expand production of, this is an important consideration. Some resources are already oversupplied in the market, if I expand production, it would only harm me."

While Fang Yuan was thinking about this, Wu Yu Bo's will brought an Immortal Gu and flew towards Fang Yuan's mountain.

"Thank you for saving my life. Lord Wu Yi Hai, this rank six vajra thought Immortal Gu will be my expression of gratitude." Wu Yu Bo's will actually gave Fang Yuan an Immortal Gu.

Vajra thought Immortal Gu!

Evidently, this was a wisdom path Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had benefited from this Moon Bowl incident — he gained an Immortal Gu!

Even though it was rank six, Immortal Gu were unique, they were priceless.

Chapter 1305: Vajra Thought

This vajra thought Immortal Gu was fist sized, it looked like a translucent glass, shining with golden lights, it looked very appealing.

Fang Yuan held it in his hands, it was heavy, as if he was holding a piece of gold.

The process of changing owners was very fast.

When Fang Yuan refined this vajra thought Immortal Gu successfully, Wu Yu Bo's will said goodbye and flew away.

Obtaining a rank six Immortal Gu like this, Fang Yuan was not surprised.

Because he had merit!

Fang Yuan saved Wu Yu Bo, it was a huge merit in Wu clan. Even though he broke the rules and Wu clan lost face, they preserved a precious rank seven battle strength. Evidently, his merits surpassed the problems he caused!

Even though Wu Yong punished Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan understood why. This was the righteous path, they had to do it on the surface.

Wu clan had to reward Fang Yuan, but Wu Yong could not do it himself.

Once he did, the political implications would be different, if it were found out, others would use it to attack his reputation.

Thus, Wu Yu Bo's will had to do it.

This vajra thought Immortal Gu was supposedly Wu Yu Bo's personal gift to Fang Yuan, but it was actually Wu clan paying for it. There had to be this middleman, it was the righteous path's way.

"Another Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

Ordinary Gu Immortals might be happy, but to Fang Yuan, the implications were different.

He had too many Immortal Gu!

The burden was huge.

"But vajra thought Immortal Gu is a wisdom path Immortal Gu, I can use it to make up for some of my weaknesses."

Fang Yuan did not lack wisdom path attainment level, he lacked wisdom path Immortal Gu.

In the past, he only had attitude Gu and unravel mystery Gu, but now he had affection Gu and vajra thought Gu.

Four wisdom path Immortal Gu, this was enough, with Fang Yuan's wisdom path grandmaster attainment level, he could use them well.

Fang Yuan instilled red date immortal essence, attempting to activate this vajra thought Immortal Gu.

Immediately, golden thoughts appeared in his mind. These thoughts were small and exquisite, they shined with a metallic luster, giving off a tough feeling.

When the thoughts collided, they created clanking sounds.

Fang Yuan tried to use these newly produced vajra thoughts to deduce.

But he found that these vajra thoughts were not good at thinking. The thoughts were hard to fuse, they often broke apart.

Fang Yuan thought 'as expected', he was not surprised.

Vajra thought Immortal Gu itself was not good for thinking, it excelled in fighting.

Fang Yuan mobilized these vajra thoughts in his mind, these thoughts were small and exquisite, when they left his mind, they expanded in the outside world, becoming fist sized golden balls, there was bright light shining on their crystal-like surface.

Fang Yuan sat on a cushion, hundreds of vajra thoughts were floating around him, at once, golden light shined and gave him an extraordinary air.

At his will, a vajra thought flew out.

Swoosh!

It was very fast.

Thoughts moved rapidly to begin with, thoughts moved faster than light in one's mind!

When the vajra thought was in the outside world, it was not as fast as in the mind, but it was still rapid.

"This speed is half of sword escape Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan's eyes twitched, he was satisfied with this speed.

Sword Escape was a rank seven Immortal Gu, and one with great speed. Vajra thought Immortal Gu was only rank six, but the vajra thoughts could have half of Sword Escape's speed.

Of course, for Immortal Gu like Vajra Thought, even if it was raised to rank seven or eight, the quality of the vajra thoughts produced would not change, only the quantity would vary.

In theory, mortal vajra thought Gu could produce vajra thoughts no different from those produced by the Immortal Gu. The difference was the quantity. Rank five mortal vajra thought Gu could produce a hundred vajra thoughts at once. But vajra thought Immortal Gu could produce thousands or even tens of thousands of vajra thoughts at once.

Then what was the power of one vajra thought?

Fang Yuan aimed at a tile on the ground and shot out the vajra thought.

Bam, the vajra thought created a trail of golden light as it crashed into the tile, drilling deep underground.

Fang Yuan nodded.

The power was decent.

This place was a mortal Gu House, the defensive power was too weak for Gu Immortals, but it was not useless.

The power of the vajra thought made Fang Yuan think of bullets from Earth.

But it was much larger than bullets.

"One use of vajra thought Immortal Gu can create thousands of vajra thoughts, if they are all shot out together, it is quite a sight."

"Wait a second..."

A flash of inspiration appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

He thought of two Gu Immortals, one was Dong Fang Chang Fan, the other was Ye Lui Qun Xing. The former had an immortal killer move called myriad star fireflies. The latter also had an immortal killer move, it used star fragments as the core, the longer he fought, the stronger he became.

"I have vajra thought Immortal Gu, why don't I imitate myriad star fireflies and create an immortal killer move?"

Fang Yuan considered it.

Intuition from his wisdom path grandmaster attainment told him that this would not be tough.

Thus, Fang Yuan stopped activating vajra thought Immortal Gu, he pondered and began to deduce the immortal killer move.

He was imitating myriad star fireflies, using vajra thought Immortal Gu as the core.

The process was smooth, there was little difficulty, it all went according to Fang Yuan's intuition.

An hour later, this immortal killer move was half complete.

A day and a night later, Fang Yuan turned into a divination tortoise to deduce it without rest, finally obtaining the complete immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan did not name this immortal killer move, because he had a new inspiration.

"Just this immortal killer move with rank six vajra thought Immortal Gu as the core is not powerful enough. Maybe I can use divination tortoise transformation to modify this immortal killer move and raise its strength!"

This modification would not be easy.

Even though he had grandmaster wisdom path and transformation path attainment level, combining the two paths would not be an easy task.

The modification took a long time.

But Fang Yuan was not anxious.

The outside situation was quite calm now.

Even though Shadow Sect was around, and Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven were pursuing him, as long as he used the dream realm, Fang Yuan's foundation would continue to grow rapidly.

Undeniably, with reverse flow protection seal, his confidence had risen greatly.

Three days later, the modification of the killer move was not done, he was only at thirty percent, but Wu Yong had summoned Wu Yi Hai.

In the hall, the two brothers talked, Wu Yong told Fang Yuan: If he was not happy with vajra thought Immortal Gu, he could choose a rank six Immortal Gu from the clan's treasury and exchange it.

The reason was, after Fang Yuan accepted vajra thought Immortal Gu, he did not make a move, Wu Yong thought that Fang Yuan was a lone immortal and did not know how the righteous path worked, he might have really assumed that it was a gift from Wu Yu Bo.

This would not do.

Wu Yong summoned Fang Yuan and hinted to him that this vajra thought Immortal Gu was all because of this elder brother's efforts. And using the excuse of exchanging Gu, he expressed goodwill to Fang Yuan.

He did not know that Fang Yuan understood the entire situation, he was just pretending to be unaware.

"It seems that Wu clan is in trouble now, because they lack Gu Immortals, Wu Yong wants to make use of me." Fang Yuan immediately understood Wu Yong's intention.

Fang Yuan did not want to interfere in Wu clan's matters.

But recently, many super forces were cooperating to emit pressure on Wu clan subtly.

There were many problems, Wu Yong was busy dealing with all of them.

And over at the giant dream realm, Ba clan was leading the Gu Immortals in giving trouble to Wu clan.

Originally, Wu Yong wanted to send Fang Yuan there, but Ba clan was creating problems, the pressure at the super Gu formation was increasing. To play safe, Wu Yong did not want to change people now, thus, Fang Yuan's plan of going to the super Gu formation was stalled.

"Thank you for the concern, brother, I would like to take a look at the inner treasury as well." Fang Yuan had created an immortal killer move using vajra thought Immortal Gu, but he still wanted to look at the Immortal Gu inside the inner treasury.

Last time, he had chosen Immortal Gu from the outer treasury, the Immortal Gu inside the inner treasury were much better and had greater value.

As the number one force of Southern Border, Fang Yuan was excited about what was inside Wu clan's inner treasury.

There were few Immortal Gu in the inner treasury, but they were all the best of the best. But Fang Yuan had too many Immortal Gu now, he mainly wanted to probe Wu clan's foundation and gain more information about them.

Chapter 1306: Immortal Gu Reputation Restriction

Among them was an Immortal Gu called Reputation Restriction, it was a rare information path rank seven Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan was very interested.

After all, he was too weak in terms of information path, it was greatly restricting his development.

Reputation restriction Immortal Gu had an incredible effect.

After it was used, it would turn into a rope to restrict any desolate beast or desolate plant, and even ancient desolate beasts or ancient desolate plants.

Indeed, even though it was an information path Immortal Gu, it had an enslavement path effect.

It was very special and unique.

What moved Fang Yuan was, this reputation restriction Immortal Gu's effect varied according to its owner's reputation.

This suited Fang Yuan very well.

Be it Fang Yuan himself or Liu Guan Yi, they were characters who shook all five regions, they were widely known. In recent times, who had the most prominent reputation? It was none other than Fang Yuan!

"But..."

"My information path attainment level is ordinary, even if I get this reputation restriction Immortal Gu, what use is it?"

"Enslaving ancient desolate beasts and desolate plants is not useful to me. Only if I can enslave an immemorial desolate beast."

"And just this rank seven Immortal Gu Reputation Restriction will be impossible to enslave immemorial desolate beasts with. The only possibility is to use it as a core to create an immortal killer move."

"But that will take forever. My information path and enslavement path attainment levels are not at grandmaster. Regarding immemorial desolate beasts or plants, grandmaster attainment level is already very limited."

Fang Yuan thought about it, he did not exchange it, he kept vajra thought Immortal Gu.

This choice surprised Wu Yong a little.

"I made some gains in Eastern Sea, from now on, the divination tortoise transformation that uses wisdom path will be my main cultivation." Fang Yuan explained.

This was in preparation for him using divination tortoise transformation in the future.

Wu Yong nodded: "I called you here for an additional matter."

Fang Yuan was calm: "Please tell me."

Wu Yong smiled bitterly: "The Frosty Peak that my clan controls is targeted by Xia clan. There are some historical reasons, they are all recorded in this information path mortal Gu. Brother, I hope you can help defend Frosty Peak for our clan."

"I am willing to solve your problem, brother." Fang Yuan agreed before accepting the information path mortal Gu, inspecting it.

Fang Yuan's attitude made Wu Yong very pleased.

Fang Yuan looked at the information in the Gu worm, he understood this matter.

As it turned out, after Immortal Yan Huang defeated Wu Yu Bo, Xia clan obtained Moon Bowl, becoming the greatest beneficiary. Thereafter, other super forces went to trouble Wu clan. After Xia clan gained this profit, they decided to continue plotting against Wu clan, to obtain greater gains for the clan.

This time, they targeted Frosty Peak.

Frosty Peak was not Wu clan's resource point originally, it belonged to a lone cultivator Gu Immortal.

Very long ago, this lone immortal sought help from Wu clan, and Wu clan wanted his territory, but the lone immortal did not want to give it away.

After a long and arduous negotiation, the lone immortal lent this place to Wu clan for several hundred years.

More than a hundred years later, this lone immortal died from tribulation, this Frosty Peak officially became Wu clan's property, it had great production output each year.

Xia clan was able to request for it because they found a descendant of this lone immortal.

The lone immortal's descendant wanted Wu clan to return Frosty Peak, this was very reasonable, there was undeniable evidence.

With Xia clan's backing, they created a lot of commotion, attempting to take back Frosty Peak by creating a ruckus.

"The lone immortal's descendant is a mortal Gu Master, they actually dare to challenge Wu clan."

"Xia clan has many wisdom path Gu Immortals, they are good at plotting."

"But this time, I must defend Frosty Peak. This is the best chance for me to display my strength. Wu Yong does not want me to go to the super Gu formation, he is afraid I cannot suppress the situation if I have inferior strength."

Fang Yuan received the mission, but he did not set off urgently.

He knew: Even though he was strong, his methods could not be exposed. Divination tortoise transformation was good at defense but lacked offense, thankfully, he had vajra thought Immortal Gu, but he had to deduce that new immortal killer move first.

Thus, for more than ten days afterwards, Fang Yuan stayed inside his house, trying to deduce and modify the immortal killer move.

This was not a peaceful time.

Xia clan saw that Wu clan did not move and repeatedly urged them, spreading the news everywhere.

Wu clan faced great pressure, Wu Yong also came to urge Fang Yuan, but he stalled for time.

"No rush."

"If we do not show up, Xia clan cannot take over Frosty Peak by force."

"Xia clan is causing a commotion? It is no problem, let them make a scene, we will remain unmoved."

"Be steady, when I was a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea, I learned that this was the meaning of life."

"Be slower, the slower we work, the better the results."

Fang Yuan gave a lot of reasons, he had a reply to everything.

In the end, even Wu Yong became anxious, Wu Yi Hai did not face much pressure, but as the head of Wu clan, his pressure was getting heavier by the day.

"The clan's affairs are my affairs."

"Since this is entrusted to me, I will definitely succeed, I will not let you down, brother, I will meet your expectations."

Fang Yuan still willfully did things his way.

Wu Yong had no choice, he had no more Gu Immortals to send.

Only when Fang Yuan deduced the immortal killer move and experimented with it successfully did he start to leave, heading towards Frosty Peak.

Wu Yong let out a sigh of relief.

Xia clan had been focusing on Wu clan all along, the moment Fang Yuan moved, they received news of it.

On Frosty Peak.

"Wu clan sent Wu Yi Hai this time." Rank six wisdom path Gu Immortal Xia Zhuo Mo spoke.

"This Frosty Peak is on par with Moon Bowl, Wu clan did not send Wu Yu Bo or Wu Zhen here? This is a terrible move." Rank seven Gu Immortal Xia Fei Kuai could not believe it.

Xia Zhuo Mo thought about it: "Wu clan has nobody to send anymore. Wu Yu Bo is a prideful person, after losing to Immortal Yan Huang, unless he can kill Immortal Yan Huang and regain his reputation, he would not come out of seclusion. As for Wu Zhen, he is busy defending Phoenix Peak, how can he leave? During this period, all the different phoenix birds are going there to produce their eggs."

"Hahaha. Wu Yong has no choice, he sent Wu Yi Hai after having no other alternatives. How is this person's battle strength?" Xia Fei Kuai asked.

Xia Zhuo Mo thought about it: "His battle strength is unclear, he used to be a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea, there is little information on him. But he could escape threats and return to Wu clan, he can defend himself. Recently, he saved Wu Yu Bo and used a divination tortoise transformation, due to a coincidence, he managed to counter Lord Xia Qing Cang's scattering mind."

Saying this, he smiled bitterly: "The divination tortoise has naturally defense against wisdom path methods, against him, I may not be of use. It will depend on you."

Xia Zhuo Mo was a rank six wisdom path Gu Immortal, while Xia Fei Kuai was a rank seven light path Gu Immortal.

The latter laughed: "I see that this Wu Yi Hai is stalling for so much time, he has no confidence. Don't worry, I will go ahead and suppress this person, after we take down Frosty Peak, our Xia clan's territory will expand, this will be a huge merit!"

Chapter 1307: Four Seasons Tea

The sky was dark, it was drizzling.

Fang Yuan flew to the sky, mist surrounding him.

"I'm here." At his will, he descended as the mist in his vision vanished, showing the land.

Southern Border had many mountains, Fang Yuan was above many mountains, it was a scene of greenery.

In this sea of greenery, Frosty Peak was unique, it was completely white and different in height, standing out from the rest.

At the apex of Frosty Peak, there was a mortal Gu House, at the entrance of the Gu House, Xia clan's two Gu Immortals, Xia Zhuo Mo and Xia Fei Kuai, had already sensed Fang Yuan's arrival.

Fang Yuan was here to negotiate, he did not purposely conceal his presence.

It was normal for the two Xia clan Gu Immortals to notice him at once.

"He is finally here. This Wu Yi Hai is really amazing, he took half a month to travel on a three day route." Xia Fei Kuai frowned deeply.

"Forget it, he's here, let's go." Xia Zhuo Mo smiled.

The two sides met in the sky.

Both sides were smiling, they had a grand demeanor, after all, they were representing two super forces.

The two Xia clan Gu Immortals assessed Wu Yi Hai, thinking: "He looks really similar to Wu Du Xiu."

Fang Yuan was also assessing these two Gu Immortals, Xia Fei Kuai was rank seven, he was the person in charge of this negotiation.

According to Wu clan's information, Xia Fei Kuai was a rash and resolute person, he had great battle strength. Meanwhile, Xia Zhuo Mo was a wisdom path Gu Immortal who considered many aspects and liked to think deeply.

Xia Zhuo Mo's personality had to do with his childhood experiences, whenever he encountered an important situation, he would think about the possibilities over and over.

Meanwhile, Xia Fei Kuai's personality was the backlash of a certain immortal killer move that he had tried to use.

This was the first time both sides were meeting, Xia clan's Gu Immortals led Fang Yuan to the apex of Frosty Peak.

"Please enter for some tea." The two Gu Immortals acted like the hosts of the place, as if they were declaring their ownership, the contest had already begun, but Fang Yuan was unmoved, as if he did not sense it.

He smiled as he sat down, drinking.

"The tea is not bad." After one sip, he praised.

Xia Zhuo Mo smiled: "This is our Xia clan's four seasons tea, our first supreme elder had created it personally. With one sip, you will taste four different flavors, making people feel the four seasons of spring, autumn, summer, and winter. Therefore, it is called four seasons tea."

Xia clan first supreme elder was a time path great expert, the four seasons tea that she created showed her incredible attainment in time path.

Xia clan's Gu Immortals used this tea to assert dominance, but after Fang Yuan drank it, his smile intensified.

"This is a great tea, I wonder if you have any extra. I would like to ask for a few more portions, may I have them?" Fang Yuan smiled as he squinted.

The two Xia clan Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Xia Zhuo Mo thought: This Wu Yi Hai is really greedy. However, even if they were enemies, their righteous path demeanor was important. Furthermore, politics was always changing, right now, everyone was opposing Wu clan, but maybe they would soon have to cooperate with Wu clan.

Xia Zhuo Mo decided and was about to speak, when Xia Fei Kuai said: "Whatever! This is nothing much, we have a lot of four seasons tea, if you want them, you can have them."

Saying this, he gave out over ten portions of four seasons tea.

"Then I will accept it." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, receiving the tea leaves.

Xia Fei Kuai quickly added: "Let's talk about Frosty Peak."

Fang Yuan raised his cup and sipped slowly, before putting it down as he said: "Please tell me."

Xia Fei Kuai quickly spoke, his mouth opened and closed rapidly: "This matter takes very long to explain. Since we all know the origin, let's cut to the chase, Little Zhang, come out."

As he said that, a rank five Gu Master walked out of a door inside the Gu House.

"This descendant of Zhang San Feng, Zhang Kai Zui, greets the three immortals." This Gu Master was old and had white hair, he greeted the three immortals without excessive reverence.

"This Little Zhang's bloodline is absolutely correct. Come, come, come, Wu Yi Hai, quickly test it." Xia Fei Kuai left his seat, walking to Zhang Kai Zui and pulling his arm, bringing him to Fang Yuan with an expression that seemed to be in a hurry.

Zhang San Feng was that lone cultivator Gu Immortal who was the owner of Frosty Peak.

Of course, Zhang San Feng was not his original name, it was sort of a title[1]. Because he owned three mystical peaks, Frosty Peak was one of them.

His real name was unknown, ever since he appeared, he had never revealed his true name, only mentioning his surname of Zhang. As a result, everyone called him Zhang San Feng. Even his bloodline descendants did not know his true name.

Fang Yuan knew this, Wu clan's information was quite comprehensive.

But he suddenly waved his hand, acting confused: "Wait, who is this Gu Master?"

Xia Fei Kuai was stunned.

Zhang Kai Zui was about to speak, when Xia Fei Kuai said: "He is Zhang Kai Zui, he introduced himself earlier, we all know it."

"I know he is named Zhang Kai Zui." Fang Yuan nodded.

But he paused and drank tea, continuing: "But what does this mortal Gu Master have to do with Frosty Peak?"

"It is like this, his ancestor Zhang San Feng had once..." Xia Fei Kuai added.

"Wait." Fang Yuan stopped him: "Who is Zhang San Feng?"

Xia Fei Kuai was stunned: "Wu Yi Hai, after so long, you have no idea who Zhang San Feng is?"

Fang Yuan gave an embarrassed looking smile: "The clan wants me to protect Frosty Peak, but I arrived in a hurry, I have no idea what the cause of all this is. Please do not mind it."

Xia Fei Kuai thought: "You arrived in a hurry, reaching here after half a month. That's arriving in a hurry?"

He thought that, but he spoke politely: "Then let me tell you the reason."

"I am listening."

Xia Fei Kuai spoke rapidly, he explained the historical reason in the blink of an eye.

Fang Yuan drank his tea and nodded.

Xia Fei Kuai said: "Are you clear now?"

Fang Yuan placed down his cup, standing up from his seat and cupping his fists at Xia Fei Kuai.

Xia Fei Kuai had no idea why Fang Yuan was cupping his fists, it was a bit out of nowhere, but they were in the righteous path, a polite demeanor was everything, no matter what, he had to cup his fists in return.

Next, he saw that Fang Yuan smiled again in embarrassment.

Fang Yuan said: "Thank you for telling me that, but it was described too quickly, I could only understand the story roughly, I did not understand a lot of it. Can you tell me again?"

"Again?" Xia Zhuo Mo, who was beside him, frowned.

Xia Fei Kuai did not repeat it once again, he said: "Which part are you unsure about? I can explain that to you."

His tone was unhappy.

[1] San Feng here is also read as 'Three Peaks'. Back

Chapter 1308: Shameless!

Fang Yuan seemed to have not noticed, he smiled: "The first line, I did not hear it clearly."

Xia Fei Kuai explained it.

Fang Yuan nodded: "And the second line..."

Xia Fei Kuai frowned.

Fang Yuan continued: "I did not hear it clearly either."

Xia Fei Kuai repeated it and said in an unhappy tone: "Is there anything else?"

"The third line..." Fang Yuan said.

Xia Fei Kuai's eyes were about to bulge out, he said directly: "Pardon my words, but did you not hear the first three sentences? Are you toying with us?"

"Please, you have misunderstood." Fang Yuan waved his hands: "The third line..."

"I heard it clearly."

Xia Zhuo Mo's expression turned dark.

Xia Fei Kuai's brows were lifted high, his eyes were popping, rage showed on his face: "Then what do you want?"

Fang Yuan said: "Actually, the fourth line..."

Xia Fei Kuai waved his hand: "I will say it again, listen closely and carefully."

He talked about it again, this time, he said it very slowly, word by word, it was crystal clear.

Fang Yuan stood up and cupped his fists at Xia Fei Kuai again.

Xia Fei Kuai felt perplexed, he had a bad feeling but he quickly cupped his fists.

He spoke calmly: "Are you clear on it now?"

"Clear, it's clear now. Thank you for explaining, everything makes sense now. Oh, so that is what happened." Fang Yuan patted his forehead, sitting down.

"Thus, your clan has to return Frosty Peak, it is the logical thing to do. Our Xia clan is upholding justice, this Zhang Kai Zui is without doubt the descendant of Zhang San Feng, please test it." Xia Fei Kuai requested again.

But Fang Yuan only took a glance at Zhang Kai Zui before smiling as he waved his hand: "No rush, no rush."

"What is it that do you not understand now?" Xia Fei Kuai's expression was grim, he asked in a dark tone.

"I have troubled you for the description, but was the situation really like this? I cannot confirm it." Fang Yuan said.

Xia Fei Kuai was about to laugh from anger: "I am speaking the truth, you can go ahead and seek verification!"

"Haha." Fang Yuan laughed, clapping his hands together: "You are a straight talker, I will seek verification from my clan."

Saying this, he shut his eyes, as if his consciousness had entered his immortal aperture, to use his information path methods.

After a long time, Fang Yuan did not open his eyes.

Xia Fei Kuai urged him: "Wu Yi Hai, are you done?"

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, he smiled in embarrassment: "Brother is too busy with his work, let's wait a while."

Regarding a rank eight Gu Immortal, Xia Fei Kuai could not say anything, so Xia Zhuo Mo interjected: "Lord Wu Yong is busy indeed, he has no choice. But Wu Yi Hai, you may ask other Wu clan Gu Immortals for verification."

Fang Yuan immediately laughed, giving Xia Zhuo Mo a thumbs up: "Worthy of a wisdom path Gu Immortal indeed, good idea!"

This praise made Xia Zhuo Mo's expression freeze.

Next, Fang Yuan said: "But I am not close with any other Gu Immortal. Do you have any recommendations?"

"Recommend your sister!" Xia Fei Kuai was listening by the side, he shouted out of anger.

"My sister? I only have an elder brother, I have no sister. You must have remembered wrongly?" Fang Yuan smiled while squinting.

"..." Xia Fei Kuai was speechless.

He looked at Xia Zhuo Mo, they communicated with their gazes, they could tell that Fang Yuan was wasting time.

"To think that Wu clan actually sent such a person over! They are too shameless!" Xia Fei Kuai was filled with anger.

He wanted to negotiate properly, but Fang Yuan refused.

And because they were righteous path characters, Xia Fei Kuai could not go overboard.

Seeing Fang Yuan's smiling appearance, he really wanted to throw out a punch and send Fang Yuan plummeting to the ground.

"Don't be anxious, don't be angry, you will fall for his trap. This person is very experienced, he is purposely angering us so we will expose a flaw." Xia Zhuo Mo quickly urged.

Xia Fei Kuai could only breath roughly, taking in huge breaths.

Fang Yuan spoke as he looked at Xia Fei Kuai seriously: "Do I really have a sister? Please let me know."

Xia Fei Kuai: "..."

He took in a few more breaths before he said: "No, it was a slip of the tongue, please do forgive me."

"Oh? Is that so." Fang Yuan nodded, saying in concern: "I see that your tongue is dry, and your chest is moving rapidly, it seems you have symptoms of getting a fever. You need to drink tea, otherwise you will get sick. In fact, this four seasons tea is great, you should take a few more sips."

Xia Zhuo Mo: "..."

Xia Fei Kuai screamed: "Drink what, we are talking about important business!"

Fang Yuan had a solemn expression: "Friend, that is not the right attitude, what do you mean important business? Is being concerned about your health not important business? This Frosty Peak is just a resource point, these are just resources. You cannot fall ill just because of these resources, you will harm yourself."

He urged heartfully, but it seemed to be adding fuel to the fire, Xia Fei Kuai slammed the table angrily.

"Wu Yi Hai!" He screamed: "Don't think that you can deceive us like this, and keep Frosty Peak for your Wu clan. Hmph!"

Fang Yuan's expression quickly changed, saying sincerely: "What are you trying to say? I am innocent. We have to follow the rules for Frosty Peak's matter. This is Zhang San Feng's possession, if this Zhang Kai Zui is a true descendant, we will return it. On behalf of Wu clan, we will do this fair and square, we will not be corrupt, and ruin the rules of the righteous path just for some benefits!"

"You are an understanding person." Xia Zhuo Mo smiled forcefully, saying with deep intentions.

Xia Fei Kuai frowned, he stopped shouting, he said: "That's right, quickly test his bloodline, Zhang Kai Zui really is Zhang San Feng's descendant!"

"No rush, no rush." Fang Yuan smiled and started to drink tea: "Let me seek verification from my clan first, it is not that I do not trust you, but this is a major task, I do not dare to decide recklessly on my own."

"Then quickly verify it!" Xia Fei Kuai shouted.

"But brother Wu Yong has not responded." Fang Yuan looked troubled.

"Then find others!" Xia Fei Kuai shouted.

Fang Yuan slapped his own leg: "That is right, but I just returned to the clan, I do not know anyone else. I am not sure who to find for verification. Earlier, I asked you two to help me, but you gave me no help, I am very troubled too."

Once he said that, the two Xia clan Gu Immortals were shocked, they looked at each other.

After such a long time, giving so many excuses, it was now Xia clan's fault?!

The rank five Gu Master Zhang Kai Zui listened as he stared at Fang Yuan with wide opened eyes.

This was... the demeanor of a Gu Immortal?

He was shameless to the max.

Zhang Kai Zui was awestruck, his good impression of Gu Immortals had shattered completely.

"Forget it, I can tell now, this person is clearly stalling for time." Xia Zhuo Mo transmitted.

"Stalling for what?" Xia Fei Kuai asked.

"Evidently, Wu clan has no justification here, they are in a passive spot. Wu Yi Hai has to continue wasting time here by giving all sorts of excuses. When Wu clan is no longer so tight on manpower, they will be able to deal with us, it will be difficult then. Let alone other matters, when the phoenix birds lay their eggs, Wu Zhen will be free to come here. If he comes, the situation will be different." Xia Zhuo Mo analyzed.

"You are right. What do we do? This Wu Yi Hai is stalling for time, but he speaks so justifiably, we have no way of finding problems with him. There are many ways to stall for time. For example, he needs time to verify this, and he also needs time to test his identity. Then what about after he tests Zhang Kai Zui's bloodline? Will he ask if Zhang San Feng only has one descendant? All these questions will be endless if he wants to bring them up!" Xia Fei Kuai realized the severity of the problem.

"I have a plan." Xia Zhuo Mo said.

"What plan?" Xia Fei Kuai asked quickly.

Xia Zhuo Mo answered, as Xia Fei Kuai became overjoyed, he quickly turned to look at Fang Yuan: "Wu Yi Hai, I have long since heard that you are extremely strong, you are the glory of Wu clan. I would like to represent Xia clan and challenge you to a spar!"

Chapter 1309: Spar

Spar?

That was just a nicer way of talking about resolving the problem by fighting.

But this fight was different from the intense battles of the demonic path. When demonic path members fought, it was mortal combat. For righteous path Gu Immortals, they had a lot of assets, why would they fight to the death? Just deciding a winner was enough.

This was also why Fang Yuan purposely stalled for time, preventing the resolution of Frosty Peak's issue. This forced the two Xia clan Gu Immortals to go on the offense and deal with the matter through force.

The truth was, on Earth, when negotiations fail, stronger countries would send their troops over.

It was the same thing.

Xia Fei Kuai's words were quite interesting, he was representing Xia clan and also claimed Wu Yi Hai to be Wu clan's glory, he said this was a spar, but this was actually a contest between both clans.

Just these words forced Fang Yuan into a corner. If he avoided battle, it would harm Wu clan's reputation, this was something that the righteous path would look down upon, he would be treated as a coward.

But the two from Xia clan did not know that Fang Yuan was not Wu Yi Hai, he did not care about Wu clan's reputation or glory.

However, he was acting as Wu Yi Hai now, he still wanted to go to the super Gu formation, Fang Yuan had to accept this challenge.

He thought briefly before saying: "If it is a spar, both of you will be fighting against me, I am outnumbered, I will definitely lose."

Xia Fei Kuai's expression changed.

These were vicious words!

In fact, requesting for the spar had already caused him to be in a passive spot. If he lost, it would be humiliation. If the two Xia clan Gu Immortals fought together and won, they would be using numbers for an unfair advantage, it would make them lose face, they could not spread news about this.

Actually, Xia Fei Kuai had not thought of fighting together with Xia Zhuo Mo, he said: "I will fight you alone, don't worry."

Fang Yuan had a reluctant expression, he said: "Since you want to spar so urgently, I cannot reject you. But since this is a spar, there has to be a time limit, right, we cannot fight on forever."

"What do you have in mind?" Xia Fei Kuai asked.

Spars had their rules, it was different from a life and death battle.

Fang Yuan said: "You attack and I defend, as long as you can break my defense within ten moves, I lose."

Xia Fei Kuai's eyelids were twitching, he said: "Okay."

Xia Zhuo Mo frowned, he felt something amiss. But since Xia Fei Kuai had already agreed, they might as well spar. He had confidence in Xia Fei Kuai.

Frosty Peak was not the place to fight, destroying it would ruin the point of the task.

Both sides flew to a desolate valley.

Fang Yuan quickly stood opposite Xia Fei Kuai.

"Start." Xia Fei Kuai could not wait, he wanted to teach Fang Yuan a lesson.

Among Southern Border's rank seven Gu Immortals, he was a famous expert. In the entire Wu clan, other than the rank eight Gu Immortal Wu Yong, the strongest rank seven Gu Immortal, Wu Yu Bo, was only slightly superior to him. Now that Wu Yu Bo was in secluded cultivation, who would Xia Fei Kuai fear?

One had to say, getting Immortal Yan Huang to defeat Wu Yu Bo was indeed a well executed move.

In terms of real battle strength, Immortal Yan Huang was not Wu Yu Bo's match, but Xia clan had managed to crack Wu Yu Bo's signature killer move.

Wu Yu Bo was targeted, his immortal killer move was broken and he suffered an intense backlash, causing Immortal Yan Huang to win the battle.

"Wait." Fang Yuan gestured with his hand.

Xia Fei Kuai was ready to fight, Fang Yuan's words made him feel very uncomfortable, he called out: "Wu Yi Hai, what else do you want?"

"I almost forgot, since this is a spar, we can't do it so casually, right?" Fang Yuan smiled.

Xia Fei Kuai thought: "How is it casual? Teaching you a lesson is this battle's most important point!"

He was thinking that, but he could not say it out loud.

Gu Immortals had all sorts of methods to record scenes. Like earlier, when Immortal Yan Huang challenged Wu Yu Bo, Xia clan's Xia Qing Cang recorded everything, it was widely spread over Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

Xia Fei Kuai held in his anger: "What do you want?"

"Simple, if I manage to win, then the status quo for Frosty Peak will remain, it will belong to us." Fang Yuan said.

"How can we do that?!" Xia Zhuo Mo, who was far away, was anxious. He rushed to Xia Fei Kuai and spoke loudly.

Right now, Xia clan was finding trouble, having the descendant of Zhang San Feng, they had justification and a huge advantage, Wu clan was forced into a passive position. If they agreed to this, they would lose their advantage, it was not wise.

Xia Fei Kuai curled his lips, thinking: "I'm not stupid."

At the same time, he rejected: "No way."

"In that case, I cannot fight. This spar is voided." Fang Yuan waved his hand, turning around and walking away.

Xia Fei Kuai almost wanted to curse at him upon seeing this.

We left Frosty Peak and came all this way, after so much trouble, and selecting a proper valley to spar. And now, you want to cancel the fight?

Are you toying with us?

His expression turned grim: "Wu Yi Hai, leaving without fighting, is this the courage and glory of Wu clan?"

Fang Yuan stopped moving.

Xia Fei Kuai smiled coldly.

Fang Yuan turned around, looking at Xia Fei Kuai with a serious expression, saying shamelessly: "You are wrong. I am not avoiding the spar, but you two are not agreeing to my request. Since our negotiation failed, it does not mean I am running away. Look, I even chose the location for it."

"What the f*ck!" These words made Xia Zhuo Mo, who was watching by the side, feel anger.

Xia Fei Kuai stared with furious eyes, he was fuming.

He stared at Fang Yuan fixedly, how could Wu clan produce such a shameless person, weren't Wu clan Gu Immortals brash and usually eager to fight to resolve problems? Where was the bravery and spirit of Wu clan? Where was it!

But soon, Xia Fei Kuai thought of Fang Yuan's origin.

Indeed, Wu Yi Hai was not a Wu clan Gu Immortal from birth, he was a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea.

This damned secluded cultivator!

Fang Yuan showed a deeper smile: "Since we cannot spar, let's continue talking and drinking tea. I have to say, your four seasons tea is really delicious, I am looking forward to it as we speak."

"Drink tea? Talk about what!" Xia Fei Kuai felt an intense urge to strangle Fang Yuan to death in his mind, his chest was burning with rage.

Xia Zhuo Mo looked at Xia Fei Kuai bitterly, thinking: "Weren't you the one who gave him a lot of tea leaves earlier?"

Fang Yuan suddenly muttered to himself before saying: "How about this, if I win, for the next five years, we will maintain the status quo, you will not harp on the Frosty Peak issue, how about that?"

"This..." Xia Zhuo Mo started to ponder over it.

Fang Yuan suddenly raised this condition, compared to before, it was much more acceptable.

"But Wu Yi Hai likely has a plan for giving us this condition." Xia Zhuo Mo was still thinking.

Xia Fei Kuai spoke: "Okay, I agree."

Xia Zhuo Mo was stunned, transmitting: "Lord Xia Fei Kuai, you..."

"Are we going to let this bastard continue wasting time? I will bear full responsibility for this, it has nothing to do with you! I cannot waste so much time, the less time I spend with this guy, the better." Xia Fei Kuai replied resolutely, he had a firm attitude.

Xia Zhuo Mo smiled bitterly.

"If this battle is lost, even if you, Xia Fei Kuai, take responsibility, can I run away from it? The clan sent me here to help you, it was to give you advice, right? Sigh!"

He sighed deeply in his mind, transmitting helplessly: "Then I will hope for lord to emerge victorious!"

"Are you two sure?" Fang Yuan asked.

His condition was just delaying the problem for Wu clan, it did not solve it.

But after five years, Fang Yuan would be done with his matters, by then, who cares about Wu clan?

"We are sure." This time, Xia Fei Kuai did not speak, Xia Zhuo Mo did.

"Okay." Fang Yuan slowly flew back, speaking in an obnoxious way: "Actually, I did not want to spar, it hurts our relationship either way. But Lord Xia Fei Kuai is so insistent, on behalf of the four seasons tea leaves that you gave me, I will agree to this."

"Stop mentioning that tea and fight." Xia Fei Kuai bellowed, his eyes were bloodshot.

Before he finished his words, Fang Yuan's body shined and turned into a divination tortoise.

Xia Fei Kuai was stunned, Fang Yuan was wasting so much time earlier, but he transformed so quickly now, it was quite a contrast.

"Divination tortoise again!" Xia Zhuo Mo frowned.

The divination tortoise's huge body stood in the valley with its four pillar-like legs, it filled up this entire valley.

The entire divination tortoise was dark in color, the shell had all sorts of markings, thousands or tens of thousands of them, they were very eye-catching, Xia Zhuo Mo looked at them for a while before feeling dizzy, he quickly stopped.

Xia Fei Kuai did not expect Fang Yuan to use an immortal killer move now.

Normally, when Gu Immortals spar, they would probe first. Fang Yuan skipped it and used his trump card immediately.

"The tough shell shows this divination tortoise's defensive power. No wonder he chose this style of sparring." Thinking of this, Xia Zhuo Mo frowned even more deeply.

"What do I do?" Xia Fei Kuai hesitated, he did not know what Wu Yi Hai specialized in, but Fang Yuan knew what he was good at.

Xia Fei Kuai only hesitated for a moment, before attacking.

First move.

He raised his fist and clenched it, floating in the sky, he aimed at the divination tortoise in the valley and punched.

His fist shot out light, it was dazzling. Pure white light gathered in Xia Fei Kuai's fist as it turned into a large ball of light, crashing down.

Auras of Immortal Gu and mortal Gu mixed together.

This was an immortal killer move — Soaring Essence Strike.

Chapter 1310: So Embarrassing

Since Fang Yuan had used an immortal killer move, Xia Fei Kuai had no choice but to use an immortal killer move as well.

A pure white ball of light moved with an average speed, not showing any signs of light path's speed advantage.

But as it flew in the air, it pushed the air aside, emitting a buzzing noise.

Boom!

The wine vat sized ball of light smashed down like the weight of a mountain on the divination tortoise's back, smashing the tortoise into the ground.

The enormous divination tortoise had sunken by over a foot in the ground.

Xia Fei Kuai's move was indeed powerful. Light path was famous for speed, but this soaring essence strike of Xia Fei Kuai was the complete opposite, it was like a heavy fist, and the enemies would often be caught off-guard by its powerful strength.

However, Fang Yuan's divination tortoise was perfectly unharmed.

"Huh?" Xia Fei Kuai's eyes almost popped out when he saw the result of his attack.

The divination tortoise was intact with not even a slight dent on it.

This was the obvious result.

Xia Fei Kuai's move used light path to imitate strength path, it was considered a unique move.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan's divination tortoise transformation was a rank seven immortal killer move, which used change form Immortal Gu and divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu as the cores. Especially the latter, just by activating it, Fang Yuan could obtain a tortoise shell that was not weaker than an ancient divination tortoise.

And now, it was an immortal killer move possessing many supplementary Gu worms, the tortoise shell's defensive capability was stronger than a real ancient divination tortoise.

Ancient desolate beasts had extremely strong and sturdy bodies with vigorous vitality, and tortoises were one of the toughest life forms among all living beings.

It was not strange for Xia Fei Kuai's soaring essence strike to show no effect.

But to the person involved, this was slightly ridiculous.

"Soaring essence strike had no effect, he has such a hard shell!" Xia Zhuo Mo was shocked.

Xia Fei Kuai stopped, he started to develop an unfamiliar feeling, that was a headache.

Looking at such a sturdy tortoise shell, he felt a headache and did not know where to start.

In fact, if he had attacked any other area, the result would not have been this bad, but he had to go and choose the hardest part, the tortoise shell. Naturally, this was also because he wanted to probe the depths of Fang Yuan's strength.

"What should I do?" Xia Fei Kuai began to think rapidly.

Although he was irascible, he managed to quickly become cool-headed in the fight.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan activated a second immortal killer move.

Auras of Immortal Gu and mortal Gu rose. Fang Yuan opened his mouth and breathed out countless small tortoise shells.

The small tortoise shells had the same appearance as the divination tortoise's shell, except that they were many times smaller.

The large numbers of small tortoise shells floated in the air, rotating at a very fast speed.

"What are these things?" Xia Fei Kuai stopped thinking and cautiously pulled apart some distance from Fang Yuan.

Boom!

He punched forward with soaring essence strike again.

But this time, the wine vat sized heavy light sphere did not even manage to touch the divination tortoise.

Those small fist sized tortoise shells seemed to be attracted like bees attracted to honey, as they looped towards the soaring essence strike.

Bam bam bam...

The seemingly hard tortoise shells shattered into hundreds of pieces in the collisions.

But the soaring essence strike also was completely consumed, finally turning into a dim fragment of light that helplessly dissipated in the air.

Immortal killer move — Vajra Shell!

This was the immortal killer move Fang Yuan had been perfecting earlier, combined with his divination tortoise transformation. This was the first time it had been displayed in Southern Border and even in the five regions.

The core of this immortal killer move was the rank six Immortal Gu Vajra Thought.

But it was combined with rank seven perseverance Immortal Gu as well as large numbers of mortal Gu.

Its might had naturally increased by a lot, it had not been a waste of Fang Yuan's time and energy.

"Ah! These tortoise shells are actually thoughts." Xia Zhuo Mo's eyes emitted sharp light as he saw through the mystery.

He was a wisdom path Gu Immortal and was very sensitive to all kinds of thoughts. This was the area he was proficient in.

As for Xia Fei Kuai, he cultivated light path, not wisdom path, even though he was rank seven, he only realized after Xia Zhuo Mo's notification.

"Xia Zhuo Mo, you are knowledgeable, the two of you are a good match." The divination tortoise spoke human language, its tone filled with sarcasm.

In fact, Fang Yuan had not intended to conceal it, it was just that after combining with divination tortoise transformation, these golden thoughts turned into dark tortoise shells.

"Little Mo, be quiet, I will break his shell." Xia Fei Kuai said.

Xia Zhuo Mo grunted, but did not speak anymore. Being ridiculed by Fang Yuan had made his expression unsightly.

Xia Fei Kuai closed his eyes.

He began to prepare.

All sorts of Gu worms' auras started brimming and linking up, before quickly spreading.

Red date immortal essence was being consumed rapidly.

At the same time, he spread his arms and slowly put his hands together above his head.

Light surged up like a fountain from him, gathering between his palms.

He was still accumulating energy.

The radiance was restrained, but a powerful aura started rising up, becoming more and more dangerous.

Fang Yuan lowered his tortoise head and firmly rooted his limbs to the ground like a silent dark mountain. But at the same time, the small tortoise shells around him were continuing to fly, their numbers increasing extremely rapidly.

There were close to ten thousand at first, but the numbers soon surpassed twenty thousand, thirty thousand, forty thousand...

Their proliferation was extremely fast.

Rank six vajra thought Immortal Gu could create ten thousand vajra thoughts alone.

As an immortal killer move now, its effect had increased by another level.

The most crucial point was that Fang Yuan's body was filled with wisdom path dao marks right now.

Actually, Fang Yuan did not have many wisdom path dao marks, but he had transformation path dao marks and there were quite a lot of them!

He had killed a lot of transformation path Gu Immortals and annexed all of their dao marks. The most significant harvest was when he had killed Wu Yi Hai and the two immortals inside the regional wall, just this alone gave Fang Yuan close to fifty thousand transformation path dao marks.

One thousand dao marks could double the effect.

Ten thousand dao marks could give ten times the amplification.

Fifty thousand dao marks meant fifty times the amplification.

What did that imply?

Ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals would have about ten thousand to thirty thousand dao marks of their main path.

Xia Fei Kuai was a rank seven expert, his light path dao marks exceeded thirty thousand in number.

But how could they compare to Fang Yuan?

As a result, Xia Fei Kuai and Xia Zhuo Mo could only stare wide-eyed at the rapid proliferation of the small tortoise shells that soon covered the whole valley, and were spreading further, the dark and dense numbers of tortoise shells were like locusts and ants.

Xia Fei Kuai's expression sank.

These small tortoise shells had increased by such a quantity in just a short while, emitting a heavy mental pressure to others.

However, Xia Fei Kuai skillfully used the circumstances of the spar, according to the rule they decided upon, Fang Yuan could only defend and not attack, so Fang Yuan could not take the initiative to use these small tortoise shells to attack Xia Fei Kuai.

Xia Fei Kuai calmed his mind and activated his immortal killer move.

Light path immortal killer move — Saw Light Wheel!

His two hands, that were above his head, chopped down at once.

A dazzling wheel of light flew out from Xia Fei Kuai's palms.

The wheel of light grew rapidly and soon was the size of a boat.

The wheel of light was continuously rotating, its edges were filled with sawteeth.

"Good!" Xia Zhuo Mo inwardly cheered: "The tortoise shells are hard, but this move saws through the target, even if the tortoise shells are very hard, they will still be sliced apart."

However, at the next moment.

Swish swish swish...

Countless tortoise shells flew over.

Crack crack crack...

Under the tortoise shells' self-destructive charge, the saw light wheel could only fly for a short distance before it was completely destroyed.

Xia Zhuo Mo: "..."

Xia Fei Kuai: "..."

Fang Yuan praised loudly: "Great killer move, this move is extraordinary, it actually destroyed over six thousand of my thoughts."

These words were like a slap upon the cheeks of Xia Zhuo Mo and Xia Fei Kuai.

Xia Fei Kuai needed a lot of time to prepare for this immortal killer move.

Normally speaking, the shorter the preparation time for an immortal killer move, the better it was, because if it took longer, it could very easily be disrupted. Once the immortal killer move's activation was disrupted, there would be backlash which often caused heavy injuries to the Gu Immortal.

Xia Fei Kuai had used the sparring rule, and was able to safely activate this immortal killer move.

However!

As he was activating the immortal killer move, Fang Yuan was also doing the same.

Xia Fei Kuai activated saw light wheel.

At the same time, Fang Yuan could create thirty-forty thousand small tortoise shell thoughts.

The outcome was obvious, the saw light wheel was besieged and destroyed by over six thousand small tortoise shell thoughts.

Even a fool could compute the numbers here.

The method which Xia Fei Kuai had placed his hopes in had ended up like this...

This was so embarrassing!

Chapter 1311: Xia Clan Retreats

"Damn it!" Xia Fei Kuai gritted his teeth.

He had taken such efforts to activate saw light wheel, but now it seemed like a joke.

The small tortoise shell-like thoughts were still proliferating.

Fifty thousand, sixty thousand...

Their numbers were increasing rapidly, not only covering the valley, they were even spreading beyond.

Among the dense number of small tortoise shells, some were floating in the air while some were leisurely revolving. In the middle was Fang Yuan's divination tortoise transformation, with its huge body that was like an iron hill.

"I can't let it continue like this!" Xia Fei Kuai was feeling an increasing sense of urgency.

"The speed of growth is too fast. No wonder Wu Yi Hai set this sparring rule, but Lord Xia Fei Kuai still has abilities yet to be used, the outcome of this battle is not certain yet." Xia Zhuo Mo thought, looking at Xia Fei Kuai with anticipation.

Xia Fei Kuai was already preparing his killer move.

Countless Gu worm auras rose and surged outwards.

An arrogant look flashed past his eyes as he looked down at the divination tortoise.

"No matter how numerous, they are only thoughts, what can they do?"

"Take this — Thirty-three Heavenly Lights!"

"Let me see how many layers of heavenly lights can your thoughts stop?"

Immortal killer move — Thirty-three Heavenly Lights!

It was one of the trump cards of Xia Fei Kuai and was renowned throughout Southern Border.

"Is he using it? Lord Xia Fei Kuai's area-of-effect method!" Xia Zhuo Mo was inwardly excited.

This killer move was quite amazing.

Once activated, from Xia Fei Kuai at the center, intense light would shoot out to the surroundings.

Under the illumination of the light, all things would receive light path injuries.

Intense lights would continue to flicker thirty-three times, with the illumination range continuing to increase. They were like lights descending from heaven, therefore it was called thirty-three heavenly lights.

At the first flicker, the heavenly light's damage was not high, it could at most only kill some insects.

But by the second flicker, its damage would increase and it could destroy plants and flowers.

By the third flicker, birds and animals would die when exposed to the light.

By the fourth flicker, large trees would be destroyed and boulders would crumble.

The fifth flicker, sixth flicker....

Like this, the power of the light would continue growing, until it threatened even desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts.

The small tortoise shell thoughts were hard, but they simply could not compare to desolate beasts, they would definitely be destroyed by the thirty-three heavenly lights.

There was no doubt about it.

Xia Fei Kuai was taking the easy route by using this move.

Thirty-three heavenly lights was actually not practical, because once it was activated, the Gu Immortal had to stop moving, if they budged even a little, the killer move would immediately stop.

Xia Fei Kuai would even suffer backlash.

Naturally, the level of backlash also had differences.

If the killer move was stopped before the tenth flicker, Xia Fei Kuai would suffer light injuries, stopping in-between the tenth to twenty-third flicker would inflict medium injuries, and stopping after the twenty-third flicker would cause heavy injuries. After the thirtieth flicker, the backlash would be even stronger, and Xia Fei Kuai might suffer fatal injuries.

The stronger the immortal killer move, the greater the danger from the backlash once its activation failed.

Soon, the light burst forth!

At the first flicker, Fang Yuan's tortoise shell thoughts remained unmoved.

Second flicker, the thoughts were still growing and did not seem to stop.

Third flicker, the thoughts started shaking.

Forth flicker, some thoughts started to crumble apart by themselves.

Fifth flicker, hundreds of thoughts collapsed into nothingness.

Xia Zhuo Mo, who was watching from the side, could not help but smile at this scene.

This was only the fifth flicker.

The immortal killer move altogether had thirty-three flickers.

"But why am I still feeling some unease?" Xia Zhuo Mo pondered.

Sixth flicker, a thousand thoughts were destroyed, the tortoise shells on the periphery started to show signs of collapse.

"Seventh flicker, time to deal with you!" Xia Fei Kuai sneered inwardly.

But, right at this moment.

Swoosh!

Seventy-eighty thousand small tortoise shell thoughts suddenly surged towards Fang Yuan like a tide.

More accurately, they entered his mind.

The divination tortoise he had transformed into was a wisdom path ancient desolate beast, its mind was incomparably spacious and holding seventy-eighty thousand thoughts was nothing to it.

"What?" Xia Fei Kuai was stunned.

Xia Zhuo Mo patted his head as he hatefully exclaimed inwardly: "I finally understand what made me uneasy! These small tortoise shells are thoughts in essence, since they are thoughts, the Gu Immortal can store them back inside their mind."

As a result, the seventy-eight thousand thoughts that filled the valley had completely disappeared and withdrawn into Fang Yuan's mind.

Only an enormous divination tortoise was left, quietly lying on the ground.

In the air, Xia Fei Kuai's immortal killer move still continued.

Seventh flicker!

Eight flicker.

Ninth flicker....

But there were no thoughts, there was no meaning to these powerful lights.

However, the immortal killer move was still in the activation process and could not be carelessly stopped.

As such, Xia Fei Kuai could only continue to activate the killer move. Tenth flicker, eleventh, twelfth....

It was an extremely awkward situation.

After the thirty-third flicker, Xia Fei Kuai had spent a large amount of immortal essence, while the divination tortoise hid inside its shell, motionless on the ground.

The mountain valley he was inside had now been turned into a flat land.

Thirty-three heavenly lights was indeed powerful, it forcefully changed a vast surrounding area into a flat plain. The hills from before were completely gone.

"This killer move is truly powerful." Fang Yuan did not stint on his praise.

While speaking, he stretched out his head, tail and limbs from inside the shell.

These parts were not as strong as the tortoise shell, so during the stronger flickers, Fang Yuan hid inside, suffering no injuries.

Hearing Fang Yuan's praise, Xia Fei Kuai immediately felt incomparably stifled.

"Too shameless!" Xia Zhuo Mo gritted his teeth, looking at Fang Yuan hatefully.

This was especially the case when he saw over a hundred thousand small tortoise shell thoughts surge out of Fang Yuan's mind and spread out, surrounding the divination tortoise. The hatred and fury in his eyes deepened by several degrees.

"How are we supposed to break his defense?" The two Gu Immortals of Xia clan were pondering over this difficulty.

"You have used three moves." Fang Yuan indifferently reminded.

Xia Fei Kuai shouted: "Then take my following move!!"

As he said so, he turned into a ray of light and pounced forward, attacking the divination tortoise from all directions. Countless tortoise shell thoughts were destroyed as they moved to defend him.

But Xia Fei Kuai displayed an expert's demeanor, he moved back and forth around the thoughts, and could not be stopped.

Fang Yuan saw that Xia Fei Kuai was serious and going at full force, he withdrew his head, tail and limbs back inside the shell.

Xia Fei Kuai was stifled.

This Wu Yi Hai was too wretched, leaving behind only the shell for him to target. A gigantic tortoise shell on the ground and countless small tortoise shells in the air, Xia Fei Kuai was increasingly beginning to feel hatred for tortoise shells.

The tenth move was over, Xia Fei Kuai's efforts gave no result, while only some slight injury marks had appeared on Fang Yuan's tortoise shell.

"You win this time." Xia Fei Kuai directly left the scene with this sentence, flying into the sky.

Xia Zhuo Mo, who was left behind, sighed, he had to clear the mess; at least, he had to take away that Gu Master Zhang.

"Five years. After five years, I will have to come back and find you." Xia Zhuo Mo also left, feeling somewhat indignant.

Chapter 1312: Ransacking Frosty Peak

Xia clan's Gu Immortals lost the spar and left without making a fuss.

Fang Yuan stopped his transformation and returned to human form, returning to Frosty Peak.

The mortal Gu house at Frosty Peak was taken away, now only a snowy mountain remained with cold air emanating everywhere.

Fang Yuan sighed softly.

His heart was calm, like a well without a ripple. Victories were not worth him treasuring and bragging. The so-called sense of glory had already left him long ago.

"For such an easy victory to have happened, it is because I had the advantage."

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

The two Xia clan Gu Immortals did not know Fang Yuan's strength, they could only estimate it. On the contrary, Fang Yuan knew a lot about them. Whether it be their killer moves, temperament or so on, he was thoroughly aware of them with the information from Wu clan.

One could see how important information was in a battle between Gu Immortals!

In fact, Fang Yuan's spar with the Xia clan Gu Immortals was like Immortal Yan Huang defeating Wu Yu Bo.

Both won due to better intel.

Wu Yu Bo was powerful, but his trump card killer move was seen through by others, as a result, one careless move and all was lost.

Fang Yuan had even more information, he advanced step by step through his layers of planning, finally making the Xia clan Gu Immortals retreat.

"Immortal killer move vajra shell is quite effective. But it won't be easy to have such a good result in the future."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals would definitely compile their experiences and insights to think of a way to restrict or even decipher and counter vajra shell.

Deciphering and countering was difficult, but creating a restrictive method was often easy.

"Wu Yi Hai will also become more famous."

"This divination tortoise transformation and immortal killer move vajra shell are quite remarkable. But once I use them a lot of times, there is a high chance someone will find a way to restrict or even nullify it."

"Actually, the same applies to reverse flow protection seal, after the battle in Northern Plains, it is definitely being analyzed by the ten great ancient sects, Longevity Heaven, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and others. I should be somewhat careful the next time I use it, especially against these people."

Fang Yuan was vigilant.

Wu Yu Bo was a clear example to him.

It was not easy to create an immortal killer move, but a powerful immortal killer move could not remain stagnant, it needed to be advanced and modified along with time, as such, when others use restrictive measures or even fully resolved your killer move, you could effectively face them.

But modifying and advancing an immortal killer move was naturally also a difficult matter.

Other than a burst of inspiration, what was truly put to test was the Gu Immortal's attainment level.

"And the best way to raise one's attainment level is through dream realms." Fang Yuan's thoughts could not help but turn towards that giant dream realm again.

Because of the widespread emergence of dream realms, there were all kinds of characters emerging one after the other during the five regions chaotic war in Fang Yuan's previous life, creating a great era filled with chaos and disorder.

"Unfortunately, it has not been long since I joined Wu clan, making a firm request to go to the super Gu formation would be suspicious."

"Although the matter of this Frosty Peak has ended, who knows when I can go back to the giant dream realm. It is better to deal with the matters at hand and otherwise go with the flow."

Fang Yuan pondered while landing on Frosty Peak.

This mountain peak was abundant in ice path resources, he still had not properly searched it.

Fang Yuan had gotten this rare opportunity after chasing away the Xia clan Gu Immortals, he naturally would not give it up.

Snow filled Frosty Peak and the air was frighteningly cold.

In the depths of this accumulated snow dwelled large numbers of insects, including many wild Gu worms, as well as cold-resistant vegetation. They mutually formed a balanced ecology.

"Frost jades." Fang Yuan soon had harvests.

A large number of frost jades appeared in his investigative perception.

These frost jades were hidden below the thick snow, below the rocky ground.

"Frost jades are only a rank five Gu material, but they have some frost jade essence inside, which is a rank six immortal material."

Without any hesitation, Fang Yuan began collecting them!

Rumble!

The snow splattered everywhere, revealing the bare surface of the rocky ground.

Soon, these rocks also flew everywhere and revealed the frost jades hidden in the mountain.

These frost jades were white, with some green hue mixed within. They released intense frost energy, but naturally they were harmless to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan picked up the frost jades in this area.

Fang Yuan naturally did not give up the frost jade essence inside, it was just that he did not extract them and they were still inside the center of the giant frost jades.

Next, Fang Yuan started searching throughout Frosty Peak.

Enormous frost jades were dug out one after the other. The smallest frost jade was already the size of an elephant, while the bigger ones were the size of large ships.

Almost every frost jade had frost jade essence inside it.

Some frost jade essences were bigger, and there were even thousand year frost jade essences, which were rank seven Gu materials.

It was not that no one had discovered these frost jades, but they were intentionally preserved by Wu clan to maintain the foundation of this Frosty Peak. It was these frost jades that formed the foundation of Frosty Peak, without them, Frosty Peak would not be such a special and remarkable resource point.

Fang Yuan took away most of the frost jades.

Not only this, he also plundered many wild Gu worms.

There was no need to think about Immortal Gu.

Normally speaking, Frosty Peak could only produce rank six Immortal Gu once in several hundred years to a thousand years.

If there were really wild Immortal Gu, Xia clan's Gu Immortals would not have accepted their defeat so easily.

The majority of these Gu worms were of ice path, there were also some of earth path and water path. Among the ice path Gu worms, most of them were called cold wave Gu.

This type of Gu worm formed groups and would often roam around in Frosty Peak. Thus, a severe wave of cold would spread out from Frosty Peak.

This was also the reason for Frosty Peak's name.

After he finished plundering, Fang Yuan flew to the air and took a last glance at this Frosty Peak.

The picturesque Frosty Peak filled with white snow was now filled with pits of different depths, with rocks and debris filling the area.

Not only was the scenery destroyed, the value of resources in Frosty Peak had dropped by over half, and because of the huge deficit, Frosty Peak's foundation was greatly damaged.

"If I use pulling mountain Immortal Gu, I might be able to pull this mountain and store it in my sovereign blessed land."

"Unfortunately, I can't do that at the moment. My identity is Wu Yi Hai, a Wu clan member, I made huge profits this time by embezzlement, this has already reached the limits of the righteous path's unwritten rules and cannot be continued. If I really pulled the mountain, not to mention exposing my true identity, I definitely cannot justify my actions to Wu clan."

Fang Yuan inwardly sighed and did not dwell on this as he flew away rapidly.

Soon, his figure disappeared in the clouds.

Several days later, Fang Yuan returned to Wu clan's headquarters and met Wu Yong.

"It is all thanks to you, brother, for protecting Frosty Peak for the clan and deterring those thieves." Wu Yong revealed an appreciative look towards Fang Yuan.

"You flatter me, it was only a fluke." Fang Yuan replied modestly.

"Elder Wu Fa, have you evaluated it? My brother's contribution was not a simple one, we should think in the perspective of the bigger picture." Wu Yong turned towards another Wu clan Gu Immortal.

This Wu clan Gu Immortal had an ordinary appearance but his status was anything but ordinary.

He was Wu Yong's trusted aide and was in charge of calculating the rewards and punishments for all the Gu Immortals in the clan.

Wu Fa spoke with a slight frown: "We have already seen Lord Wu Yi Hai's bravery. With this battle, lord's name will definitely spread throughout Southern Border's Gu Immortal world. But if we talk about rewards, on one hand, Lord Wu Yi Hai has not completely settled this problem and only set a five year agreement, on the other hand, Frosty Peak has been viciously plundered, its foundation has been damaged and its value has greatly reduced..."

"Oh? Such a thing happened to Frosty Peak?" Wu Yong turned towards Fang Yuan with a surprised look.

Fang Yuan sighed: "I also did not expect Xia clan's Gu Immortals to be such horrible people!"

Wu Yong frowned slightly: "Brother, did you personally see Xia clan's Gu Immortals looting Frosty Peak?"

"I did not, it is just my guess. Maybe it was other lone cultivators?" Fang Yuan replied with no flaw in his argument.

Wu Yong nodded and spoke after a brief silence: "Since that is the case, Elder Wu Fa shall make the final decision."

Elder Wu Fa calculated for a while before giving a detailed list to Fang Yuan.

Chapter 1313: Dragon Scale Sea Area

Fang Yuan took the list and skimmed through it, the list was filled with various kinds of Gu materials, most of them were naturally mortal Gu materials, but there were a few immortal materials as well.

Fang Yuan was well aware that if he had handed the frost jades, the frost jade essences and so on, the reward would not just be this.

Wu Yong and Wu Fa were actually acting now, they were not scheming against Fang Yuan, but giving Fang Yuan a way to resolve this issue peacefully.

Fang Yuan had plundered Frosty Peak, although it did not cross the bottom line, Wu clan would rather have an intact Frosty Peak.

Fang Yuan, however, seemed to not know this and was silent for a while before he replied: "I wonder if I can exchange these rewards for a mortal Gu material, dragon scale soil?"

Wu Yong was slightly stumped, and looked at Wu Fa.

The latter thought briefly and nodded.

Returning to his home, Fang Yuan continued to cultivate.

This time, he had obtained a lot of frost jades and frost jade essence, Fang Yuan might even be able to build a Mini Frosty Peak in Mini Southern Border within his sovereign immortal aperture.

But this was not the important point.

The important point was the dragon scale soil.

This special type of soil was only an ordinary Gu material, grainy and tough. If a layer of dragon scale soil was viewed from afar, it would resemble overlapping dragon scales.

Dragon scale soil was the soil that dragon type desolate beasts, ancient desolate dragons, or even immemorial desolate dragons lived on, thus it had the aura of dragons.

Fang Yuan had purchased this soil before, because this soil gave his dragonfish greater impulse to propagate.

Right now, he did not take the other rewards, instead exchanging them for this Gu material because he had the same idea.

"The rate of time in the sovereign immortal aperture has slowed down by many times, this has led to a huge decrease in the production of resources."

"I don't have enough immortal essence reserves currently, the same goes for immortal essence stones, but the pressure in this aspect can be relieved if I expand the scale of my resource production."

After Fang Yuan thought over it, he set dragonfish as the first resource point to be expanded.

Desolate beast dragonfish as well as ordinary dragonfish were always traded in huge numbers in treasure yellow heaven.

Dragonfish seemed to be a product of food path, they could be used as supplementary ingredients to feed many Gu worms.

Not every Gu Immortal possessed Immortal Gu.

But every super force would purchase large numbers of dragonfish at set intervals of time.

The dragonfish trade was one of the largest markets in treasure yellow heaven.

During the following period of time, Fang Yuan would mainly concentrate on creating a sea area.

Currently, Mini Eastern Sea of the sovereign immortal aperture was no longer filled with shallow pools and lakes like before. Because Fang Yuan had annexed large numbers of water path immortal apertures, Mini Eastern Sea was filled with raging waves, although the water level was not deep, it was a boundless aquatic expanse.

There were almost no islands, and sea areas themselves were indistinguishable.

Fang Yuan's plan was to construct a dragon scale sea area.

A man-made sea area!

This was not Fang Yuan's innovation or creation. In fact, there were many Gu Immortals in Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world creating man-made sea areas.

On the current ranking list for Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world, many famous sea areas were man-made, built step by step.

Of course, the naturally formed sea areas still held most of the positions in the ranking.

Constructing a sea area artificially was not easy.

Fang Yuan spent a large amount of time and energy to lay out the dragon scale soil, then he constructed a mortal Gu formation in that area and used the Gu formation's power to isolate this sea area and make it a special sea area.

Then, he led his dragonfish group to this sea area.

The dragonfish group was indeed more satisfied in this sea area, and there was a lot more mating.

However, this was not enough.

Next, Fang Yuan started to prepared an immortal killer move — Bountiful Year!

This immortal killer move came from Hei Fan's true inheritance, but as a matter of fact, Hei Fan did not create it, he had traded for it with a Gu Immortal great expert named Pill Immortal.

He created this immortal killer move, and Hei Fan had exchanged for it with other resources.

This was a quite rare killer move, as it was an immortal killer move that was specially used to manage the immortal aperture and did not have any offensive ability.

But its practicality was extremely high, even Hei Fan had left words of praise towards this immortal killer move in his true inheritance.

Gu worms rose one after the other, a mysterious aura swelled up and gradually thickened.

The bountiful year Fang Yuan was using right now had gone through some modifications.

The original bountiful year's core Immortal Gu was year Gu, with tens of thousands of supplementary Gu worms. But now, Fang Yuan had obtained a rank seven Immortal Gu - Perseverance, and he ingeniously added perseverance Immortal Gu into the killer move as the first supplementary Gu worm.

More than ten days later, bountiful year was fully activated.

A mysterious power spread throughout the whole dragon scale sea area, but its effects would take some time to be seen.

"Even Hei Fan required two to three days of time to activate the original bountiful year. This is already quite long. After I modified it by adding in perseverance Immortal Gu,the time required has become even longer, approaching half a month. Fortunately, the activation succeeded and there was no backlash."

Fang Yuan constantly reflected on his experiences.

"My time path attainment level is still ordinary, I was barely able to add in perseverance Immortal Gu. This is the main reason for the enormous extension of time."

The shorter the activation of an immortal killer move, the simpler the process, the higher the probability of the killer move's successful activation. And, as far as Gu Immortals were concerned, it was safer.

However, Fang Yuan's action had more advantages than disadvantages.

With perseverance Immortal Gu's support, the duration of bountiful year's effect had doubled!

The original bountiful year could only influence the immortal aperture for a year. But now, a single activation from Fang Yuan could last for two years. This had also covertly saved Fang Yuan a portion of red date immortal essence.

"There is still plenty of room for improvement in bountiful year. Adding in perseverance Immortal Gu along with day Immortal Gu could raise bountiful year's effect. But, with my current attainment level in time path, I have reached my limit. Forget it!"

The matter was settled, this construction was Fang Yuan's first big project.

Right now, in Mini Eastern Sea, the first special sea area — dragon scale sea area, had completely formed.

Large numbers of dragonfish lived here, and there were one or two extremely conspicuous desolate beast dragonfish among the dragonfish group.

Bountiful year's effect did not just cover the dragon scale sea area, it also included a vast range of this sea area's surroundings.

According to what was written in Hei Fan's true inheritance: The expenditure of immortal essence to activate bountiful year was huge, but for the next year, starting right from the moment of successful activation of the killer move, all of the resources inside the immortal aperture would be produced at a higher rate!

However, the result was not like this.

Fang Yuan's bountiful year's effect only covered a portion of Mini Eastern Sea.

On one hand, this was because Fang Yuan had added perseverance Immortal Gu, which reduced the effective range of the killer move. On the other hand, the sovereign immortal aperture was simply too vast, wanting bountiful year to cover the whole sovereign immortal aperture was no different to a fairy tale.

From dragon scale lake to dragon scale sea, this was an enormous leap, and its significant was profound.

But after this project, Fang Yuan's immortal essence stones and immortal essence reserves were almost dried up.

To be safe, Fang Yuan began to sell all the unnecessary resources in his possession.

Like the frost jades and frost jade essences he had plundered in Frosty Peak, as well as large numbers of ice path mortal Gu.

Where there are gains, there are losses. His current management focus was on dragonfish.

After selling some resources, Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, he used a portion of the gains to buy many dragonfish from treasure yellow heaven.

He placed these dragonfish in dragon scale sea area.

One could say he was staking a lot on this project.

No doubt, this had some risks. But if he went at it safely, the efficiency would be lower. Moreover, he was in a safe and stable environment right now, so Fang Yuan chose to be slightly aggressive and took bigger steps.

But like this, because his immortal essence reserves had become scarce, Fang Yuan appeared to have his hands tied, not being able to casually cultivate, comprehend, train any immortal killer moves and so on.

Days seemed to pass with difficulty.

After half a month, the first batch of dragonfish was sold, the situation began to turn for the better.

After over a month, Fang Yuan sold the second batch of dragonfish directly to Wu clan!

"Who could have thought you would be so proficient in managing dragonfish!" Even Wu Yong was slightly surprised.

Wu clan did transactions of dragonfish to begin with, but previously, they had to buy from outside, now, they could be considered internal sales.

Besides Wu clan, there were also Qiao clan and some other super forces which had close relations with Wu clan.

Fang Yuan's third batch of dragonfish was sold.

Because of his identity as Wu Yi Hai and the low price, Fang Yuan's dragonfish smoothly entered the market of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

After the third batch of dragonfish was sold, Fang Yuan's situation had turned a lot better, his immortal essence reserves were expanding bit by bit. Fang Yuan was out of his financial predicament, and started to continue his cultivation with a brand new stance.

Chapter 1314: Purchasing Divine Deer Fruits

Southern Border, Wu clan.

In a secret cultivation room, Fang Yuan was floating in the air, his expression solemn.

His long hair was fluttering in the air, and all kinds of Gu worm auras rose from his body, mixing with each other.

"The crucial step..." Fang Yuan mumbled, his gaze turning sharp.

He carefully activated a mortal Gu.

This was a metal path mortal Gu and was only rank one.

Activating just this Gu alone naturally had no risks. But the situation now was different.

Bam.

A muffled sound spread from Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan's body shook violently like he had been electrocuted, his expression was pale and a trace of blood flowed out from the corners of his lips.

"I failed again." He heaved a long sigh.

He landed on the ground and held his chest while checking his injuries.

"Fortunately, I only used a rank one mortal Gu, these injuries are not much of a problem and there is no need to use Man as Before. I will recover in a couple of days with the sovereign immortal body's recovery speed."

Fang Yuan was attempting to further improve the killer move vajra shell.

Immortal killer move vajra shell used rank six Vajra Thought as a core. Fang Yuan had relied on this killer move and strategy to defeat Xia clan's Gu Immortal, Xia Fei Kuai.

After the matter, Fang Yuan had felt this killer move was still not satisfying enough and still had room for improvement.

Fang Yuan paid attention to this feeling.

He knew his wisdom path and transformation path were both at grandmaster level, such a feeling did not emerge from nowhere and had great value to him.

"Unfortunately, although I have made some progress over these days, there have been little to no results. It seems my attainment level is still not enough, I can only let it be for now."

Fang Yuan let out a sigh.

In fact, his speed of progress was extremely remarkable compared to other Gu Immortals.

In the past, Vicious Lightning Fiend had used up several years to deduce the immortal killer move lightning deity. He was not even at ten percent of Fang Yuan's current speed.

However, it was also a wise choice for Fang Yuan to give up.

Because he had a way to rapidly raise his attainment, as long as he raised his attainment levels, he could improve the killer move vajra shell at once.

After Fang Yuan's transactions of dragonfish, his financial condition had improved, and as such, he had spare energy to try modifying immortal killer moves.

Deducing an immortal killer move was actually very resource consuming. For instance, if the attempt failed, Gu Immortal could suffer backlash and be injured. Gu worms would also be destroyed and would need to be replenished. And if Immortal Gu were damaged, that would be even more troublesome.

But if the attainment level was enough, the killer move could be improved at once, saving large amounts of time, effort and resources.

Fang Yuan's attainment level barely met the requirements of improving vajra shell, although he could improve it, he would have to pay quite a heavy price.

He thought it over and resolutely gave up on this small project.

After resting for a while, Fang Yuan activated his Gu worms and sent his divine sense into treasure yellow heaven.

Inside treasure yellow heaven, his divine sense moved nimbly and reached a Gu Immortal's will to converse.

"I will pay one thousand three hundred immortal essence stones for all your divine deer fruits." Fang Yuan spoke.

This Gu Immortal will's shook its head and said helplessly: "The price I quoted is already low. You have already come here three times, if you really want to buy, add two hundred immortal essence stones and you can take them away."

Divine deer fruits were rank six immortal material.

It was not a rare Gu material, but there were few people who sold it because there was not much demand for it.

Fang Yuan, however, needed it to feed vajra thought Immortal Gu.

He had obtained vajra thought Immortal Gu and had to solve its feeding problem.

Fang Yuan did not reply, instead, he sized up the products.

The divine deer fruits in this stall were of good quality, Fang Yuan had strolled several times around treasure yellow heaven and had found the divine deer fruits here were of top quality.

The price was also quite reasonable.

Thus, he had visited this stall several times.

Divine deer fruits were about the size of a baby's fist and did not grow on trees or plants, instead growing on the antlers of a type of deer desolate beast, fruit deer.

It was a deer that bore fruit.

Fang Yuan had already inquired about the specific name of this desolate beast, and also saw them being sold in treasure yellow heaven.

However, even if he bought a batch of them, the number of divine deer fruits they could produce was a question that needed to be explored.

Any resource had its own cultivation methods.

For instance, Fang Yuan's dragonfish production was not a result of casual attempts, but was from the insights and experiences of Dong Fang tribe.

This was the accumulation of a super tribe. As a result, Fang Yuan's dragonfish were of the best quality, and the production was also smooth, giving higher profits while requiring slightly lower capital.

"I should just buy a portion of divine deer fruits for now to deal with the first feeding of vajra thought Immortal Gu."

"When I have sufficient funds in the future, I can consider how to raise fruit deers and be able to be self-sufficiently provide for vajra thought Immortal Gu."

"As for whether I can turn this divine deer fruit's production into another source of income, that would depend on future opportunities."

Fang Yuan pondered while communicating with that Gu Immortal will: "Then, let me check again."

But at this time, the Gu Immortal will in front of Fang Yuan suddenly shook and spoke: "My main body's divine sense has entered, he says he can discuss the price with you. You should talk it out between yourselves."

Saying this, the Gu Immortal's will took a back seat.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

He was waiting for this situation.

The Gu Immortal who was selling the divine deer fruits had left the divine deer fruits in treasure yellow heaven and also left a will to look after them.

But although this will could think and communicate, it had to strictly abide by the bottom-line price set by its main body, and this was not negotiable.

But now that the Gu Immortal's divine sense had come over, Fang Yuan could properly communicate with him about many things.

There were many contents up for discussion.

"I want the divine deer fruits to feed Immortal Gu."

"If we can reach a consensus, this absolutely won't be the last transaction."

"How about it? I will offer one thousand three hundred immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan started to negotiate.

The Gu Immortal hesitated: "This is our first interaction, how can I believe you based on just empty promises? Hehehe, forget it, we can reach a deal for one thousand four hundred immortal essence stones."

"Once we have transacted three times like this, the price can be lowered to one thousand three hundred. What do you think?"

Clearly, this Gu Immortal was not foolish and was quite astute.

Fang Yuan refused: "If I had ample funds, I would not be haggling with you like this. How about one thousand three hundred and fifty?"

That Gu Immortal forced a smile: "Alright. If not for my urgent need for funds and the fact that these divine deer fruits are selling slowly, I would not have agreed to your price."

One gave the money and the other handed the goods.

Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief after the transaction was completed. The feeding problem of vajra thought Immortal Gu was settled for the moment.

Now, it was divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu's turn.

This Immortal Gu fed on kelp.

Naturally, it was not common kelp, but ancient ink kelp, which was a rank six immortal material.

This kelp was complete black like ink, and when its skin was torn, it would dye the surrounding water into pitch-black ink.

Fang Yuan was currently short on funds, so he intended to purchase and store some ancient ink kelps to feed divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu.

He would consider more in the future.

In the aspect of food, day Immortal Gu was much more pleasant. Because it fed on the water of the River of Time, there was no need to think about obtaining its food.

In comparison to divine deer fruits, there were many more sellers of ancient ink kelps in treasure yellow heaven.

But Fang Yuan was not able to make a deal with any of them.

The issue was the price.

But he was not in a hurry, there was still some time left before the next feeding of divination tortoise shell Immortal Gu.

"Fortunately, dragon scale sea area's construction is finished, as long as it continues to develop like this, I will have plenty of funds in the future."

"Next is the construction of coiling thread caves to produce regretful spiders on a large scale."

Fang Yuan had considered it, the market for regretful spiders was huge, especially over in Western Desert. Although the demand was not as large as dragonfish, it was still a lot.

But for the moment, Fang Yuan was tight on funds and needed some time to accumulate his wealth before he could start this project.

"According to this situation, I estimate that it will be over a month before I am able to gather the first sum of funds and start on the construction of coiling thread caves."

"Hopefully, Wu clan would have stabilized by then and would let me return to the giant dream realm."

Wu Yi Hai's identity restricted Fang Yuan's freedom. Especially under the current situation of Wu clan, it was not good for him to voice out his intention.

Over the course of this month, Wu Yong had led Wu clan to deal with the problems created by the various super forces. There were losses and gains, Wu clan's prestige sank, but in truth, there was not much damage to their benefits.

Thus, this situation was still continuing.

Wu Yong wanted to regain their reputation, while other super forces were not satisfied and wanted to seize some material benefits.

The confrontation between righteous path forces was different from the demonic path.

Confrontations in the demonic path were fierce and violent, while righteous path confrontations were light like drizzle and often lasted for a long time. Especially when it was a confrontation between super forces with huge assets, it was difficult for them to fight against each other without reservations, they would not fight to the death.

Fang Yuan's idle cultivation lifestyle did not last for long.

Some days later, he received another task from Wu Yong.

"Mount Snail? Mountain Moving Old Monster?"

Fang Yuan's brows slowly started to furrow.

It was not that he did not have the confidence to complete this task, but the current trend of situations was not looking good.

Previously, though Fang Yuan had resolved Frosty Peak's matter, he had in fact withheld his strength and methods, obtaining a barely passable result. He had only created an agreement of five years and had plundered the resources of Frosty Peak.

Although this was an unwritten rule of the righteous path, he had touched the bottom-line.

This was naturally Fang Yuan's intent, to leave a bad impression on Wu Yong. Higher-ups did not like using such people, and if they sent Fang Yuan away to the super Gu formation earlier, it would match Fang Yuan's wish.

But Wu clan was indeed short on manpower at present, while its territory was too large. A matter concerning Mount Snail had happened suddenly, Wu Yong had no choice but to use Fang Yuan to deal with this problem.

Chapter 1315: Convincing Old Monster

Southern Border.

Light rain was drizzling on a range of verdant mountains.

Fang Yuan wore a blue robe, and was gazing at these grand rivers and mountains from atop a rock, before his gaze finally settled on a mountain.

This mountain was rather special.

The mountain peaks beside it were either tall or short, steep or slanted.

But this mountain was round in shape.

This was Mount Snail.

Or it could be considered a snail mountain.

It was an immemorial desolate beast! It was an enormous river snail with a tall, tower-like spiral shell drenched with green moss.

When it stayed still, its body would hide in the shell, looking like a towering mountain.

Right now, it was awake and was slowly moving.

Rumble...

As it moved, all the surroundings quaked slightly, birds and beasts fled in disorder.

Fang Yuan was calmly looking at the movement of this immemorial desolate beast, Mount Snail, from another mountain peak.

Its speed was slow.

Mount Snail might be an immemorial desolate beast, but its temperament was simple and mild, it was hard to anger it, it could even be said to be harmless.

Not only harmless, it also provided benefits.

Because Mount Snail's body was full of enslavement path and earth path dao marks, which created a special environment around it that would spawn many enslavement path and earth path resources.

Mount Snail's ownership had all the while been an unsettled issue.

Few Gu Immortals could control Mount Snail, it was very difficult for even rank eight enslavement path Gu Immortals.

Because Mount Snail itself was full of enslavement path dao marks.

There were already seven known Mount Snails in Southern Border. Long ago, Southern Border's super forces had set an agreement: As long as these Mount Snails were not controlled by anyone, that is to say, they were wild Mount Snails, they would be considered as a resource of the clan whose territory it was staying in.

This Mount Snail was originally living in Wu clan's territory, naturally it belonged to Wu clan.

There was no doubt about this.

But now, it was time for the Mount Snail's migration, it was currently leaving Wu clan's territory for other territories.

Mount Snail's original location was at the periphery of Wu clan's territory.

In fact, during Wu Du Xiu's time, Wu clan had intentionally expanded their territory to include this Mount Snail.

Currently, Mount Snail was leaving Wu clan's territory, but the place it was going to did not have other righteous path super forces.

This also meant this Mount Snail was going to become wild again.

Wu Yong naturally did not want to see such a situation happening, and under the situation where he did not have enough manpower, without other options, he could only assign this task to his younger brother, Wu Yi Hai.

"Wu Yi Hai? I am Qin Jin Sheng, I am also called Mountain Moving Old Monster." A Gu Immortal flew over from another mountain peak.

Fang Yuan gazed at the Gu Immortal.

This old Gu Immortal was adorned in a suit of rocky grey armor, his hair was a mix of black and white, looking messy like straws. He looked slovenly, with the corners of his clothes being in shreds.

But the rank seven aura he gave out was majestic and forceful, especially his eyes which shone with sharp light. Right now, as he looked at Fang Yuan, it was like a senior sizing up a junior.

"It is me indeed, Wu Yi Hai, I greet Senior Mountain Moving." Fang Yuan bowed slightly, his greeting had the style of the righteous path.

This Mountain Moving Old Monster's title had 'old' in it, it naturally was because he was an old veteran, an old senior, having lived for over two thousand years.

He had lifespan Gu and also had unique lifespan extension methods.

His battle strength was also very high and he was a famous expert among lone immortals, almost at the level of Old Treeman Ba De and Wu clan's Wu Yu Bo.

Rank seven Gu Immortals like Xia Fei Kuai could not compare to Mountain Moving Old Monster.

Thus, when Mountain Moving Old Monster sized up Fang Yuan, he was not humble and treated himself as a senior, even if Fang Yuan came from Wu clan.

"Hehehe, considering the time, it was time your Wu clan sent someone as well. Let's sit and talk." Mountain Moving Old Monster laughed and sat on a rock.

Fang Yuan smiled and also sat down.

Mountain Moving Old Monster saw that Fang Yuan had no objection to sitting on a rock and also did not have a high-and-mighty attitude, his impression of Fang Yuan improved: "I almost forgot you were a lone cultivator, although you have joined Wu clan, you don't have the hypocritical attitude of those righteous path members."

Fang Yuan slightly shook his head: "The righteous path has to act like the righteous path, as for me, I spent most of my time as a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea, these habits cannot be changed."

"Hahaha." Mountain Moving Old Monster laughed heartily, "I hear you chased away the two Gu Immortals from Xia clan, but plundered the resources of Frosty Peak."

Fang Yuan revealed a surprised expression: "Senior, these are groundless rumors, I have never stated that."

Mountain Moving Old Monster laughed loudly, before heaving a deep sigh: "The righteous path Gu Immortals can't understand you, but I understand. How difficult is it for us lone cultivators to become an immortal? We have to earn every cultivation resource with our own hands. There won't be future opportunities, so we need to grasp the present benefits with all our strength. Who knows what will happen in the future?"

"As for those righteous path Gu Immortals, even if they stay in their homes, plenty of resources are provided to them. How could they understand the pain and difficulties we lone cultivators face?"

Fang Yuan's expression was calm, he did not praise nor did he retort.

He knew that Mountain Moving Old Monster's words were absolutely not just to get close to him, but to express his resolve — he, Mountain Moving Old Monster, was a lone cultivator, and the present benefit in front of him was this Mount Snail. His resolve could not be shaken, and the former lone cultivator, Wu Yi Hai, should be aware of it.

"I am clear of your intention, senior, but I still have to ask you to have some understanding, I have my own difficulties in coming here." Fang Yuan spoke.

Mountain Moving Old Monster snickered: "Everyone has their own difficulties."

With age and experience, one's words would carry deeper meaning.

Everyone has their own difficulties; not only was it replying to Fang Yuan's words, it also meant he, himself, had his own difficulties, and more importantly, it was also indicating that Wu clan was currently in a difficult situation.

Fang Yuan did not speak anymore.

Sometimes, silence was a tactic which could be used in a confrontation between words.

Sure enough, Mountain Moving Old Monster could not sit still and handed an information path mortal Gu to Fang Yuan: "Take a look at it."

The contents listed in this mortal Gu had high value. If Fang Yuan obtained them, he could directly construct coiling thread caves!

"We will cooperate, I will take Mount Snail and you will get these, what do you think?" Mountain Moving Old Monster smiled.

He was actually trying to bribe Fang Yuan!

But this was not strange.

Instead, it fell within Fang Yuan's expectations.

Mountain Moving Old Monster was a lone cultivator, and from his point of view, he naturally did not want to offend the number one righteous path super force, Wu clan. Despite Wu clan currently being in a predicament, such a colossal force was not something Mountain Moving Old Monster could threaten by himself.

More importantly, if Mountain Moving Old Monster obtained this Mount Snail, he would no longer be a person who could freely move.

Mount Snail could not be stored inside an immortal aperture, unless it was completely subdued.

Mountain Moving Old Monster was an earth path Gu Immortal, he clearly did not have such attainment. Like this, he would become the 'owner' of this Mount Snail, and would have to defend it if someone attacked it in the future.

If he offended Wu clan, Wu clan's Gu Immortals would attack in waves, how could he defend against them by himself?

Even if he could defend once, what about the second time, the third time?

Even if he was able to defend against them all, there would be losses in battle. Would Mountain Moving Old Monster still have time to cultivate if he were to be disturbed repeatedly?

As such, there was only one option in front of Mountain Moving Old Monster.

That was to negotiate with Wu clan.

Wu clan did not want to let go of this Mount Snail, but even the large Wu clan was an organization formed by its clansmen. And so long as it was an organization, it could not be an airtight fortress, there would naturally be chinks in the armor.

Wu Yi Hai's arrival gave even greater hope to Mountain Moving Old Monster.

"Senior, you want to use these to exchange for an immemorial desolate beast?" Fang Yuan held the information path mortal Gu and said with a faint smile.

"The resources inside are very valuable! This Mount Snail might be an immemorial desolate beast, but who can control it? If I become its owner, I will also only be taking the resources produced by it. Naturally, we can talk if you have any conditions." Mountain Moving Old Monster's eyes glimmered brightly, his attitude turning much warmer.

Since Fang Yuan had not directly refused, Mountain Moving Old Monster cheered inwardly and had much higher hope.

"The contents inside this list needs to be doubled at least." This was Fang Yuan's first condition.

Mountain Moving Old Monster immediately frowned.

"Mount Snail cannot be yours in name, it will still belong to Wu clan." This was Fang Yuan's second condition.

Mountain Moving Old Monster's eyes opened wide, his warm expression suddenly changing to that of anger.

"But in truth, senior, you will be this mountain's owner, the benefits will mostly go to you, but you need to hand over a portion of the resources to our Wu clan every year." This was Fang Yuan's third condition.

Mountain Moving Old Monster began to sneer, his expression had turned dark: "Wu Yi Hai, are you playing with me?"

"Of course not." Fang Yuan had a sober expression, he stood up and looked at Mountain Moving Old Monster's eyes with no fear: "Senior, may I ask three questions?"

Mountain Moving Old Monster barely restrained his anger: "Speak."

"Senior, first, you are a lone person not affiliated with any super force, how could my Wu clan leave Mount Snail in your hands? It would be alright if it were a super force, but letting a lone cultivator take benefits would negatively affect my Wu clan's prestige."

"Second, even if you can take possession of this Mount Snail for the moment, how long can you defend it? Even if my Wu clan doesn't interfere with you, what about the other super forces?"

"Third, senior, do you think that by only bribing me, the whole of Wu clan will simply watch from the sidelines?"

Mountain Moving Old Monster fell into silence.

After a long while, he sighed and spoke with a hoarse voice: "Then if we go with your idea, wouldn't I become the guard for your Wu clan's mountain?"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "It is just some insignificant reputation. How could everything go perfectly? The conditions I mentioned are actually not excessive, it is because I considered how I was also once a lone cultivator. The question is, do you want face or real benefits, please consider it properly."

Mountain Moving Old Monster fell into silence.

This time, the silence lasted an even longer time, only when the light drizzle gradually stopped, he spoke: "Alright, we will go according to your idea."

Chapter 1316: Moon Festival

A few days later.

Looking at Mount Snail loudly moving away, and Mountain Moving Old Monster standing on top of it with an owner's air, Fang Yuan retracted his gaze and started to leave.

Mount Snail's matter had been settled.

With Fang Yuan as the representative, Wu clan had reached an agreement with Mountain Moving Old Monster. Mountain Moving Old Monster obtained most of the benefits of Mount Snail, but this immemorial desolate beast still belonged to Wu clan in name.

Wu Yong had assigned Fang Yuan to retain Mount Snail.

Fang Yuan had retained it, although it was only a portion, it could be considered as completing the task.

"Mountain Moving Old Monster agreed to my conditions because of Wu clan's force behind me."

"As for Wu Yong, he is currently worn out by dealing with the difficulties created by other super forces. He has no choice but to forcibly acknowledge the resolution of Mount Snail."

"Wu clan is in a grave situation at present, as Wu Yong's brother, I should not idle around outside and must return as quickly as possible."

Fang Yuan was thoroughly satisfied with the outcome of this matter.

He had an explanation to hand to Wu clan, and more importantly, he had reaped many benefits from this task.

He could already begin the construction of coiling thread caves.

Because of these resources, Fang Yuan immediately had spare funds to engage in a large scale expansion of his second major resource.

According to the previous development speed, he would have had to wait more than half a year. And in this duration, there could not be any unexpected mishaps, for instance, intense battle would consume a lot of red date immortal essence. The rate of time in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture was slowed down at present, the amount of red date immortal essence he produced was a lot less than before, and Fang Yuan needed to use immortal essence stones to turn them into red date immortal essence.

Now, his immortal essence was no longer green grape immortal essence, one hundred immortal essence stones were required to turn into one bead of red date immortal essence.

"I need to arrange the Gu formation to construct the coiling thread caves, I also need rank six immortal material dark soft silk and rank seven immortal material regret water rocks."

"With these funds, all this can be completed and it is only a matter of time."

"The important thing is, when can I return to the dream realm? Wu Yong's attitude is the crucial factor!"

Fang Yuan thought as he moved forward.

Right as he was on his way back, in the headquarters of Wu clan, two Gu Immortals were currently talking about him, Wu Yi Hai.

One was Wu clan's rank eight Gu Immortal, first supreme elder Wu Yong.

The other was Wu Yong's trusted aide, Wu Fa.

"Who could have thought my brother would resolve Mount Snail's matter so quickly? Elder Wu Fa, as per the clan rules, how should we reward him?" Wu Yong asked.

Wu Fa was silent for a moment.

He knew that Wu Yong's question was not superficial, he was asking about his attitude towards Wu Yi Hai.

He was testing Wu Fa.

Because Wu Yi Hai's identity was special, he and Wu Yong were half-siblings!

Wu Fa quickly thought and replied: "Lord Wu Yi Hai has a lone cultivator background."

One sentence.

But Wu Yong laughed heartily: "Right, your remark is correct. Yi Hai has a lone cultivator's disposition, even after returning to the clan, he has not changed and is always thinking of quickly making cash and eyeing up cheap benefits."

Wu Fa, however, did not agree: "Frosty Peak and Mount Snail are not small benefits."

Wu Yong's laughter stopped, and a sharp light flashed in his eyes as he nodded: "That is indeed not good, if everyone were to be like this, how would Wu clan continue to exist? But he did not overstep the bottom line and has not left behind any weaknesses that could be exposed."

As he said this, Wu Yong sighed and remarked: "He has some ability."

How could Wu Fa not realize Wu Yong's meaning?

Wu Yong naturally could not be pleased at seeing Fang Yuan use the situation to his advantage.

But the situation left him no choice, he was lacking manpower and sometimes had no choice but to send Wu Yi Hai to deal with some matters.

Fang Yuan had also revealed his ability by handling these two matters.

This ability had obtained Wu Yong's acknowledgement, so Wu Yong would still continue to use Fang Yuan. But when the time arrives and Wu clan's situation eases up, Fang Yuan would be cast aside by Wu Yong, to the extent that if Fang Yuan were to leave behind any evidence, Wu Yong would grasp the opportunity and deal a huge blow to Fang Yuan.

After all, no higher-up would feel comfortable with someone like Fang Yuan, who sought after personal gains.

Fang Yuan successfully returned to Wu clan.

He met with Wu Yong and described the whole matter briefly, and obtained a reward from Wu clan once again.

Fang Yuan chose to exchange for immortal essence stones.

Naturally, this sum of immortal essence stones could not compare to what he had obtained from Mountain Moving Old Monster, it was far too few.

Over the following days, Fang Yuan cultivated in peace.

The construction of the coiling thread caves was slowly progressing. This was his current focus.

Every set interval of time, Fang Yuan would have to place his immortal aperture to absorb heaven and earth qi, stabilizing the sovereign immortal aperture.

After all, Reverse Flow River was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it was extremely taxing on the immortal aperture.

This matter was slightly troublesome.

Fang Yuan could not directly absorb heaven and earth qi, because the amount he absorbed every time was huge and the interval between them was also short.

As such, Fang Yuan had to search for some immortal materials in treasure yellow heaven, disintegrating them into heaven and earth qi to infuse into himself.

This no doubt consumed a lot of Fang Yuan's spare energy and finances, but he would rather do this carefully. This was the only way he could stick around long enough and avoid showing any flaws that could let others expose his identity.

Days passed by, Fang Yuan started to feel somewhat impatient.

"The problems on the giant dream realm's end have already settled down. But Wu Yong does not seem to show any signs of letting me return. Looks like what I was worried about happened after all. Sigh!"

Fang Yuan sighed.

In this world, people often had no choice.

Wu Yong was busy dealing with difficulties from all sides, doing everything to stabilize the situation. If he let Fang Yuan return, and a problem occurred on the super Gu formation's end, would he not be creating trouble for himself?

Moreover, Wu Yong saw Fang Yuan had some ability and wanted to continue letting him deal with some problems.

As for Fang Yuan embezzling resources while doing the tasks, Wu Yong was turning a blind eye to it for now and did not look into it.

He did not pursue it, but Fang Yuan wanted him to.

Looking at the reason Fang Yuan disguised as Wu Yi Hai and entered Wu clan, wasn't it for the dream realm?

"It seems I need to make a move."

On this day, Fang Yuan left his residence.

For the policies of higher-ups, there were countermeasures.

Fang Yuan was an old fox, how could he not have a method to respond to this?

Around twelve days later, in a pavilion on Yue Hua Mountain, several Gu Immortals were seated around a stone table.

Warm moonlight flowed down like water.

Night birds cried out in the lush green hills.

Soft wind brushed past, the view was beautiful beyond imagination.

"Today is Southern Border's yearly moon festival[1], it is my fortune to enjoy this festival with all our honorable guests." Qiao Si Liu said with a smile.

Her voice was beautiful like the soft murmurs of mountain springs, giving a pure feeling.

Her appearance was even more beautiful, dressed in a pure white brocade dress, along with her exquisite features, it gave a feeling of a fairy from mortal tales.

"Being able to receive Fairy Si Liu's invitation to enjoy the moon festival together is my, Luo Mu Zi's, honor." A Gu Immortal with the looks of a young man spoke.

His smile was glowing with enthusiasm, particularly the gaze he had when looked at Qiao Si Liu, it was scorching hot.

Qiao Si Liu was one of the three publicly recognized top beauties in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, what stood out even more was her background.

Qiao clan, although affiliated with Wu clan, was also a righteous path super force.

Among the six Gu Immortals present, there were two women and four men, other than the one couple, Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were pursuers of Qiao Si Liu.

There were many pursuers of Qiao Si Liu, but being able to receive an invitation to this festival from her showed these two were not at the same level as the rest.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were naturally happy, they came rushing over immediately when they received Qiao Si Liu's invitation.

But at this moment, Qiao Si Liu spoke to another male Gu Immortal: "Yi Hai, you said you wanted to integrate yourself into Southern Border, tonight's moon festival is a custom of Southern Border."

"Southern Border has a lot of mountains, separated from each other, but the moon festival is a common custom. Every year, at this time, we will all appreciate the moon."

Her eyes were glistening with light, her soft voice and her smiling rosy lips created an extraordinary image.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei immediately frowned, as they rigidly stared at Fang Yuan with eyes that could burst into flames.

Qiao Si Liu's differing attitude could be clearly seen by anyone who had eyes, moreover, the seating arrangement had already put Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei in a bad mood.

Because on the main seat was Qiao Si Liu and on her right seat was Fang Yuan, while to her left was her best friend, Fairy Tian Lu.

As for the other male Gu Immortals, their seats were arranged quite far away.

"Moon festival?" Fang Yuan's expression was indifferent, he asked even though he already knew: "Interesting, what do we do besides appreciating the moon?"

"We drink tea, recite poems, and also dissect rocks." Qiao Si Liu explained with a smile.

"Dissect rocks?" Fang Yuan looked puzzled.

Qiao Si Liu did not reply, instead she handed a cup of fragrant tea to Fang Yuan: "First, please taste my personally brewed tea."

Luo Mu Zi almost stood up at this sight!

Lun Fei's eyelids twitched violently, wishing he could be in Fang Yuan's place.

Fang Yuan took a light sip of the tea and commented: "This tea is not bad."

"Only not bad? This is Fairy Si Liu's renowned willow spiral tea!" Luo Mu Zi almost yelled.

"Is there something special that I am unaware of?" Fang Yuan looked at Qiao Si Liu.

Qiao Si Liu met Fang Yuan's gaze, before her eyes turned and she laughed softly.

Lun Fei's heart started beating faster at the fairy's charming laughter.

At this moment, Fairy Tian Lu aptly chirped: "This willow spiral tea, if you lightly shake it, a whirlpool will form on the surface of the tea in the appearance of a willow leaf. You will only get the true extraordinary taste of the tea when you drink it at that time."

"Oh? So it was like that?" Fang Yuan shook the cup in his hand, and immediately, there was a change on the surface of the tea.

He drank it then, and felt the fragrance overflow in his mouth, giving him a pleasant aftertaste and satisfaction.

"Great tea." Fang Yuan praised.

"Of course it is a great tea, Fairy Si Liu's personally brewed tea is not something just anyone can get to drink!" Luo Mu Zi sourly said.

"To be able to receive your praise, Si Liu's efforts were not wasted. You should know that you need to spend six hours to make this tea and you cannot be even the slightest bit careless during the whole process." Fairy Tian Lu said.

Lun Fei was extremely moved: "It is truly my lifetime's honor to be able to taste Fairy Si Liu's personally brewed willow spiral tea tonight!"

Fairy Tian Lu's eyebrows immediately rose: "Who said you can taste the willow spiral tea? Si Liu took out some time from her busy schedule to make this one cup."

"Ugh."

[1] This is the Gu version of the Chinese mid-autumn festival, you look at and appreciate the beauty of the moon while drinking tea. Back

Chapter 1317: Tea Competition

Qiao Si Liu only made one cup of willow spiral tea, which was given to Fang Yuan.

Such a brewing method immediately changed the significance of this cup of willow spiral tea.

Fang Yuan's expression slightly changed, showing flattered joy on his face, but his mind was tranquil with no ripples.

"This is truly a pity. No matter how beautiful you are, without eternal life, you will just be a pile of bones in the end."

"Beauty is superficial, but people cannot stop indulging in it."

"But this Fairy Tian Lu is indeed Qiao Si Liu's best friend, their coordination is remarkable."

The only cup of brewed tea was given to Fang Yuan by Fairy Si Liu, Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei, who were still thinking of tasting the tea, however, obtained such a reply.

Their expressions had become quite stiff at this moment.

Qiao Si Liu smiled: "The willow spiral tea was only a token of goodwill. I have brought bewitching tea for everyone, please have a taste."

She waved her silk sleeve, five servings of tea appeared on the table.

This tea was different from willow spiral tea, it was not in a cup, but in a white porcelain dish.

At the center of this dish was a fist sized dewdrop.

This dewdrop was lustrous like a jade, its surface wobbling slightly against the night wind, looking delicate.

"Bewitching tea is a renowned tea of Qiao clan, to think I could have a taste tonight." Luo Mu Zi gave himself an excuse, but in fact, his gaze was still fixed on that cup in front of Fang Yuan.

Lun Fei had already tightly clenched his fists below the table, grinding his teeth as he raised the small porcelain dish and took a sip of the bewitching tea.

"Good tea." He exclaimed, but his expression was slightly rigid.

In fact, bewitching tea was multiple grades higher than willow spiral tea, the latter was only Qiao Si Liu's creation, while the former was Qiao clan's signature tea. A super force's signature tea was naturally more outstanding than the tea created by Qiao Si Liu, a single Gu Immortal.

However, as far as Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were concerned, they would rather give up a hundred servings of bewitching tea to drink a serving of willow spiral tea.

"Bewitching tea is really refreshing and has endless aftertaste. Si Liu, how can I take out my aurora tea when you brought out this tea?" Fairy Tian Lu smiled.

Qiao Si Liu, however, was not the slightest bit polite to this best friend of hers: "Just don't take it out then, I am already tired of drinking your aurora tea. Right now, I am anticipating Sheng Liu's drunken flowers tea. It is rumored this tea was a creation from his inspiration when he fell in love at first sight with you. I wonder if I might have the opportunity to taste it today?"

"I am ashamed, ashamed." Sheng Liu rubbed his nose, giving a bitter smile, "My drunken flowers tea is a crude creation, it is not exquisite enough for today."

Fairy Tian Lu also smiled while covering her mouth: "Si Liu, you are making things difficult for my darling Liu, this won't do! Only I can drink drunken flowers tea, outsiders can stop dreaming about it."

Her face showed pride and love as she said this.

Gu Immortal Sheng Liu who was beside her, looked lovingly at Fairy Tian Lu, they were already holding their hands below the table.

Qiao Si Liu gave a deep sigh: "Oh, I wonder when I will meet a person who will create a tea for me?"

There was a sense of dejectedness in her soft query.

At this moment, moonlight shone into the pavilion.

A beauty sighing softly under the moonlight was truly a very loveable sight.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei felt their bodies heating up, Luo Mu Zi even stood up: "Fairy Si Liu, I have a tea which is called nine recollecting fragrances. It is my own creation, fairy, I would like to offer it to you on this auspicious occasion."

Not willing to be left behind, Lun Fei also quipped in: "I also have prepared my tea, this is yin-yang tea, there is a clear distinction between yin and yang, fairy, please have a taste."

These two Gu Immortals only offered the tea to Qiao Si Liu, just like Qiao Si Liu had given her willow spiral tea to Fang Yuan.

Qiao Si Liu took a sip of both tea, and said with a smile: "Nine recollecting fragrances is aptly named, the moment the tea enters the mouth, fragrances coil around the tongue. Tasting it carefully, there are actually nine moments when the fragrances intensify, it is really extraordinary."

"Haha, fairy, it is not worthy of such praise from you." Luo Mu Zi laughed heartily, his previous bad mood swept away completely.

Qiao Si Liu then said to Lun Fei: "Yin-yang tea, although it is not a unique creation, I have heard of it before. There are three levels to brewing this tea. First level is when yin and yang are obscure. Second layer is when yin and yang are separate. Third level is when yin contains yang, and yang contains yin, yin and yang revolving around each other. Lun Fei, your skill can be seen for being able to achieve the second level of brewing this tea, there are probably less than ten people who can achieve that in the whole of Southern Border, worthy of a food path Gu Immortal like you."

Tea, wine, delicacies, in this world, they were naturally not ordinary.

There were countless ways to brew tea. It was not as simple and shallow as putting tea leaves in hot water.

Like the tea discussed by the immortals in the pavilion: Willow spiral tea, bewitching tea, drunken flowers, nine recollecting fragrances and yin-yang tea, they were all incomplete Gu recipes.

And when these Gu recipes were completed, and the Gu Immortal brewed tea at that time, they could refine food path Gu worms.

Food path was one of the many cultivation paths, it was just that it had never flourished. Although it was extremely significant and there was a lot of interests in it, unfortunately, because of historical reasons, there were very few food path inheritances left in the world.

"This Lun Fei's main cultivation is actually food path?" Fang Yuan gave Lun Fei a quick glance, feeling slightly surprised inwardly.

"What is this guy's origin? I have many Immortal Gu, if I could obtain his food path inheritance, it might be a huge help to me." Fang Yuan immediately had malicious intent.

Even if you had no intention to harm others, they might still want to harm you.

Fang Yuan was somewhat moved.

His current strength was already among the best below rank eight. When he activated reverse flow protection seal, although his offensive methods were still weaker, he could stand toe to toe with Feng Jiu Ge.

"I need to first check Lun Fei's background and see if I can make a move against him or not."

"If I can, Wu Yi Hai's identity must not be implicated!"

With Wu Yi Hai's identity, Fang Yuan definitely could not brazenly kill Lun Fei. Because he was a righteous path Gu Immortal Gu, and could not adopt demonic path methods.

A super force had much more robust strength than a lone immortal, but these forces usually did not lightly offend any Gu Immortal.

The same went for Wu clan.

A super force had huge assets and businesses, if a Gu Immortal could not be killed and escaped, they could destroy many resources of the super force and be a huge headache to the super force.

Wu Yong had this consideration as well when he accepted Fang Yuan's idea of giving some concessions to Mountain Moving Old Monster in regards to Mount Snail.

"Hmm... it is better to probe and determine the value of Lun Fei's inheritance. If it is not high, forget it."

"If the value is high and I am to make a move, I need to be absolutely careful to not let his soul self-detonate."

There was no need to think about Immortal Gu, they could not be obtained.

But Fang Yuan could kill Lun Fei and capture his soul, to obtain the food path inheritance by soul searching.

Fang Yuan had always held food path inheritances in high expectations.

Unfortunately, due to a lack of fortuitous encounters, he could do nothing about it.

Since there were no fortuitous encounters, then he had to make a move himself and rob others.

Fang Yuan did not have any feeling of guilt!

Many Gu Immortals were particular about not attacking others if others did not attack them.

However, Fang Yuan was someone who, even if others did not attack him, would go attack them.

"I brewed this tea over seven days and seven nights, fairy, now being able to receive your praise, it was all worth it." Lun Fei's tone was slightly shaking with excitement.

He then looked at Fang Yuan and said with a hint of challenge: "I wonder what tea Lord Wu Yi Hai is going to show us?"

He had not even the slightest idea that Fang Yuan was already brewing thoughts of killing him.

"Eastern Sea is the most plentiful region in terms of resources. Wu Yi Hai has lived in Eastern Sea for many years, any tea he brings out will definitely surpass others and be the top tea." Luo Mu Zi sat back and spoke with enthusiasm.

Fang Yuan smiled.

These two were Qiao Si Liu's pursuers, after realizing Fang Yuan's 'threat', they had tacitly allied to put Fang Yuan in an awkward situation.

They praised Fang Yuan highly, making it difficult for him to refuse their request.

Qiao Si Liu slightly frowned.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei's thoughts were slightly devious. If Wu Yi Hai could not showcase such a tea, the situation would be awkward. Even if he could, his reputation would suffer.

The reason?

Because this event was hosted by Qiao Si Liu. Qiao clan's bewitching tea was the main tea, while other Gu Immortals' teas were supplementary.

The guests should not overshadow the host, this was an unwritten rule of the moon festival. Qiao clan might not care about it, but Wu Yi Hai's reputation would suffer.

The righteous path was very concerned about reputation!

Fang Yuan, however, had no hesitation.

He directly took out five cups of tea and indicated to the others: "Please enjoy."

Fairy Tian Lu's eyes brightened, being the first to pick up a cup: "I am very curious as to what Lord Wu Yi Hai's tea is like?"

But the first person to drink the tea was not her, but Lun Fei.

He looked somewhat hurried.

This was the best opportunity to knock down his rival, as a food path Gu Immortal, he was proficient in this aspect, how could he not take this opportunity?

But with just one sip, he immediately frowned and spat it out: "Pshaw, what rotten tea is this?"

"Awful, too awful." Luo Mu Zi also took a sip before placing the cup down: "This is the most revolting tea I have ever had in my life, it might even be worse than mortal tea."

His tone was extremely impolite, with no hint of respect towards a rival.

The two had firmly grasped the opportunity to attack Fang Yuan's reputation.

Fairy Tian Lu wanted to help mediate the situation, but after drinking it, she gave a helpless smile: "This tea is salty and bitter, it is like seawater."

Fang Yuan smiled and unexpectedly admitted: "It is seawater."

"What?"

"You actually brought seawater? Are you trying to shame Fairy Si Liu!"

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei quickly sent verbal attacks.

The smile on Fang Yuan's face disappeared, replaced by solemness: "I don't like to drink tea, if I had to choose, this seawater would be my tea."

"You do not understand."

"I lived the life of a secluded cultivator in Eastern Sea, an orphan with no one to rely on and with calamities and tribulations pressuring me at all times."

"Every day, I would wake up early and scoop a bowl of salty seawater to drink, this was to remind myself to not slack and continue persevering."

The pavilion immediately fell into silence.

Qiao Si Liu slowly lifted her cup amidst this silence and took a sip, before slowly putting the cup down.

She smiled, her rosy lips and white teeth seemed brighter than the beautiful moonlight: "This is the most special tea I have had in my life, thank you, Yi Hai. This tea is good, I am truly moved."

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei fell into silence seeing that the person they loved had responded like this.

Chapter 1318: Story of the Moon Festival

"Are you kidding me! My nine recollecting fragrances cannot even compare to a cup of seawater?" Luo Mu Zi roared inwardly, while maintaining his calm appearance on the surface.

"Damn! This Wu Yi Hai is playing tricks and pulled a fast one, we are offering tea, yet he offers seawater? He is too shameless! Fairy Si Liu even approved of him, this is too infuriating!" Veins started to bulge in Lun Fei's clenched fists below the table.

Fairy Tian Lu quickly calmed the situation: "The moon is high in the sky, since we have already drunk tea, if there are no poems to accompany this festival, it would not be complete."

Fang Yuan pretended to not understand: "Are we really going to recite poems?"

He looked like he had heard it for the first time.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei's eyes immediately brightened. This was another opportunity!

Another opportunity to knock down their rival.

"You managed to get away with it the previous time, duping your way through. This time, I am going to push you down from the limelight, then fiercely step on you a couple times."

Luo Mu Zi's mind was revolving around this thought, but on the surface, he was still wearing a smile and had a graceful demeanor.

The same went for Lun Fei, having similar thoughts.

However, they did not know what kind of person Fang Yuan was.

Competing in poetry?!

Heavens!

This was worse than showing off in front of an expert.

Fang Yuan came from Earth, he had a large stockpile of traditional poems in his head, including those renowned works as well as earthshaking masterpieces. He could easily use one of them and these two would be unable to save face.

"Yes, we are going to recite poems, there is a story behind this." Qiao Si Liu answered Fang Yuan.

"Oh? Please explain." Fang Yuan continued to ask.

"This is a story that has been passed down in Southern Border, and is also the origin of the moon festival." Qiao Si Liu said with eloquence.

Once upon a time, at a certain village in Southern Border.

A young man fell in love with an old Gu Master's daughter, and this Gu Master's daughter also was in love with this mortal youth.

The youth mustered up his courage to propose the marriage, but he was met with the old Gu Master's rejection.

"You are only a mortal, while my daughter is a Gu Master with a bright future, how could you be worthy of my daughter? Get lost!"

The young man implored and begged, but the old Gu Master sneered: "You are daydreaming, thinking I will let my daughter marry you! You, a mere mortal who cannot even brew tea? What use do you have?"

The youth replied: "Isn't it just tea? What is so difficult about it, if I brew it, will you marry your daughter to me?"

The old Gu Master felt a headache.

He knew his daughter loved this youth deeply, forcefully breaking them up would only make his daughter hate him.

"If you can make a cup of tea that meets my expectations, I will give you a chance."

The youth was joyous and agreed immediately: "Sir, I will definitely make it."

The Gu Master daughter was extremely worried when she heard about this: "My family is reputed for our famous tea, and you have to make a tea which can satisfy my father. You are only a mortal with no Gu Master abilities, how can you brew a good tea?"

The young man, however, replied: "Don't worry. Who says mortals cannot brew tea? Let me tell you three principles."

"The first principle: the law of the jungle, big fish eats small fish, and small fish eats shrimps."

Saying that, the young man walked to a stream and hooked a big fish, he cut the fish, retrieving a small fish inside, he then cut the small fish, and took out a shrimp from the inside.

"The second principle: humans need to eat and also need to defecate."

The young man then ate the shrimp and pooped out a pile of faeces.

"The third principle: faeces can nourish vegetation to grow better."

The young man buried his faeces under the soil, and sure enough, flowers and plants started to flourish and grow.

The young man plucked a kind of flower from among them and soaked it in the stream, the entire small stream turned into tea.

The old Gu Master could not speak for a long while after he took a sip of this tea.

His daughter said, "Father, you are not thinking of reneging on your promise, right?"

Only then did the old Gu Master nod reluctantly: "Boy, you have passed the first test. But it is still impossible for you, a mortal, to marry my daughter. You are too crude and lack talent, you cannot recite poems."

The youth scratched his head and spoke worriedly: "Although I have not recited poems before, I can give it a try."

The old Gu Master scoffed: "You?"

The youth asked back: "Why can't I?"

"Boy, reciting poems is not just casually chanting a few phrases. We Gu Masters can cause heaven and earth to change by reciting poems, we can make humans dance with joy. Can you do that?"

The youth said in a low tone: "How would I know if I don't give it a try?"

"Alright, then try, don't say I didn't give you a chance. If you fail, then you need to leave and never see my daughter again."

The youth had no choice but to agree, he began to pace around, thinking of a poem to recite.

But he had never recited a poem before, he had no clue how to start.

At this moment, he saw the ants on the ground, he saw the birds and the setting sun outside the window. Suddenly, he patted his head.

He began to recite: "Sparrows fly low and snakes slither around, ants move their homes as it rains down."

Southern Border had many rainy days, and it was currently springtime as well.

The youth had just finished speaking, when light rain began to appear in the sky.

The old Gu Master's expression changed.

The youth continued: "A drop of spring rain resembles a drop of oil, too much of it sends us into turmoil."

The rain got heavier and the sky turned dark.

The old Gu Master's expression was slightly unsightly.

The youth grabbed his head and scratched his cheek: "Elm trees droop as farming commences, hair falls as seeds scatter."

At this point, the youth was stuck and for the life of him, he could not recite the final line.

"I will give you some more time." The old Gu Master sneered.

The youth's eyes brightened as he pointed at the old Gu Master and said: "Lord took away all the grains, our hungry stomachs are all in pain."

The old Gu Master immediately stomped his foot in anger and stood up, breaking the teacup in his hand.

Then, he pointed at the young man and shouted: "A mere mortal dares to be so audacious!"

But his daughter laughed and clapped: "Amazing, this song changed heaven and earth, and even made father dance."

The old Gu Master was furious at seeing his daughter side with her boyfriend, but was unable to retort.

"Good, good, good, consider that you have passed the second test, but there is still the final one. You want to marry my daughter, what about the betrothal gift? Can you take out a betrothal gift that can satisfy me?"

The youth lowered his head dejectedly, he lived in a thatched cottage, slept on a straw mat and only had one set of patched clothes.

"I will use all my assets as the betrothal gift." The youth spoke in a serious tone.

"Let me see them!" The old Gu Master said.

The young man brought the old Gu Master to his residence, to that old thatched cottage.

He then said: "These are all my assets."

"This old hut with holes everywhere?" The old Gu Master pointed with disdain.

"This straw mat that is about to break?" The old Gu Master threw the straw mat.

"These rocks used as stools?" The old Gu Master kicked the rocks and broke them.

The youth lowered his head.

Every sentence the old Gu Master said made the young man's head lower further down.

When the old Gu Master said his third sentence, the youth's head had almost hung down to his chest.

But right at this time, from a rock the old Gu Master has kicked open, a beautiful Gu worm that looked like the moon flew out leisurely, shining brightly.

The old Gu Master was stunned.

The youth was also stunned, he had picked up this rock casually from the base of the mountain.

The old Gu Master's daughter cried out happily: "This Gu worm is definitely enough as the betrothal gift, right?"

The old Gu Master was unable to retort, he could not say anything and finally, he could only rub his nose and marry his daughter to this mortal lad.

Fang Yuan had already heard of this story before, it was indeed interesting.

The story portrayed a conflict between a mortal and a Gu Master, and actually ended up with the mortal's victory.

The youth had braved through the three hurdles, finally getting together with the beauty, who was also a Gu Master. The old Gu Master had not used strength from start to finish, this did not conform to logic. It, however, showed a lowly mortal's thirst towards a better life, as well as pursuing happiness.

Qiao Si Liu narrated the story to Fang Yuan, conveniently explaining the customs of the moon festival as well.

Why it was that during the moon festival, the people in Southern Border, be they Gu Immortals or mortals, would make tea, recite poems and dissect rocks.

Naturally, the tea brewing of mortals was done with ordinary tea leaves, and as for dissecting rocks, it was replaced by breaking pebbles as a way of receiving auspicious blessings.

"This is quite an interesting story, thank you, Fairy Si Liu, for answering my doubts." Fang Yuan said, politely.

Qiao Si Liu smiled: "Why are you so polite, you can just call me Si Liu."

"Huh?!" Luo Mu Zi's eyes opened wide.

Qiao Si Liu's attitude towards Wu Yi Hai was completely different from how she treated the two of them.

"We have had tea already, now let us recite poems." Lun Fei said, his gaze towards Fang Yuan flashed with some coldness and his tone had also turned somewhat icier.

Qiao Si Liu's beautiful eyes turned towards Lun Fei: "Lun Fei, you are already eager, I am very interested to listen to your masterpiece."

Lun Fei laughed happily, the coldness on his face completely dissipated as he replied: "Then let me recite my simple work."

He stood up and slowly walked outside the pavilion as he recited —

Stepping into society as an ignorant youngster,

Step by step I walk by myself.

But tonight I do not drink alone,

Because my dream beauty is here under the moon.

Lun Fei, in his blue robe and with fair appearance, recited slowly.

The first two lines described his cultivation experiences, hinting at his lonely journey.

The last two lines described the current situation, especially the last line, it was an implicit confession.

He had walked out of the pavilion, and after his recital, he returned inside, gazing deeply at Qiao Si Liu.

Qiao Si Liu sensed the passion in his eyes and quickly turned around to look at Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan neither looked at her nor showed hostility towards Lun Fei, he was just quietly drinking tea.

A trace of disappointment flashed past Qiao Si Liu's eyes.

Chapter 1319: Poem Competition

"Good poem, good poem." Fairy Tian Lu laughed charmingly: "Especially the last line, my dream beauty is here under the moon, it was truly beautiful. I think it is definitely talking about me, hehe."

She improvised a humorous remark, easing the atmosphere in the pavilion.

Lun Fei gave a helpless and bitter smile, sitting down again: "Please don't mind my crude creation, it is hardly presentable."

"Lun Fei, you are too modest, I have a poem as well." Luo Mu Zi said.

"Oh? We would love to hear it." Qiao Si Liu smiled, looking at Luo Mu Zi with anticipation.

Luo Mu Zi turned silent for a moment before slowly reciting.

Climbed mountains to seek immortality,

Danger present in every step.

Dust specks float like light,

Dark Gu lurk in heart.

A dream like golden jade,

Thousands of years of loneliness.

Five regions and nine heavens,

Everything is in one breath.

The concept and imagination in this poem with five words in each line immediately moved the Gu Immortals.

They carefully savored it.

Climbed mountains to seek immortality, referred to a Gu Immortal's cultivation.

Danger present in every step, Gu Immortals needed to deal with calamities and tribulations in their cultivation, devoting all their effort in managing their immortal aperture. It was like climbing a mountain, the higher they reached, the more dangerous it became.

Dust specks float like light, the meaning was that time was always passing by, and in the mortal world, dust gathered on people and people were like floating dust.

Dark Gu lurk in heart, on the surface, it referred to Gu Immortals storing Immortal Gu and mortal Gu in their immortal apertures. But the Gu Immortals present had deep background in literature, they could already savor the deeper meaning.

Dark Gu referred to darkness, setbacks, failures, compromises, disappointments, and other negative feelings.

Mortals thought immortals had good lives, but immortals faced difficulties they did not know. Just look at the living beings in the world, who was truly free and unfettered?

Gu Immortals endured huge pressure in their cultivation, it was unavoidable for them to have negative feelings, even Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables were not an exception.

Climbed mountains to seek immortality, danger present in every step. Dust specks float like light, dark Gu lurk in heart. These phrases were brief but contained profound meaning, which when carefully considered, resonated greatly with Gu Immortals.

The lines after this, 'a dream like golden jade, thousands of years of loneliness'; it referred to gold and jade, all kinds of wealth, being superficial objects and just like dreams. As time passes, love, hatred, and all feelings disappear. It showed how the poet looked indifferently at the changes in the world, that their mind was free from mortal emotions.

The final phrase 'five regions and nine heavens, everything is in one breath' was filled with vigor and majesty, sweeping away the gloominess and heaviness from the previous lines. There were several other meanings to it, as long as humans had one breath left in them they were living, when they lose this breath, they would die. People strived and fought for that one breath. Using the world as an analogy, Gu Immortal cultivation was just like the pillars holding up the five regions and nine heavens, everyone was just working hard to support themselves.

The entire poem was slow at first before it became faster in momentum, creating a majestic scene that filled the listeners with admiration.

For a moment, the pavilion was filled with silence, the immortals quietly ruminating over this poem.

Qiao Si Liu thought to herself: "Strange, from my understanding of Luo Mu Zi, how could he create such a poem with his nature? He probably stole someone else's work, hmm, he also did not say it was his creation."

She sized up Luo Mu Zi.

Luo Mu Zi looked calm on the surface, sitting upright as he quietly drank his tea, but the smile on his lips gave away his inner feelings.

Qiao Si Liu inwardly smiled, but did not expose him.

She then turned her sight towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's expression was unexpectedly strange!

"This is Qi Jue's Five Words Poem? How is it possible! Didn't Demon Immortal Qi Jue's grotto-heaven only appear when dream realms flourished in the five regions chaotic war?"

'Strange! Strange! Strange!'

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was a great expert from the Olden Antiquity Era, a rank eight Gu Immortal with immense battle strength who had once fought Limitless Demon Venerable three times, the results were a win, a draw, and a loss.

Naturally, the first two battles were when Limitless Demon Venerable had yet to advance to rank nine.

And, in the final battle, Limitless Demon Venerable had advanced to rank nine, surpassing Demon Immortal Qi Jue. But the battle had still lasted for nine days and nine nights, before the latter was defeated. However, Limitless Demon Venerable did not kill Demon Immortal Qi Jue and let him go.

Limitless Demon Venerable had said this at the time: "You were my biggest enemy, but without you, I would not have trained so desperately. You also had a hand in pushing me towards my current cultivation level."

Having received the recognition and praise of a grand Demon Venerable, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's name was marked in history.

The grotto-heaven left after his death had lasted until the present.

In Fang Yuan's first life, dream realms manifested one after another during the five regions chaotic war, regional walls disappeared and the five regions turned into one. Such a huge change created a turbulence in heaven and earth qi, exposing many hidden blessed lands and grotto-heavens to the outside world.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's grotto heaven was revealed in such a situation.

Undoubtedly, the moment it appeared, it caused an uproar in the five regions.

"That shouldn't be."

"Simple logic is that Qi Jue's Five Words Poem was engraved in Qi Jue grotto heaven. How did Luo Mu Zi know of it at this time?"

'Could it be, he has already entered Qi Jue grotto heaven?!'

Fang Yuan's thoughts became somewhat chaotic for a moment.

Qi Jue grotto heaven contained the Demon Immortal's true inheritance. This Demon Immortal was on the same level as Sword Immortal Bo Qing, even Hei Fan paled in comparison to him!

"If I could obtain this true inheritance..."

"Will I obtain Qi Jue's true inheritance by killing this Luo Mu Zi?"

Intense killing intent rose in Fang Yuan's mind once again.

Without knowing Fang Yuan's thoughts, Luo Mu Zi gave a challenging glance to Fang Yuan: "I wonder what great work Wu Yi Hai has? We are really looking forward to it."

"That is natural." Lun Fei quickly chipped in: "Lord Wu Yi Hai's origin is not ordinary, he has plenty of experiences and what's more, Eastern Sea is very rich in resources. I can't compare to the scholarly attainment of Wu Yi Hai."

These two praised Fang Yuan with pleasant words, but their thoughts were anything but good.

Qiao Si Liu was well aware of it, at this moment, she did not protect Fang Yuan but stared at Fang Yuan and encouraged him: "I also really want to listen to your poem, I am sure it will definitely be interesting and special."

"Yes, yes." Fairy Tian Lu quickly agreed.

For a moment, Fang Yuan was pressured by everyone, he rubbed his nose and gave a forced smile: "Friends, you are all overestimating me, how could I have poems, I don't know how to make any."

"Wu Yi Hai, you are modest! Too modest!" Luo Mu Zi laughed.

Fang Yuan shrugged: "I am telling the truth, I did not even know we would have to recite poems to appreciate the moon."

"Since that is the case, Wu Yi Hai, why don't you make one right now, it should be a wonderful work, don't worry if it takes a bit of time, we are all willing to wait." Lun Fei said, not letting Fang Yuan off.

Fang Yuan heaved a deep sigh.

Of course, he had a lot of poems in his head.

There was many poems praised since ancient times from Earth, he could casually copy any of those famous stanzas, it would be enough for this occasion and resolve the difficulties from these Gu Immortals.

But...

But so what?

Fang Yuan gazed around.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei loved Qiao Si Liu, they naturally considered Fang Yuan an eyesore, both had come to a tacit agreement to work together and knock down their rival. What good would it do for him to contend with such losers?

Fairy Tian Lu was Qiao Si Liu's best friend and was indeed working hard, helping Qiao Si Liu wholeheartedly. As for her lover, he did not speak much and was silent most of the time, quietly drinking tea from the side, this showed how astute he was.

As for Qiao Si Liu...

This fairy had both appearance and background, and was one of the three great beauties of Southern Border, she naturally had her pride.

Qiao clan might have ordered her to approach Fang Yuan, but she had her own methods.

She had thought meticulously in hosting this moon festival today. She had thought out everything, not only taking care of small details like seating order, she had also brought her best friend to help her, and an even more brilliant move was that she had invited Lun Fei and Luo Mu Zi to take part in the event.

When two men compete with each other over a girl, even if she was a pig, they would think she is awesome. Only when one wins and the other is out of the competition, and when the victor looks at this pig, he will then realize: oh, this was a pig after all!

This was rather exaggerated, but the logic was similar.

When a competitor appears, it would make the girl who is being pursued seem even more precious and more valuable.

Qiao Si Liu was well aware of this logic, so she made this arrangement to evoke Fang Yuan's thoughts and make him take the initiative to pursue her, then she could conveniently agree and hook Fang Yuan in.

If it were the real Wu Yi Hai, perhaps he might have already fallen into the planning of beauty.

Unfortunately, the one she was facing was Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan remained unmoved the whole time because he knew the relation between Wu clan and Qiao clan, and also the scheme of Qiao clan's higher-ups.

With this understanding, Fang Yuan was in a strategically superior and stable position, while Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were no more than roadside clowns.

When Fang Yuan sized up the Gu Immortals in the pavilion, the Gu Immortals were also focusing their gazes on him.

There was silence in the pavilion, this silence was no doubt a kind of pressure.

"Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei want to embarrass me. Qiao Si Liu also wants me to accept the challenge, hmm....maybe she is feeling a little upset. After all, for such a beauty, the seawater was too rude. As for Fairy Tian Lu, she is completely on Qiao Si Liu's side, and is nothing to worry about..."

Fang Yuan thought of all this, smiling inwardly as he said: "Then let me recite one, don't laugh at me."

"We are all ears!"

"We are looking forward to it!"

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were all smiles.

At the next moment, the immortals heard Fang Yuan's poem —

"Oh great sea, you are made of water."

"Oh horse, you have four legs."

"Oh beauty, you have large eyes and a mouth!"

The poem ended.

The entire pavilion was silent!

Everyone's expression seemed to have stiffened.

Even Qiao Si Liu and Fairy Tian Lu were no exception.

"This, this, this... what the f*ck!"

"This is a poem? This is rubbish!!"

"This Wu Yi Hai is an utter boor."

"What nonsense is this? Appreciating the moon and reciting poems, it was an elegant event, now it is completely ruined!"

The Gu Immortals were unanimously screaming internally.

Fang Yuan was all smiles as he looked at Qiao Si Liu: "I wonder if Fairy Si Liu is satisfied?"

"Satisfied? Screw you!"

"You still have the nerves to ask this question? You are simply too outrageous!!"

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei roared inwardly, but being mindful of their bearing, they showed nothing on the surface. The pavilion was still a scene of silence.

"Heh... hehe..." Qiao Si Liu laughed, even though it sounded very forced: "This poem is really special, to tell the truth, I... I have never heard such a poem. It is indeed worthy of being your creation... now that I carefully consider it, it is actually quite funny."

Luo Mu Zi:"..."

Lun Fei:"..."

Chapter 1320: Please 'Evaluate'

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were utterly speechless.

They wanted to criticize Fang Yuan, but Qiao Si Liu had made such a remark, if they criticized now, would they not be embarrassing Qiao Si Liu?

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei felt like they had swallowed a housefly but were unable to spit it out, it was unbearable.

Fang Yuan was laughing on the inside as he gazed around.

Qiao Si Liu was forcefully maintaining her smile, while Fairy Tian Lu gazed at her concernedly, her gaze seemingly containing some sympathetic feeling. As Qiao Si Liu's best friend, how could Fairy Tian Lu not know of her intention? It was just that Fang Yuan did not take the bait at all, making them be unable to do anything.

As for Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei, they had such stiff expressions that it was quite funny.

Fang Yuan looked at these two: "How was it? My poem was not bad, right?"

"Not bad?!"

Luo Mu Zi's and Lun Fei's eyes immediately opened wide as they looked at Fang Yuan, seemingly wanting to see how shameless this person could possibly get.

But immediately afterwards, they heard Fang Yuan speak: "Although I had a flash of inspiration, it seems a true masterpiece poem is also created like this. Si Liu really approves of my poem, but I still would like to hear your constructive feedback."

"Constructive feedback? This dogshit thing can be considered a poem? You want feedback?!"

"Si Liu, Si Liu... why are you speaking of her so closely? You scumbag, hey! Who let you address her so intimately!"

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were madly raving inside their minds.

But they could not lose their temper, they had to evaluate it and give good remarks just like Qiao Si Liu's words so that they would not embarrass her.

This disgusted them even more than eating a housefly.

Fang Yuan was clearly their rival in love and it was also garbage that could not be considered a poem, but Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei still needed to 'evaluate' it and give nice comments!

"This poem, ah... it is clear, easy to understand... and easy to read..." Luo Mu Zi stammered, his expression was becoming increasingly unsightly and he felt like he was going to vomit!

Fang Yuan nodded with a smile, then turned towards Lun Fei: "What do you think?"

Lun Fei saw Fang Yuan staring at him, the corners of his lips were raised slightly in a smile and seemed to be twitching, he insipidly remarked: "This is a good poem."

Fang Yuan's eyebrows rose, how could he let this person off so easily, he pursued: "What is so good about it?"

Lun Fei was furious, his face flushed red with anger as he screamed internally: "How would I know what's good about it? There is nothing good about it! You created this garbage and still want to be praised! You scumbag!!"

Looking at Fang Yuan's smiling expression, Lun Fei had an intense urge to smash the teacup on Fang Yuan's face.

It would really appease his anger!

But he could not do that.

Qiao Si Liu was right beside them, if Lun Fei did that, what would happen to Qiao Si Liu's face? Wouldn't he embarrass this fairy?

Moreover, he was not like Luo Mu Zi, he was a lone immortal. By contrast, Wu Yi Hai had a noble status, he was in Wu clan, and was the younger brother of Wu Yong!

Lun Fei could only restrain his anger as he racked his brains to think of words for 'evaluating' Fang Yuan's 'poem'.

"I am really pleased with this moon appreciation festival, never had I thought I am talented in composing poems." Fang Yuan smiled at Qiao Si Liu, his gaze full of deep meaning.

Qiao Si Liu's mind shook slightly as she smiled: "Next is rock dissecting, maybe you will have a huge harvest."

"Indeed, indeed. I am also most expectant towards this event, let us dissect rocks." Fairy Tian Lu quickly helped to change the subject.

"I have prepared a huge amount of rocks here for everyone to choose. Please." Qiao Si Liu naturally had come prepared, with Qiao clan as her background, gathering some rocks was of course not a troubling matter.

The mood in the pavilion eased.

Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei also let out sighs of relief, at least they no longer needed to praise Fang Yuan's poem against their own will.

The rocks prepared by Qiao Si Liu were of all sizes, the Gu Immortals chose them one after the other and dissected them on the spot to see if there were any Gu worms inside.

As far as mortal Gu was concerned, it was very easy for Gu Immortals to get them.

As such, the atmosphere was relaxed, unlike the seriousness when Gu Masters dissected rocks.

Naturally, this only applied to mortal Gu, if Immortal Gu were involved, this rock dissecting activity would be given serious attention by Gu Immortals.

Gu Immortals had a lot of methods to check whether a rock had mortal Gu or not. However, in today's event, they naturally would not use their methods to cheat and only relied on their insight and luck.

As for rocks that had Immortal Gu, they could only be found by chance and not through seeking, the investigative methods of Gu Immortals were deficient and without options in regard to such rocks.

Trying to get an Immortal Gu in tonight's event would be wishful thinking and unrealistic.

No one present had such expectations as this was only meant to be an entertaining event.

It was just that this entertainment held different meaning to Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei compared to the past.

They were secretly contending with Fang Yuan, but the result was they were almost at the verge of coughing out blood, Fang Yuan's rock dissecting results had maintained first place from start to finish.

Rock dissecting relied on the Gu Master's discerning eye, Fang Yuan naturally did not lack in this aspect, he had even started his own rock gambling den in his first life.

As for luck, was Fang Yuan's luck bad?

Not to mention he had connected his luck with several other lucky people, he himself had dogshit luck Immortal Gu to help him.

However, although Fang Yuan obtained victory, it was a rather close one. He maintained superiority from the start, but this superiority was not obvious at times.

The one who exerted such strong pressure on him was Luo Mu Zi.

This person was not a lone immortal, he came from one of Southern Border's super forces — Luo clan.

His insight was very sharp, and most importantly, his luck was quite good, his results were only slightly inferior to Fang Yuan.

"Looks like his luck is quite good."

"Otherwise, he would not have known about Qi Jue's Five Words Poem, isn't that right..."

Fang Yuan thought to himself.

It would not be troubling for him to make a move against Lun Fei, but to target Luo Mu Zi, he had to worry about Luo clan.

Naturally, no matter what he decided to do, Wu Yi Hai's identity absolutely could not be implicated.

By the time the moon appreciation festival ended, it was already deep into the night.

Everyone bid their farewells one after the other, the scene was quite lively.

"I will see you off." Qiao Si Liu took the initiative to see Fang Yuan off.

Luo Mu Zi's and Lun Fei's eyes flushed red.

"Let's go!" Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei were originally competitors and found one another an eyesore, but through the course of tonight's event, they had instead reached a tacit agreement.

The four Gu Immortals left the pavilion successively, leaving behind Fairy Tian Lu and her lover.

"Sigh." Fairy Tian Lu sighed: "Tonight's moon appreciation festival was so tiring."

"Nothing to be done about it." Her lover also sighed, his gaze clear and bright.

Both held each other's hands and smiled as they stepped on the clouds and left.

"This Wu Yi Hai is a complete boor. What in the world did he compose? Can that thing even be called a poem?!" Luo Mu Zi was burning with rage.

"But Fairy Si Liu actually has a completely different view of him!!" Lun Fei gritted his teeth.

"Hmph, what different view, his greatest worth is his identity." Luo Mu Zi said in a slightly envious tone.

Lun Fei's expression was malevolent: "I cannot take this lying down, I cannot let Wu Yi Hai continue living so happily!"

On their way, Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei conversed heatedly.

"Oh? What idea do you have? Wu clan might be facing difficulties from all sides and they might lack the initiative, but they still have the ability to maintain their status. If you want to make a move against Wu Yi Hai, you will have to consider Wu clan. Whether it be publicly or privately, Wu Yong will stand behind Wu Yi Hai. We need to take this relationship properly into account." Luo Mu Zi spoke, he was a righteous path Gu Immortal and was aware of the difficulty here.

If they overestimated their relationship, they would not be able to cause any harm to Wu Yi Hai. But if they underestimated it, who would be able to bear Wu clan's retribution?

Lun Fei curled his lips as he thought: Righteous path Gu Immortals have to worry about everything. On the other hand, the demonic path can directly take action.

However, Lun Fei was not a demonic cultivator, he was a lone cultivator who was more inclined towards the righteous path.

Lun Fei sneered as a sinister light flashed in his eyes: "We don't need to personally make a move. Fairy Si Liu has a lot of pursuers, not just us two. We can inform that person, he will definitely be furious because Fairy Si Liu did not invite him this time."

"You are talking about that guy from Chi clan?" Luo Mu Zi's expression became slightly complex.

That Gu Immortal from Chi clan was the biggest pursuer of Qiao Si Liu. Before tonight, Luo Mu Zi greatly loathed him. But now, he was about to make use of his strength to teach a lesson to Wu Yi Hai.

"Although Wu Yi Hai won against Xia Fei Kuai, it was because he relied on his knowledge of the enemy. If he was strong, why would he have to discuss any conditions with that Mountain Moving Old Monster, he could have directly seized back Mount Snail. That guy from Chi clan is definitely stronger than Wu Yi Hai, moreover, he hates it when others have any desire towards Fairy Si Liu." Lun Fei continued.

Luo Mu Zi's gaze became resolute: "Alright, we will inform Chi Shang of today's matter!"

Qiao Si Liu accompanied Fang Yuan for a distance before she bid a reluctant farewell to Fang Yuan.

But she did not directly return to Qiao clan's headquarters, instead returning to the pavilion.

Inside the pavilion, there was a Gu Immortal sitting on a rock chair and quietly drinking bewitching tea.

This person was Qiao clan's first supreme elder.

The crucial character who had helped Fang Yuan return to Wu clan previously!

Qiao clan's first supreme elder slowly put down the teacup: "Although Wu Yi Hai grew up in Eastern Sea, he is after all Wu Du Xiu's son. So what do you think?"

Qiao Si Liu's gaze was slightly dim as she softly said: "I agree."

Fang Yuan targeted Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei, forcing them to say his poem was good, but in fact it was an indirect attack on Qiao Si Liu.

Qiao Si Liu was well aware that this was the way of a righteous path confrontation, it was all smiles and jovial on the surface, but was actually a maelstrom of dark undercurrents.

Qiao clan's first supreme elder sighed: "Our Qiao clan has all along been allies with Wu clan, but we have never been able to penetrate deep into their core. For the sake of Qiao clan, Wu Yi Hai is a huge opportunity, do you understand?"

Qiao Si Liu bit her lips, her gaze containing reluctance, but she still nodded in the end: "I understand."

Chapter 1321: Can Be Used, But Unreliable

The moon festival passed, but Fang Yuan was still moving about outside.

He took the initiative to get close to Qiao Si Liu, although the latter was angry at his attitude during the moon festival, due to her clan's orders, she was unable to refuse Fang Yuan.

Gradually, rumors began to spread —

Wu clan's Wu Yi Hai and Qiao clan's Qiao Si Liu were very close and often made trips to scenic spots.

Whether it be Wu Yi Hai, Wu Yong's brother, or Qiao Si Liu, one of the three great fairies of Southern Border, they were no doubt famous people in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

Their actions soon led to rumors.

While Qiao Si Liu's pursuers were indignant, they had to admit Wu Yi Hai was an extremely strong rival. Regardless of everything else, just based on Wu clan's and Qiao clan's relations, Wu Yi Hai had an enormous advantage.

Fang Yuan was slightly helpless regarding this.

He actually did not want to become famous, it was better to keep Wu Yi Hai's identity low profile.

A pity that the circumstances went against his wishes, because of Qiao Si Liu, Fang Yuan's fame soared in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world!

This situation soon influenced Fang Yuan.

The number of times someone tried to deduce him, which had just showed signs of decreasing, rose rapidly and even became frequent.

It was very difficult to deal with this situation with just dark limit Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had to often place his aperture down and hide inside his sovereign blessed land.

The immortal aperture was an independent world, isolated from the outside, as long as Fang Yuan did not reveal crucial clues, deductions would become extremely difficult.

Unless someone had clues like those from 'Connect Luck', or had information that could deduce his specific location.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan himself could make use of frequently placing down his aperture in absorbing heaven and earth qi. With the addition of Reverse Flow River, the consumption of heaven and earth qi was truly huge.

Besides placing his aperture, Fang Yuan had to handle Qiao Si Liu while also using Wu clan's channels to get information about Luo Mu Zi and Lun Fei.

It was still not the time for him to make a move.

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

Gu Immortals had endless mysterious methods. With just slight carelessness, one could fail miserably in carrying out a task.

For example, Fang Yuan had actually been able to resist the offense of rank eight Gu Immortals with Reverse Flow River. Before the battle in Snowy Mountain, who could have imagined such a result?

Fang Yuan was cautious, even if he had a plan to take Luo Mu Zi's and Lun Fei's lives, he would only start on the plan after sufficiently understanding their details.

Afterwards, he would accumulate strength, so that when there was an opportunity, he would immediately deal the fatal strike!

Only then would the risks be the lowest, and it would best suit his interests.

Lions used all their strength even when hunting rabbits, let alone Lun Fei and Luo Mu Zi, whom were not weak themselves.

Half a month passed like this, on this day, Wu Yong summoned Fang Yuan.

"Brother, I have few tasks here, choose one of them." Wu Yong said without beating around the bush.

"Brother, please tell me, it is my duty to contribute to the clan." Fang Yuan calmly replied.

An information path mortal Gu flew out of Wu Yong's sleeve, Fang Yuan took a glance and saw this Gu had three tasks recorded.

The first task was related to Xuan Ming Mountain.

Recently, someone discovered that in the depths of Xuan Ming Mountain, there seemed to be the aura of a wild Immortal Gu.

This information had already attracted many lone immortals to make a trip.

More importantly, Yang clan, a super force, had also mobilized its members.

If the information was true, they could obtain an Immortal Gu, which, to any super force, was a joyous matter of being able to increase their foundation, Wu clan naturally would not let go of such a good chance.

Currently, Wu clan's situation was normal, neither good nor bad. Under Wu Yong's command, the clan had already stabilized itself.

Moreover, Xuan Ming Mountain was near Wu clan's territory, although not inside Wu clan's territory, it bordered on it.

If Wu clan did not send its Gu Immortals for this, other super forces would probably think Wu clan had weakened.

As such, Wu Yong intentionally included: If they could not seize the wild Immortal Gu, they must destroy it and could not let it go to Yang clan.

The second task was that red dragon river's water level was rising sharply recently, if it was not controlled, it was very likely to lead to a flood disaster.

If there was a flood, it would be of extreme threat to the nearby living beings. Resources would deplete and it could even change the surrounding environment.

The super forces near red dragon river were paying heavy attention to it.

A portion of red dragon river flowed past the territories of Qiao clan and Wu clan.

They had to send Gu Immortals to inspect the situation and attempt to control the situation to prevent a huge flood.

As for the third task, Yi clan's second supreme elder was holding a banquet for his one thousand two hundredth birthday.

Wu clan needed to send a Gu Immortal to represent the clan in the banquet and deliver the birthday gift.

Yi clan was a powerful clan, its headquarters were in Lin Chi Mountain, which was located in the north-east corner of Southern Border and was the closest to Eastern Sea.

In fact, Yi clan had all sorts of close connections to Eastern Sea.

As for Wu clan, it was located in the southwest area of Southern Border, although it was not at the southwest corner, it was to the farthest south among all the super forces.

Such locations determined that the relation between Yi clan and Wu clan was always maintained at a good level.

Befriend the distant enemy and attack the near ones, this not only applied to the politics and diplomacy of super forces, it was a fundamental principle.

Even though many clans were creating difficulties for Wu clan, Yi clan had never participated in it. To preserve this layer of relation, Wu clan had to send a Gu Immortal to Yi clan second supreme elder's banquet to give well-wishes.

"What do you think, have you decided?" After a while, Wu Yong asked.

Fang Yuan nodded: "I have thought it through, and I choose the second task. My battle strength is not high, choosing to go to Xuan Ming Mountain will probably result in fighting with Yang clan's Gu Immortal, Yang clan is specialized in soul path while I do not excel in dealing with this path."

"Then why not choose the third task?" Wu Yong smiled, "Actually, your status is the most suitable for this task, because you are my brother. You will be very warmly received in Yi clan."

Fang Yuan shook his head, giving a bitter smile: "Brother, spare me. Although it is a birthday banquet, there will definitely be representatives from other super forces. With our Wu clan's current situation, if I go to the banquet, the other Gu Immortals will definitely create difficulties for me. I won't be able to deal with all of them, my own embarrassment is nothing, but more importantly, I would be losing face for Wu clan, that would be too big of a sin."

Wu Yong laughed: "Since you have thought of everything, it will be improper for me to insist. Then let's do it according to your decision."

"Brother, if there aren't other matters, I will bid farewell."

"Go, go." Wu Yong waved his hand.

Fang Yuan turned around, but when he reached the entrance, Wu Yong asked: "Ah, right, when are you going to set off?"

Fang Yuan turned around, standing close to the door: "If red dragon river overflows and turns into a calamity, it will definitely cause countless living beings to suffer. I would not dare to be slow on this important matter, I will simply pack up my things and leave shortly afterwards."

"Good, I can rest at ease then. This matter shall be left to you, you must handle it properly." Wu Yong seemed to be fully confident in Fang Yuan.

"I will certainly do my best!" Fang Yuan solemnly assured, then turned around and left.

However, he did not see that after he left, the smile and confidence in Wu Yong's face slowly disappeared.

Replacing them was a shade of gloominess.

"Success." Fang Yuan's heart was shaking with joy, but he showed no expression on the surface. Just like he said to Wu Yong, he packed some things and immediately set off towards the north.

He was moving rapidly on his way, but when he had just flown across yellow dragon river, Gu Immortal Wu Fa called him to stop: "Lord Wu Yi Hai, please slow down, I have new orders from first supreme elder."

Fang Yuan was laughing on the inside: "Here it comes."

On the surface, however, he showed a surprised expression. He stopped in the air and asked the quickly arriving Wu Fa: "Elder Wu Fa, what's the matter?"

"Oh!" Wu Fa heaved a deep sigh, his aged face filled with anxiety: "There is truth in the saying, when it rains, it pours, there has been an accident over on the super Gu formation's end. Ba clan has been creating difficulties for our clan, Elder Wu Bei, who was stationed there, is injured and is unable to stabilize the situation. Lord, didn't you want to be sent back there? The opportunity is here!"

"First supreme elder was mindful of this and decided to swap Elder Wu Bei with you, to let Elder Wu Bei return to recuperate his injuries. Lord Wu Yi Hai, you will be back in command over at the super Gu formation."

Fang Yuan frowned deeply, looking like he was caught unprepared: "How could this happen? I still..."

As he said this, he seemed to subconsciously glance to the north-west, and said with hesitation: "But red dragon river's issue is quite severe, it needs to be resolved quickly."

"First supreme elder has already made proper arrangements for this matter, Lord Wu Yi Hai, you do not need to worry. Lord, you need to quickly go and stabilize the situation over there. This is a letter Gu that Lord Wu Yong has personally sent you, you can directly go to Yi Tian Mountain without returning to Wu clan." Wu Fa handed an information path mortal Gu to Fang Yuan as he spoke.

Fang Yuan received the letter Gu and immediately scanned it with his consciousness.

The contents of the letter Gu were naturally Wu Yong's voice, saying a serious situation had occurred on the giant dream realm's end and required Fang Yuan to immediately move over there.

Fang Yuan gave a deep sigh: "Looks like I have no choice but to go."

"Please make haste, Lord Wu Yi Hai." Elder Wu Fa looked anxious.

Fang Yuan shook his head, glancing towards the north-west once more before he turned around and flew towards the north-east.

Elder Wu Fa kept on looking at Fang Yuan till he disappeared in the horizons.

He then sneered as he looked at the north-west. Everyone knew there was a mountain in the north-west, Da Peng Mountain, which was Qiao clan's main headquarters.

Elder Wu Fa returned to Wu clan's Wu Yi Mountain and reported to Wu Yong: "First supreme elder, the matter has been handled, Lord Wu Yi Hai is already moving towards the super Gu formation."

Wu Yong was current in the study, he stood up straight, his hand holding a brush which made vigorous movements on a piece of paper.

He slightly nodded at Wu Fa, and suddenly stopped his actions.

There were five large words written on the paper: Can be used, but unreliable.

"A long time ago, when I was still young, mother asked me about my opinion of Qiao clan, I replied with these five words, I can still remember mother's smile very clearly." Wu Yong sighed: "It's a pity my brother has not understood this."

Chapter 1322: Restrictions of the Righteous Path

Southern Border, at the location of Yi Tian Mountain, in the super Gu formation.

"Wu An (Wu Liao) pays respects to Lord Wu Yi Hai." Inside the super Gu formation, Wu clan's Gu Immortals, Wu Liao and Wu An, greeted Fang Yuan respectfully.

Fang Yuan nodded: "Sit down and explain what happened. Elder Wu Bei actually suffered such heavy injuries?"

Wu Liao and Wu An glanced at each other; Wu Liao kept quiet, letting Wu An, who was good with words, report: "Lord, this is what happened..."

Originally, Ba clan was already eager to make a move against Wu clan, and after Wu clan was involved in all kinds of difficulties, the Gu Immortal leading Ba clan here, Old Treeman Ba De, made a move against Wu clan.

Ba De had already been scheming for a long time, and when he made the move, it was so shocking that it put Wu clan into a passive situation.

Wu clan naturally would not just sit still, Wu Bei set forth, but was schemed against by Ba De and had no choice but to have a spar with him.

The result of the spar was naturally Ba clan's victory and Wu clan's defeat.

"It is just that we did not expect Lord Wu Bei's injuries to be so severe. Although Lord Wu Bei lost in the spar, he still had a fearsome air."

"Yes, although he lost to Ba De, Lord Wu Bei was still able to engage in the secret discussion with Qiao clan's and other clan's Gu Immortals. We all thought his injuries were not serious."

When Wu An finished speaking, Wu Liao added in a couple of sentences.

Fang Yuan sneered inwardly, but had a concerned expression on the surface: "I understand the situation, Wu Bei has left and I am here now, everything will be like before, I won't move if the enemy doesn't move."

"Yes, lord." Wu Liao and Wu An immediately responded.

They were not surprised at such a command.

As far as others were concerned, how could Wu Yi Hai's battle strength compare to Ba De's?

Although Wu Yi Hai had recently gained some limelight, his victory against Xia Fei Kuai was only in a spar, furthermore, the rules were decided by him.

Although he had resolved the conflict over Mount Snail, there was no show of might during the whole process and it was resolved through discussion with Mountain Moving Old Monster.

Finally, the rumors with Qiao Si Liu carried the feeling of illicit love, and would not engender respect in others.

"If there is nothing, the two of you may leave. I hurried to get here, I am slightly tired." Fang Yuan waved his hand.

Wu Liao immediately excused himself and left, but Wu An hesitated and said softly: "Lord, there is something I need to report...."

"Speak." Fang Yuan already knew what Wu An wanted to report.

Sure enough, Wu An's words did not deviate from Fang Yuan's expectation, it was related to the matter of dream realm business which Wu clan and other super clans were engaged in.

"The situation is tense now, the other clans are also anxious and fearful, should we stop this business for some time?" Wu An worriedly asked.

Fang Yuan was silent for a moment: "You don't need to worry, I have already said everything will be like before. If there is nothing else, you may leave."

"Yes, lord." A trace of joy flashed past Wu An's face as he bowed and left.

As long as this dream realm's business continued, Wu An could continue to gain profits from it. Why would he not be happy?

Even if the matter turned south and the business was exposed by Ba clan, Wu An's responsibility was still very low. Because his superior, Fang Yuan, had allowed the business to continue like before.

Fang Yuan was obviously well aware of Wu An's thoughts.

He sneered inwardly: "This Wu An is simply shortsighted."

It was true that Wu clan's situation was not too good at the moment, but it was still the number one clan of Southern Border.

Ba De was very astute, although he made a move, he did not target this dream realm business. He knew his limits, because these benefits were not solely enjoyed by Wu clan, but also by other clans.

If he had laid a hand on this business, it would lead to hostility from the other clans, who would then ally with Wu clan to deal with this common enemy.

It was due to his clear insight towards the situation of the whole of Southern Border that he did not target this weakness to create difficulties. This was a significant weakness, but if he used it now, the results would not be optimal at this time. If some day in the future, Wu clan's prestige truly crashed, that would be the time to use this and add fuel to the fire.

Ba De saw this accurately, Fang Yuan did as well.

The matters of the world were like games of chess, the best chess players always planned their future moves, knew when to use certain tactics and what chess pieces would achieve the best result.

As such, the dream realm business could continue to run, what truly decided whether Ba De would make a move or not was not this business itself, but Wu clan!

The matters of the world were often this strange.

The deciding factors of many matters were not the matters themselves, but something that was outside of them.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan subconsciously gazed at the direction of Wu clan.

Wu Yong might be a rank eight Gu Immortal, but was still schemed against by Fang Yuan.

Because this was not a contest of cultivation and battle strength, but experience and methods.

The reason Fang Yuan took the initiative to approach Qiao Si Liu was naturally not for Qiao Si Liu herself, but for something else, that was — to return to the giant dream realm!

Wu Yong could endure Wu Yi Hai's greed, but he could not stand Wu Yi Hai contesting for authority.

This was an expected situation.

The seed had already been planted before Wu Du Xiu passed away. Before she passed away, her last words were that she wanted to give her Immortal Gu to Wu Yi Hai.

Wu Yi Hai's bloodline and origin were already approved, once he gained some authority, he would become a huge threat to Wu Yong's rule.

Just like when Wu Du Xiu was in power, she was wary and on guard against Qiao clan, within Wu clan, Wu Yong was on guard against two threats - Qiao clan and Wu Yi Hai.

Right now, these two were close to each other, even looking like they would wind up together, how could this not make Wu Yong vigilant?

Previously, when Wu Yi Hai had joined Wu clan, Qiao clan had mobilized its agent inside Wu clan, whom unexpectedly was Wu clan's third supreme elder. Many perceptive people were given a fright, how could Wu Yong not be wary?

And now, it looked like Wu Yi Hai was going to collaborate with Qiao clan, how could Wu Yong not make a move early?

Wu Yong's action was quite extraordinary.

He did not directly question if Fang Yuan still wanted to return to the giant dream realm.

He gave Fang Yuan three choices, Xuan Ming Mountain, red dragon river and Yi clan's banquet.

There was deep meaning behind these three choices.

The first task of Xuan Ming Mountain was naturally the most intense task, there was definitely going to be conflict since it concerned a wild Immortal Gu. If Fang Yuan chose this task, it would show he did not fear taking risks for the clan, and Wu Yong could make great use of him in the future.

The third task of Yi clan's banquet was a test. Yi clan had close relations with Eastern Sea, if Fang Yuan chose this task, it would mean he still had attachment towards Eastern Sea in the depths of his heart.

The second task of preventing red dragon river's flood was a trap.

Wu clan and Qiao clan both had territories near red dragon river. Wu clan wanted to prevent a flood, Qiao clan naturally would also do the same.

As such, there would be an opportunity to collaborate with Qiao clan's Gu Immortals.

When Fang Yuan chose this task, Wu Yong's heart had immediately chilled, even if he had been all smiles at that time, he had already made the decision to transfer Wu Yi Hai away as soon as possible! He could not let Wu Yi Hai be in contact with Qiao clan any longer.

Qiao Si Liu was one of the three great fairies of Southern Border, she had astonishingly enchanting beauty. Even if Wu Yi Hai's heart was not moved yet, what about in the future?

Even outstanding men might be unable to resist the charms of a beautiful woman, let alone a beauty like Qiao Si Liu!

Let alone when besides beauty, she was also tied to extraordinary benefits for him.

Once Wu Yi Hai married Qiao Si Liu, it was a hugely profitable matter to both him and Qiao clan.

Wu Yi Hai could use Qiao clan to greatly increase his authority inside Wu clan. And Qiao clan could also finally break their historical limit, with a son-in-law like Wu Yi Hai, this vine that was Qiao clan could truly penetrate deep into the inner core of the giant tree that was Wu clan.

How could Wu Yong make such a mistake?

It was not feasible for him to forcefully break the relationship between the two, it might even backfire if he did not handle it well.

Moreover, the righteous path had to do things according to rules. He could not act willfully like in demonic path.

Wu Yong had thought for a while, but found it was difficult to handle Wu Yi Hai. Despite having evidence of Wu Yi Hai's corruption, Wu Yi Hai was his own brother in the end.

After thinking for a while, Wu Yong thought of the giant dream realm.

He could use this dream realm to 'exile' Wu Yi Hai for as long as possible, after all, wasn't it peaceful when Wu Yi Hai had stayed in the Gu formation earlier?

This past success finally made Wu Yong come to a decision.

He immediately took action after making up his mind. Although he gave Fang Yuan three choices, in truth, he did not let Fang Yuan have any power to choose, they were just a way of testing him.

"The righteous path is like this."

"If one is not at the top, there is no freedom."

"But even when one is at the top, the whole organization will become the shackles that bind them."

Fang Yuan sighed inwardly, but he quickly sorted out his mood and began looking at the dream realm in front of him.

He had returned to this familiar place once again, and there were still two Immortal Gu that belonged to him here.

The dream realm was always expanding and always moving.

"Oh? This dream realm is pretty good, it is a dream realm made of true memories and experiences, and not from absurd imagination."

Soon, Fang Yuan finished inspecting it and entered a shiny bright blue dream realm.

His vision changed.

In a gently sloping hill, a middle-aged Gu Immortal had his back towards Fang Yuan: "My son, do you know why our Tu clan has dominance over this mountain range?"

Fang Yuan inspected himself, he found he had already turned into a child.

"Father, I don't know." He replied after giving it a thought.

"Formation path!" The middle-aged Gu Immortal's voice rose, carrying strong pride within it.

"Formation path?" Fang Yuan mumbled.

"Right! Formation path." The middle-aged Gu Immortal turned around, revealing his aged face and resolute eyes, giving off the air of an authority figure.

"Among the numerous paths, formation path might be the most complicated path. Son, starting today, father will impart to you the essence of formation path and guide you in cultivation." The middle-aged Gu Immortal said with a burning gaze.

"Yes, father, I will definitely study properly." Fang Yuan replied.

The middle-aged Gu Immortal shook his head: "Studying is not enough, you must achieve success, put in all your effort to be the best, be better than all your peers and even those young Gu Immortals. Because you are my, Tu Shi Cheng's son, because you are the future leader of the clan!"

Chapter 1323: Formation Path Contains Countless Paths

"Tu Shi Cheng? I have never heard of this name..." Fang Yuan thought to himself.

Since his father's surname was Tu, this boy Fang Yuan was acting as naturally was surnamed Tu. Being able to leave behind a dream realm meant he indeed had remarkable skill in formation path, but there seemed to be no formation path great experts with the surname Tu in the history of Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan scanned through his memories, but did not have any findings.

Naturally, his knowledge could not encompass the whole of Gu Master history. Maybe this was the dream of a hidden expert.

"Come, sit by me." The middle-aged Gu Immortal sat on the ground, and patted the area beside him.

Fang Yuan quickly sat down beside him.

"My son, do you know how many Gu Master paths there are in this world?" Tu Shi Cheng asked with a warm smile on his face.

Fang Yuan pondered, there were naturally many Gu Master paths, and looking at the trend, even more were starting to thrive. For instance, when Gu Master cultivation had just started to flourish, space path and time path were the mainstream paths, afterwards, wisdom path, qi path, strength path, rule path and other paths emerged one after the other, and now, there were even more paths like fire path, water path, metal path, bone path, poison path and so on.

"Five hundred years later, there is also dream path... innovation never stops, Gu Immortal paths will continue to increase." Fang Yuan pondered inwardly, while replying: "According to what I know, there is space path, time path, hmm, and also qi path, wisdom path and so on."

Tu Shi Cheng nodded: "You are correct, but it is still not detailed. Let me tell you, in Ren Zu's time during the Immemorial Antiquity Era, there were space path and time path, these two paths researched and expounded on the profundities of time and space."

"In the Remote Antiquity Era, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable created qi path and enslavement path, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable created wisdom path and star path, and our formation path was also created during the later period of the Remote Antiquity Era. But its true founder could not be verified. Refinement path and fire path were also created during this period."

"In the Olden Antiquity Era, Limitless Demon Venerable created rule path, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable created transformation path. Strength path, wind path, light path and dark path were also created in this era."

"In the Medieval Antiquity Era, Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable created wood path, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created theft path, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable created luck path. Moreover, metal path, water path, ice and snow path, cloud path, earth path, lightning path, information path and sound path emerged one after another, this was an era where all kinds of diverse paths appeared."

"And in our present era, bone path was created, there are also phantom path and restriction path. Naturally, what I mentioned are only the mainstream Gu Master paths, minor paths like enchantment path, illusion path, and others will be omitted for now."

Fang Yuan immediately came to an understanding when he heard these words.

"So this dream realm is set in the Late Antiquity Era. Right now, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable has yet to appear, otherwise Tu Shi Cheng would have mentioned him."

Tu Shi Cheng continued: "Son, I have elaborated on so much because I want to tell you our formation path is one of the longest standing paths in history. Although it cannot be compared to space path and time path, it was created in the same era as qi path and wisdom path. Just based on seniority, it appeared even before transformation path."

As he said this, Tu Shi Cheng asked: "The essence of transformation path is to project countless paths, son, what do you think is the essence of formation path?"

Although Fang Yuan's attainment in formation path was extremely ordinary, this question was fairly simple and common, he knew about it.

He replied: "Formation path contains countless paths."

"Haha, good answer!" Tu Shi Cheng did not stint on his praise, and gave a deeper explanation: "Our formation path can set up Gu formations, which can use Gu worms of space path and time path, we can also use Gu worms of metal path, wood path, fire path, water path and so on. Just because of this, formation path can be said to be the most complex path among all the paths."

"Setting up a Gu formation is very difficult, because it might need to use Gu worms of many other paths. As such, when cultivating formation path, we need to have some understanding of other paths, even if the understanding is not deep, we need to have basic knowledge of them, at the least, we need to have deep understanding of the Gu worms we are using."

Fang Yuan continued to nod while listening.

This was one of the difficulties of formation path cultivation.

Actually, every path had some areas which it was proficient in and weak in. For instance, cultivating enslavement path allowed one to fight many by oneself, but it had an extremely huge demand on resources.

Cultivating and learning formation path was a large obstacle, because it involved Gu worms of other paths. Formation path Gu worms were only the foundation and framework of a Gu formation, the rest of the content required large numbers of Gu worms from other paths.

Because of this, it was difficult to learn and master formation path.

Nurturing a formation path expert was not easy. On one hand, it had high demand towards resources, time and knowledge, on the other hand, the Gu Master needed to have talent for it and put in effort as well.

As such, in the Gu Immortal world, there had always been very few Gu Immortals who specialized in formation path.

Naturally, this rarity was only relative, at the very least, there were more formation path Gu Immortals than wisdom path Gu Immortals.

This was also the reason why Fang Yuan had not involved himself in formation path in the five hundred years of his previous life.

The barrier to entry was high, and it was difficult to learn.

"Son, since you have become a Gu Master today, I will give you your first Gu worm." At this time, Tu Shi Cheng's palm slowly opened, revealing a small Gu worm.

This Gu looked like a ladybug, its carapace was glossy and round, it was as small as a little finger, and it had a glistening yellow shine, giving a cute appearance.

"This is formation heart Gu, come, refine it first." Tu Shi Cheng said.

With Tu Shi Cheng's help, Fang Yuan directly refined this rank one Gu worm.

Formation heart Gu's carapace opened up, the thin wings inside continuously flapped as it merrily flew around its new master, Fang Yuan.

This Gu worm was not precious and could even be said to be extremely ordinary.

Because it was one of the most basic Gu worms to lay a formation, and was commonly available throughout the five regions.

"Alright, let's play a game." Tu Shi Cheng smiled, taking out four Gu worms.

"They are all rank one Gu, I will lend them to you temporarily. Come, use your formation heart Gu as the core, choose the Gu worms from here and arrange them, see if you can form a Gu formation."

Fang Yuan's eyebrows slightly rose, glancing at Tu Shi Cheng in surprise.

Was this a joke?

This boy had just become a Gu Master, and he wanted him to construct a Gu formation on the same day?

Although Fang Yuan had not truly cultivated formation path, he had some superficial knowledge of formation path. For instance, normally speaking, this youth should only be involved in constructing a Gu formation after at least two to three months, After all, he had just become a Gu Master, controlling a Gu worm was strenuous, everything was new to him, calculating primeval essence, nourishing the aperture, feeding Gu worms, and other aspects, they all required him to adapt and train.

Now, in this dream, this Tu Shi Cheng was actually asking his son, a boy who had just become a Gu Master, to construct a Gu formation?

"Hah, this style of education is truly 'original'... fortunately, it is a dream realm and it is all up to me. How could a normal child accomplish this task? Or maybe... it is because he could not accomplish this, his obsession turned into this dream realm?"

While guessing, he sized up the four Gu worms.

But, he actually was not able to recognize them all!

With his knowledge, he only recognized three of them, and could not identify the remaining one.

It was somewhat awkward.

But when he thought of it, it was also not strange.

The time period of this dream was the Late Antiquity Era, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had not appeared yet, thus the situation compared to the present was very different.

Moreover, there were countless Gu worms, unique and mysterious. There were also many innovated Gu worms and many secretly guarded Gu worms, of which little were known by others. How could Fang Yuan know of all the Gu worms?

Even though he was not able to recognize them all, Fang Yuan was still aware of the paths of these four Gu worms.

They were of earth path, water path, wind path and fire path.

The one that Fang Yuan did not recognize was the earth path Gu worm.

"To construct a Gu formation, I need to first understand these Gu worms. There is no need to worry about formation heart Gu, but what use does this earth path Gu worm have?" Fang Yuan intended to test this Gu and see its ability.

But this action was stopped by Tu Shi Cheng.

Tu Shi Cheng spoke with solemness: "Use your heart to sense it, listen to the sound of your heart, rely on your feelings. Construct the Gu formation according to your feelings. Remember, you only have one chance."

Fang Yuan was immediately dumbfounded.

Chapter 1324: Fang Yuan's Two Trump Cards

Although Tu Shi Cheng was the father of this boy that Fang Yuan was disguised as, he was completely unreliable.

What did he mean by rely on feelings?

Innate talents could not be embodied like this.

If the construction of the Gu formation failed, in a minor case, the Gu worms would be injured or destroyed, and in a severe case, the Gu Master themselves would suffer the backlash. If one could create a Gu formation just by relying on feelings, formation path Gu Immortals would not be so rare in the present five regions.

Arranging a Gu formation was a precise and rigorous task, like deducing Immortal Gu recipes. They both were similar, requiring a process, detailed consideration and continuous tests.

However, since the dream realm was like this, Fang Yuan calmed his mind, and continued to ponder how he should tackle this situation where it seemed he truly had to do it in the way Tu Shi Cheng said.

Fang Yuan asked: "Do I need to use all the four Gu worms?"

"Of course not. But you need to at least select two to set up a Gu formation." Tu Shi Cheng replied.

"I simply don't know about this earth path Gu worm, so it will be better to give it up." Fang Yuan continued to think, as such, he had three choices in front of him.

"Hurry up, don't think too much, rely on your feelings!" Just as Fang Yuan had spent slightly longer in thinking, Tu Shi Cheng's expression sank a little, urging: "I will give you three breaths of time."

Three breaths of time?

And there was only one chance!

Wasn't he purposely making it difficult?

A thought flashed past Fang Yuan's mind: "Do I need to use unravel dream?"

His current accumulation was already different from the past. Last time, when he explored the giant dream realm, he had limited quantities of dream path mortal Gu, which led to a limited number of times that unravel dream could be used, Fang Yuan had to be very efficient when using it.

But it was different now.

Fang Yuan had enough confidence.

Because he had captured many nightmare demonic colts, using these natural dream path immortal materials along with his persistent refinement, he now possessed very many dream path mortal Gu.

Thus, the number of times he could use unravel dream was at a peak now.

Precisely because of this, Fang Yuan had an unprecedented amount of confidence.

"Forget it. This is only the first layer of the dream realm, even if it fails, I can continue to explore. Although I can use unravel dream much more now, I cannot waste it like this."

Fang Yuan thought for a moment and gave up on using unravel dream.

He began to activate the Gu worms.

First was formation heart Gu.

This yellow ladybug was already refined by him, his primeval essence was consumed, it immediately hovered and stopped in front of Fang Yuan, shining with pale yellow light.

"Fire path, water path, wind path..."

Fang Yuan mumbled, since he had given up on the earth path Gu worm, then he only had these three choices remaining.

He chose the rank one water path Gu worm.

The reason for this choice was simple, his fire path and wind path attainment levels were ordinary, but in water path, he was a grandmaster!

Grandmaster attainment was not for show.

The water path Gu worm was successfully activated, it was bathed in the yellow light and revolved around the formation heart Gu, flying up and down.

"Fire path and wind path..."

Fang Yuan chose wind path.

The wind path Gu worm also mixed in, and like the water path Gu worm, it flew around the formation heart Gu. It was just that the wind path Gu worm was in the periphery, while the water path Gu worm was nearer to the formation heart Gu.

Fang Yuan waited for a bit. Among these three Gu worms, one was hovering in the air while the other two were continuously flying around, they were all activated but were still extremely stable.

"Although they have not formed a true Gu formation, this progress is quite good." Fang Yuan was slightly pleased.

To use an analogy, arranging a Gu formation was like building blocks.

Each Gu worm was a strangely shaped building block, the Gu Master needed to arrange these building blocks into the shape they wanted. These scattered building blocks would form high towers, buildings and other shapes, creating an effect that far surpassed the individual building block.

Although Fang Yuan had not successfully arranged these building blocks into a shape, these three Gu worms were at least mutually compatible and did not collapse.

This was quite good progress.

However, a trace of gloominess and disappointment flashed past Tu Shi Cheng's eyes.

Fang Yuan, who was focused on setting up the Gu formation, did not notice it.

"Now, I need to adjust it."

"Does the formation heart Gu need to stay in the center?"

"Can the positions of the water path and wind path Gu be swapped? Water path inside, and wind path outside, can I adjust it to water path outside, and wind path inside?"

"Or maybe, the water path Gu and the wind path Gu can be together, should I let the wind path Gu revolve around the water path Gu instead of the formation heart Gu?"

As Fang Yuan pondered, all kinds of plans emerged in his mind.

He did not know what results these plans could give, or what effects would they have.

His formation path attainment was truly too lacking.

"Rely on your feelings, stop hesitating." Tu Shi Cheng urged, looking somewhat impatient.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, actually, he didn't need Tu Shi Cheng's urging, he also knew he had to take action.

If nothing else, his primeval essence was about to dry up.

In the dream realm, he had just become a Gu Master, although he had A grade aptitude, he was activating three Gu worms at the same time, which intensely burdened on his primeval essence.

He already did not have much time to think.

"Let's give it a try then." Fang Yuan inwardly gritted his teeth, as he activated the fire path Gu worm as well, putting it inside the newly created structure.

He made no changes to the previous foundation.

Because he did not know what use making changes would have, and also did not know if there was a need to make changes.

He was a pure beginner with no feeling for the right action, the attempt was done blindly.

"But my luck is good, maybe I can succeed by chance?" Fang Yuan still had some hope.

But soon, his hope was ruined.

The moment the fire path Gu worm was added in, it immediately led to a chain reaction.

The fire path Gu's strength joined with the wind path Gu, immediately increasing the power. This immediately conflicted with the water path Gu that was inside, water and fire were opposing forces, immediately creating an explosion.

A soft explosion echoed, it was not intense, but it still exploded, covering Fang Yuan's face with black soot.

His hair stood up on end, white smoke was rising.

At the same time, the formation heart Gu was directly destroyed, the other three Gu worms were also injured to various degrees; the water path and fire path Gu worms were on the verge of death, while the wind path Gu worm was also heavily injured.

"You have failed!" Tu Shi Cheng's expression changed, he said with a cold tone: "You truly disappoint me."

Guh.

Fang Yuan's vision changed as he was expelled out of the dream realm.

The first exploration had failed.

His soul returned to his body, his body slightly shook, his healthy complexion suddenly paled.

Fang Yuan immediately inspected his injuries, and found that the injury to his soul was much more severe than he expected.

But it did not matter.

Guts Gu!

Fang Yuan took out a guts Gu and crushed it, the injuries of his soul were immediately relieved greatly. Fang Yuan used another guts Gu, and immediately his soul injuries were completely healed.

The slight sense of vertigo had disappeared at once.

Because he had guts Gu, Fang Yuan was not afraid of failing in his dream realm exploration and his soul being injured.

"Right now, I should be the first person to explore the dream realm. Even Shadow Sect's remnant forces won't be able to catch up to me." Fang Yuan calculated.

This was because he had two great trump cards to explore dream realms.

First was guts Gu, it could heal soul injuries.

Second was unravel dream. Once used, it would get one straight to solving the problem, its usefulness was somewhat unreasonable.

Guts Gu came from Dang Hun Mountain, Fang Yuan had placed Dang Hun Mountain in Lang Ya blessed land, and was even cooperating with Lang Ya Sect in trading guts Gu.

They had a monopoly on guts Gu business, they were the only ones producing it, and its demand was always higher than its supply.

Recently, Fang Yuan had not been selling his portion of the guts Gu for profit, instead, he was accumulating them.

He had a single objective, to be fully prepared in exploring the dream realm.

Thus, he had large numbers of guts Gu with him. Because of this, he was short on money, and had no choice but to expand the scale of some of his resources to improve his finances.

The first failure did not matter.

With guts Gu, Fang Yuan's soul immediately recovered, and could go for a second exploration.

But he was not hurried, instead using connecting heaven Gu to let his divine sense enter treasure yellow heaven.

He began to gather information.

First was that earth path mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan did not recognize it, so he needed to understand it.

Fang Yuan soon bought a set of \<\<The Encyclopedia of Earth Path Gu Worms\>\> from an earth path Gu Immortal.

This was an information transaction and was among the businesses in treasure yellow heaven.

There were transactions of methods to target against Gu worms, there were introductions and understandings of Gu paths, there was news of the present political situation, there were also deductions of time path and wisdom path Gu Immortals on the past, present and future.

Fang Yuan naturally could rely on his five hundred years of experiences to sell information that could definitely attract people.

But this kind of information was normally very cheap, and not long after selling them, Fang Yuan's rebirth advantage would weaken, so Fang Yuan had never even considered it.

Fang Yuan was not satisfied with just this Gu Immortal's work, \<\<The Encyclopedia of Earth Path Gu Worms\>\>, and bought some relevant information, naturally including some mortal formation path inheritances.

These cost him close to ten immortal essence stones.

To Fang Yuan, this was just peanuts.

He soon learned of that earth path mortal Gu from the information he bought. This was a Gu worm that appeared in the early stages of the Late Antiquity Era. It was soon extinct, because the Gu materials required to refine it had been wiped out. The information recorded briefly introduced this earth path Gu worm's ability. Fang Yuan even obtained the recipe of this earth path mortal Gu from another information source.

Chapter 1325: Four Elements Concept

Naturally, the practicality of this Gu recipe was extremely low.

Because most of the materials for this Gu no longer existed.

If Fang Yuan wanted to refine this mortal Gu, he would have to modify the recipe.

He naturally would not do such a pointless thing. With the information he gathered, he already had a deep understanding of this mortal Gu.

Next, Fang Yuan read those mortal formation path inheritances.

This enriched some of his formation path foundation.

Despite him not having taken the initiative to research formation path, he had come into contact with it indirectly in his first life, or come across some formation path contents in fortuitous encounters.

As such, this enrichment was limited and not high in scope.

It was just that he was only focusing on the test in the dream realm this time.

He had an objective when gathering the formation path information, and he knew from some information: In the Late Antiquity Era, formation path had a prevailing concept.

This concept stated that the four basic elements of earth, water, wind and fire could make a Gu formation stable, they could make most basic Gu formations and were the most inclusive.

Naturally, this concept only prevailed for some time, after dozens of years, it went out of favor. Compared to the whole history of formation path, dozens of years was too short, this concept was like a small ripple that disappeared in the long river of history.

"It is just like the origins of mankind. On Earth, people once believed that humans were made by divine beings, be it the Chinese concept of Nüwa creating mankind, or the Western concept of God creating mankind. This was an ideology that lasted for a long time, and after it dominated people's thinking for a long period, it was broken by Darwin's theory of evolution. But in regards to whether Darwin's theory of evolution pointed precisely to the truth or not, as science develops, people over time may find flaws in it."

Fang Yuan's thoughts were wandering.

This earth, water, wind and fire concept was similar.

Following formation path's development, people started to find that the Gu formations created by the four basic elements of earth, water, wind and fire were not the most inclusive formations.

People made new discoveries, continuously deepening their knowledge and continuously progressing. Even though this concept was abandoned not long after, back then, it was progress of some kind.

This information was quite valuable, it directly gave Fang Yuan the correct way to pass the first stage of the dream realm.

"It turns out that I had to use all the Gu worms to truly create a Gu formation." Fang Yuan gained an epiphany.

At the same time, he sighed: "This Tu Shi Cheng is really quite deceitful, clearly all four Gu worms had to be used, but he actually played dumb and said I needed to use at least two mortal Gu."

Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

Even though he knew this, he still did not know how to make the four Gu worms revolve around formation heart Gu to build an effective Gu formation.

If these four mortal Gu could be refined, Fang Yuan could test it out in reality.

This was also a common method used by laymen in deciphering dream realms in the early stages.

But now, that earth path Gu worm was difficult to refine, even if he refined an earth path mortal Gu by modifying the Gu recipe, could it truly be the same as the one in the dream realm?

This was a dream realm, sometimes there would be some differences in the dream realm from reality, and it was not a direct reproduction of reality.

Fang Yuan pondered, and decided it was better to test it in the dream realm.

The second attempt played out like before. But this time, Fang Yuan chose to activate all these four mortal Gu at the same time and coordinate them with formation heart Gu.

It failed.

The four mortal Gu self-detonated simultaneously, Fang Yuan was injured and kicked out of the dream realm.

The third attempt, Fang Yuan chose to use the earth path Gu worm first, and water path Gu worm second, but it failed again.

Following the fourth attempt and fifth attempt... only by the seventh attempt did Fang Yuan succeeded.

The four mortal Gu were flying around formation heart Gu. The water path and fire path Gu worms were flying in an elliptic orbit, sometimes near and sometimes far from formation heart Gu. Earth path Gu was hovering below formation heart Gu, while the wind path Gu was hovering above, both were still.

Under the control of formation heart Gu, these four Gu worms formed a mysterious force that continuously let out hazy rainbow colors.

A Gu Master's primeval essence would recover at twice the speed inside this light.

"To Gu Masters, this is an extremely practical Gu formation!" Fang Yuan thought to himself.

"Hahaha, good, very good, you are truly my son, you have natural talent for formation path after all!" Tu Shi Cheng laughed loudly and happily at Fang Yuan's success.

Fang Yuan: "..."

The hill, the sky, and the land slowly disappeared from Fang Yuan's vision.

The first stage of the dream realm was over, the second stage was starting.

Fang Yuan breathed out a sigh of relief, he had persisted on not using unravel dream in the first stage, in the end, only about ten or so guts Gu were consumed, the total expenses were still low.

Without checking how much his formation path attainment had risen, Fang Yuan focused his attention on the surroundings.

He discovered he was in a cage.

And inside this enormous cage, there was a smaller cage.

Inside this cage was a pitch black panther, it was skinny and its eyes shined with mad hunger, indicating how dangerous it was right now.

"What's going on?" Fang Yuan was bewildered.

Right at this moment, Tu Shi Cheng, who was standing outside the cage, said to Fang Yuan: "I will give you five minutes to arrange these Gu worms into a Gu formation. After five minutes are over, this panther will be released, I absolutely won't make a move at that time, and will only see if you can use the Gu formation to resist this panther."

"What?!" Fang Yuan's eyes opened wide.

This method of education, hey, are you really this kid's father?

"You are the son of Tu Shi Cheng, you can definitely do it. If you can't do it, then you are not worthy of being my son!" Tu Shi Cheng continued with an expressionless face.

"My goodness!" Fang Yuan thought, lips twitching as he looked at himself.

He found that he had not grown much and not much time had passed since the first stage, he was at most about the age of fourteen.

"This Tu Shi Cheng looks like he should be a righteous path Gu Immortal, why is he so heartless? Maybe this is intimidation to force his son to fully release his potential?"

Fang Yuan speculated inwardly.

"Regardless of who this Tu Shi Cheng's son is, he is truly unlucky."

Time was limited, Fang Yuan calmed his mood and began to inspect the Gu worms he had.

The caged panther was only an ordinary beast, but with his current young body, he definitely could not oppose it.

He could only make a Gu formation to resist it.

There were five Gu worms, they were still rank one. Among them, one was formation heart Gu, while the other four belonged to earth path, wind path, water path and fire path.

It was almost the same as in the first stage.

The difference was that although the paths were the same, the four Gu worms were different ones from the first stage.

How should he group these Gu worms to form a Gu formation?

Fang Yuan began to try.

With the precious experience from the first stage, Fang Yuan was quite proficient.

The first attempt quickly failed, Fang Yuan spat out a mouthful of blood in the dream realm due to the backlash, but fortunately, the Gu worms were not injured.

He was also not expelled from the dream realm.

"Looks like I can continue to try until the limit of five minutes is reached?"

"Although there are still chances to continue, there is in fact almost no hope."

Fang Yuan frowned.

Because of the injuries, although nothing happened to the Gu worms, his own state was very bad, his primeval essence had depleted and he was injured.

Fang Yuan soon discovered that because of the injuries, when he continued to try again, he was unsteady, and although the Gu worms flew up, they were shaking.

The second attempt also failed.

There was more time left, but Fang Yuan was unable to continue attempting, because a Gu worm had died in the second failure.

If it were any of the other paths mortal Gu, it would not be the end, but it just happened to be the formation heart Gu.

"Father, my Gu worm is destroyed, can you give me another formation heart Gu?" Fang Yuan quickly asked.

But the reply he got was a ruthless shake of the head from Tu Shi Cheng: "What if you were in a battle, who would give you a substitute Gu worm? Son, you disappointed me, you have no chances left."

Sure enough, the moment the time limit was reached, the small cage opened up and the panther pounced forward, biting at Fang Yuan's throat instantly.

This dream realm was extremely realistic, Fang Yuan could clearly sense his throat being torn, his breathing becoming difficult, the heartrending pain that came when his skin was ripped apart by the panther's sharp fangs.

Blood spewed out rapidly from his wounds, and the panther drank it contentedly.

Tu Shi Cheng shook his head, sighing: "You are not worthy of being my son."

He then turned around and left.

"Not giving the solution even at the end, is this Tu Shi Cheng of the righteous path or demonic path?" After being expelled from the dream realm, Fang Yuan's soul returned to his body, he was naturally gloomy.

After using guts Gu to heal his injuries, he continued to explore.

Second failure, third failure, forth failure...

Every time he failed, Fang Yuan would be killed by the panther and relive the miserable pain from being eaten alive.

If it were any other person, their mind might have already collapsed.

However, Fang Yuan was not afraid, he had suffered pain beyond this an uncountable number of times.

He only treated the pain as a cool breeze blowing across his face, his mind still focused on constructing the Gu formation.

Tenth failure, eleventh, twelfth...

This second stage was much more difficult than the first stage. After Fang Yuan was expelled from the dream realm, his soul injuries were also much more severe than what he suffered in the first stage.

His soul would be healed using just two guts Gu in the first stage, but in the second stage, he needed at least three guts Gu and sometimes even four to be healed.

Fang Yuan calmly calculated his expenses.

"If this continues, the cost will become steeper, do I have to use unravel dream?"

"Wait."

While he was feeling troubled, he suddenly had an inspiration.

He entered the dream realm and continued to attempt it.

There was a way!

Chapter 1326: Rise in Formation Path Attainment Level

A while later, after two tries, Fang Yuan successfully constructed a Gu formation in the dream realm.

This Gu formation still used formation heart Gu as the core, it was just that the earth path Gu worm was hovering above the formation heart Gu, while the fire path and wind path Gu worms revolved around the water path Gu worm. And the water path Gu worm spanned the distance of a hand below the formation heart Gu, continuously moving up and down.

The Gu formation made by these Gu worms emitted a hazy white light that shrouded the panther.

That's right.

This Gu formation was an entrapment Gu formation targeted at the panther, and did not protect the Gu Master themselves.

Constructing it was not easy. The panther continuously moved around, influencing the construction of the Gu formation. Occasionally, Fang Yuan had to stop and wait for the panther to move away from a specific location[1].

This was also the reason why Tu Shi Cheng gave five minutes, Fang Yuan needed the time to arrange the formation.

"Hahaha, good, you are indeed my son! You will continue to study with me in the following days. In a month, there will be an even stricter test which will concern your life and death. If you cannot pass, you shall die." Tu Shi Cheng laughed, his laughter containing madness.

Fang Yuan's young body was standing inside the cage, he glanced at the panther that was constantly struggling inside the Gu formation, and then glanced at Tu Shi Cheng, sighing softly.

This formation path dream realm's second stage was passed.

Next was the third stage.

Fang Yuan followed Tu Shi Cheng to a riverside where the tides were coming in fast.

Looking at the water of this river that was flowing to the east and was red like blood, Fang Yuan immediately realized: this was Southern Border's red dragon river.

Southern Border had three great rivers that passed through the whole region, red dragon river, jade dragon river and yellow dragon river.

Fang Yuan immediately had a bad feeling when he saw this river.

Sure enough, at the next moment, he heard Tu Shi Cheng's voice: "I have already lent you the Gu worms, now you can only depend on yourself, if you cannot construct a Gu formation, you are well aware of the consequences."

Fang Yuan was just about to speak to stall for time, but he was slapped on the back by Tu Shi Cheng.

Fang Yuan was simply unable to resist the enormous strength and was immediately pushed into red dragon river.

"F*ck!" Fang Yuan cursed inwardly as he fell into the surging river and was immediately swept away by the current helplessly.

Fang Yuan struggled with all his might, he only had a young body, fortunately, Fang Yuan's swimming ability was carried over, and after struggling for a while, he was able to raise his head out of the water and took in large breaths.

Making the best use of his time, Fang Yuan inspected the Gu worms he had.

"Damn it!" Soon, he mentally cursed once again, because this time, it was not just the four mortal Gu like he expected, but twelve.

He had to arrange them in such a short period of time?

There were too many ways to arrange them, and under such terrible conditions, hope was slim.

Fang Yuan did not hesitate this time, and directly activated unravel dream!

Immediately, an answer appeared in his mind.

He immediately understood the first three steps of how to activate the Gu worms and arrange the Gu formation.

"Only the first three steps?" Fang Yuan had no choice but to continue to activate unravel dream, the fourth step, fifth step and sixth step also appeared in his mind.

It was an accurate and precise answer.

But there were still some steps from being able to construct the Gu formation.

Fang Yuan was just about to activate unravel dream for the third time, when suddenly a change occurred in the river, and he was swallowed by a whirlpool.

Bam, a muffled sound echoed.

Fang Yuan crashed head-first into a tree floating in the whirlpool, falling unconscious immediately.

The next moment, Fang Yuan woke up, he had returned to reality.

His soul was severely injured, making him see stars.

He quickly used guts Gu, one, two... six guts Gu before he finally recovered.

"The third stage is even more difficult, the environment to arrange the formation is so hazardous."

"But..."

"My formation path attainment has already advanced to quasi-master level."

After Fang Yuan realized it, he slowly opened his eyes with a trace of joy.

What was attainment level?

Attainment level was a Gu Master's unique cognition, involving their sensations and experiences, their insights towards nurturing, using, refining Gu and so on, summed up and condensed. It was their comprehension of the Great Dao of heaven and earth.

Attainment levels were divided into five levels, ordinary, master, grandmaster, great grandmaster and supreme grandmaster.

Naturally, in-between these, there were small levels like quasi-master, quasi-grandmaster and quasi-great grandmaster.

Ordinary attainment was the level that most Gu Masters would reach in their lifetimes.

Quasi-master attainment was already rare. Young Gu Masters with outstanding aptitude or experienced old Gu Masters could reach this.

Master level was when the use of Gu worms went beyond superficial workmanship to the level of an art. It was rare to find even one master among ten thousand Gu Masters. For example, during the contest of Imperial Court, there were only five enslavement path masters - Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying, Ma Zun, Chang Shan Yin (Fang Yuan) and Nu Er Tu. Naturally, the one in ten thousand was referring to mortals, to rank six Gu Immortals, their main paths were this level at minimum.

Those who possessed quasi-grandmaster attainment were often elites among rank six Gu Immortals.

Grandmaster level was when one had a very profound grasp of the path, having deep foundations and being able to mimic the effects of other paths. Specifically, the main path's Gu worms could be used to imitate the advantages of other paths. Hei Fan's true inheritance had an immortal killer move, hundred years harmony, which was a classic example. It used time path Gu worms to produce an effect of information path. This also showed that Hei Fan's time path attainment level was at least grandmaster.

Normally speaking, there were few Gu Immortals that could attain grandmaster level. It often required a hundred years or even hundreds of years of accumulation, along with natural talent. In Fang Yuan's first life, he had attained grandmaster in blood path only in the latter stage of his five hundred years of life.

Those whom were able to have grandmaster attainment level were mostly rank seven Gu Immortals.

Above grandmaster was quasi-great grandmaster, which was even rarer, they were often rank seven experts or certain rank eights.

As for great grandmaster level, most rank eight Gu Immortals would attain this in their lifetimes.

Those whom were able to attain quasi-supreme grandmaster were scarce, few produced even in thousands of years.

The rarity of supreme grandmasters need not be explained, for instance, in refinement path, there were only three supreme grandmasters in history. Among them was a hairy man — Long Hair Ancestor.

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level could not even be counted as ordinary, but now it had soared to quasi-master level.

Most Gu Masters would find it difficult to reach this in their lifetimes, no matter how much effort they put in.

Fang Yuan had attained this just by using up a few days of time and exploring two stages of the dream realm.

This was the power of dream realms.

They contained true meaning, once a Gu Immortal successfully explored a dream realm and obtained the true meaning, their attainment level would be directly raised and their understanding of part of the Great Dao would be deepened.

"Just two stages were enough to advance to quasi-master level in formation path, this dream realm is extraordinary."

"No wonder it has such difficulty."

"But I really haven't heard of Tu Shi Cheng..."

His method of education was truly unique, leaving Fang Yuan speechless. But the person he was educating was this dream realm's source. This youth was clearly a major character.

Fang Yuan could clearly sense he was only a step away from master level in formation path.

"As long as I complete the third stage, my formation path attainment level will soar to master!"

Fang Yuan excitedly licked his lips.

A successful exploration of the dream realm raised his foundation, this increase was so huge, allowing Fang Yuan to go through an extraordinary shortcut, and he was unable to stop desiring for more.

But since he had already left the dream realm, Fang Yuan was not in haste to go back in.

He recalled all the scenes in the third stage, especially the Gu worms with him.

He had only recognized sixty percent of them, thus he was now searching for information on these Gu worms to increase his understanding.

These were all mortal Gu, it was just that most of them had long since vanished in history.

Fang Yuan soon found the information he wanted, and gained an understanding of these mortal Gu.

Then he began to re-read those mortal formation path inheritances he had bought before.

The feeling he got from reading this time was a completely different experience from before!

Previously, Fang Yuan only saw the surface of most of the contents of the inheritances, but now, he was able to see their deeper meanings with just one look. They were clearly things he had already read, but Fang Yuan made new discoveries this time.

This feeling was extremely mysterious, like sudden enlightenment.

However, there were things which Fang Yuan could not completely comprehend.

After all, he was only at quasi-master, some outstanding characters among mortal Gu Masters could reach master level. The inheritances they left behind naturally had some things Fang Yuan could not understand properly at the moment.

Fang Yuan was immersed in the profundity of formation path, unaware of the passing time.

If he was thirsty, he drank water, if he was hungry, he ate some fruits.

Many thoughts emerged and disappeared like waves in his mind, he was using wisdom path methods to help quicken his progress of learning formation path.

Formation path's contents were truly vast, having connections with every path. Thus, it was considered the most complicated path.

Only when Wu An requested an audience did Fang Yuan slowly come back to his senses.

"Unknowingly, eight days have already passed..." Fang Yuan was in a daze for a moment before his gaze slowly cleared up.

In his mind, most of the disordered thoughts gradually faded.

For the last ten days, Fang Yuan was lost in the learning process, not only did his formation path attainment level receive a boost, his comprehension of various basic contents of formation path had also strengthened.

"What is he here for?" Fang Yuan impatiently furrowed his brows.

But after thinking for a moment, he still decided to see this Wu clan Gu Immortal.

As it turned out, Wu An brought over Lady White Rabbit, who reported the situation of the dream realm business and gave concrete accounts to Fang Yuan for inspection.

Despite Fang Yuan not placing attention on this business, he was, after all, the leader of the whole business.

As a subordinate, Lady White Rabbit had to hand over the report.

[1] Pokemon Ranger vibes. Back

Chapter 1327: Letter of Challenge to Chi Shang

Fang Yuan roughly skimmed through the accounts, increasing his understanding of the forces around him. He then asked Wu An and Lady White Rabbit to leave.

"Lord, there is a matter, I don't know if I should speak of it or not." Before leaving, Wu An spoke with some hesitation.

"Speak." Fang Yuan was straightforward.

Wu An reported to Fang Yuan that there were some rumors recently saying that Chi clan Gu Immortal Chi Shang was coming over to inspect the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan immediately understood Wu An's meaning, and waved for him to leave.

"Qiao Si Liu has many pursuers, this Chi Shang is the most important one among them."

"He has never taken the initiative to do an inspection, this time, he is most likely coming over to find trouble with me."

However, righteous path Gu Immortals could not disregard all considerations and engage in life and death battle. At most, there would be a drop in reputation.

"At worst, I will give up my reputation and avoid fighting." Fang Yuan rubbed his chin: "But I also need to prevent my secrets from being exposed. After all, this super Gu formation was built under the leadership of Chi clan. Among Southern Border's super forces, Chi clan is absolutely the number one force in formation path."

Fang Yuan already understood those mortal formation path contents clearly, and there were only a few things which he could not understand completely.

However, when he looked at this super Gu formation he was in, there was still no change, he was still dazzled like an ant facing a vast river of stars.

Chi clan's first supreme elder had personally set up this super Gu formation, he was a great grandmaster in formation path!

Chi Shang's arrival was quicker than everyone's expectations.

A banquet to welcome him was essential.

Because Chi Shang represented Chi clan in this trip, what's more, he was responsible for inspecting around the super Gu formation to see if there were any defensive flaws and so on.

During the banquet, everyone interacted with each other, portraying a cohesive gathering on the outside, but secretly, there were undercurrents brewing.

The perceptive people knew this was not originally Chi Shang's task, but he had taken the initiative for this duty. Everyone in Southern Border knew Chi Shang was pursuing Qiao Si Liu, but in these recent times, there were rumors of Wu Yi Hai being very close with Qiao Si Liu.

Chi Shang's objective in this trip was self-evident.

But unfortunately, Fang Yuan did not partake in this banquet, instead holed up in the Gu formation, continuing to explore the dream realm.

Many people interested in this could not help but be disappointed at not being able to see a good show.

Ba De slowly put down his cup: "Nephew Chi Shang, I have already introduced all the Gu Immortals here to you, they are all elites. Unfortunately, there is still one person who has not appeared today, this person is even more outstanding. He came from Eastern Sea, and later on, became a part of our Southern Border. Recently, he has defeated Xia Fei Kuai and Mountain Moving Old Monster, and is the head of Wu clan here."

All the Gu Immortals in the banquet felt a jolt in their minds, they all knew precisely whom Ba De was talking about.

Chi Shang wore a white robe, he had a handsome face, deep eyes and an aquiline nose, giving him a dark and devious aura. He was a hundred and sixty years old by now.

Old Treeman Ba De was much older than him. Chi clan and Ba clan were also united by marriage, thus Ba De was not randomly addressing Chi Shang by calling him nephew.

Chi Shang smiled: "I have also heard of the great name of Wu Yi Hai. It is truly regretful that I could not meet him today. But I will be here for some time, and I will also be inspecting all around the Gu formation. At that time, I will definitely meet Wu Yi Hai."

Chi Shang showcased initiative, immediately making everyone think over this: Fang Yuan, who was hiding away, looked quite weak-willed, compared to Chi Shang.

The banquet ended, Wu An and Wu Liao were aggrieved, and both requested to have an audience with Fang Yuan.

They had a very uncomfortable time in this banquet. They were cast aside by the others and even taunted, the only thing missing was nobody asking them for a spar.

"Oh? Since that is the case, then I shall hold a banquet tomorrow, send an invitation to Chi Shang." Fang Yuan thought for a bit, before speaking.

Wu An and Wu Liao glanced at each other, they felt excited as they retreated with Fang Yuan's order.

Only Fang Yuan, alone, remained in the large hall.

He walked to the depths of the hall and looked at the dream realm.

He had already explored more than half of this formation path dream realm.

After using unravel dream, Fang Yuan had passed through the third, fourth and fifth stages.

The main contents of the dream realm were Tu Shi Cheng teaching his son about formation path. His education style was brutal and harsh, using survival to forcefully stimulate his son's potential, Fang Yuan had suffered so much from this that he no longer had the energy to curse.

Unravel dream had outstanding effects indeed, these stages were no obstacle to Fang Yuan, letting Fang Yuan's current formation path attainment soar once again. He had not only stepped into master level, he even went one step further, becoming a quasi-grandmaster.

"But I still am a long way from truly reaching formation path grandmaster level." Fang Yuan had an extremely clear sensation of this.

Towards the later stages, attainment levels became increasingly difficult to raise.

"This dream realm is still not over, according to its size, there are at least two stages left!"

"This Tu Shi Cheng's son was truly amazing, his formation path attainment was definitely above grandmaster level."

"But recently, Chi Shang has been inspecting the various places of the Gu formation, I should restrain myself a bit and stop exploring the dream realm."

After all, this super Gu formation was constructed mainly by Chi clan, Fang Yuan was still not able to thoroughly understand this super Gu formation, so it was better for him to be careful.

Fang Yuan knew that once the secret of him being able to effectively explore dream realms was exposed, it would create an extremely huge impact.

At that time, not only Southern Border, the other four regions would also be shaken and would mobilize their forces to find him.

"Wu Yi Hai is inviting me to a banquet tomorrow?" Looking at Wu An, Chi Shang smiled.

"I appreciate Wu Yi Hai's good intention, but... forgive me, I am on official business and have to prioritize it, wait for me to finish inspecting the Gu formation, after that, I can visit to thank him for his hospitality." Chi Shang refused Fang Yuan's invitation with a slight smile on his face.

Wu An felt helpless, as he left with a face filled with anger and embarrassment, he reported this to Fang Yuan.

Chi Shang's action was slightly overboard and had slapped Wu clan's face. This made both Wu Liao and Wu An indignant.

The other clans' Gu Immortals, however, were secretly laughing at this, anticipating a good show.

Regardless, Fang Yuan was calm the whole time.

He indifferently looked at Wu An and Wu Liao: "Since that is the case, then we shall wait."

He did not look the least bit angry.

"But..." Wu An and Wu Liao were inwardly anxious, feeling like their face had been torn by Chi Shang, but since Fang Yuan did not look anxious at all, they could only take their leave.

Although Fang Yuan could not continue exploring the dream realm, he still had a lot of other things to do.

For instance, constructing coiling thread caves to expand the scale of regretful spiders.

This was to be the sovereign immortal aperture's second large scale resource expansion.

Fang Yuan had been preparing for it these last days.

It was all to construct an environment that was suitable for ordinary spiders to qualitatively transform into regretful spiders.

According to Dong Fang tribe's method, constructing coiling thread caves required setting up a Gu formation, and it also required a rank six immortal material, dark soft silk, and a rank seven immortal material, regret water rock.

Fang Yuan had already gathered dark soft silk and regret water rocks, he had paid a large amount of immortal essence stones as well as some other immortal materials for them.

Next was setting up the Gu formation.

This was clearly a Gu formation that concerned immortal materials.

Normally speaking, this kind of Gu formation which relied upon immortal materials could only be deduced and created by a grandmaster level formation path Gu Immortal. And a great grandmaster formation path Gu Immortal could construct a Gu formation using the natural dao marks in the world as the foundation.

Prior to exploring the formation path dream realm, Fang Yuan felt like he was looking at an illegible book when he considered this Gu formation. But now, he understood it clearly, after all, he had quasi-grandmaster attainment.

Moreover, Fang Yuan still had some inspiration.

"Maybe I can improve this Gu formation and add in perseverance Immortal Gu! According to the principle of this Gu formation, if I add in perseverance Immortal Gu, the production of regretful spiders will at least multiply by eight."

Fang Yuan's heart thumped with excitement at such a concept.

If he could achieve this target, then the regretful spider business would surpass the dragonfish. The profits it could bring Fang Yuan could surpass even the guts Gu business.

This seemed to be exaggerated, but if looked at carefully, it was true!

Guts Gu's production was restricted by the quality and the quantity of souls. Currently, Lang Ya Sect was killing desolate beasts in Tai Qiu and using their souls as the resources to produce guts Gu. They were also bringing in some souls from treasure yellow heaven as well as the northern icy plain as replenishment.

The key point was there was Western Desert's Xiao clan, which could take in all the regretful spiders even if its supply was much higher.

There was no need to worry about the sales of regretful spiders, furthermore, Fang Yuan had a collaborative relationship with Xiao clan.

Fang Yuan started deducing.

But soon, he ran into a problem.

He was unable to arrange a part of the Gu formation, this already surpassed his limits regardless of how many wisdom path methods he used.

"I am only a quasi-grandmaster, if I were a grandmaster, I would have the foundation to modify this Gu formation." Fang Yuan realized.

"But although I am not a formation path grandmaster, there is someone nearby who has this attainment level."

This person was none other than Chi Shang!

After Chi Shang refused Fang Yuan's invitation, he started patrolling all the places around the super Gu formation.

Every stationed Gu Immortal welcomed Chi Shang warmly.

Chi Shang was intentionally delaying his inspection. Everyone knew that the longer he delayed, the more Wu clan's face would be lost.

Naturally, it was Wu Yi Hai that Chi Shang held hostility towards, not Wu clan.

A love rival!

"Wu Yi Hai, you think of yourself as so high and mighty, you look down on me. By inviting me, do you think I will scuttle towards you? Hmph! I want you to come look for me personally!" Chi Shang had such an intention in his mind.

But soon, this plan of his was destroyed.

Because Fang Yuan's letter of challenge was in his hands.

In the letter, Fang Yuan wrote: I once toured scenic spots with Fairy Si Liu, and in that time, your name was mentioned. Fairy Si Liu praised you as a genius in formation path, but I, Wu Yi Hai, don't accept that. I have created a formation path problem, let's see if you can answer it. If you can, then it is your win. If you can't, it is your loss, I will be informing Fairy Si Liu of this result when I return.

Chi Shang completely lost it!

"Wu Yi Hai, as expected, you could not take it any more."

"But you actually want to use formation path to trouble me?"

"You, a transformation path Gu Immortal, want to use formation path to embarrass me? What gave you the guts?!"

"You are asking for your own humiliation! I will definitely tell Fairy Si Liu of your loss and prove my, Chi Shang's, strength!!"

Chapter 1328: Fang Yuan's Shamelessness

Chi Shang felt he was humiliated.

Yes, humiliated!

At present, in the entire Southern Border Gu Immortal world, who did not know of Wu Yi Hai's identity? Who was not aware he cultivated transformation path? But now, Fang Yuan did not use his primary cultivation to trouble Chi Shang, but instead picked Chi Shang's most proficient domain.

This was like saying: I don't need to use transformation path to trouble you, because you simply can't compare to me!

The disdain overflowed in this challenge.

He could not take it!

This could not be endured!

Chi Shang's eyes were wide open as he pinched Fang Yuan's information path Gu worm and mumbled: "Let me see what problem you brought out."

"Eh? This is quite something..."

Soon, a trace of solemness appeared on Chi Shang's face.

As far as he was concerned, Fang Yuan's question was quite challenging.

But soon, Chi Shang settled himself: "No wonder he is confident of using formation path to harass me. This problem is slightly difficult."

"He made this problem? That should not be possible! His main cultivation is transformation path, it should be a Wu clan formation path Gu Immortal behind him who created this problem. Hmph, with his identity as Wu Yong's brother, how could Wu clan's Gu Immortals not help him?"

Although Wu clan was not specialized in formation path, as long as it was a super force, they would have some involvement in formation path.

Because super forces needed to guard their resource points, and had a large scale demand for Gu formations.

"But even if a Wu clan Gu Immortal helped you, so what? In terms of the clan's strength, my Chi clan is indeed slightly inferior. But if just comparing formation path attainment, my Chi clan is undoubtedly in first place in Southern Border!"

Chi Shang felt intense pride towards his clan.

He gathered all his senses and dived into Fang Yuan's problem.

The more he pondered, the more he lost himself.

With his analysis, he had divided the problem into dozens of segments.

"Normal methods cannot be used to solve the issue of water and fire opposing each other."

"The whole Gu formation demands a circular formation, a square formation can be discarded..."

"How to solve this difficulty?"

"Hiss... this is slightly difficult."

"But this can't defeat me!"

Chi Shang's fighting spirit soared high like he had been injected with adrenaline, he inwardly told himself that he had to teach Fang Yuan a fierce lesson!

Let him know that he, Chi Shang, could not be humiliated!

"Lord, the evening banquet that Luo clan's Gu Immortals invited you to is going to start soon. We should be on our way." At this time, a rank six Gu Immortal of Chi clan, Chi Liu, reminded Chi Shang from outside the door.

"Not going, not going!" Chi Shang did not even raise his head, he refused while continuing to deduce the problems in his mind.

"But, we already agreed..." Chi Liu hesitated.

"I said I am not going. Leave." Chi Shang impatiently replied.

Chi Liu could only helplessly leave.

Chi Shang took in a deep breath, looking at the formation path problem Fang Yuan sent him, his eyes brightened as he mumbled: "What good is there in a banquet? The important thing is to defeat him! The faster I can solve this problem, the better it is. You, you dare to humiliate me!"

The night passed like this.

Chi Shang had not slept the whole time, his eyes were bloodshot, his hair was in a mess and he was extremely tired.

With a Gu Immortal's physique, it did not matter if they stayed up all night. But Chi Shang was rather exhausted, he had not rested even a moment during this night, and had put in all his effort to deduce and plan, taxing both his mind and energy.

"This problem is indeed slightly difficult. But... I have already solved it. Hahaha, you dare to mess with me! I will let you taste my awesomeness!"

Despite being exhausted, Chi Shang was extremely excited and laughed heartily.

He could not wait to see how Fang Yuan would respond.

"I will go right now and enjoy your expression!"

Chi Shang walked to the entrance when he suddenly stopped.

"Hmm? No! I am standing against Wu Yi Hai right now, we are like generals, how could I take the initiative to visit him? My reputation will be lost! I need to send a subordinate..."

Soon after, Chi clan rank six Gu Immortal Chi Liu arrived in Chi Shang's study.

"Little Liu, send this to Wu Yi Hai. Haha, I want to teach him a lesson!" Chi Shang instructed.

Chi Liu quickly agreed.

His cultivation level was lower than Chi Shang, and he knew Chi Shang was the hope of Chi clan in formation path. Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You, had said a few times in the past that Chi Shang would inherit his legacy.

The significance of these words was huge.

Chi Qu You was a formation path great grandmaster, him acknowledging Chi Shang meant Chi Shang was very likely to become a formation path great grandmaster as well.

Chi Shang also did not let down the clan.

He had displayed his talents and aptitude in formation path since a young age, and with the clan's resources being poured into him, he cultivated hard all year round and did not slack. After receiving Chi clan's nurturing, his current formation path attainment was not to be underestimated.

"Hmm... relaxing." Fang Yuan slowly woke up and stretched out his arms.

Although his soul had the protection of guts Gu, it would become agitated when used too much.

Guts Gu was not able to resolve this, but sleep could restore the soul's calmness.

After Fang Yuan had a night's sleep, his exhausted state was swept away, and his mind was vigorous again.

Chi Shang's information path mortal Gu had already been delivered while he was asleep.

When Fang Yuan glanced at it, a look of pleasant surprise flashed past his eyes: "Oh? He indeed solved it!"

"This speed is quite fast."

Fang Yuan sighed as he then immersed himself into the information and started studying it.

His eyes shined repeatedly as he gained great enlightenment from Chi Shang's solution.

"So it was like this!" Fang Yuan rubbed his chin, this was a completely new thought process and it opened a new window to him.

"According to this thought process, this answer is still not suitable for my entire Gu formation, I need to make slight adjustments in some areas."

Fang Yuan inwardly pondered.

He did not give the whole Gu formation to Chi Shang, and only took out parts of it for Chi Shang to solve.

Chi Shang's answers had no errors, but there would still be deviations when the entire Gu formation was arranged.

However, Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was already at quasi-grandmaster, and using the foundation of these answers, he fully could make some adjustments.

Chi Shang was a grandmaster, and Fang Yuan a quasi-grandmaster, there was not a huge difference between the two. If the difference was too high, it would be impossible to modify the formation.

It was just like how Fang Yuan currently saw this super Gu formation that covered the dream realm, it was still a mystery to him, he could not understand a thing.

Fang Yuan made huge gains by receiving the answer to the issue that was troubling him.

"Indeed worthy of being Southern Border's Chi clan." He mumbled, praising Chi Shang's formation path attainment.

With this problem solved, Fang Yuan could continue his plan to modify the Gu formation.

His mind was calm and serene, as he began deducing once again.

A few days passed like this.

Chi Shang was very anxious.

After he sent the answer, he had been waiting for Fang Yuan's reply. But, even after some days, he had not received a response, he did not even feel he could taste his food and drinks properly.

"What is Wu Yi Hai playing at?" Chi Shang mumbled.

"Chi Shang, what did you say?" In the banquet, a Luo clan Gu Immortal asked in confusion.

Chi Shang slowly came to his senses, only then realizing he was still in the banquet.

He had refused a banquet invitation from Luo clan before, but after solving Fang Yuan's problem, he came to attend one.

He had to attend it, otherwise, was it not the same as not giving face to Luo clan?

Gu Immortal Chi Gui, who was sitting at the side, quickly mediated: "Forgive us, Chi Shang has always been like this. His mind often wanders, sometimes he even forgets to eat when he is thinking of a formation path problem. He would stand still all of a sudden, and it can happen even while he is walking."

Chi Gui had rank seven cultivation, and was the leader of the Chi clansmen stationed here.

The Luo clan Gu Immortal laughed loudly: "I have heard about Chi Shang's behavior. He is indeed a formation path genius. Sigh, if my Luo clan could produce one or two geniuses with just twenty or thirty percent of Chi Shang's talents, I would be content."

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan's brows were tightly furrowed.

He ran into another problem.

"It seems modifying this Gu formation is already beyond my limits."

Fang Yuan had encountered a new problem, and this one was much more difficult than the previous one.

He could still make an attempt for the previous one, but this time, he did not even think to attempt it as his ideas were too unreliable.

"Since that is the case, let's hand it to Chi Shang." Fang Yuan smiled.

"It's here, it's here." When Chi Shang returned to Chi clan's station, he soon got Fang Yuan's information path mortal Gu.

His eyes brightened in excitement.

"Do you think it was easy for me!"

"Even I was getting impatient from waiting."

Chi Shang sneered while feeling proud. Right now, he was like a winner picking up his battle spoils.

However, after his consciousness entered and he learned of the contents in the information path mortal Gu, his eyes opened wide in anger.

"What is Wu Yi Hai saying!"

"He is actually acting so shamelessly?!"

Chi Shang immediately cursed.

In the letter, Fang Yuan did not mention a single word about the previous challenge letter, instead, he casually admitted Chi Shang had some ability. Naturally, it could also be Chi Shang getting lucky.

"If you can solve this problem, I will admit you have the qualifications to pursue Fairy Si Liu." This was what was written in the letter.

At the mention of Qiao Si Liu, Chi Shang was even more unable to endure it.

"Are my qualifications up to you to decide?"

"Wu Yi Hai, I misjudged you. You shameless guy!"

Chi Shang felt like Fang Yuan was standing in front of him, sneering in disdain and looking down on him.

He suddenly had a strong impulse to rip apart Fang Yuan!

"Still mentioning going on a sightseeing tour with Si Liu. Even I have only traveled once with Si Liu. Damn this guy..."

Chi Shang paced around the study, gritting his teeth in resentment.

He almost crushed the information path mortal Gu in his hand.

But he thought for a moment and withstood this impulse.

"If I crush this Gu, wouldn't it be satisfying Wu Yi Hai's wish?"

"Hmph, he was not able to create difficulties for me, he is definitely afraid of me now, so he is intentionally saying this."

"Right! Me giving up is probably what he wants to see."

"I can't let that happen, I will continue to win and make him completely admit his defeat. Make him fully realize my strength!"

"Of course, to prevent him from acting shamelessly again, I must make this matter public, the more people that know of it, the better."

Chi Shang learned from his mistake.

The origin of this matter was a dispute about a girl, Chi Shang had also found it slightly embarrassing, but now, he was willing to throw caution to the wind against Fang Yuan!

Chapter 1329: Fang Yuan Admitting Defeat

Chi clan's area, in the study room.

Chi Liu had been summoned, and after hearing Chi Shang's intention, he said with an awkward expression: "Lord, is that good? Our Chi clan and Wu clan's relation... is still quite good. At least, even with Wu clan's current situation, our Chi clan has been maintaining neutrality."

"So what? Other clans can make a move, but our Chi clan can't?" Chi Shang was getting angry.

Chi Liu thought to himself: "Lord Chi Shang is truly like what the rumors said. What should I do now?"

While thinking, Chi Liu said: "I understand lord's mood, but over here, hehe, we have some business where we have been closely collaborating with Wu clan. If we just suddenly fall out..."

Chi Shang immediately came to a realization.

"Oh."

"You are talking about the dream realm business?"

Chi Liu nodded: "Lord is wise."

Wu clan wanted to do dream realm business for some income under the table, but how could their actions be unnoticed by Chi clan?

The Immortal Gu used in this super Gu formation belonged to Southern Border's super clans, but the Gu formation itself was personally set up by Chi clan's first supreme elder.

Although Chi clan contributed few Immortal Gu, as far as this super Gu formation was concerned, they had an enormous influence.

Thus, Wu clan had to bring in Chi clan if they wanted to do this dream realm business. Chi clan's Gu Immortals had much more understanding of the Gu formation, if they were not brought in, this business could not be done.

Chi Shang sighed inwardly: "No wonder first supreme elder had once said that it is hard to fathom the minds of people. Sigh, Chi Liu is a fellow Chi clan Gu Immortal, but for personal gains, he is actually not standing on my side."

His expression was gloomy, it was hard to resolve the matter now.

He wanted to publicly fall out with Fang Yuan, but he encountered an obstacle in the first step. What should he do now?

For a moment, Chi Shang was quite helpless.

Because he had taken a position here all of a sudden and had always taken cultivation as his main goal. He had very little contact with other Chi clan Gu Immortals and was always focused on researching formation path, his influence in Chi clan was quite small and could even be said to be the smallest influence among rank seven Gu Immortals.

It was also the first time he had come to this super Gu formation, now, with his lack of connections, as a grand rank seven Gu Immortal, he was actually unable to mobilize Chi Liu.

Chi Liu's mood was quite bad, disobeying a rank seven Gu Immortal, especially when the latter was an important future hope of the clan, he naturally did not feel good.

However, people in low positions naturally had their own survival methods.

Chi Liu thought for a bit and said: "Lord, it is not that I don't want to do this matter on your behalf. It is just that your status is high, once this matter is proclaimed, it will have a great impact. How about this, please let me inform Lord Chi Gui about this matter. He is the leader here, we will listen to his decision, what do you think?"

Chi Liu's tone was humble and polite, and was even subtly flattering Chi Shang.

Chi Shang felt extremely comforted upon hearing this, and nodded: "Alright, then let's see what Lord Chi Gui says."

Chi Gui's brows furrowed when he heard Chi Liu's report.

A fight over a woman, nobody would feel good about involving themselves in a dispute merely over this.

Chi Gui felt quite troubled.

On one hand, his clansman was Chi Shang, he had to show respect because Chi clan's first supreme elder was behind Chi Shang.

On the other hand, if they really escalated this matter, it would no longer be a personal matter, but a political one which could affect the diplomatic relations between Wu clan and Chi clan.

This was a world where the strong were respected and where one individual's strength could surpass a group's.

Thus, politics was also determined by individuals.

Chi Shang and Wu Yi Hai had very high status, a conflict between them was a conflict between Wu clan and Chi clan.

This was not exaggerated at all.

"Especially Wu clan, it is in a difficult situation, being harassed from all sides. If, at this time, my Chi clan joins in, it will damage the neutrality of Chi clan, and not to mention that we will gain poor reputation for kicking someone when they are down, it will also worsen our relation with Wu clan, harming my clan's interests."

"But I also have to appease Chi Shang..."

Chi Gui racked his brains for a while before he actually thought of an idea.

He then secretly gave his idea to Chi Shang: "We cannot make this a big issue, otherwise, the impact will be very bad. Even if we win, we will be making a joke of ourselves. This is, after all, a personal matter, we should deal with this privately. You can tell Fairy Si Liu about the situation. Wu Yi Hai also has affection towards Qiao Si Liu, if you can ask her to be the witness, Wu Yi Hai would absolutely not dare to act shamelessly."

Chi Shang slapped his thigh and shouted: "Great idea!"

Chi Gui smiled, slightly pleased with himself.

From what Chi Gui saw, this method had even more allure to Chi Shang — who did not want to ruthlessly crush their love rival in front of the girl they loved, and gain her attention.

Soon, Chi Shang informed Qiao Si Liu of the matter through an information path Gu worm.

Regardless of what was going on with Fang Yuan, Chi Shang immediately felt enormous pressure.

"Now, Fairy Si Liu knows of this. This is a duel between gentlemen and it was he, Wu Yi Hai, who sent the challenge, she should not feel disgusted, right?"

"I need to quickly complete Wu Yi Hai's challenge!"

"This is my specialty, I absolutely cannot lose."

The enormous pressure became a huge motivation for Chi Shang.

He started concentrating on the problem.

"Is this another part?"

"It has a slight relation to the previous part of that Gu formation."

"It is likely the whole Gu formation was divided into two parts. Damn it, if I knew the whole Gu formation, it would have been much easier. Now, I can only deduce according to this part."

He was getting a headache!

Chi Shang began to use his methods.

He was a formation path Gu Immortal who knew a mystical Gu formation taught to him personally by first supreme elder.

This Gu formation used wisdom path Gu worms as the core, while the supplementary Gu worm was an Immortal Gu.

Normally speaking, be it an immortal killer move or an immortal Gu formation, both used Immortal Gu as the core and mortal Gu as supplementary. However, this Gu formation actually did the opposite.

The supplementary Immortal Gu used was a water path Immortal Gu named Sweat.

The Gu formation's name was wisdom sweat formation. It slowly activated as Chi Shang poured in his immortal essence.

There were no gorgeous lights or sparkles, instead, an intriguing smell that seemed somewhere between fragrant and foul was formed.

The smell grew more intense, shrouding Chi Shang. Gradually, the smell condensed into a fog which covered Chi Shang's face, making him unable to see anything.

For three days and nights, Chi Shang did not sleep or rest, continuing to deduce.

Finally, the fog dissipated and the Gu formation stopped, some mortal Gu were expended and dead, only about ten percent of them remained, which Chi Shang stored back into his immortal aperture, among them was sweat Immortal Gu.

Chi Shang's whole body was soaked with sweat, as if he had been drenched in a rainstorm, his face also looked pale.

But his eyes were shining brightly.

All of a sudden, he raised his head and laughed loudly: "Hahaha. I finally solved it, I will see how you can get out of this, Wu Yi Hai!"

After a while, Fang Yuan received the letter.

"Oh, he got smarter, using Qiao Si Liu to create difficulties for me?"

"Unfortunately, my goal is not her, this little threat is useless."

Fang Yuan soon praised once again.

"Interesting, interesting, this solution is indeed a good method!"

"But why could I not think of it?"

Although Fang Yuan obtained the answer, he did not focus on it, instead he started to evaluate himself.

There were many areas in Chi Shang's solution that Fang Yuan had not been able to grasp. Formation path was extremely vast, the inheritances Fang Yuan obtained were only of mortal level, it was natural for him to not be able to grasp them.

As for Chi clan, they would not lack immortal level formation path inheritances. Moreover, with generations of development, and innovating new things based on the original foundation, they were Southern Border's number one force in formation path.

"But even if I don't have immortal inheritances, if my attainment level can reach grandmaster, I should also be able to solve this problem."

Attainment level was one's understanding of the essence of the Great Dao.

A simple analogy would be the solving of a mathematical problem.

Fang Yuan wanted to modify the Gu formation and achieve his goal, it was like he wanted to reach a number, for example 5.

Despite having the Gu worms, he did not know how to obtain 5. At this time, Chi Shang's answer was 2+3=5.

Fang Yuan came to a realization that he could achieve his target like this.

If his attainment level was enough, even if he did not know, he could rely on his instincts to understand the question from parts, to extrapolate information and obtain the answer of 2+3=5, or 10/2=5.

Naturally, Gu formations were not as simple as this, especially when there were many Gu worms involved, it became harder to arrange them successfully.

The contents of Gu formations were complicated and varied. There were simple Gu formations, compound Gu formations as well as formations within formations, depending on the form, there were square formations, circular formations and so on, depending on the activation style, there were instant activation formations and delayed activation formations. Then, they were divided further according to paths, fire formations, water formations and so on. Some Gu formations were like towers, with layers upon layers of designs. Some Gu formations were easy to modify and were like a set of clothes, modifying them were like sewing a patch. Some Gu formations could not be modified, they were like building blocks and changing one of them could cause the whole Gu formation to collapse. If one sub-divided the Gu formations, the Gu worms involved would become even more complicated. For example, some Gu worms needed to be used together, while some had to be dispersed to influence their respective targets.

By the night of the second day, the eagerly waiting Chi Shang received Fang Yuan's reply.

"This time, with Fairy Si Liu as the witness, I want to see how you will act shamelessly!" Chi Shang impatiently sent his consciousness into the information path mortal Gu.

His face soon brightened up.

Because Fang Yuan had admitted his capabilities in the letter and that he was indeed worthy of Fairy Si Liu's admiration. But, Fang Yuan had also written that Wu clan had people that could do this, and it was not anything strange.

Chi Shang frowned when he saw this, but he was unable to retort since Wu clan indeed had people who could solve the problem.

At this moment, he saw the last paragraph of the letter.

Fang Yuan had put forward a problem again. Moreover, he promised that if Chi Shang could solve this, he would admit Chi Shang was superior to him, even in front of Fairy Si Liu, he would admit he was inferior.

Chi Shang started to breathe in deeply.

He imagined the situation, when he and Wu Yi Hai appeared in front of Qiao Si Liu at the same time, with Wu Yi Hai cupping his fists and saying: I am inferior to you.

A love rival admitting he was inferior.

The more Chi Shang thought of this, the more moved he became.

"Wu Yi Hai has a high status, he is my biggest rival."

"I can win this and defeat him."

"More importantly, Fairy Si Liu is the witness, I don't have to be afraid of Wu Yi Hai reneging on his promise!"

Chapter 1330: So It Cannot Be Solved

Wisdom sweat formation.

Chi Shang set up this Gu formation again, doing his utmost to deduce the formation.

But this time, he met with an unforeseen challenge!

Difficult, it was really difficult, even the first two rounds added together and multiplied by ten could not match this.

Chi Shang felt like he was a baby trying to ascend a tall mountain.

"This difficulty... no wonder Wu Yi Hai is so confident!"

"It is related to the contents of the first two Gu formations."

"No, I must use this chance to humiliate Wu Yi Hai. I will make him admit that he is inferior to me in front of Fairy Si Liu!"

After a day and a night, Chi Shang's eyes were filled with blood vessels, he was doing his best to try and tackle this problem.

At the same time, Fang Yuan was thinking.

"This difficulty, it has likely surpassed the limits of grandmaster attainment level?"

Not long ago, Fang Yuan received Chi Shang's help, he was able to modify the Gu formation of the coiling thread caves, he took a huge step forward, there was an immense breakthrough.

However, right before succeeding, Fang Yuan was met with an unprecedented obstacle.

If the first problem was a pit, the second was a mound, and this final obstacle was a mountain.

Only by climbing to the top and removing the obstacle could he complete the modification of this Gu formation.

This obstacle greatly surpassed Fang Yuan's expectations.

"Hmm... my initial estimation was that if the Gu formation could be deduced, the regretful spider production would be doubled three times."

That was not the same as three times as much. It would increase by seven times, becoming eight times the production of the initial size.

This growth was terrifying. When the Gu formation was created, he would have seven extra coiling thread caves out of nowhere.

Fang Yuan's plan was wonderful, but the realization of it was met with great difficulty.

The first two steps, he managed to complete, but now, he had no clue.

He was just a step from success, how could Fang Yuan give up now? Thus, he placed his attention on Chi Shang.

Many days later, the wisdom sweat formation stopped.

Chi Shang's expression was pale.

His gaze was drifting, there was no light in his eyes.

"Damn it!!" His hair was messy, like growing weed, his expression was of frustration, he gritted his teeth.

Even though he gave it his all, he did not succeed.

This way, he could not beat Fang Yuan, and worse, Qiao Si Liu knew of this third challenge, Chi Shang had already bragged that he would resolve this problem.

If he failed, forget about Wu Yi Hai, but how would he face Qiao Si Liu from now on?

Chi Shang felt an unforeseen pressure weighing on him.

He quickly ate and rested before going back to his deductions again.

Chi clan.

It was to the west of Southern Border, or rather, it was towards the west of all the super forces currently in Southern Border.

Yang clan was the neighbor of Chi clan.

This clan was a neighbor of Wu clan, and was finding trouble with Wu clan recently, conflict arose due to a wild Immortal Gu.

Chi clan, Yang clan, Wu clan.

Following the basic rule of making friends with those far away and making enemies with those close by, Chi clan and Wu clan had always had a good relationship.

The newest information was sent to Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You.

Chi Qu You took a look and frowned.

This intel was talking about none other than the challenge from Fang Yuan to Chi Shang in the super Gu formation.

Inside the super Gu formation, Chi clan's leader, Chi Gui, was afraid that conflict between Fang Yuan and Chi Shang would escalate, he had wisely reported this incident to Chi Qu You.

This way, even if the situation worsens, Chi Gui's responsibility would be lowered, after all, he had informed them.

Chi Qu You would divert a portion of his attention to this conflict while he was dealing with complex political matters.

After all, both sides had extraordinary statuses, if this was handled improperly, it would escalate further.

"Chi Shang is troubled, this Gu formation problem is... beyond the abilities of a grandmaster."

The information had recorded Fang Yuan's third formation path issue.

Chi Qu You was a great grandmaster, he only needed a look to spot the difficulty of this problem.

"Together with the first two problems, Wu Yi Hai is trying to create a Gu formation to farm resources. But this person who made the Gu formation is too greedy, they have insufficient attainment level and cannot notice it."

"If I do not say anything to him... with Chi Shang's obsessive nature, he would continue to research it, if he gets injured from this, he might even die."

"Is this Wu clan's scheme?"

"They can see Chi Shang's potential, so they are trying to eliminate our future hope?"

"Mm... with Wu clan's current situation, it is unlikely. But I cannot be careless."

Chi Qu You thought of this, a sharp light shined in his eyes, he muttered: "It seems I have to do something."

A moment later, Chi Gui visited Chi Shang, bringing with him an information path Immortal Gu from Chi Qu You.

"This is first supreme elder's instruction, I have to pass this Immortal Gu to you." Chi Gui said.

Chi Shang blankly received the Immortal Gu, after looking into it, he saw the details and his expression changed, he cried out in surprise: "This is the immortal inheritance left by secluded cultivator Tu Yuan. His earth water wind fire four elements formation is unique to him alone. But it had little reputation, because he kept a low profile, few people knew of it. First supreme elder actually gave this immortal inheritance to me! I asked for it so many times but I did not succeed in the past."

Chi Shang was so excited, he looked into the immortal true inheritance without caring about the outside world.

When he snapped back to awareness, a long time had passed, it was night time already.

"Time passed really quickly, hmm? When did supreme elder Chi Gui leave, hmm, forget it." Chi Shang's eyes shined brightly, unable to be looked at directly.

Chi clan first supreme elder's true inheritance came at a timely moment, it was what Chi Shang needed most right now.

Chi Shang was filled with admiration and gratitude towards Chi Qu You.

"So first supreme elder has been taking notice of me all along."

"He saw that I was in trouble, so he helped me."

"Is this cheating?"

"Probably not. First supreme elder did not help me directly, he only gave me a true inheritance. The inspiration to solve the problem was thought of by me."

"Mm, that's it! I have wasted enough time, I need to quickly resolve this problem and show Wu Yi Hai what I'm capable of!"

Chi Shang was excited and driven, he used the wisdom sweat formation again.

Two days passed, the Gu formation stopped working as Chi Shang walked out angrily.

"So this Gu formation problem cannot be solved!"

"Wu Yi Hai, you dare to scam me!"

"Too devious, too scheming!!"

"Thankfully, with first supreme elder's guidance, I exposed this truth."

Thinking of this, Chi Shang gritted his teeth, he had suffered a lot these last days, he barely slept at all, he was invested in the problem.

But then, he realized this was unsolvable.

Chi Shang felt that Wu Yi Hai had toyed with him, he was very angry.

But soon, he laughed: "That's right, this problem cannot be solved, as long as I expose this fact, I win. In fact, I can tell Fairy Si Liu about this, and embarrass this devious Wu Yi Hai."

Chi Shang immediately acted upon it, sending out two information path mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan received two information path mortal Gu immediately.

The first one was from Qiao Si Liu.

It was not unexpected that Qiao Si Liu sent a letter, after looking at it, he was a bit puzzled.

But then, he thought of something and looked at Chi Shang's letter.

Fang Yuan realized at once.

"This Chi Shang has improved, he actually went to complain about me, telling Qiao Si Liu about the result of this challenge, before sending me this letter. This way, he can prevent me from retaliating? He really has improved."

Fang Yuan's smile faded.

The result was unexpected.

His Gu formation had no solution!

This was a common situation.

Before a deduction succeeds, any new Gu recipe, killer move, Gu formation, they could be unsolvable, they could be impossible to complete. They were merely illusions, there was no possible way of success.

Some problems were easy to tell, but others were not so obvious.

Especially formation path, it used too many Gu worms and paths, it was too complex. Some ideas could not be exposed as unsolvable until the very end.

"Multiplying my production eight times, this idea is hoping for too much, it is not possible."

"Since it is unsolvable, I can only abandon it and find a new modification."

"But forget about it now."

"Since I lost the challenge, I should invite Chi Shang over. This person is quite interesting."

Chi Shang did not even think about it, he agreed to go over for the banquet.

His attitude was different from before.

Initially, he thought that Fang Yuan was too arrogant, he refused to go. But now, he was the winner, he felt that this was an apology banquet, he had to go with the attitude of a winner, to savor the feelings of the loser.

Thus, when he saw Fang Yuan, his first words were: "Wu Yi Hai, will you relent now?"

Fang Yuan rubbed his nose, smiling: "Of course, of course, you are a genius, why would I not relent?"

Chi Shang was shocked, he did not expect Fang Yuan to act like this, he admitted his defeat.

He did not know what to do now. Before this, he had thought of many possible outcomes, and how to deal with Fang Yuan's excuses.

But now, Fang Yuan admitted his defeat, he relented.

Chi Shang felt like he had nothing to say now.

Chapter 1331: Inviting Chi Shang Over

The banquet started.

In this small hall, there was only Fang Yuan, Wu An, and Chi Shang, three Gu Immortals. Wu An naturally did not play a key role, the only important thing was that Fang Yuan and Chi Shang were interacting.

Fang Yuan toasted Chi Shang, speaking politely with a smile, he expressed a lot of admiration and praise towards Chi Shang's formation path attainment.

After smiling and admitting defeat, could Chi Shang bear to give him a hard time?

Chi Shang was straightforward and unguarded, unschooled in interacting with others, he drank a lot of wine.

He assessed Fang Yuan, looking at him in a different perspective.

"This Wu Yi Hai is quite a friendly guy. What happened earlier? Was he trying to purposely anger me? Or does he have a request of me?" Chi Shang thought to himself.

"I will not hide it, Chi Shang, talented people like you are the people I admire the most!" Fang Yuan laughed, toasting.

Chi Shang raised his cup and drank before Fang Yuan even drank.

The toasting from earlier had already made Chi Shang used to this subconsciously.

But Fang Yuan's words were nice to hear. Especially when they were love rivals, such praise made Chi Shang feel deep accomplishment.

"No."

"I must be alert!"

"This Wu Yi Hai might be acting, he is very scheming."

Chi Shang did not let down his guard, but no matter how he looked at it, Fang Yuan's smile was full of sincerity.

Hehe, forget about Fang Yuan's acting skills, but don't forget attitude Gu.

"Chi Shang, take a look." Fang Yuan stretched out his arm, handing over an information path mortal Gu to Chi Shang.

"What is this?" Chi Shang muttered, he looked into it and his expression changed.

As it turned out, this was an information path mortal Gu that Fang Yuan was going to send to Qiao Si Liu. He praised Chi Shang in the letter, his admiration was overwhelming, he admitted his own insufficiencies, using formation path questions to challenge Chi Shang was just him overestimating himself, he was truly ignorant and could not see Mount Tai, Chi Shang was a true Southern Border hero.

There was no such thing as 'Mount Tai' in this world, but the meaning was the same.

After Chi Shang saw this letter, he felt embarrassed.

Fang Yuan's praise was too exaggerated.

"Am I really so good?"

"Southern Border hero, why have I never thought of that."

"What would Fairy Si Liu think after she sees this?"

All sorts of thoughts appeared, Chi Shang could not contain his emotions.

When he looked at Fang Yuan again, his gaze transformed.

Fang Yuan directly sat beside him, Chi Shang did not feel any dislike towards this closeness.

"Chi Shang, throughout the Southern Border Gu Immortal world, only you are talented enough for Fairy Si Liu, I am truly in admiration!" Fang Yuan laughed loudly.

"Oh?" Chi Shang did not know what to say, he had joy on his face but also suspicions.

Fang Yuan said again: "But I will not give up, all gentlemen may pursue beautiful and clever women, even though I am less talented than you, I will work harder. You won this time, but we will compete fairly again in the future! What do you think?"

Hearing this, Chi Shang's suspicions faded, he raised his cup for the first time and tasted Fang Yuan: "Yes, fair competition! A contest between gentlemen should be fair and square."

Saying this, he treated Fang Yuan as a gentleman.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, patting his shoulders: "To speak the truth, I hate the other competitors, but you are different. You are so talented and upright, I admire you. If you can get Fairy Si Liu's love, I will bless you two, because I know that I did not lose unfairly! As for the others, they are just clowns."

Chi Shang was embarrassed from being praised, he rubbed his nose, saying: "Actually, some of them are quite strong."

"Friends are often made after a fight, come, drink!" Fang Yuan raised his cup.

Chi Shang acted even more openly: "Drink!"

He raised his head and gulped, drinking all of the wine in one mouthful.

Next, he burped, his face turned red.

"Awesome!" Fang Yuan gave a thumbs up, pouring wine for Chi Shang again.

He smiled sincerely and enthusiastically, he was very friendly.

But the truth was, he was calm in his mind, he thought about Chi Shang's information.

Wu clan's intelligence was very reliable.

Fang Yuan knew long ago: This Chi Shang had been noticed by Chi Qu You when he was young, he saw the talent that Chi Shang had in formation path, thus he nurtured him deeply.

Chi Shang was known as the 'formation devotee'.

He was chosen when he was a youth, he was sent into a cave in Myriad Snake Mountain to study. He stayed there for thirty years.

When he was forty, he came out and had rank three cultivation level, but he surpassed rank four and five Gu Masters in creating formations, his formation path attainment shocked the entire Chi clan.

Next, his clansmen realized that Chi Shang had actually come out of seclusion because he lost his way and accidentally left the mountain.

His performance resulted in great fame, fortune and women came to him, but he rejected them all, his only request was to return to the cave and continue his formation path research.

This alerted the supreme elders.

Chi Qu You permitted Chi Shang's request, creating a cave solely for him, with attendants and servants to cater to him.

Chi Shang continued his research, he was so engrossed in it, it was shocking, as if formation path was the only joy in his life.

He was invested in it, regardless of what happened outside, he only stayed in his cave, engrossed in his formation path cultivation without seeing daylight.

When his hair turned white and his lifespan was ending, Chi Qu You came to see him and asked: "In this life, did you regret anything? Do you have any requests before dying?

Chi Shang cried loudly, saying: "Life is too short, a hundred years passes by too quickly, my formation path research still has many things left to do, how can I rest in peace? This is my biggest regret."

Chi Qu You sighed in admiration, granting him a lifespan Gu.

Chi Shang obtained it, regaining his youth and lifespan.

Chi Qu You talked to him about formation path, guiding him for three days and three nights before confirming that Chi Shang was the clan's future hope, his formation path attainment could reach great grandmaster in the future!

Chi Qu You did not just say it, he acted on it, nurturing Chi Shang with a lot of resources from the clan.

With the clan's help, Chi Shang's cultivation level rose rapidly, he became an immortal. In a few decades, he became a rank seven Gu Immortal.

Even though he became an immortal, his living habits did not change at all.

He was still invested in formation path, he continued to research it endlessly, his closed cultivations lasted from years to over a decade.

The only shocking thing was that he pursued Qiao Si Liu with a firm attitude.

When news got out, Chi clan was taken aback, to think that other than formation path, Chi Shang actually liked women!

After getting Wu clan's intelligence, Fang Yuan thought that Chi Shang was an interesting person.

With this knowledge, he used a special method to deal with Chi Shang instead.

He did not meet with Chi Shang earlier, it was part of Fang Yuan's scheme. He purposely used the formation path problem to challenge him, that was the second step, and this third step was the banquet.

Chi Shang's performance was not out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

Everything progressed according to plan.

Not long ago, Qiao Si Liu had sent a letter according to Fang Yuan's expectations. As the person involved, Qiao Si Liu had to express her attitude clearly.

Even though she did not state it, in the letter, she talked about her first encounter with Chi Shang.

According to Qiao Si Liu, back then, she visited Chi clan with Qiao clan's orders, she was attended to by Chi clan first supreme elder's son, Gu Immortal Chi Bang.

But to think that this Chi Bang was hitting on Qiao Si Liu by using the beautiful scenery and some poems.

If this were normal times, Qiao Si Liu might not get mad, but now, she was the envoy from Qiao clan, Chi Bang's actions were disrespectful to Qiao clan, Qiao Si Liu felt resentment towards him.

To deal with him, Qiao Si Liu purposely got closer to Chi Shang.

Chi Bang was Chi Qu You's son, the supposed next first supreme elder of Chi clan, he had the second highest authority in the clan, nobody dared to trifle with him except the formation devotee Chi Shang.

Chi Shang did not know about the issue, he had no interest in Qiao Si Liu initially, but she purposely talked to him about formation path, and even explained some of Qiao clan's formation path knowledge.

Chi Shang was deeply attracted, he gained a lot of interest.

Qiao Si Liu used Chi Shang to deal with Chi Bang, Chi Bang could not do anything, he could only apologize to Qiao Si Liu secretly.

Qiao Si Liu completed the clan's mission and returned in success, also gaining a suitor in Chi Shang.

Qiao Si Liu's letter gave Fang Yuan important information, he gained a clearer understanding of Chi clan's internal affairs.

"Chi clan's first supreme elder has limited lifespan, he can no longer use lifespan Gu, but his son, Chi Bang, became an immortal due to his protection, he has limited capability."

"Chi Qu You knows about his son's abilities, but he wants him to become Chi clan's future first supreme elder, thus, after noticing Chi Shang's personality and talent, he decided to invest in him and nurture this formation devotee."

"As long as the formation devotee protects him, Chi Bang will have a good chance of staying first supreme elder. And the formation devotee's admiration and gratitude towards Chi Qu You will make him unable to escape the control of Chi Bang."

"Kinship... hehe."

Qiao Si Liu's letter showed Chi clan's internal political conflicts to Fang Yuan.

And because of this problem, a genius like Chi Shang emerged. At the same time, some questions that Fang Yuan had was answered.

"Come! Wu Yi Hai, let me toast you." At this time, Chi Shang toasted Fang Yuan for the first time, breaking his train of thought.

Chi Shang continued: "You are a very sincere person, when Fairy Si Liu and I get together, you do not need to be too upset. You are very talented, there are lots of women in the world, but few are well learned about formation path!"

Chapter 1332: Happy Host and Guest

Chi Shang drank a lot, his face was red, he spoke a lot.

It seemed that after defeating Fang Yuan in this contest, his confidence had risen sharply, he felt that he could obtain the love of his life.

Gu Immortals had all sorts of methods to prevent getting drunk. But that way, the joy of drinking would be gone, and it was very rude to their drinking buddies.

Fang Yuan quickly raised his cup, drinking the wine as he smiled: "If that is the case, I will admit I am unlucky, it was too bad that I had a competitor like you! Sigh..."

Fang Yuan sighed to himself, as if lamenting that the heavens saw fit to put someone so gifted in his way, he expressed that sentiment fully in his act.

Chi Shang laughed loudly, stretching out his arm and patting Fang Yuan's shoulder, consoling him.

Fang Yuan laughed internally.

This Chi Shang was so innocent and pure.

This matter was decided long ago.

As long as Fang Yuan agreed, Qiao Si Liu would enter his embrace, this was a certain thing.

But Qiao Si Liu did not express her intention clearly, because this fairy had her schemes and pride, she wanted to play hard to get, so as to raise her own value.

Actually, Fang Yuan could tell very clearly.

Like this time, Qiao Si Liu's letter was the expression of her attitude.

"Qiao Si Liu is seeing that Chi Shang and I are competing, she is very happy about it. Earlier, she had been watching on the fence, this suited her intentions."

"When I lost, she then took the initiative to tell me about the situation between her and Chi Shang. She wants to console me and let me know that she has no feelings for Chi Shang. It was his one sided affection."

"But this clever woman did not state her attitude clearly, she just talked about a fact to show her purity, while showing that she had a lot of value to her suitors."

It was natural instinct for men to pursue women. How many men pursued her, and the type of men that went after her, these somewhat determined the perceived value of a woman.

"Qiao Si Liu is seeking to be with me, this is not her personal wish, but the political desire of Qiao clan."

"And with just this, I am already ahead of all her suitors."

"No matter how many times I fail, no matter how many women I go after, no matter how weak I am, even if I make a scene like during the moon festival, so what?"

"I am already victorious!"

"In fact, even if I go after another woman instead of Qiao Si Liu, she will turn around and pursue me instead."

"Of course, this is not love, this is... politics!"

Fang Yuan sneered in his mind, he had seen through everything.

But he could not accept this 'love' from Qiao Si Liu.

Once he accepted it, he would be dragged into this vicious political spiral, he would no longer be simply Wu Yi Hai, he would be the key pawn that Qiao clan had inserted into Wu clan to fight for their own benefits.

Wu Yong would no longer give him such a relaxed environment like now, he would keep Fang Yuan under close observation, suppressing him and maintaining alertness against this brother.

If that happened, would Fang Yuan be able to enter the dream realms easily?

Evidently, he could not, he might even get exposed.

And that would lead to greater problems.

Once Fang Yuan's identity was exposed, he would face the attacks of Qiao clan, because they were a righteous path force, they had to keep a clear distance from Fang Yuan, and Wu clan and Qiao clan would try to defend their own reputation by going after Fang Yuan with all their effort, far more than the other clans.

"However, even though I cannot accept it, and won't accept it, I can make use of this 'love'."

Using Qiao Si Liu, Fang Yuan would make Wu Yong more alert, he would arrange for Fang Yuan to be sent back to the super Gu formation, Fang Yuan's goal would be achieved.

Of course, there was nothing perfect in this world, even though this method was brilliant, it had its drawbacks.

Wu Yong's alertness, Luo Mu Zi, Lun Fei, and Chi Shang, as well as Qiao Si Liu's other suitors were all lingering problems.

There was pure love in this world, but it was indeed rare.

When people lived in this world, they had to consider many things.

Qiao Si Liu's beauty, background, cultivation level and others, these were alluring temptations.

Among her suitors, Chi Shang was the purest, but he still considered the element of formation path, not to mention the others.

As for Fang Yuan, he was the most special one.

Chi Shang's arrival was not out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

In fact, he was mentally prepared.

Even without Chi Shang, others were going to come and find problems. Even if they did not come now, they would in the future.

Because Fang Yuan was approaching Qiao Si Liu, and the benefits associated with her, he angered many people. Among these people, there were suitors, and there were forces behind them after the benefits.

As the saying goes, beautiful women are trouble.

A beauty was not easy to pursue.

Only a naive person would think of using love and emotions to conquer a beauty.

Actually, there was far more.

A woman's beauty was her natural dowry.

This dowry was extremely valuable, it was a huge amount of wealth.

Who would not want such wealth?

But not everyone could protect this wealth.

If a beauty was willing to give this wealth to her partner out of pure love, then this lucky person should treat her well.

But the truth was, such situations were too few.

If it happened, treasure it, if it didn't, don't bank on it.

This was not 'unseemly'.

This was — reality.

When Fang Yuan returned to the super Gu formation, he started to think of how to settle the aftermath of this.

A true chessmaster would consider many steps ahead before even moving.

In fact, when Fang Yuan decided to use Qiao Si Liu's 'love' to achieve his goals, he had already started to think of how to resolve the fallout of this issue.

If he handled it badly, Chi Shang would be only the first one here. The second, third, and so on, these people would be unending.

This would be huge interference for Fang Yuan's exploration of the dream realm.

At the same time, Wu Yi Hai's identity restricted Fang Yuan greatly in dealing with these challenges, he could not expose himself during the process.

Fang Yuan needed to resolve this problem carefully and accurately.

How?

It was difficult, and yet easy.

He would create a target, someone who would attract the attention of those suitors.

Fang Yuan had been expecting people to find trouble with him.

Chi Shang came here at such an opportune time, Fang Yuan was secretly happy about it.

When he looked through Chi Shang's information, his joy increased by several times!

His opponent's stupidity was his own fortune.

Of course, there was a point: Such stupidity had nothing to do with IQ or EQ.

There was a clear example from Earth, it was Yue Fei[1].

Yue Fei went on a campaign, and when he was about to succeed, the emperor he served used twelve golden plaques to recall him back to the capital, and executed him on false charges.

The reason?

Was the emperor being stupid?

He was!

But were the emperor and officials idiots?

They were not!

If Yue Fei succeeded in his campaign, the reputation of his personal army would rise greatly, the emperor's authority would be lower than this general, the threat was too big. And most importantly, if Yue Fei won, he would bring back the former emperor. Then what would the current emperor do?

And now, Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You, intentionally nurtured a Gu Immortal like Chi Shang, was he senile, did he not know that a person like Chi Shang, who was focused on researching formation path and had no capabilities in political conflicts, would eventually become a tool that was used?

He was not senile of course, he nurtured Chi Shang extensively precisely because he knew this.

Because his son needed to be the first supreme elder, he needed a 'tool' to assist his son, Chi Shang was the chosen one.

Many people thought that Chi Shang was Fang Yuan's problem.

But that was not the case from Fang Yuan's perspective, he felt like this was an opportunity.

If he handled this well, he would resolve all the future problems ahead, he would be able to peacefully explore the dream realm and raise his foundation for the following period of time.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to lose.

If he did not lose, how would he create the bigger threat than himself, Chi Shang?

Without this meat shield, how would he divert all of the attention away?

Chi Shang was the easiest to plot against.

From his information, Fang Yuan knew that Chi Shang loved to research formation path, he was most skilled in answering problems, and creating the necessary Gu formations.

Fang Yuan thus challenged him using this.

As a researcher, Chi Shang had his unique pride in this domain he was specialized in.

He could ignore everything else, he did not pay attention to his appearance, nor did he have any interest in fortune, but he cared about this. Because this was the meaning of his life!

Fang Yuan, a transformation path Gu Immortal, was using this to challenge him, this was a huge slap on Chi Shang's face to begin with.

How could Chi Shang endure this?

He could not.

Thus, he fell into the trap that Fang Yuan had set, he could not climb out.

Not only was he stuck in the trap, he even toasted Fang Yuan, feeling that Fang Yuan was a very sincere person!

"You are a competitor, but, but what can I say? We are truly friends made after a fight, haha..." Chi Shang laughed, placing his arm around Fang Yuan's shoulder.

"Enough talking, let's drink!" Fang Yuan gulped.

Chi Shang stared at Fang Yuan with wide eyes, he gave a thumbs up and said: "Brother, you are so cool! Let's drink!"

Both sides continued to empty their cups.

"Good wine." Chi Shang sighed: "Sigh, to speak the truth, this is the first time I am drinking so much..."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, but he was unmoved inside.

The wine of the righteous path was not so easy to drink.

The demonic path fought and killed, they were direct in their actions. The banquets of the righteous path was shrouded in rumors and suspicions, they were filled with schemes and plots, all sorts of devious thoughts were like undercurrents, waiting to sweep unknowing prey into the abyss.

Fang Yuan lost the challenge to Chi Shang, but he was very happy, he spread news about this.

So what if he lost?

Sometimes, losing was a way to achieve one's goals.

Chi Shang was also very happy, he felt that this was the happiest he had ever been in a banquet.

At once, both the host and guest were happy.

[1] The guy whose mother carved tattoos on his back to be loyal to his country. Back

Chapter 1333: Plunder Shadow

A joyous banquet was not the end, it was the beginning.

Fang Yuan and Chi Shang became good friends.

For the next few days, Fang Yuan frequently invited Chi Shang, and Chi Shang often came to Wu clan's territory to visit Fang Yuan.

It was both easy and difficult to get close to someone and create a good relationship.

The key was simply lowering the status of oneself and accommodating to the other party's wishes.

Fang Yuan was an old schemer, with attitude Gu in his possession, how could Chi Shang be his match?

Chi Shang was the 'formation devotee', he was not interested in ordinary Gu Immortals. But Fang Yuan was a formation path quasi-grandmaster, he had a connection to this formation path grandmaster.

Both parties conversed on the topic of formation path.

Chi Shang was soon amazed with Fang Yuan's formation path attainment, he expressed his doubt at this. Because Fang Yuan was a transformation path cultivator.

But Fang Yuan told him: "I had always been interested in formation path, when I was a mortal, I researched formation path and primarily cultivated it due to some fortuitous encounters. But circumstances in life force twists and turns, later, I had to become a transformation path Gu Immortal. But I am already very lucky, after all, how many lone cultivators can become immortal?"

This helplessness made Chi Shang sigh deeply, he felt a deep sense of compassion towards Fang Yuan.

"If you want to cultivate formation path, I can help you. Chi clan has a few formation path Gu Immortals, I can intervene and transact formation path Immortal Gu for you." Chi Shang stated.

It was not easy for him to offer this. This proved that Fang Yuan's hard work had paid off.

It was possible to change paths, but the vital Gu had to be changed too.

Fang Yuan looked very moved: "If I want to change paths in the future, I will find you for help."

Chi Shang nodded: "By then, just tell me!"

He knew that it was not easy for a Gu Immortal to change paths, it could not be done quickly, this was a huge matter and needed a lot of aspects to be considered. There were also negative repercussions on the immortal aperture as well.

While interacting with Chi Shang, Fang Yuan gained a lot of benefits.

Even though his attainment level did not increase, Fang Yuan's knowledge did, his basic understanding of formation path had been supplemented, it was of huge help to him.

Fang Yuan gained a more comprehensive and deeper understanding of formation path.

What was the difference between Gu formations and killer moves?

Chi Shang told Fang Yuan: "Gu formations are a type of killer move. Killer moves use multiple Gu worms at the same time, Gu formations are the same. Gu formations are the killer moves of formation path, each Gu formation is a different killer move. Thus, formation path is the path with the most killer moves among all paths. Of course, Gu formations and killer moves have slight differences in details. For example, Gu formations last a longer time. And after a Gu formation is set up, the amount of mental energy the Gu Master uses up also decreases..."

"What is the essence of formation path?" Fang Yuan asked Chi Shang.

Chi Shang shook his head: "Even though I am a formation path grandmaster, I have insufficient attainment level to talk about the essence of formation path. But my clan's Lord Chi Qu You had once told me, the essence of formation path is to create environments."

Fang Yuan heard this and felt deeply enlightened.

The Gu formation of the coiling thread caves was precisely to nurture more regretful spiders by creating a new habitat and environment for them, right?

"It seems that formation path great grandmasters can use the natural dao marks of the surroundings to use fewer Gu worms in setting up their Gu formations. In some places with abundant natural dao marks, just using mortal Gu can form an immortal Gu formation. Is that true?" Fang Yuan asked Chi Shang again.

Chi Shang nodded, explaining patiently: "That is true. But actually, at our level, we can only use dao marks. Some Gu formations are not just built on the foundation of Gu worms but also Gu materials. But we can only use the dao marks inside the immortal materials to set up the Gu formation. After a long time passes, these immortal materials will be destroyed. Formation path great grandmasters are one step ahead, not only can they use immortal and mortal materials, they can also use the dao marks of the surroundings according to the environment."

...

This conversation was a huge inspiration to Fang Yuan.

Thereafter, he attended to Chi Shang even more enthusiastically.

Fang Yuan soon realized that banquets were not very effective at improving their relationship, he might as well converse with him about formation path.

Sometimes, an intense discussion would incite the passion in Chi Shang's heart, and make him feel closer to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan also had another trump card, he wrote letters to Qiao Si Liu.

Every time he wrote a letter, he would praise Chi Shang and exclaim about his shocking formation path talent, and his incredible ingenuity.

Chi Shang was getting embarrassed from being praised, he looked at Fang Yuan in a different light, he thought that this person was truly a gentleman, conducting himself uprightly and with an open mind.

Returning the favor, he also wrote letters to Qiao Si Liu, praising Fang Yuan deeply, saying that he cultivated transformation path and even formation path alongside it, his attainment was so deep that he felt great admiration and surprise at it.

Qiao Si Liu: "..."

She looked at the letters she received, she felt that these two suitors were praising each other so much that they had forgotten about her!

She did not expect to see this situation, while she rolled her eyes to herself, she also wrote back letters of praise, especially towards their open-mindedness.

Undeniably, Fang Yuan and Chi Shang turned from enemies to friends, this transformation made everyone watching from the side feel deeply shocked.

Southern Border, Plunder Shadow Earth Trench.

This was a famous Earth Trench in Southern Border, because it had countless fierce dark path beasts, as well as shadow monsters that were renowned in Southern Border.

At the same time, this was also one of the most dangerous places in Southern Border.

Right now, deep within this Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, inside a certain cave.

"Ahhhhh..." A crazed old man with purple hair and messy clothes was running around barefoot in the cave, while screaming and making a din.

Plop.

Suddenly, he fell to the ground, and his body started to twist as he started to crawl like an earthworm.

After moving for a while, he suddenly stood up, laughing sheepishly.

But a moment later, his laughter stopped, his cloudy eyes regained clarity.

"Lord Purple, you are awake." Ying Wu Xie suddenly appeared in the cave, he sighed with a complex expression.

This crazed old man was Purple.

Shadow Sect's party of four had vanished after the battle of Reverse Flow River, they had returned to Southern Border at some point in time. They had even entered deep into Plunder Shadow Earth Trench.

Purple sighed deeply, he patted the soil on his body, his body shrunk to his miniman form with miniature wings.

"Call me Purple Mountain True Monarch, this will help our future actions." Purple Mountain True Monarch said: "What information do you have now?"

Ying Wu Xie said: "Southern Border's political situation is progressing according to our plan. But it is a pity, Chi Shang and Wu Yi Hai did not have an intense conflict, they even became good friends."

"Oh?" Purple Mountain True Monarch was slightly surprised.

After looking at the information, he nodded: "This Wu Yi Hai is quite interesting, he primarily cultivates transformation path but also has enough formation path attainment to gain Chi Shang's approval."

"This would help him, but he could not defy Wu Yong, he was sent to the super Gu formation again."

Ying Wu Xie nodded: "Wu Yong is a rank eight Gu Immortal with great authority now, Wu Yi Hai had just returned not long ago, he did not even join with Qiao clan, and cannot get their full support."

"But this proves further that even though Wu Yi Hai is a lone cultivator, he has great ambitions. Because he got close to Qiao Si Liu, yet he did not get together with her, it shows that he has not agreed on the profit distribution with Qiao clan yet. Is his ambition something we can make use of?"

"Hmm..." Purple Mountain True Monarch thought about it: "We might be able to make use of this, but we know too little about this person. Right now, our plans on Wu clan should focus on Wu Yong. Wu clan is the number one force in Southern Border, they are the pillar of the righteous path, if they fall, Southern Border would have huge political turmoil. By then, we will take advantage of it and destroy the super Gu formation, we will be able to save our main body."

It turned out that Wu clan's political problems were not simple, Shadow Sect was behind them, causing many of the situations!

"Hmph! So what if Southern Border's politics get into chaos?" Bai Ning Bing appeared outside the cave, having a cold expression: "With just the four of us, even if the super Gu formation only has four Gu Immortals defending it, it will be difficult. Furthermore, our main fighting strength is so unstable."

Bai Ning Bing spoke without any politeness.

Even against the rank eight Purple Mountain True Monarch.

She was fearless, because when Fang Yuan chased after them, she had already set a new alliance agreement with Ying Wu Xie and the others, they were of equal status.

And Purple Mountain True Monarch's constant insanity made the respect in her heart dwindle.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was unmoved, smiling: "Political unrest is not enough, of course, these righteous path forces are not stupid. But this is just to weaken the strength of the righteous path in the super Gu formation. The four of us are not enough, we are too short on manpower, so now, we will recruit people."

"Recruit people?" Ying Wu Xie was surprised: "There are still hidden cards in Southern Border that I do not know about?"

Because he knew that Southern Border's Shadow Sect forces were heavily crippled. If they wanted to attack the super Gu formation, these new members needed to have high power level, ordinary rank six Gu Immortals were simply useless.

But such people would definitely have been recruited when Ying Wu Xie was facing Fang Yuan's pursuit earlier.

Or even further back, if such people existed, when Spectral Soul defied heaven to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, they would have been used already, to deal with Central Continent's Gu Immortals."

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded, before shaking his head: "Do you two know why I fall into insanity sometimes?"

Chapter 1334: Assimilating with Heaven's Will

Purple Mountain True Monarch suddenly changed the topic.

Bai Ning Bing did not speak, while Ying Wu Xie asked: "Is it not the interference of heaven's will?"

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "It is heaven's will indeed, but I was the one who initiated it."

"What do you mean?" Bai Ning Bing heard this and showed shock on her face.

Hearing Purple Mountain True Monarch's words, it seemed like his insanity was due to his own actions.

Purple Mountain True Monarch sighed eerily, scenes of the past drifted in his mind: "In the past, along with the other first generation split souls, we found the major enemy was heaven's will, and tried to find ways to deal with it."

"I cultivated wisdom path, I was the leader of the split souls, I had to be the one to find a way to deal with heaven's will."

"Using a part of the true inheritance of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable that we found, and together with my wisdom path attainment, I devised a method, that was to assimilate with heaven's will."

"Assimilate with heaven's will?" Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie looked at each other, frowning.

"That's right, heaven's will is vast and immense, it is everywhere, back then, we had just started to interact with it, we did not know as many secrets and weaknesses of it as now. Back then, we were greatly restricted, the situation was worsening and getting more dangerous every day. More and more members died after being targeted by heaven's will, hope was turning bleak."

Purple Mountain True Monarch continued: "Left without a choice, I used this method that was not a proper solution. Since the enemy was so powerful, I pretended to surrender and infiltrate the enemy to obtain intelligence about it. After all, know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated."

Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie's eyes shone.

Even now, they could see the innovation of this method.

Heaven's will was formless, Purple Mountain True Monarch actually wanted to infiltrate heaven's will, it was truly an incredible idea.

Purple Mountain True Monarch did not just think about it, he did it!

Purple Mountain True Monarch continued explaining: "Heaven's will, you must be clear of it. When grotto-heavens devour fragments of the nine heavens, heaven's will enters, and any heavenly spirit inside would turn dull and robotic. The heavenly spirit becomes like this, it's similar for Gu Immortals. Every time I assimilate with heaven's will, I will become crazy and lose my sense of reason."

"However, this is also why I can greatly reduce heaven's will's intention of killing me, and am able to live until now."

"There is also one benefit of this, when I fuse with heaven's will, I can clearly understand it and learn about its strengths and weaknesses."

"When I learn about heaven's will's thoughts, I can see the planning of heaven's will and am able to plot for myself and Shadow Sect."

"The principle of heaven is to be merciless, it treats all beings as pawns. From the perspective of heaven's will, all beings in this world are its chess pieces. And in this chessboard of destiny, there are some crucial points that attract my attention."

Purple Mountain True Monarch's explanation made both Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie deeply interested.

Because they had already sensed that Purple Mountain True Monarch's following words were going to be very important.

As expected, Purple Mountain True Monarch continued: "I assimilated with heaven's will, I found that in heaven's will's arrangements, there were some very crucial pawns. So every time I went crazy, I would use heaven's will to get close to these pawns, and by the time I regain my senses, I would try to turn them over to my side, and use my own power to make them my pieces."

"And in the battle not long ago, I believe you have already seen the use of one of these pawns."

Bai Ning Bing's body shook.

Ying Wu Xie said in realization: "Lord Purple Mountain True Monarch, you are talking about Tai Bai Yun Sheng?"

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "That's right, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a crucial pawn in the chessboard of destiny, even though heaven's will arranged it, I managed to influence him and eventually used his power to allow you all to escape."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had once met Purple Mountain True Monarch when he was a Gu Master, obtaining his true inheritance.

There were heaven's will's arrangements on him, and also Purple Mountain True Monarch's influence.

Thus, when Fang Yuan was used by heaven's will to return to the past and overturn Spectral Soul's plan, Fang Yuan received Tai Bai Yun Sheng's help during the process.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng submitted to Fang Yuan.

One of the reasons was Fang Yuan's own intelligence. The other factor was heaven's will.

But later, Tai Bai Yun Sheng separated from Fang Yuan, helping Shadow Sect instead.

This was because Fang Yuan betrayed heaven's will, at the crucial moment, he did not destroy sovereign immortal fetus Gu, he used it for himself. Tai Bai Yun Sheng thus helped Shadow Sect greatly as a result of Purple Mountain True Monarch's influence.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng died in battle, on the surface, it was due to Fang Yuan, but from another perspective, this was the sacrificial piece from the conflict between Shadow Sect and heaven's will.

Ying Wu Xie heard this and finally understood Purple Mountain True Monarch's intent.

He called out: "I get it, all these years, Lord Purple Mountain True Monarch has traveled the world, you influenced many crucial pawns, and now, they will be the strength to break the super Gu formation and rescue our main body!"

Purple Mountain True Monarch smiled lightly: "Precisely."

Southern Border, super Gu formation.

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Central Continent.

An intense jade green light shot into the sky with an alluring fragrance.

Countless Gu worms were flying around in the jade light, just one look would make a person dizzy.

Fang Yuan maintained a high level of concentration, as time passed, a portion of the Gu worms stopped flying, they landed and fell underground.

More and more Gu worms went underground, they started to shine and resonated with the previous Gu worms, creating a mystical power.

The jade pillar of light shrunk and got fainter, at Fang Yuan's will, an Immortal Gu flew out.

This Gu resembled a round pearl, it was as large as a goose egg, the pearl had countless markings on it that were moving around, they were brilliant like a blooming field of lotuses, or the rumbling of clouds.

It was rank six Immortal Gu Blood Asset.

Fang Yuan breathed roughly, the arrangement of the Gu formation had reached its most crucial moment.

Blood asset Immortal Gu slowly floated into the jade light.

Almost instantly, the jade light was dyed by blood asset Immortal Gu and turned blood red.

The red light got stronger and stronger, several breaths later, it reached an intensity that was on par with the jade light earlier.

Fang Yuan let out a breath, the most crucial step was over, he just had to follow the routine now.

The bright red pillar weakened before dissipating, but the fragrance still remained in the air, permeating the cave below.

This cave was huge, it was around 200000m2.

Deep underground, there was a few li of distance.

The cave was not completely sealed, there were a hundred tunnels that resembled air vents, connecting the cave to the outside world. On the surface of the ground, there were countless holes that were dark and deep, but they gave off fragrance.

"The Gu formation for the coiling thread caves is arranged! The creation of the coiling thread caves is half done."

"Next, I have to move those regretful spiders over and start nurturing them."

"This process would require the modification of the Gu formation, in a month or two, I will be done."

Fang Yuan was filled with joy.

Chi Shang left this place and returned to Chi clan, as Fang Yuan continued his dream realm exploration.

In the formation path dream realm earlier, there were two scenes left, they were solved by Fang Yuan's unravel dream killer move.

As he had expected, Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level reached grandmaster!

Using his formation path grandmaster attainment level, as well as the immense gains from interacting with Chi Shang, Fang Yuan easily deduced a brand new coiling thread Gu formation.

This coiling thread Gu formation still used blood asset Immortal Gu, and the effect was only doubled.

Fang Yuan's initial Gu formation concept could multiply his gains by eight, but this was not solvable. There was no way of setting it up.

Doubling it made Fang Yuan satisfied already.

He still had a lot of accumulations left, he could use unravel dream many times, and with Chi Shang leaving and diverting attention away for him, he could secretly explore dream realms now.

Fang Yuan treasured this rare opportunity, in the following days, he gave an excuse of going into closed cultivation in order to to delve into dream realms.

Right as he was laboriously exploring dream realms, shocking news came out that shook the Gu Immortals of all five regions.

Central Continent's ten great ancient sects and Heavenly Court had lost!

They sent a powerful group to Northern Plains, but they did not manage to save Ma Hong Yun and even had a crushing defeat.

Out of the three rank eight Gu Immortals, Wei Ling Yang, Myriad Tidal Dragon and Bi Chen Tian, two died while one went missing.

The one who killed the rank eight Gu Immortals was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's former steed, legendary immemorial desolate beast — Dog Tail Life Extending Ferret.

But Central Continent had survivors too.

Zhao Lian Yun, Yu Yi Ye Zi, Shi Zheng Yi and the rest were saved by Wei Ling Yang risking his life, they managed to hair-raisingly escape with their lives under the reinforcements of Central Continent later.

This news made the entire world shocked!

Central Continent's foundation and strength was publicly recognized as the strongest in all five regions.

The ten great ancient sects were super forces which governed Central Continent, any one of them could defeat the average level of super clans or tribes in all five regions.

And Heavenly Court was in charge of the ten great ancient sects, not only did it rule Central Continent, its influence extended to the other four regions.

Its status in the hearts of Central Continent's people was unshakeable. In the hearts of the people in the other four regions, it was the number one force in the world.

After all, it had three Immortal Venerables that were in it, which force in this world could match it?

But this extremely powerful Heavenly Court actually lost in Northern Plains.

After their shock, everyone learned about more information and expressed their understanding.

Because it was traditionally known that Northern Plains was tough and had high battle strength, and this time, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's descendants, Longevity Heaven, were the ones who fought!

As for Heavenly Court's defeat, they had ventured into another region, their true strength had not been used.

In fact, the group from Heavenly Court that went to Northern Plains was not just fighting Longevity Heaven, they also fought against Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

But regardless of the reasons, they had lost, the reputations of Longevity Heaven and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable soared, while those of Heavenly Court and the ten great ancient sects fell drastically.

Chapter 1335: Heavenly Court's Countermeasure

"Wei Ling Yang and Bi Chen Tian died while Myriad Tidal Dragon escaped..."

Fang Yuan muttered.

Information was transmitted to him, in this super Gu formation, he was the person with the clearest understanding of that situation.

"Looking at the date, it is about time."

"Heavenly Court went to Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, which was represented by Longevity Heaven, Central Continent was dealt a huge blow as a result."

"Dog tail life extending ferret... as expected of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's steed, its battle strength is truly fearsome."

"Even though this raises Northern Plains' morale, it is not a problem for Heavenly Court."

With the five hundred years of his previous life, and experiencing the first half of the five regions chaotic war, Fang Yuan knew that Heavenly Court had immensely deep foundation. Compared to it, Longevity Heaven was just Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grotto-heaven, its foundation was far less abundant.

"This kind of event is incredibly rare. It had never happened in my previous life."

"After this, Northern Plains and Central Continent are basically enemies, or rather, Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court are on opposite sides."

"And now, will Heavenly Court take revenge? If they do, it will be very interesting."

Fang Yuan thought in his mind, continuing to deduce and try to find out the possible political outcomes.

Longevity Heaven came from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, while Heavenly Court had three Immortal Venerables, they were all righteous path forces, to think that they would attack each other so harshly.

Right now, the Gu Immortals of all five regions, and all the different forces, were focused on this matter.

They were focusing on Heavenly Court's reaction.

According to conventional reasoning, Heavenly Court had to counterattack, because it was the number one Gu Immortal organization in the five regions. If it did not do anything, its reputation would fall.

But the five regional walls prevented any large scale war between Gu Immortals.

And most people did not know about Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's Luck Suppression Heavenly Palace.

It was too difficult for Heavenly Court to attack.

Thus, whether it attacked or not, it had its own excuses.

And no matter what Heavenly Court chose, its next step would decide the direction that the five regions would progress towards.

Fang Yuan let out a sigh.

He had predicted this long ago.

Heavenly Court sent Gu Immortals to save Ma Hong Yun, they would definitely face the obstruction of Northern Plains' Gu Immortals. After Central Continent's Gu Immortals failed the rescue, they escaped back to Central Continent, and this battle, which had lasted a long time, finally reached a conclusion.

But when he received news of this, Fang Yuan felt something amiss.

There was something wrong.

But he could not state what the problem was.

"Perhaps, because everyone has changed so much because of my actions, there were too many chain reactions, and the advantage of my rebirth is shrinking, so I am feeling increasingly uneasy?"

The radiance of dream realm shone on Fang Yuan's face, his expression became dark and uncertain.

"No matter what, increasing my strength is most important."

"Dream realm, here I come!"

Regardless of the situation outside, or how treacherous or uncertain it was, as long as he got stronger, Fang Yuan would feel safer.

His soul entered the dream.

Regaining his senses, Fang Yuan quickly found out that he was in the wilderness.

Night time.

The crescent moon emitted a cold light.

Wild dogs were barking, Fang Yuan was immobile, he was carried by two people from the front and back.

"What is the matter?" Realizing that he could not move, Fang Yuan started to assess the situation around him.

Grunt grunt...

Sounds that resembled a pig eating entered Fang Yuan's ears.

He soon realized that this weird sound came from the two who were carrying him.

These two weird people carried Fang Yuan until halfway up the mountain.

The dark clouds in the sky faded, using the cold moonlight, Fang Yuan found that the two strange people holding him up were not humans, they were two boar headed beastmen.

"In the current world, beastmen are extinct. Since beastmen appeared in this dream realm, what era is this?" A question appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

Fang Yuan felt something amiss, he started to struggle but he soon realized that he was extremely weak, he was heavily injured.

He struggled intensely, but he only managed to move his body slightly.

"Grr! Grr!"

The two boar headed beastmen noticed Fang Yuan's movement and started to growl.

"Oh no!!" Fang Yuan cried out internally.

But the two beastmen were faster, they suddenly let go, Fang Yuan fell to the ground.

The intense pain almost made Fang Yuan faint on the spot.

Using his firm determination and willpower, Fang Yuan forced his eyes open and saw that the boar headed beastman in front of him raised his leg.

He stomped on Fang Yuan's face as the shape of the boar leg enlarged in Fang Yuan's vision.

Bam.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan's entire head was smashed like a watermelon, blood flowed out with brain matter scattering everywhere.

"F*ck!" The dream realm exploration ended, Fang Yuan's soul was injured, he was forced out.

"This means, I need to wait for my chance, I cannot act rashly?" Fang Yuan thought as he used guts Gu to heal himself.

Unravel dream had limited usage in numbers, the nightmare demonic colt immortal materials had already been expended.

But guts Gu was different, as long as he had Dang Hun Mountain, guts Gu was infinite in supply.

Thus, Fang Yuan was more willing to use guts Gu and suffer soul injuries than use unravel dream unnecessarily.

Soon, Fang Yuan's soul healed, and he entered the dream realm again.

This time, Fang Yuan did not move, he allowed the two boar headed beastmen to carry him halfway up the mountain.

"Grr grr." At a certain point, the boar headed beastmen stopped as one of them grunted.

The other one lifted Fang Yuan's legs as he walked up.

Using the moonlight, Fang Yuan could see that these two boar headed beastmen were on the edge of a cliff.

"Oh no!" Fang Yuan was about to struggle when these two boar headed beastmen tossed Fang Yuan down the cliff.

Fang Yuan rapidly fell down the cliff.

"This is?!" His eyes were wide opened, the bottom of the cliff was a mass grave.

Countless corpses were casually lying around, the rotten corpses had a thick mist of foul smelling odor around them.

Before Fang Yuan could think anymore, plop.

With a loud sound, Fang Yuan fell to the bottom of the cliff.

He was crushed into meat paste, he was dead with a ruined corpse left behind.

Fang Yuan was forced out of the dream realm again.

"This dream realm, what is it exactly?"

While Fang Yuan was exploring the dream realm, in Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

"Lord Duke Long, please." An old woman spoke, she had a hunched back, she was bending down, her hair was yellow like wheat, her face was wrinkled and her eyes were blurry.

She wore a yellow-brown robe, there was a ring of sand around her waist, she was standing before Duke Long reverently.

Duke Long was no longer in a weak state after taking away Di Zang Sheng's life force, he was mighty and commanding now, he had regained his demeanor as the apex of a legend.

At this moment, he was looking at the tower in front of him as he nodded: "Granny Sha, you did well."

This tower was Heaven Overseeing Tower.

A rank nine Immortal Gu House!

It had incredible reputation, it was famous throughout history.

Even though it was shattered in Southern Border, most of the Immortal Gu were preserved, after it was sent back to Heavenly Court, Gu Immortal Granny Sha woke up and had been refining Gu, repairing Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Right now, her work was done, Heaven Overseeing Tower was repaired completely!

"Lord Duke Long, please." Granny Sha led the way.

Duke Long and Fairy Zi Wei followed, entering Heaven Overseeing Tower.

The white jade stairs spiralled upwards, it was no different from before.

But Heaven Overseeing Tower had not activated, so Duke Long and the others went up without anything happening.

When they got to the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, the three Gu Immortals saw an Immortal Gu.

This Immortal Gu gave off an intense rank nine aura, it was like a spider, colored in black and white, there was a scarlet wound on its body that almost cut it in two.

What else was it but rank nine fate Immortal Gu?

This fate Immortal Gu was damaged by Red Lotus Demon Venerable using the power of love Immortal Gu, it almost died. But after the hard work of generations of Heavenly Court's members, it had finally recovered to fifty percent during the last Central Continent Refinement Path Convention.

After reaching this point of qualitative change, fate Immortal Gu's recovery speed was many times that of before.

Right now, even without success dao marks, it had recovered to sixty percent due to Granny Sha's hard work.

"Good, very good, Granny Sha, you have contributed greatly to Heavenly Court, you have contributed greatly to humanity. I am sure that when Heavenly Court rules the five regions, your merits will be recorded in history and be revered by all descendants in the future." Duke Long sighed with an appreciative tone.

Granny Sha smiled: "I am flattered, Lord Duke Long, I was merely contributing my meager strength. Furthermore, repairing Heaven Overseeing Tower was that old man's wish too. Hehehe..."

Granny Sha laughed continuously as her body turned into sand while she laughed.

A wind started blowing from nowhere, causing the sand to scatter in the air.

Rank eight Gu Immortal Granny Sha, refinement path great grandmaster, had died at this moment!

She had little lifespan to begin with, when the previous generation Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord died, she woke up from shock, and contributed the last spark of her life to Heavenly Court.

Silence.

Another Heavenly Court rank eight Gu Immortal had sacrificed herself, during this period of time, Heavenly Court had sacrificed many members.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes were slightly red.

Duke Long's expression did not change, his body was straight like a ruler, he spoke: "In the passage of history, generations of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals have sacrificed themselves like this, to give a bright future to our descendants. Wei Ling Yang, Bi Chen Tian, they were sacrificed, Granny Sha was sacrificed, and in the future, the two of us will do the same."

"Why has Heavenly Court always been the top Gu Immortal force? Other than the three Immortal Venerables, there is another important reason, that is, us Heavenly Court Gu Immortals are not afraid of sacrificing ourselves. Because we know that humanity needs us, everyone needs us, heaven and earth need us!"

Fairy Zi Wei breathed in deeply, trying to regain her calmness: "Then, Lord Duke Long, what do we do now?"

Duke Long shut his eyes, before opening them again: "The great era is beginning, some people cannot be allowed to live anymore."

"But that Fang Yuan, Ying Wu Xie, Purple, and others are all crafty, we have no idea where they are now. It is too tough to deduce their locations with the obstruction of regional walls." Fairy Zi Wei had a worried expression.

"No need to worry." Duke Long waved his hand: "No matter where they are now, we both know that they will go to one place, the giant dream realm in Southern Border."

"Forget about Northern Plains and Longevity Heaven, they are small problems."

"We have to get rid of these largest threats first!"

Chapter 1336: Part Man Part Beast, Zuo Ye Hui

Cold moon and desolate mountain.

Two boar headed beastmen carried Fang Yuan up the mountain from the front and back.

Fang Yuan continued to observe, he did not act rashly.

"My body is a rank four Gu Master, I have an aperture and primeval essence but I have no Gu worms."

"And I am heavily injured and extremely weak, even if I am in a healthy state, without any Gu worms, I am no match for these two boar headed beastmen."

"However, once we get to the cliff, these two boar headed beastmen will toss me down. From this height, I will definitely die without the protection of any Gu worms, unless I had the sovereign immortal body."

"Thus... my only hope of survival is on this road up the mountain?"

Immortal killer move — Unravel Dream!

After analyzing this, Fang Yuan used this trump card.

After activating unravel dream, Fang Yuan saw immediate effect.

He felt like he regained some strength at this instant. For example, he was like an adventurer who was about to die of thirst in the desert earlier, but now, he drank a few drops of water.

"There was an effect, but isn't the strength I recovered too little?"

Fang Yuan had no choice, he could only use unravel dream again.

This time, some of his injuries had instantly formed scabs, the pain he was feeling became less intense.

But on his chest and back, there were still several deep wounds where bones could be seen, they were not recovering.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Fang Yuan had to use this immortal killer move continuously, his major injuries healed drastically, though they did not form scabs, his bleeding condition had ceased. He regained quite a bit of strength, his body had regained some warmth from its initial icy state.

But this did not give Fang Yuan any notable battle strength.

He was still a mortal now, he had primeval essence but he could not fight any of the boar headed beastmen alone.

Moreover, there were two boar headed beastmen, not just one.

"What is going on?"

"Immortal killer move unravel dream's effect was so little?"

"I used it five times but this is all I got?"

Fang Yuan looked at the cliff that he was reaching, he made up his mind: "Forget it, I should take action first!"

His body bounced up like a lobster.

The two boar headed beastmen were caught by surprise and he managed to get free from them.

Fang Yuan landed on the ground, the tough rocks stabbed into his wounds as he almost fainted from pain.

The two boar headed beastmen had already reacted, they shouted as they pounced at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan used his profound fighting skills to dodge while escaping and running down the mountain.

The two beastmen chased after him.

In a while, the two boar beastmen found Fang Yuan.

Plop.

Two white boar tusks stabbed into Fang Yuan's injuries on his back, penetrating out of his chest.

Fang Yuan stopped moving, blood flowed out of his mouth.

Soon after, his vision turned dark.

When he opened his eyes, he was in a hall.

He had returned to reality again, sent out of the dream realm.

His face was pale, his soul was injured, but what made Fang Yuan surprised was this strange dream realm.

"This dream realm is the most difficult one I have ever been in."

"Even though it is a realistic dream realm, the difficulty is incredibly high."

"As of now, I have not even finished exploring the first scene, and I have already died multiple times."

"Unravel dream is also extremely weak in there, what is going on?"

This problem made Fang Yuan very perplexed.

He thought about it and could not deduce anything, he had to take a step back and think about how he could deal with the two beastmen and escape alive.

"The boar headed beastmen have huge bodies, if I can enter the forest, it would be easier. But this desolate mountain has no trees around, there are not even any piles of rocks."

"I can only use unravel dream five times, any additional tries would have no effect."

"Even though it can allow me to regain my strength and stabilize my wounds, the effects are not much, it would be better to have a single Gu worm."

"Furthermore, even if I have Gu worms and a forest around, my stamina is limited, I cannot get far."

After some analysis, Fang Yuan finally realized: "So this dream realm forces me to fall to the bottom of the cliff?"

Entering the dream realm again.

This time, Fang Yuan did not act rashly, he used unravel dream and preserved his strength and mental energy.

When he was at the cliff, the two boar headed beastmen tossed him over the cliff.

But the point of difference was, in midair, Fang Yuan started to adjust his body, getting close to the cliff.

Several breaths later, he saw some strange rocks on the wall, they were protruding out. There were also some trees that lived tenaciously on the cliff face.

Bam.

With a loud crash, Fang Yuan landed on a rock, his bones broke and he died.

"The speed of descent was too fast, my injuries were too severe, I died the moment I landed on a rock, it seems I need to land on the trees."

Entering the dream realm again.

Using this experience, Fang Yuan landed on a tree.

Crack crack.

Following the sounds of some breaking branches, Fang Yuan fell downwards after his body broke some branches.

But this time, he fell much slower.

He used his soles and arms to grab at the cliff wall and adjust his direction.

The second tree.

Plop!

Fang Yuan landed on the tree trunk, he was pierced thoroughly by countless sharp leaves that were as long as an arm.

He died on the spot.

"What, what is this tree?" Fang Yuan was expelled from the dream realm again.

After many tries, continuously using guts Gu and unravel dream.

After dying eighteen times in the dream realm, Fang Yuan finally landed at the bottom of the valley.

But his injuries were too severe, his four limbs were unusable, only his right arm had some sensation left. He was batched in blood as his injuries tore open again, his warm blood was flowing out continuously. His bones were mostly fractured, the intense pain was assaulting him like burning fire.

But this was the best result that Fang Yuan could achieve after countless tries.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Fang Yuan used unravel dream, after he got to the bottom of the valley, it could be used again.

Fang Yuan's injuries healed a little, he could exert strength in his right arm, his left leg also regained some sensation, but his right leg was completely broken, it was twisted by his ankle at an awkward angle.

Fang Yuan quickly inspected the situation around him as he looked around.

There was a pile of corpses, like a mountain, flesh was rotting, the stench of corpses was dense as a mist, assaulting his nose.

"What do I do now?" While Fang Yuan was dazed, he felt a strong Gu Immortal aura above his head.

Two variant human rank seven Gu Immortals appeared in the sky.

They were both beastmen, one had a boar head and human body, while another had a snake body and human head.

"Be careful, it's a big one down there!" The Gu Immortal with a snake body and human head said in a cold voice.

"Hahaha, big fellow, why are you sleeping, wake up!!" The boar head and human body Gu Immortal laughed loudly.

The two were not quiet, they purposely amplified their voices, they sounded like rumbling thunder, reverberating in the valley.

Incited by this voice, an overwhelming aura burst out of the mist-like stench of corpses.

Rumble!

An intense aura burst out in the surroundings, all of the stench in the valley was blown away.

A giant figure appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

It was a giant.

Seven to eight stories tall.

It was black in color, its black hair flowed like a cape, extending to its waist. Hidden by its hair were two bright red spots.

It had awakened!

The two beastman Gu Immortals were stunned by this aura, they were no longer arrogant, they were filled with anxiety and fear.

Fang Yuan was the same.

Because this monster's aura showed him: "Rank eight peak Gu Immortal aura! But it seems like a man, and an immemorial desolate beast at the same time."

"Big fellow, go eat."

"That's right, this flesh and blood was obtained by our clan after many battles."

The two beastman Gu Immortals urged.

"How many times have I said it, I have a name, I am Zuo Ye Hui." The black giant actually spoke, but it went back to eating after saying that.

It stretched out its arms, corpses were grabbed by its monstrous hands as it stuffed them into its mouth.

"This is not good." Fang Yuan thought, at this rate, he was going to be eaten.

...

Southern Border, black demon pit.

Southern Border had many mountains and many pits.

Black demon pit was not eye catching among all the pits, it was small and did not have many dao marks.

It produced some dark path resources, but for super forces, it was not useful, and for normal forces, the excavation was too tough.

Thus, nobody came here.

But at this moment, Purple Mountain True Monarch and the others came to black demon pit.

"What are we doing here?" Bai Ning Bing looked around, she used the investigative method from Bai Xiang's true inheritance but could not see anything.

Purple Mountain True Monarch did not answer her, he spoke seemingly at the air: "I am here, act according to our agreement, previously, I passed you my true inheritance, you owe me a favor."

"Favor? What favor?!" A voice came from within the pit.

Afterwards, an intense aura burst out, from weak to strong, in the blink of an eye, Bai Ning Bing's, Ying Wu Xie's, and the others' expressions changed.

Only Purple Mountain True Monarch remained calm as before: "Haven't you always wanted to be human? Zuo Ye Hui."

"Human? Oh, I remember now, you are that guy from back then."

"Right, back then, I helped you, you owe me a favor."

"Mm! I, Zuo Ye Hui, want to be human, I need to return the favor. Tell me, what help do you need."

"What you are most skilled at — eating humans."

"Hahaha, I am sick of eating normal humans."

"Don't worry, they are immortals, there might even be rank eight Gu Immortals." Purple Mountain True Monarch smiled.

"That's good!!!"

Chapter 1337: Mushroomman Paradise, Dark Grandmaster

Southern Border, giant dream realm.

"Zuo Ye Hui?!" Hearing the name of this giant monster, Fang Yuan's heart shook intensely.

This was an immemorial desolate beast with a mysterious origin, it had existed since a million years ago, during the Olden Antiquity Era.

Every time it appeared, there would be endless slaughter and fighting. In terms of seniority, the dog tail life extending ferret from Northern Plains was merely a newcomer that rose to fame three hundred thousand years ago.

Zuo Ye Hui, You Tian Guang, these two names were once placed side by side in human history. They were the nightmares of the Olden Antiquity Era, Medieval Antiquity Era, and Late Antiquity Era.

They were immemorial desolate beasts, but they possessed human forms, nobody knew why.

Whenever they appeared, they would create endless slaughter, no matter which region, they would whip up a bloody storm.

Even Central Continent's Heavenly Court could not exterminate them.

They were extremely crafty, they worked together and whenever a Demon Venerable or Immortal Venerable was alive, they would hide and not show up.

Thankfully, when it was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's era, the kindest Immortal Venerable throughout history was determined to get rid of these evils, he spent a lot of time and effort, finally locating these two legendary immemorial desolate beasts' hiding spot.

After an intense battle, You Tian Guang died, while Zuo Ye Hui was heavily injured, it managed to escape but it went missing, it was unknown if it was dead or alive.

"Zuo Ye Hui... I actually encountered this legendary immemorial desolate beast in a dream realm?" Fang Yuan held in his shock, he continued to climb.

Zuo Ye Hui was eating all of the corpses around it, in the surroundings of this beast, the mountain-like pile of corpses was pouring into its bloodthirsty mouth.

Immortal killer move!

This was obviously an immortal killer move.

Its chewing alone could not allow it to eat at such a rapid speed.

Fang Yuan was having a tough time.

He was heavily injured and could not move fast, the speed of his climbing could not match the speed of suction by Zuo Ye Hui, he was dragged towards the center by these moving corpses.

Suddenly, Zuo Ye Hui breathed in deeply.

Intense winds blew, Fang Yuan was caught off guard and the winds blew him away, into Zuo Ye Hui's mouth.

Zuo Ye Hui chewed rapidly, Fang Yuan was chomped up into meat paste by its sharp teeth.

"I died again!" Fang Yuan returned to reality with his soul injuries.

"How do I pass this dream realm?" This problem was like a giant boulder blocking Fang Yuan's advancement.

He fell into deep contemplation.

While he was brought up the mountain by the two boar headed beastmen, Fang Yuan tried many ways but could not escape.

He knew now that this dream realm was forcing him to enter the valley.

But this valley was more dangerous than the boar headed beastmen.

Because a legendary immemorial desolate beast was there.

Immemorial desolate beasts rivaled rank eight Gu Immortals, but most of them had low intelligence, they were not the match of rank eight Gu Immortals.

But there were exceptions to everything, among immemorial desolate beasts, there were a certain few unique individuals.

Due to all sorts of fortuitous encounters, they had wisdom akin to that of humans, they learned the ways of Gu cultivation and had immortal apertures, they knew how to manipulate Immortal Gu and could even unleash immortal killer moves.

Their danger was extremely large, thus, every legendary immemorial desolate beast had its own name.

Like dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu, Central Continent's Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng as well as Huo Kong, along with Zuo Ye Hui and You Tian Guang. These were all legendary immemorial desolate beasts.

Such existences were often stronger than most rank eight Gu Immortals.

This could be seen from how the dog tail life extending ferret, Mao Li Qiu, killed two Heavenly Court rank eight Gu Immortals.

Man is the spirit of all living beings, but they had weak bodies and could not compare to other lifeforms if Gu worms were not used. Be it speed, strength, lifespan, recovery speed, vision, hearing, and others, humans were inferior.

Immemorial desolate beasts possessed extremely dense dao marks, they had longer lifespan than humans, their recovery, strength, and others surpassed an ordinary human. Once they could use Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves, possessed an immortal aperture and had wisdom like humans, their strength would naturally surpass rank eight Gu Immortals.

"Does this dream realm want me to try and escape from getting eaten by Zuo Ye Hui?"

Fang Yuan entered the dream again.

Using unravel dream along the way, he went to the bottom of the giant corpse pile with a shred of life remaining.

"Good." Fang Yuan gathered his focus, and pushed away all of the corpses before Zuo Ye Hui started eating, burying himself.

As Zuo Ye Hui started to suck, intense winds blew.

The surface of the corpse mountain started to fly away towards it.

Fang Yuan was intact as he had dug into the corpses.

But soon, the intense winds continued unceasingly as he was swept into Zuo Ye Hui's mouth again.

"F*ck!" Fang Yuan's final view was a row of sharp teeth stabbing into his body.

...

Entering the dream again.

"I'll dig, dig and dig more." Fang Yuan continued as he used unravel dream to find some easy spots to drill into, allowing his progress to be faster.

Zuo Ye Hui continued to breathe in, after a long time, the winds stopped.

Fang Yuan was also on his last breaths, hiding among the corpses.

"I finally endured it." While he was rejoicing, one of the two beastman Gu Immortals in the air spoke.

"Zuo Ye Hui, good appetite."

The dark giant said: "Too few, too few! I want to eat more humans, the more humans I eat, I closer I am to becoming human."

"Don't worry, there's more." The beastman Gu Immortal laughed as it opened its immortal aperture, a large number of human Gu Master corpses fell down like a waterfall.

"F*ck." Fang Yuan's expression changed, he uncontrollably cursed.

At the next moment, he was squashed to death by the pile of corpses.

...

Entering the dream again.

Fang Yuan dug into the corpse pile, but this time, he did not use his full strength.

After the intense winds vanished, he was at the top layer of the remaining corpses.

Corpses rained down as Fang Yuan quickly climbed towards the walls, trying to find some mountain rocks as his shelter.

After the corpses rained down, he was intact.

"What should I do now?" Fang Yuan looked at the pile of corpses in front of him as he thought rapidly.

Currently, he was still buried among the corpses, he was about six meters away from the top layer.

And now, he felt a numb sensation in his chest.

Fang Yuan could not see in the pile of corpses, he used his hand to touch it.

Next, he touched a slippery tail, it seemed like a snake or a centipede.

Next, this tail drilled into his chest.

"Am I dying again?" This question had just appeared in his mind when he was kicked out of the dream realm yet again.

...

"Earlier, that seems to be a Gu worm?" Fang Yuan thought in real life.

"There are so many mortal Gu Master corpses, it seemed like a huge battle occurred and some mortal Gu were not taken away, that is normal. Even if Gu Immortals find them, those tiny mortal Gu are not of significance to them."

"Of course, in an extreme environment like the sea of corpses, wild Gu might be created, it is not strange."

Fang Yuan acutely sensed that this Gu worm was his opportunity.

After his injuries healed, he entered the dream realm again.

Refinement of the Gu worm failed, he died.

Refining again, this time, he was in a deadlock as Zuo Ye Hui started to eat again, Fang Yuan was interrupted and failed, he died.

Finally, after refining the Gu worm, he realized that it was a rank two Gu worm used for offense, Fang Yuan cursed as once again, he died.

Again, he died.

And died.

And died.

"What sort of rotten dream is this?" There were an uncountable number of failures, even one time, because of his actions, the two Gu Immortals took notice and waved their fingers, causing Fang Yuan to die from a mystical light.

Despair.

In this dream realm, Fang Yuan was too weak.

Any mishap or wind was a fatal danger to him that caused him to die.

"Should I give up on this dream realm?" Thoughts continuously appeared of giving up.

Fang Yuan's investment in this dream realm was beyond the rest, but hope was bleak, he could not see any chance of success.

This dream realm was unimaginably difficult!

"Let's try once more."

"I can persevere once more."

"I died again... should I give up?"

There was another chain of deaths, Fang Yuan wanted to give up, but he could not bear to because he had invested so much, more importantly, he had never seen such a dream realm, if he succeeded, it would be a huge accumulation of experience to him!

Even if he gave up now, would he encounter such a dream realm again in the future?

Gritting his teeth and persevering.

Until the final time.

There were about sixty corpses in the ground in the valley, Fang Yuan struggled for a long time before preserving his life, he was mixed among them.

A Gu formation appeared.

Fang Yuan discovered that Zuo Ye Hui was trapped by this super Gu formation, its lower body was buried in the ground, only its upper body could move.

"This damned four elements formation, let me break you!" After it ate enough, Zuo Ye Hui roared at the sky as it burst out with a powerful dark grey light.

The grey light enveloped the entire valley.

"Oh no, this is the immortal killer move grey night! Let's retreat!" The two beastman Gu Immortals flew into the sky.

The four elements formation activated, as earth, water, wind, and fire, four mystical lights burst out and resisted the grey light, limiting it to the valley.

Zuo Ye Hui growled in anger and unwillingness to give in, but it was useless.

"What the, how can I dodge this?!" The grey light was everywhere, enveloping the valley, the beastman Gu Immortals could run, but Fang Yuan could not.

He watched as the surrounding grass and rocks were eliminated by this grey light, he himself was no exception.

Fang Yuan fell into deep despair: "This is an unsolvable dream realm?! The grey light cannot be dodged! If I had known this, I would've given up long ago, that was the wiser decision!"

Feeling deep regret, Fang Yuan returned to the real world.

His soul injury was much more severe than any of his previous attempts.

But...

What made Fang Yuan joyful was that his dark path attainment level had risen to grandmaster level all of a sudden.

"What happened?" Fang Yuan quickly inspected.

He was shocked to find out that this dream realm had vanished.

"So lasting until the final moment meant passing this dream realm! I succeeded! This is a survival type dream realm, I only needed to last till the end."

"This dream realm only had one scene, but after passing it, my ordinary dark path attainment level rose up to grandmaster level!"

"Is it because of Zuo Ye Hui's existence?"

Many questions were left unanswered.

Fang Yuan's knowledge of dream realms was too shallow. After all, he had not invested effort into dream realms in the five hundred years of his previous life.

At the same time, Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan were filled with questions.

"Where is this?" Hei Lou Lan looked at the world of birds and flowers that was shrouded in thin fog as she asked.

"This is the Mushroomman Paradise." A variant human Gu Immortal appeared from within the fog.

"Mushroomman Gu Immortal?" Bai Ning Bing's dragon pupils shrunk.

Mushroommen were a type of variant humans, they resembled humans but there was a mushroom cap on their heads, resembling a hat.

Below the mushroom cap were the mushroomman's brows and eyes, as for nose, ears, and other features, they were all present.

"Mushroomman... Paradise?" Hei Lou Lan muttered these two words: "Don't tell me, this is Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's..."

Chapter 1338: Seven Illusions True Inheritance, Chakra Melons

Before Hei Lou Lan finished her words, Purple Mountain True Monarch interrupted: "That's right, this blessed land has been modified by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, it faces no calamities and tribulations, the Mushroomman blessed land has turned into the Mushroomman Paradise. Of course, there are many paradises in this world, but this one is very special, because Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had cultivated here before he became a venerable."

"Oh!" The mushroomman Gu Immortal sighed deeply: "Ever since I obtained that true inheritance, I knew that one day, I would have to pay a huge price. But if you want me to help you with evil deeds, that is impossible, you can just kill me."

"I won't kill you." Purple Mountain True Monarch showed a crafty smile: "I want you to bring them into the melon cave, where Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had once stayed in and cultivated for some time. You won't refuse this request, right?"

The mushroomman Gu Immortal's expression became even more bitter, he thought for a while before nodding solemnly: "Alright, I agree."

Mushroomman Paradise, melon cave.

This cave was guarded by the mushroomman Gu Immortal.

Purple Mountain True Monarch assimilated with heaven's will, he could sense heaven's will's plotting, he used this mushroomman Gu Immortal to successfully send Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing into this magical place.

"These are the chakra melons that my tribe grows. You can cultivate here secretly, but don't damage a single melon." The mushroomman Gu Immortal said.

Chakra melons?

Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan looked at each other, seeing the shock on their faces.

Chakra melons were rank seven immortal materials, containing refinement path dao marks, they could be used in any Gu refinement.

Thus, this immortal material was very widely used.

And now, both of them saw the scale of this melon plantation cave, it was simply terrifyingly huge. How many chakra melons were there?

Purple Mountain True Monarch explained from the side: "No need to guess, this is the largest chakra melon production area in treasure yellow heaven, they have almost sixty percent of the market share."

"Of course, I did not bring you here for the chakra melons, the important thing is this super Gu formation."

"This super Gu formation uses rule path ripe Immortal Gu as the core, and it also uses rank seven dew Immortal Gu as a supplementary Immortal Gu. When you train your immortal killer moves here, the effectiveness will rise sharply, you will become more proficient in them."

"And because of dew Immortal Gu, your immortal essence recovery speed will be very fast inside the Gu formation."

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing heard this and showed great joy.

Such a cultivation paradise simply suited them perfectly.

Hei Lou Lan cultivated strength path primarily along with fire path, she had few strength path Immortal Gu, and many fire path Immortal Gu, she also had countless fire path immortal killer moves left by her aunt in the fire path true inheritance.

Bai Ning Bing had just obtained Bai Xiang's true inheritance, she was not weak either, she had many Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves.

Right now, what restricted them was the fact that they had just obtained their true inheritances and did not have the time to fully convert these gains into battle strength.

In the regional walls, when they fought Fang Yuan, this weakness was very obvious.

Purple Mountain True Monarch woke up and took charge, in order to raise his side's battle strength, he brought these two here, using this paradise to train the two immortals.

Melon cave had a huge space, the mushroomman Gu Immortal easily provided an area for Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan to cultivate.

After making arrangements for them, Purple Mountain True Monarch left the Mushroomman Paradise.

Days passed by.

Fang Yuan was still in the super Gu formation, exploring dream realms.

On the surface, he was cultivating in seclusion, he had deceived everyone, nobody knew that he was exploring dream realms, his gains were immense.

Chi Shang was a good benchmark.

Chi Shang was the formation devotee, after more than a hundred years of researching formation path, he reached his formation path grandmaster attainment level. At his age, his talents and achievements were considered rare among Gu Immortals.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan only spent a month or two to pass a dream realm with formation path true meaning and become a formation path grandmaster.

Because dream realms were so amazing, and could reduce the time needed for accumulations, during the five regions chaotic war, all sorts of Gu Immortal experts appeared, they were like shining stars in the sky, there were countless geniuses.

Right now, Fang Yuan was not only a formation path grandmaster, he was also a dark path grandmaster.

With such attainment level, Fang Yuan had new ideas towards the use of dark limit Immortal Gu.

"Right now, I can use dark limit Immortal Gu as the core to form an immortal killer move targeting myself, to prevent the deduction of others. Along with my dark path dao marks, this immortal killer move's power will be very terrifying."

"I can even use dark limit Immortal Gu as the core to form an immortal killer move that can unleash an attack resembling dark arrow Immortal Gu."

"There is also another idea, I can use dark limit Immortal Gu in other immortal killer moves to conceal all of the auras of these killer moves. After using them, I can catch people off guard, and achieve incredible effects."

Actually, for Fang Yuan, he needed food path and information path dream realms most.

Food path would allow him to feed Immortal Gu more easily with lower costs. The savings could be used to assist in his cultivation or development of resources.

Information path was even more important.

Fang Yuan had many information path alliance agreements right now.

This made him lose a lot of freedom, when he did things, he was restricted, it was inconvenient.

There was another point, if his information path attainment level rose, Fang Yuan would be able to decipher many information path traps and methods, he would be able to cooperate with Shadow Sect.

But things in this world did not come according to one's wishes.

The place that Fang Yuan was guarding was like a window. After he finished his exploration, Zuo Ye Hui's dream realm vanished, the new dream realms that filled up the space were all strange and absurd types.

Fang Yuan did not want to try these types of dream realms, even if he had unravel dream.

Fang Yuan patiently waited.

Dream realms changed among themselves occasionally.

But because he met with absurd dream realms consecutively, Fang Yuan could only divert his efforts elsewhere.

Developing his immortal aperture was the key goal, secondly, his newly obtained dark path attainment level allowed him to create some useful immortal killer moves, and finally, he had to collect information.

After Heavenly Court lost three rank eight Gu Immortals, they kept a low profile.

The five regions were in a state of peace.

But Wu clan's troubles did not end. Even with Wu Yong suppressing the situation, sending people to resolve conflicts, the other super forces were causing all sorts of problems, Wu clan was extremely busy in dealing with them.

There was a troublesome matter recently.

The cause was the Immortal Gu recipe of bathing flames Immortal Gu, a mortal Gu Master had by chance excavated it.

Once news spread, Yao clan's and Wu clan's attention was drawn.

This Immortal Gu recipe was part of the content of the fire path true inheritance left by Stunning Immortal.

A thousand years ago, Wu clan and Yao clan had lingering enmity after fighting over this fire path true inheritance. Eventually, both sides suffered losses, but they did not obtain this fire path true inheritance.

The fire path true inheritance was said to be destroyed, but since the recipe of bathing flames Immortal Gu appeared, everyone started to have hope.

Especially Wu clan and Yao clan, due to historical reasons, these two super forces had to get this Immortal Gu recipe. Even if they could not get it, the other party was not allowed to get it.

Thus, Wu Yong sent out Wu Yi Ran, he gave up on defending blood tide pit, a resource point.

Wu Yi Ran had rank seven cultivation level, he had outstanding battle strength, he obeyed the orders as he wanted to quickly settle the matter, but soon, he found that there was no Stunning Immortal true inheritance, only this bathing flames Immortal Gu recipe was left.

As a result, many Gu Immortals left, they did not want to offend two super forces just for an Immortal Gu recipe.

Yao clan was not going to give up, they sent a powerful person, Yao Geng.

Wu Yi Ran and Yao Geng fought four times, they had two wins and losses each, the final match was the crucial one.

During this crucial moment, Purple Mountain True Monarch secretly arrived at a meeting point.

On a nameless mountain, he met a mysterious Gu Immortal.

The mysterious Gu Immortal was covered in rainbow light, concealing his appearance: "You called me here?"

Purple Mountain True Monarch nodded: "That's right, regardless of how you obtained the complete Seven Illusions true inheritance, you have already made an alliance agreement, you need to do seven things for me."

"Alright, which seven?" The mysterious Gu Immortal answered openly.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's lips curled: "First, kill Wu Yi Ran."

The mysterious Gu Immortal was stunned: "Are you sure?"

Purple Mountain True Monarch's smile widened, continuing: "Second, kill Yao Geng."

The mysterious Gu Immortal was wary: "What are you trying to do?"

"You don't need to care about that. Just kill the two of them." Purple Mountain True Monarch chuckled.

The mysterious Gu Immortal snorted coldly, his body vanished on the spot as he left.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's smile gradually faded, his arms were behind his back as he looked at a far away mountain with a deep gaze.

"There is not much time left, I need to take action." He muttered softly.

A few days later, shocking news emerged.

Wu Yi Ran and Yao Geng both went missing, the result of their fight was unknown.

Wu clan and Yao clan were shaken, because from their life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, Wu Yi Ran and Yao Geng were already dead!

Who was so ruthless?

Wu Yong was enraged, right when he sent Gu Immortals to investigate this, blood tide pit erupted, a huge blood tide caused great destruction.

Wu clan quickly sent Gu Immortals to suppress the situation, but they found traces that an immortal killer move, collapsing art, was used at the scene.

Collapsing art was a killer move self-created by Yao Geng. The traces at the scene were indisputable.

The situation became complex.

"Did Yao Geng die after all?"

"Is this Yao clan's scheme?"

"Other than Yao clan, is any other clan striking?"

Wu Yong felt something amiss, he could sense a dangerous storm brewing!

Chapter 1339: Framing, Blood Tide Pit

Splash splash splash.

Sounds of waves were unceasing, the air was filled with a bloody smell, assaulting everyone's noses.

The two Gu Immortals from Wu clan, Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao, were flying in the sky now, looking at the sea of blood below, the former's expression was solemn while the latter's was bitter.

"The blood flood has spread an enormous distance, more than ten mountains were flooded, if we do not seal it now, this calamity will cause even greater damage later." Wu Yuan Ju said solemnly.

Blood tide pit was originally defended by Wu Yi Ran, but after he died, blood tide pit was taken down and the Gu formations inside were destroyed. This caused the blood tide to burst out and flood the surrounding area, causing this huge disaster.

Rong Hao had a worried expression: "It will not be easy for the two of us to create a new Gu formation and seal the blood tide again. If we had another rank six, with three Gu Immortals, we would barely be able to do it."

These two had rank six cultivation level, it was not difficult to handle this blood tide disaster, but Wu Yong gave them a limited amount of time. Two people were not able to resolve this in a short period of time.

There was no choice, Wu Yong could not deploy more people to handle this troublesome situation.

During Wu Du Xiu's era, Wu clan rapidly expanded without obstruction, because Wu Du Xiu could suppress the entire situation alone.

Once Wu Du Xiu died, Wu Yong took over, Wu clan only had one rank eight left, even though Wu Yong had great capabilities, Wu clan's territory was just too big.

Due to Purple Mountain True Monarch's scheme, the super forces could not control their desires, Wu clan was faced with obstacles created by many of the super forces.

Wu Yong stayed in their headquarters and was maintaining the situation and deciding on who to send.

But this time, Wu Yi Ran had died, with him gone, a huge gap formed instantly in Wu clan's defense line.

Sending out Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao was already Wu clan's limit.

"Give it our all, even if we exceed the time limit, we have already tried our best." Wu Yuan Ju sighed, starting to act.

Rong Hao cooperated.

He was not a Wu clansman, he was an external supreme elder recruited by Wu clan.

Southern Border's clans were very unwelcoming to outsiders, it was not easy for Wu clan to break tradition and recruit an external Gu Immortal into Wu clan.

Under the two Gu Immortals' methods, the blood tide continued to push backwards, the blood tide pit was like a huge monstrous mouth, devouring the blood outside.

The situation was under control.

It was getting better.

Wu Yuan Ju sighed: "After suppressing this blood tide and rebuilding the Gu formation, Rong Hao, you will have to take over the position of guarding this place. I hope you can be careful, the situation is quite tense now."

Rong Hao nodded:"I understand. I heard that this blood tide pit was not naturally formed, it was created by Blood Sea Ancestor on purpose?"

Wu Yuan Ju nodded: "Blood Sea Ancestor left behind seven true inheritances, this is one of the seven true inheritances that he had meticulously arranged. It was not eye-catching earlier, similar to normal pits, but when a Gu Master from Shang clan entered, he obtained a Blood Sea true inheritance, obtaining blood handprint Gu. This person is Shang clan's previous clan leader, Shang Yan Fei, he had died on Yi Tian Mountain."

After Shang Yan Fei took away the Blood Sea true inheritance, blood tides started to appear in this pit unceasingly.

Wu Du Xiu sent Gu Immortals here and made this part of Wu clan's territory.

Due to Wu clan's management, blood tide pit quickly became a blood path resource point. Wu clan was developing blood path, this resource point made great contributions.

"You two sure are happy." At this time, Rong Hao heard a voice in his mind.

"Who?!" Rong Hao was shocked.

He wanted to use his methods to defend himself, but he could not move at all.

He quickly looked over at Wu Yuan Ju to seek help, but he was soon met with despair, as Wu Yuan Ju was also immobilized, in the same state as him.

A small figure had appeared on Rong Hao's shoulder.

He was the size of a thumb, he had wings on his back, resembling dragonfly wings, his purple hair was very eye catching.

It was none other than rank eight wisdom path Gu Immortal Purple Mountain True Monarch!

"Miniman Gu Immortal?" Wu Yuan Ju was shocked, but he quickly calmed down, Purple Mountain True Monarch's aura was concealed, he did not expose his rank eight aura.

Rong Hao quickly added: "As a variant human, you must know that humans are the rulers of the world. No matter who instigated you, I hope that you will not act rashly. Because we are not only human Gu Immortals, we are also members of Wu clan. Wu clan is the number one righteous path force in Southern Border, if you kill us, the consequences will be severe."

"We have no grudges between us. We of Wu clan would not bully people, if you have any requests, we can help you with them, we can become friends." Wu Yuan Ju continued.

He had great chemistry with Rong Hao, both threatening and urging at the same time.

But before he finished his words, he started to stutter as his gaze turned hollow.

Rong Hao was shocked, he blurted out: "Wisdom path Gu Immortal?!"

At this point, he also became incoherent.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's wisdom path methods interfered with Wu Yuan Ju's and Rong Hao's thoughts, they could not even think and speak now, they were completely defenseless.

When Gu Immortals manipulate Gu worms, thoughts were needed, their body actions also needed thoughts to act.

Purple Mountain True Monarch directly interfered with their thoughts, controlling them from this aspect, these two rank six Gu Immortals had no way of resisting him.

Easily controlling the situation, Purple Mountain True Monarch looked at the blood tide pit and smiled.

Next, his rank eight aura burst out, in the blink of an eye, it engulfed the surroundings.

The blood tide below his feet became calmer.

After some time, Purple Mountain True Monarch opened his mouth, letting out a breath.

His breath floated into the blood tide pit, it was not eye catching, quickly devoured by the rushing blood tide, vanishing.

At this point, Purple Mountain True Monarch turned around, looking afar and saying: "Your turn."

Light in seven colors appeared as a voice said in a trembling tone: "You are a rank eight great expert! With your strength, you can move unhindered in Southern Border, why must you find trouble with a minor character like me?"

"I have my own plans. You have to pay for what you owe. When you inherited Seven Illusions true inheritance, you should have expected this day." Purple Mountain True Monarch said.

"But the inheritors before me have never received any orders. Why me?" The mysterious Gu Immortal covered in rainbow lights said in a reluctant tone.

Purple Mountain True Monarch sighed, looking at Heavenly Court: "Maybe this is your fate. Alright, use Qiao Zhi Cai's method to kill this person."

Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao were still dazed, unable to move.

Purple Mountain True Monarch captured these two alive, but he still wanted the mysterious Gu Immortal to kill them.

The mysterious Gu Immortal did not dare to disobey Purple Mountain True Monarch, he used his profound light, as it transformed and landed on these two Wu clan Gu Immortals, destroying their souls, and even their bodies turning into wooden statues.

Purple Mountain True Monarch released control on them, as these two statues fell into the blood tide.

"Let's go." Purple Mountain True Monarch said plainly.

How could the mysterious Gu Immortal defy Purple Mountain True Monarch? Even if he was not a rank eight great expert, with just the information path alliance agreement in the true inheritance, it could restrict the mysterious Gu Immortal.

Both of them left as quickly as they came.

Of course, Purple Mountain True Monarch did not forget to clean up his traces in the battlefield.

A moment later, intense winds blew in the air, countless clouds were scattered, clear skies could be seen everywhere.

A grand and vast rank eight aura enveloped the area.

Wu Yong's expression was of rage, his eyes were slightly red as he descended.

Who was it?

Who had killed them?!

Wu Yi Ran died earlier, and now, Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao were dead. Because of life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, Wu clan received news almost immediately.

Wu Yong was enraged, he decided to go out himself.

Wu clan lost three Gu Immortals at once, one rank seven and two rank sixes, the losses was tremendous, Wu Yong felt both loss and anger.

He wants to see who it was that could step past this bottom line and anger Wu clan!

But next, after seeing Wu Yuan Ju's and Rong Hao's corpses, Wu Yong was stunned.

"Wooden statue murder?" His pupils shrunk to pin size: "Qiao Zhi Cai?"

A moment later, Qiao clan Gu Immortal Qiao Zhi Cai rushed to the scene.

Blood tide pit had been suppressed, the ground was completely covered in blood, and there were also two Wu clan Gu Immortal corpses.

"Qiao clan first supreme elder, what do you have to say?" Wu Yong had a calm expression, his tone was very plain.

But the calmer he was, the more fearful Qiao Zhi Cai was.

He was Qiao clan's first supreme elder, his signature immortal killer move was wooden statue murder, if any ordinary Gu Immortal was hit by this, their souls would crumble and disperse, they would lose their life, their bodies would turn into wood, and the remaining life force could be used to grow trees.

Ignoring the cold sweat on his forehead, Qiao Zhi Cai explained: "Lord Wu Yong, please listen, I did not do this, someone is trying to frame me. Qiao clan and Wu clan have a long relationship, we are closely related..."

Before Qiao Zhi Cai finished his words, Wu Yong interrupted him.

His eyes were shining, he stared at Qiao Zhi Cai: "Of course I am willing to trust you. Qiao clan and Wu clan, we have marriage connections, we are in an alliance, how can our relationship be ruined by this?"

Qiao Zhi Cai let out a breath of air, bowing deeply: "Lord Wu Yong is wise!"

Wu Yong continued: "If someone is trying to frame you, this is way too obvious. Who is it? What motives do they have? What plans do they have next? This is what I am concerned about. Wait a while, I have already invited Tie clan Gu Immortal Tie Mian Shen!"

Chapter 1340: Ghost Summoning, Tie Mian Shen

Southern Border, Tie clan, Wan Cheng Mountain.

Rumble...

A chain of low sounds enveloped this unassuming valley.

At the bottom of this valley, there was a girl.

She had a tall body, her legs were more than sixty percent of her total height, she looked heroic and agile. Right now, her eyebrows were sharp like swords, her eyes were shining like stars, she looked upwards.

Giant rocks that were the size of houses were crashing down towards her by the cliff.

The girl breathed in deeply, at this moment of life and death, she shut her eyes.

Hundreds of giant rocks were about to land on her, but at this moment, she opened her eyes.

In an instant, golden light radiated, it was extremely dazzling, as if a miniature sun had appeared in the valley!

The light lasted for a while before vanishing.

The loud sounds also vanished, endless white powder scattered down, slowly descending.

The young woman was bathed in the rock powder, joy showing on her determined face.

"Good, Tie Ruo Nan, you succeeded in this killer move I taught, passing the final test. From now onwards, you will follow me and cultivate, I will teach you the ways of becoming an immortal." A grand voice echoed in this valley.

The young girl knelt on the ground: "Thank you for the guidance, lord supreme elder!"

"You hate evil so much and have great talent, you are suited for my Iron Mask true inheritance. Originally, your father was one of my chosen seeds, but to think that his daughter had countless times his talent... hmm?" The grand voice suddenly stopped.

But soon, Tie Ruo Nan heard: "There is a sudden issue, stay here and cultivate. The killer move I taught you might have succeeded, but you are not proficient enough. During this period, you need to practise more, when I return, we will have further plans."

"Yes." The girl respectfully bowed, excitement could not be concealed on her face.

"Finally, I finally did it. Father, I surpassed you. Watch me in heaven, I will become a Gu Immortal and obtain true strength."

"This world is too dark and chaotic, only with greater strength can I punish evildoers and reward those who carry out good deeds, justice will prevail and the world will be a better place!"

...

"Zhang Li, you bitch who murdered your own husband, to think that my brother treated you so well, and in the end, you actually acted so ruthlessly and killed him. Today, I will cut you into pieces, you will die without a proper corpse!" A young Gu Immortal shouted, his rage was unstoppable, his rank seven aura was bursting.

Fang Yuan: "..."

Ever since he passed the dream realm regarding Zuo Ye Hui, his dark path attainment level had risen to grandmaster level. But next, there was an absurd dream realm.

Fang Yuan played safe and did not explore this dream realm full of uncertainties.

After waiting for a while, he finally encountered a realistic dream realm.

But in the end, he became a female Gu Immortal in this dream realm, and was very... risque.

Because this female immortal cultivated enchantment emotion path.

This was a tiny path, derived from wisdom path as a minor path. It used emotions to fight, and enchantment to allure enemies.

Right now, Fang Yuan was a female immortal, he wore a pink dress, there were two huge treasures on his upper body, the corners of his skirt were open and exposed until his upper thigh. When he smiled, it was incredibly seductive.

Fang Yuan was helpless about this.

This was another person's dream realm, he had to be a character in it if he wanted to take part in the dream.

Of course, becoming a woman would not disrupt Fang Yuan's impassive mental state.

He was vigilant against his enemy as he concentrated on his immortal aperture.

What made Fang Yuan glad was that this female immortal had many Immortal Gu.

"I'll try this Gu first." Fang Yuan instilled immortal essence as he heard an alluring cry from it.

This voice that appeared was not controlled by Fang Yuan, it was a woman's voice filled with seduction and temptation.

The young Gu Immortal was very angry earlier, but after hearing this sound, his body went limp, his killing intent faded.

His momentum was lost as he gritted his teeth, clarity returning to his eyes: "Vicious woman, you dare to toy with me! Take this move!!"

Saying this, he pushed with his hands as a huge tornado swept towards Fang Yuan with countless wind blades.

Fang Yuan quickly retreated, dodging as he used his second Immortal Gu.

Immediately, Fang Yuan's skirt turned into a pink fog as it coiled around him, bringing Fang Yuan away quickly.

The speed was impressive, Fang Yuan sighed, it was not inferior to sword escape Immortal Gu, the only regretful part was, the farther he flew, the thinner the pink fog on his body, it was able to cover his entire body earlier, but now, his tender white thighs and arms were exposed already.

Fang Yuan was not afraid of running naked, this mindset of being embarrassed was no longer in him, moreover, this was a dream.

The regretful thing was, this Immortal Gu could not be used for long, otherwise, with just this speed, his enemy was not a problem.

"Slut, you ran quickly. But you will die today, in order to kill you and avenge my brother, I will do anything and pay any price!"

The young Gu Immortal shouted loudly with blood red eyes.

At the same time, he used his immortal killer move.

Jade green wind gathered into a small dagger in his palm.

The dagger shone with jade light, Fang Yuan took a look at it and felt fearful.

"Oh no!" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

"Just these one or two Immortal Gu alone cannot stop the immortal killer move. But I do not know what immortal killer moves this Zhang Li possesses."

As he felt troubled, Fang Yuan quickly used unravel dream.

Suddenly, a mysterious power moved in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture. An Immortal Gu and dozens of mortal Gu were activated under this mysterious power.

"This is?" Fang Yuan sensed this and felt great joy.

He quickly continued to use unravel dream, under its influence, the mysterious power continued to exert its strength, many Gu worms in his immortal aperture were used.

Next, a completely unknown immortal killer move was activated.

Fang Yuan did not know what this immortal killer move did, or what effect it had.

There was no time to lose, right now, the young Gu Immortal had already blown at his hand with his lips. That jade wind dagger shot out like an arrow, flying towards Fang Yuan, fast and ruthless!

Fang Yuan sighed to himself, at this moment, it was all up to chance.

Would unravel dream use an effective immortal killer move to defend against this jade wind dagger, Fang Yuan had no idea.

But under the effect of this killer move, Fang Yuan could not help but pinch his fingers, waving at this young Gu Immortal as he whispered bewitchingly: "Ghost summoning!"

This voice was enchanting to the limit, even Fang Yuan shuddered upon hearing it.

Next, a ghost really came.

This Gu Immortal soul had rank seven battle strength, it flew towards the jade wind dagger relentlessly.

That young Gu Immortal saw the ghost and his expression changed, he shouted: "Brother!!"

It turned out that this female immortal, Zhang Li, had killed her husband and refined his soul into an immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan saw this and had a flash of inspiration, he called out: "As long as I stop this killer move, your brother's soul can be saved, destroy it if you dare!"

The young Gu Immortal was enraged, but he was afraid of harming his brother, he could not fight properly.

Fang Yuan was intensely joyful, he quickly attacked and stabilized the situation.

A moment later, he found a flaw and killed him.

He passed the dream realm!

"Huff." Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, returning to reality.

"This dream realm only had one scene." Fang Yuan was slightly surprised.

This was a tiny dream realm.

Fang Yuan passed it in one try, inspecting himself, he found that his attainment level for wisdom path and soul path had risen.

"Enchantment emotion path had never left wisdom path, there are no enchantment emotion path dao marks in this world, only wisdom path dao marks. Thus, my wisdom path attainment level grew."

"As for soul path... perhaps that Zhang Li cultivated soul path too. Her ghost summoning immortal killer move belongs to soul path."

He analyzed and looked at his attainment level.

Right now, he had eight grandmaster level paths, they were blood path, strength path, transformation path, star path, wisdom path, water path, dark path, and formation path.

Refinement path was quasi-grandmaster, luck path was master, phantom path was empty. His sword path attainment level was ordinary, his soul path was also ordinary, but after Zhang Li's dream realm, it had risen to quasi-master level.

"That immortal killer move, ghost summoning, is quite interesting, even though I do not have enough soul path attainment level, my wisdom path is grandmaster. It was from a realistic dream realm, I very likely can use this same killer move again, with a portion of its strength. Even if I cannot replicate it, I can create a similar immortal killer move."

"But even if I replicate this immortal killer move, it is inferior to improving vajra shell."

Ordinary Gu Immortals would be happy if there was a possibility, they would try to deduce the immortal killer move.

But Fang Yuan was different.

Recently, his attainment level had risen a lot, he had countless inspirations, he could only choose to modify the immortal killer moves with the highest value to him.

This was a good problem to have.

His dark path attainment level was grandmaster, he could use dark limit Immortal Gu and perseverance Immortal Gu as the cores to create a new immortal killer move. This immortal killer move would allow him to conceal himself.

His formation path attainment level rose, Fang Yuan had a new idea about vajra shell.

This made him extremely moved. The original vajra shell used vajra thought Immortal Gu and perseverance Immortal Gu as the cores, but in his concept, if he could add in precaution Immortal Gu and some formation path mortal Gu, the power would rise by multiple times.

After Zhang Li's dream realm, the following ones were not suited for exploration.

Fang Yuan started to shift his focus, modifying the immortal killer move vajra shell.

Just as Fang Yuan rapidly increased his strength, Tie Mian Shen arrived in front of Qiao Zhi Cai and Wu Yong.

This rank seven Gu Immortal wore a martial uniform, his chest and legs were covered in light armor, there was a thick iron mask on his face.

He had not brought a mask to wear, it was the trait of cultivating the Iron Mask true inheritance.

All the Gu Immortals who cultivate this true inheritance must have a heart of justice, they also were often people most skilled in Southern Border in investigating the truth.

After seeing those two corpses, Tie Mian Shen declared: "It was not Qiao Zhi Cai."

Qiao Zhi Cai let out a breath of air.

"Who was it?" Wu Yong asked.

"Someone mimicked his immortal killer move wooden statue murder. This is something seen before in history." Tie Mian Shen answered: "Lord Wu Yong, I wonder if you have heard of Seven Illusions Demon Immortal?"

Wu Yong frowned: "You mean the inheritor of the Seven Illusions true inheritance? It is said that the Gu Immortal who inherits it will have a method to mimic almost any method used by Gu Immortals in this world, Tie Mian Shen, is that true?"

Tie Mian Shen nodded: "Our clan's Demon Suppression Tower had once contained a Seven Illusions Demon Immortal. We did not manage to get the contents of the Seven Illusions true inheritance, but we know a lot of its secrets. This Seven Illusions true inheritance has seven different layers. The inheritor can choose to inherit any of the layers or get the complete Seven Illusions true inheritance. But after inheriting one true inheritance, they will have to agree to one condition, in the future, they would need to do something for someone. Taking all seven layers would mean seven conditions."

"Our clan has already devised methods to locate a Seven Illusions inheritor, and differentiate their methods. I used it earlier, this was undoubtedly a Seven Illusions Demon Immortal."

"Interesting." Wu Yong nodded, frowning deeply.

Even if they knew the truth, so what?

Who was the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal? Which force or person was behind them?

Wu Yong still did not know the answer to this problem!

But at the next moment, Tie Mian Shen's words eased Wu Yong's frown.

Chapter 1341: Purple Blood River Traps Wu Yong

"I can locate the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal." Tie Mian Shen's words eased Wu Yong's frown.

As it turned out, after capturing one Seven Illusions Demon Immortal, Tie clan had started to make arrangements against the Seven Illusions true inheritance.

Among the Southern Border super forces, Tie clan was the force that targeted the demonic path most fiercely. Especially after they built the Demon Suppression Tower, they were the pillar of the righteous path in pursuing demonic path Gu Immortals.

Right now, Tie Mian Shen was using his immortal killer move to investigate the area for clues.

"This way!" After finding the direction, Tie Mian Shen flew towards the east.

Wu Yong and Qiao Zhi Cai looked at each other for a second before following after him.

The clues were broken, but found again time after time, with the experienced Tie Mian Shen leading the way, the three immortals had great progress.

But an hour later, they returned to the blood tide pit.

Qiao Zhi Cai was shocked: "Why are we back here?"

Tie Mian Shen smiled coldly: "The most dangerous place is the safest place..."

Qiao Zhi Cai reacted as he praised: "Such guts."

Wu Yong looked around coldly, after a few breaths, his gaze was locked onto an area in the blood tide pit.

Roar—!

The peaceful lake suddenly raged with waves, countless blood beasts emerged from it.

Large numbers of desolate level blood beasts, with a small number of ancient blood beasts, formed into an army as they charged at Wu Yong and the others fiercely.

Blood beasts were a type of path beast.

They did not reproduce normally, but were born from heaven and earth, created using natural blood path dao marks.

Similar to blood beasts were snow monsters, mud monsters, cloud beasts, soul beasts, year beasts, and rock dragons.

"Blood tide pit had such an incredible thing? A blood beast breeding ground?" Tie Mian Shen said softly as he looked at Wu Yong.

Wu Yong expressed surprise on his face.

Blood tide pit contained a true inheritance of Blood Sea Ancestor, it was obtained by mortal Gu Master Shang Yan Fei, and was later taken by Wu clan. Wu clan turned the blood tide pit into their possession, and explored it, but did not find anything special. It was only treated as a resource point after that.

"So many blood beasts in ambush, no wonder the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal is hiding here." Qiao Zhi Cai said.

Blood beasts formed into an army and attacked, they had all sorts of forms, some had tiger heads and horse bodies, some had snake heads and rabbit bodies, some had tortoise shells and dragon tails, some were like trees, while some were giant fruits...

The pungent smell of blood assaulted the nose as these blood beasts growled sinisterly.

This force suddenly attacked, even super clans would be caught off guard.

But Qiao Zhi Cai's and Tie Mian Shen's expressions were unchanged, they did not intend to retreat.

Because at this moment, Wu Yong was standing in front of them.

"A bunch of trash." Wu Yong snorted, rage flickering in his eyes.

He was very angry.

Because during this period, he was staying in Wu clan, deploying members everywhere to deal with all sorts of situations, he was extremely repressed. And now, this Seven Illusions Demon Immortal had vile intentions, they actually caused the deaths of Wu clan's Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao!

Tiny traces of wind was gathering around him.

The gentle green wind had unknowingly surrounded the growling blood beasts as well.

The blood beasts were still rampaging, their speed did not fall at all.

Just when they were about to reach the three immortals, blood beasts started to explode!

The explosions were not loud, they were very gentle, like the bursting of bubbles.

Blood beasts detonated one after another, even though they were close to the immortals, they were no threat, unable to deal any damage.

The growling and attack was like a joke.

Hundreds of rank six battle strength and dozens of rank seven battle strength beasts had disintegrated in front of Wu Yong, fragile like toys made of paper.

This was the power of a rank eight!

"What immortal killer move is this... the aura is completely concealed, I cannot detect anything!" Qiao Zhi Cai was full of shock.

Tie Mian Shen had a solemn expression, staring at Wu Yong's back.

Wu Yong's expression was dark, he stared at the blood tide below him.

The blood beasts did not form out of nothing, the blood tide had dried out, the blood tide pit that was oozing with blood earlier was now drying up.

Qiao Zhi Cai sighed, it was a pity. He could see that the dense blood path dao marks in blood tide pit had vanished. From now on, blood tide pit no longer existed, it was only an ordinary pit now.

Wu Yong did not care.

This pit, unfathomable to the eyes of normal people, was completely exposed to him.

A rainbow colored figure appeared in Wu Yong's investigative range.

"You are the daring person who is trying to challenge Wu clan's authority?" Wu Yong said calmly, but everyone could hear his killing intent and rage.

The mysterious Gu Immortal in the pit smiled bitterly: "Lord Wu Yong, I had no choice, I was forced to. Now... I seek your understanding!"

"Hmm?" Wu Yong's expression changed.

At the next moment, his environment changed abruptly!

The blue sky and mountainous ground had vanished, the surroundings had turned into a color of purple.

The three immortals could not sense their distances, their sense of space had been severely disrupted.

Rumble...

Tides could be heard, the blood beasts that were destroyed earlier turned into bloody water as they gathered into a river, flowing below the three immortals.

The blood colored waves and ripples appeared, countless purple thoughts rained down and assaulted the immortals.

"Damn it! These blood beasts were just the prelude and trap. So vicious!" Qiao Zhi Cai cursed.

Tie Mian Shen looked around nervously: "What immortal battlefield killer move is this, is it a super Gu formation?"

With his investigative abilities, he could not see through this place!

Wu Yong was unhappy, he snorted coldly and waved his sleeves.

Boom, intense winds blew as a giant tornado surrounded the range of one li, encircling the three immortals.

Purple thoughts rained down furiously, landing on the ball of wind as they splattered, but could not break the defense.

Wu Yong did not move, his expression was cold, he raised his right arm and flicked.

A crisp sound echoed.

A dark jade worm flew out of his finger tips.

The small worm got out of the ball of wind and flew towards the blood river rapidly.

While flying, it grew larger as its body expanded to ten feet, fifty feet, a hundred and fifty feet.

After a few breaths of time, it turned into a vicious wind dragon that was two hundred and twenty feet long, it bared its fangs and claws, breaking the rain of purple thoughts, crashing into the blood river.

The blood river gushed and formed a spiral, trying to devour the wind dragon like a giant beast.

Wu Yong's eyes flashed with a green light, the wind dragon roared and turned into countless jade wind blades, shooting everywhere.

The blood river spiral was broken by the wind blades, but the wind blades continued to cut as the red blood river was split into two.

Qiao Zhi Cai and Tie Mian Shen watched with wide opened eyes, they had shocked and chaotic emotions.

Wu Yong's every attack was an immortal killer move with outstanding power, far beyond rank seven. If they were his opponent, they would not last for a move.

Wu Yong could actually use such a powerful immortal killer moves, it was like his instinct, it was as easy as breathing.

"Every killer move of Lord Wu Yong had its aura concealed to the limit, he was truly hiding his strength." Qiao Zhi Cai's heart was still in a commotion.

"This wind dragon killer move actually has a second style variation move, turning into countless wind blades... Wu Yong is definitely not as useless as the rumors say, he has such incredible battle strength... this person is hiding so deeply!" Tie Mian Shen's eyes shone with brilliance.

He looked at Wu Yong's back, feeling glad that Tie clan and Wu clan were allies, they had not turned on each other.

Wu Du Xiu and Wu Yong were mother and son, the former was like a fierce wind blowing on the top of a mountain, while the latter was a powerful tornado at the bottom of a valley. They acted differently and had opposite personalities, but they were equally powerful and domineering!

However, even with Wu Yong's fierce attacks, the surroundings did not change.

The split river turned into two, expanding and forming two blood rivers, both were equally big as before.

Qiao Zhi Cai's expression changed, to be able to remain under the attack of a rank eight Gu Immortal and trap all three of them, what sort of method was this?

His doubts did not last long, because a figure soon emerged from the blood river, speaking and giving them the answer.

"This is my purple blood river formation. Wu Yong, if you do not use the two rank eight Immortal Gu that your mother left you, with just that rank eight gentle wind Gu, you cannot break this formation." Purple Mountain True Monarch said.

He was not in his miniman body, he was as large as a human now.

When he spoke, his body rose up as an 'island' floated below his feet.

Qiao Zhi Cai and Tie Mian Shen's expressions changed, Wu Yong was also moved. This was because Purple Mountain True Monarch did not conceal his aura, he was undoubtedly a rank eight.

"Who are you? What do you want?" Wu Yong called out.

Purple Mountain True Monarch smiled, looking at Wu Yong with his clear purple eyes: "Of course, it is to kill you. Once you are dead, Wu clan will go into a commotion, other clans will attack it, it will break apart."

Wu Yong was stunned, he suddenly laughed as he raised his head.

He was laughing from anger.

After laughing, he lowered his head, a fierce light shooting out of his eyes: "Such guts, in that case, I will kill you and raise my prestige as a rank eight."

Saying this, a strong aura burst out of his body.

Countless Gu worms were activated in his immortal aperture.

Qiao Zhi Cai and Tie Mian Shen both retreated, they could feel unparalleled threat coming from Wu Yong's body.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's smile faded.

Wu Yong's immortal killer moves earlier were undetectable, their auras were concealed completely. But now, the immortal killer move he was conjuring had incredible aura, it was like a raging storm.

From this perspective, Wu Yong was using his full strength to fight!

What immortal killer move was it that made Wu Yong unable to conceal the aura?

No matter what killer move it was, once activated, an incredible power would be unleashed, the might would be unstoppable.

How could this be allowed?

At Purple Mountain True Monarch's will, countless purple thoughts burst out like a storm, gushing out...

Wu clan.

Ancestral hall.

"This, this! This!!" The Wu clan Gu Immortal guarding the ancestral hall had a change of expression as sweat rolled down his face, his expression was deathly pale.

He shouted in shock: "Lord Wu Yong's life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu were destroyed! Lord Wu Yong... is he dead?!"

Chapter 1342: With Elder Brother Gone, Younger Brother Takes Over

Ancestral hall.

The ancestral hall on top of Wu Yi Mountain was a mortal Gu House. Using a large number of rank five mortal Gu, even though it was inferior to Immortal Gu Houses, it was extremely significant to Wu clan.

Essentially, every super force and normal force would have an ancestral hall. Inside, life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu would be used, or even blood rope Gu.

The former two were common, while blood rope Gu was rare, because it was blood path.

Even the small and big sects in Central Continent had buildings similar to the ancestral hall, storing life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu.

At this moment, Wu Ba Chong was standing in the ancestral hall, looking at the Gu worm fragments blankly.

After the life tablet Gu shattered, it would be like wood scraps, while soul lantern Gu would become a cracked ladybird, it would not be shining with a dark blue light anymore.

Wu Ba Chong was old, but he had a muscular body resembling a bear, his hair was white and his nose was wide, he had thick brows and sharp eyes, he was a steady and responsible person.

He was the second supreme elder of Wu clan, he had gone through many ordeals, resulting in his calm nature, but now, his forehead was full of sweat, his breathing was ragged, his gaze was chaotic and in a mess.

"Lord Wu Yong died?!" Wu Ba Chong stared at the two mortal Gu fragments, he had already stood here for a while, but his mind was in a mess.

"How could this happen? A great rank eight existence, the pillar of our Wu clan, he died like this?!" Wu Ba Chong did not dare to imagine this or believe it.

"Did Lord Wu Yong die or not???" He kept asking himself.

After all, life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu were mortal Gu, it was possible to interfere with them using some methods.

But Wu Yong was uncontactable now, no matter how Wu clan tried to communicate with him, none got through, this was an undeniable fact!

Regardless of whether or not Wu Yong was dead, his situation was definitely not good.

"Being able to make a rank eight Gu Immortal end up in such a state, who is it?"

"A rank eight existence among the demonic path and lone cultivators?"

"Or is it the other super clans, are they collaborating to deal with our Wu clan?"

Wu Ba Chong continued to guess.

The more he thought, the more messy his mind was.

Wu Du Xiu died, Wu Yong went missing, in this huge Wu clan, the number one super clan in Southern Border, there was actually no rank eight existence guarding it now.

This was a severe situation, Wu clan was in a disastrous state, and the most fearful thing was, the perpetrator was still unknown!

After his shocked emotions returned to normal, fear and loss filled Wu Ba Chong's heart.

Normally, there was Wu Du Xiu or Wu Yong suppressing the situation, he did not feel anything.

But now that the two rank eight great experts were gone, Wu Ba Chong realized that his stable and firm shoulders could not bear the weight of Wu clan.

During Wu Du Xiu's era, he was the second supreme elder, after Wu Yong ascended to her role, he continued to assist him. In terms of seniority, he was among the oldest and most experienced Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals.

However, it was pointless.

He was only rank seven in cultivation level, his battle strength was not outstanding, if he fought against Old Treeman Ba De, he could not win. Even among Wu clan, there were many rank seven Gu Immortals who could fight him evenly.

However, he was the first person to return among Wu clan's higher-ups.

Thus, he had the initiative.

"What do I do?"

"Even if Lord Wu Yong is not dead, he has gone missing and his life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu have shattered, once news gets out, there would be a huge commotion, everyone's hearts would waver."

"Should I hide the information?"

Wu Ba Chong quickly shook his head.

This shocking news had already been exposed to many Wu clan Gu Immortals by the Wu clan rank six Gu Immortal who was guarding the place.

If Wu Yong was confirmed to be dead, the mastermind who attacked Wu clan would not give up this chance to target their morale.

Thus, he could not seal this news even if he wanted to.

"Is the matter at hand to find the missing Lord Wu Yong, or should we shrink our defensive lines and recall the supreme elders who are outside to guard our base?"

Wu Ba Chong frowned.

Both choices were dangerous.

Searching for Wu Yong would definitely be dangerous, to be able to destroy Wu Yong's life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu and have him disappear, the mastermind was definitely powerful. Sending rank seven Gu Immortals to find him was like sending sheep to a tiger.

And if they retracted their defensive lines and called back the elders, it would be a huge political loss, many of their resource points would be lost. If the surrounding super forces tried to take over at this time, Wu clan would suffer immense losses.

What should he do?

Wu Ba Chong was hesitant, he was stuck between two tough options.

After a long time, he licked his dry lips, he decided to put both options on hold, he was going to hold a meeting with the Wu clan Gu Immortals as the second supreme elder, they would execute the plan after coming to a consensus.

Wu Yong was missing and uncontactable, a huge storm surrounding Wu clan was quietly forming.

Southern Border, super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan sat on his bed, cultivating with his eyes closed, he was multitasking as he listened to Lady White Rabbit's report.

Lady White Rabbit had inherited the White Rabbit true inheritance.

This true inheritance was quite famous in Southern Border, the inheritor had to be pure hearted. And when they cultivate in the future, they had to maintain the same pure heartedness. Otherwise, most of the true inheritance's methods could not be used, using them forcefully would result in backlash.

Precisely so, Lady White Rabbit was naturally trustworthy, she was a popular person among lone immortals and demonic cultivators.

Wu An had noticed this initially, thus he convinced Lady White Rabbit to be the intermediary in hosting this immortal opportunity business.

Once in a while, Lady White Rabbit would enter the super Gu formation and report the situation of the immortal opportunity business to Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan did not gain any benefits from the immortal opportunity business, he listened to the business situation as it could help him learn about the changes in the area surrounding the giant dream realm.

Lady White Rabbit spoke softly, her voice was like smooth water, she reported with a gentle gaze on Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan was in Wu Yi Hai's appearance now, his face was handsome, his nose was tall and wide, his manly heroic aura was completely displayed.

Lady White Rabbit had fallen for him already, she purposely spoke slowly, treasuring this precious time she could spend with Fang Yuan alone.

Unfortunately, each time Fang Yuan met with her, he spoke only twice, the first sentence was to ask Lady White Rabbit to sit as she gave her report, and the second was for her to leave.

But even so, Lady White Rabbit was very satisfied.

She knew deeply that Wu Yi Hai had a high status, she felt like she was a lowly person and could not match Fang Yuan. She was very happy to spend this time with him once in a while, she felt very blissful.

Right at this time, Lady White Rabbit's voice halted.

Because she saw Fang Yuan's expression change.

This situation was very rare, Lady White Rabbit's heart clenched, what happened to Wu Yi Hai? Did he encounter any problems?

Fang Yuan gradually shut his eyes, willing as he opened the hall.

"Yi Hai, at this point in time, you still have the mood to relax and spend time with a woman?" A female immortal barged into the hall.

Lady White Rabbit turned around and looked, this was a young woman wearing green clothing with wavy sleeves. her skin was smooth like snow, her body was curvy and she resembled a delicate willow.

She had an extremely beautiful face, especially her attractive eyes, concealed by her long eyelashes, they seemed clear as water.

"She is Qiao clan's Qiao Si Liu!" Lady White Rabbit recognized this person as she flustered, lowering her gaze in panic.

She knew this person's relationship with Fang Yuan.

Some time ago, there were rumors about Fang Yuan and Qiao Si Liu circulating around.

"Fairy Si Liu is so beautiful, as expected of one of the top three fairies in Southern Border."

"Only someone like this can be with Lord Wu Yi Hai."

Lady White Rabbit thought this, as she felt pain in her heart nurturing and fermenting.

Qiao Si Liu took a look at Lady White Rabbit who was lowering her head, she seemed to be nonchalant but she was actually very attentive.

Qiao Si Liu was trying to seduce Wu Yi Hai into becoming Qiao clan's son-in-law, Qiao Si Liu had to look at all of Fang Yuan's information.

And in Fang Yuan's information, Lady White Rabbit was present.

This was the first time Qiao Si Liu was meeting Lady White Rabbit.

She saw that Lady White Rabbit had a delicate body, her eyes were like rubies, she had fluffy rabbit ears that were drooping, her eyes were looking down, it was cute and endearing. Even though under close examination, her appearance was slightly inferior to Qiao Si Liu, men loved these tiny pitiful creatures that were full of cuteness.

"But now is not the time to deal with her." Qiao Si Liu snorted internally, passing White Rabbit as she went up to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had opened his eyes, standing up from his bed as he smiled towards Qiao Si Liu: "Fairy, this sudden visit is truly joyful."

Lady White Rabbit looked at Fang Yuan in a daze, thinking: "Wu Yi Hai is smiling again, I have not seen him smile for a long time. He looks like the sun shining in spring when he smiles, if only he could smile at me!"

Qiao Si Liu looked at Fang Yuan, disregarding pleasantries: "It seems you really do not know! Sigh... my next words will only be shocking, there is no joy."

Fang Yuan's expression changed: "What happened?"

Qiao Si Liu did not answer him, she turned around and said to Lady White Rabbit: "Little lady, please leave first, I need to talk to your lord."

"What?" Lady White Rabbit was dazed.

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "White Rabbit, please."

Lady White Rabbit did not dare to defy Fang Yuan, she acknowledged as she left the hall.

As the doors closed, Qiao Si Liu said: "Wu Yong is missing, his life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu are destroyed, news has not spread in Southern Border yet, but Wu clan is in chaos now."

"What?!" Fang Yuan was deeply shocked.

This was simply too shocking.

With the destruction of his life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, Wu Yong was likely to have died.

He was the pillar of Wu clan, if he died, would Wu clan be able to defend its territories?

Qiao Si Liu continued: "Yi Hai, I am here to lend you a hand. You are Wu Yong's brother, the person closest to him in bloodline, and you have sufficient cultivation level. With Wu Yong gone, you have to take over as first supreme elder! From today onwards, you will hold the authority of Wu clan."

Chapter 1343: Gaining Authority Without Even Moving

Taking over Wu clan?

Qiao Si Liu's words made Fang Yuan moved.

How could he not be moved?

After all, Wu clan was a super force, and it was not an ordinary super force, it was already very powerful, having the number one position for years after years in Southern Border's history.

Wu clan had a huge territory with all sorts of resource points, it had a deep foundation and an incredible rich treasury. If he could control this super force, becoming the person with the highest authority, Fang Yuan's future cultivation resources would be unrestricted!

Right now, Fang Yuan had a lot of assets.

The trading of Dang Hun Mountain's guts Gu, dragonfish, regretful spiders, eerie fire dragon pythons, star fragment grass, star dart Gu, star river Gu, stellar fire Gu, falling meteor Gu, as well as the spirit snake trade which had started recently.

It was not an exaggeration to say that Fang Yuan was raking in gold every day.

If the rest of the resources in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture were included, he had an ordinary rank eight Gu Immortal's foundation. If he also included Lang Ya blessed land's wisdom Gu, and Dang Hun Mountain located inside it, and City Well in the turbulent flow sea area, Fang Yuan had surpassed ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals!

But he paled in comparison if he placed his resources against those of a super force.

Any super force had an incredibly deep foundation, even if they currently did not have a rank eight great expert, they had them in history. In addition to the resource points that the super forces controlled in the five regions, Fang Yuan's assets were truly inferior in comparison.

For example, Wu clan's blood tide pit produced more profits than Fang Yuan's dragonfish transactions.

Wu clan had twenty to thirty resource points similar to blood tide pit.

And resource points inferior to blood tide pit, like Northern Plains' Liu tribe's bone burial field or jade light pit, were countless.

There were also about ten top tier resource points better than blood tide pit.

And don't forget, the resources in the immortal apertures of Wu clan's Gu Immortals, and also the blessed lands and grotto-heavens of Wu clan's predecessors.

Of course, super forces had lots of earnings and also spending. Wu clan was currently in a state of having more assets than manpower, they were barely able to defend these resources when Wu Yong was around. But with him gone, they were sure to have losses, they had to give up some.

But even so, if Fang Yuan could control Wu clan, his gains would be immense, far beyond him working alone.

Fang Yuan quickly calmed down.

He took a look at Qiao Si Liu, immediately realizing her intention.

Like what Qiao Si Liu said, with Wu Yong gone, the role of Wu Yi Hai, whom Fang Yuan was acting as, was the best choice of becoming Wu clan's first supreme elder.

This was an unbelievably rare chance!

Fang Yuan did not doubt that Qiao Si Liu was speaking the truth, because it was too easy to verify.

Qiao Si Liu was here in a rush, she showed her sincerity.

Fang Yuan frowned and smiled bitterly: "Such a huge thing happened! I had no idea."

"The urgent matter at hand is to get back to Wu clan. Wu Ba Chong has already gathered the supreme elders, many Gu Immortals have already returned, even if they did not return, their wills are present. But they purposely left you out, I wonder what their intentions were." Qiao Si Liu said anxiously.

Using Wu Yi Hai was the best chance that Qiao clan had in interfering with Wu clan.

Fang Yuan sighed deeply: "Sigh! I have only been in Wu clan for a short time, I have no foundation or network. It is too difficult to take over and become the first supreme elder. They purposely left me out, it shows that my chances are way too slim."

"No, you have a big chance. Yi Hai, don't forget that you have me, Qiao clan is backing you up!" Qiao Si Liu looked at Fang Yuan with deep emotions.

Fang Yuan blinked: "How will Qiao clan help me? What will Lord Qiao Zhi Cai do?"

Qiao Si Liu's expression froze, she hesitated for a while, but she did not dare to hide it from Fang Yuan, she said the truth: "Our first supreme elder went with Lord Wu Yong, he has vanished as well, his life tablet Gu broke and we cannot contact him. Other than them, Tie clan's Tie Mian Shen also went missing. They were investigating the deaths of Wu Yuan Ju and Rong Hao, but now we do not know if they are alive or not."

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk: "What is going on?"

Qiao Si Liu smiled bitterly: "Trust me, this is all I know."

Fang Yuan showed hesitation: "Such a shocking event, we cannot hide it from the world for long. Who was it? Without Lord Qiao Zhi Cai, how will Qiao clan help me?"

"Don't worry about that, Qiao clan has already come to a consensus, I am the chosen representative." Qiao Si Liu said.

Fang Yuan was slightly shocked.

Qiao clan was the weakest among Southern Border's super forces. Despite that, they were united, even with Qiao Zhi Cai missing, they still carried out their plans accordingly, as expected, any super force had its extraordinary aspect.

But Fang Yuan did not want to go.

He sensed that there were undercurrents brewing a huge vortex, the mastermind was a powerful force!

Even if he took over as Wu clan's first supreme elder, so what?

No resources could match his gains in exploring dream realms.

Fang Yuan did not need more resources, he needed attainment level from the dream realms.

The latter was the truly precious fortuitous encounter!

Even if he became Wu clan's most authoritative figure, which was alluring and beneficial to him, Fang Yuan knew that there were countless choices in life, if one wanted to progress further, they could not be blinded by profits, they needed to be clear about what were the most important things!

"Once I become first supreme elder, I would need to return to the clan and hold the fort, back at Wu Yi Mountain. How can I leave the giant dream realm? I had put in so much effort to come here."

"But rejecting Qiao Si Liu is not wise. If I anger Qiao clan and ruin our relationship, I will gain nothing."

"But the most important thing is, in the eyes of everyone, if I stay here and do not return to gain control of the clan, it would be very strange and suspicious. After all, I also displayed a level of political ambition earlier."

Fang Yuan thought as he paced around the hall.

Qiao Si Liu was stomping her feet in anxiety: "Yi Hai, why are you hesitating?"

"This is too shocking, I need some time to think." Fang Yuan waved his hand.

"There is no time, we need to leave now, you can think along the way." Qiao Si Liu said.

"No, this is not as simple as you think!" Fang Yuan shook his head, having a grim expression: "Do you know? You have already fallen for their trap."

Qiao Si Liu was stunned: "What?"

Fang Yuan said: "If we return openly like this, what would Wu clan's supreme elders think? They are not stupid, if I, Wu Yi Hai, goes back with Qiao clan and take over as first supreme elder, leaving my brother in the lurch and instead, bringing in outsiders to fight for benefits in the clan, the entire clan will be torn apart, without sufficient strength and reputation, how can I take over as first supreme elder?"

Qiao Si Liu blinked, thinking: Wu Yi Hai's words made sense.

"Then do we stay here while Wu Ba Chong controls the situation and takes over as first supreme elder?" Qiao Si Liu retorted.

Fang Yuan thought that this Qiao Si Liu was not easy to get rid of, but he smiled: "We can wait, there is no rush."

"No rush?" Qiao Si Liu stared with wide eyes.

Fang Yuan's smile deepened, he looked at Qiao Si Liu with a sharp gaze: "I believe that even if I do not return, Wu Ba Chong cannot control the situation, am I wrong?"

Qiao Si Liu was stunned again.

Wu clan, discussion hall.

Boom!

Wu Ba Chong slammed the table, dust flew upwards from the damage.

He shouted: "Wu Qiao[1], what do you mean?! No matter what suggestions I bring up, you object, are you trying to find trouble with me?"

Wu Qiao smiled coldly, standing in the middle of the hall as he looked at Wu Ba Chong: "Second supreme elder, you are too hasty. We do not know if Lord Wu Yong is dead or alive, just the life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu cannot determine it. Look at you, you are sitting in his seat already, I was warning you earlier out of kindness, you should sit in your own seat."

"Supreme elder Wu Qiao, Wu clan is in grave danger now, we should discuss the important matters and not bother with these small details."

"I feel that there is no issue with Lord Wu Ba Chong leading the discussion, he is the second supreme elder after all. And now, Wu clan needs a leader!"

"Do you think we do not know what intentions you have, Wu Qiao? I just want to remind you, you are a Wu clansman, not a Qiao clansman."

In the hall, some Gu Immortals spoke, helping Wu Ba Chong target Wu Qiao.

Wu Qiao sneered: "In terms of bloodline, the most qualified person to become first supreme elder is Lord Wu Yi Hai! Should the second supreme elder take over the position? Are we in a Central Continent sect?"

There was silence.

"That makes sense."

"As clans, we emphasize on bloodline."

"Why did Wu Yi Hai not come? Wu Ba Chong, did you inform him?"

Some Gu Immortals spoke out, most of them were defending their territories, only their wills were participating in this.

Wu Ba Chong observed their expressions, even though he showed anger on his face, he was calm as ice in his heart.

"I did not succeed." He sighed internally.

On the surface, he stood up, patting his forehead as he sighed: "I was rash, I was too worried about the clan. You are right, Lord Wu Yi Hai should be leading us, I will welcome his return! I am willing to listen to him."

"Huh?"

Once he said that, the Gu Immortals were shocked.

Wu Qiao was also evidently surprised.

What was this Wu Ba Chong planning?

The contents of Wu clan's discussions soon got to Fang Yuan.

Qiao Si Liu showed joy as she looked at Fang Yuan: "Great, even though we did not return, we can still take over Wu clan."

Fang Yuan had a grim expression, the situation was progressing at an unpleasant rate.

Wu Qiao's actions were understandable. After all, this former Wu clan third supreme elder was already bribed by Qiao clan.

But Wu Ba Chong's action of taking a step back was truly brilliant, Fang Yuan was quite impressed.

"The situation is not good." Fang Yuan shook his head and sighed.

[1] As a reminder, the Qiao in his name is not the same Qiao of Qiao clan Back

Chapter 1344: Troubled Thoughts, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Building

"What is it?" Qiao Si Liu did not understand.

Fang Yuan did not answer her, he paced around, using wisdom path methods as he fell into deep thought.

The situation was very complex now, the mastermind was hidden, while Wu Yong was missing, everything was shrouded in mystery. But Fang Yuan had no choice but to decide his course of action now.

He had no choice.

Fang Yuan could deeply feel how helpless he was in this situation.

Wu clan's Gu Immortals, Qiao clan's Gu Immortals, as well as Southern Border's situation and the mastermind, they all forced him to leave the super Gu formation.

This was the helplessness of the righteous path.

Fang Yuan was faced with a difficult test.

He did not want to be a chess piece of Qiao clan and Wu clan, he wanted to keep his benefits amidst this complex situation.

What to do?

Fang Yuan had already guessed Wu Ba Chong's intention and desire.

"Maybe I can make use of this?" Thinking of this, Fang Yuan decided to make use of it.

He stopped walking around, he faced Qiao Si Liu: "Since they want me to lead the clan, I will give my orders."

"Yi Hai, this is the demeanor of a heroic man!" Qiao Si Liu's eyes shone, she praised.

Fang Yuan continued: "With the mastermind hidden, we need to play safe now. I will order Wu clan's Gu Immortals to give up on the faraway resource points and return to Wu Yi Mountain, we will activate our Immortal Gu Houses to defend against the unknown."

Qiao Si Liu was very satisfied with Fang Yuan's action.

Fang Yuan informed her of his thoughts regarding Wu clan's internal affairs, he did not treat her as an outsider.

Qiao Si Liu was joyful, she said: "This is the best method to play safe. But it is a severe loss, by giving up the defense of so many resource points, the surrounding super forces will take over them."

"We have no choice, Wu clan's strength is too dispersed, with this uncertain situation, we can only regroup and defend against future challenges." Fang Yuan sighed.

"That makes sense too, let's go, we should return to Wu Yi Mountain." Qiao Si Liu approved of Fang Yuan's idea, she said.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "No, we are not leaving."

"This will be too dangerous."

"Even my brother was ambushed, we are just rank seven, wouldn't that mastermind easily deal with us?"

"If this mastermind wants to deal with Wu clan, their next target is me. How can I leave now? The route back to Wu clan is too dangerous!"

Fang Yuan's excuse was very reasonable.

Qiao Si Liu's expression turned grim, nodding: "That is true! We need to be safer, it will be best if we can be escorted by an Immortal Gu House."

After spending so much effort, he finally convinced Qiao Si Liu, Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief.

But he was still frowning.

He had finally managed to stay in the super Gu formation, but now, how long could it continue?

Wu Yong's survival was uncertain, this situation made even Fang Yuan, who knew about certain future events, feel helpless.

Inside the purple blood river formation.

There were over a dozen blood rivers now.

In this dim place, countless purple thoughts were pouring out unceasingly.

Tie Mian Shen shouted loudly, iron sand that resembled fog was surrounding him, forming a huge veil that defended him.

But the purple thoughts turned from solid to phantom, entering the iron sand veil towards Tie Mian Shen unobstructed.

"Damn it!" Tie Mian Shen gritted his teeth, he had no options against such a phantom path method.

But at the moment of crisis, a clear wind blew.

The purple thoughts that had turned into phantom burst like bubbles.

"So close..." Tie Mian Shen looked around, giving Wu Yong a look of gratitude.

Purple thoughts formed into a storm around Wu Yong, there were countless blood beasts mixed among them.

But even in this intense battle, Wu Yong was uninjured, he still had the spare energy to take care of Tie Mian Shen and Qiao Zhi Cai, who were far away in the battlefield.

"This purple blood river formation has phantom path effects, if we do not get rid of the ruin bat corpses, these phantom path effects will not end!" Qiao Zhi Cai shouted.

He needed to shout.

Because voice transmissions would not work here.

Wisdom path methods like communicating with thoughts were also unusable.

Tie Mian Shen had a cold gaze, sharp as a dagger, he looked around and saw that there were thirty to forty ruin bat corpses, most were desolate level, but there were some ancient ruin bats and even an immemorial ruin bat, defended by two blood rivers.

In fact, at this point, Tie Mian Shen could understand some things already.

These ruin bat corpses were rapidly melted in the blood river. Especially when the purple thoughts turned from solid to phantom, these ruin bat corpses were being consumed at a rapid rate.

But so what if he knew about the importance of the ruin bat corpses?

Not long after they fought, that rank eight Gu Immortal (Purple Mountain True Monarch) had vanished.

Wu Yong was greatly restricted now, he was defending against Purple Mountain True Monarch's sneak attack.

"It is unwise to get Lord Wu Yong to destroy the ruin bat corpses, that purple haired rank eight will use it to his advantage."

"In this situation, Qiao Zhi Cai and I need to work together to clear the ruin bat corpses."

"If that purple haired enemy attacks, Lord Wu Yong would be able to block him and save our lives..."

But what if he could not?

Or rather, even if he could save their lives, if he had to give up a chance to destroy the Gu formation, what would Wu Yong do?

Tie Mian Shen was hesitant, because trust between the three was lacking.

But at this time, a complex aura burst out from the very center of the battlefield.

Great winds blew, Wu Yong's sleeves were fluttering like the king of the wind. At this moment, his ordinary appearance had turned into one of grand boldness and authority.

"Since you want to see the rank eight Immortal Gu that my mother left me, I will show you." Wu Yong called out coldly.

A vast number of purple thoughts were blown away, the blood rivers were in turbulence, several rivers were cut apart from this intense wind.

Qiao Zhi Cai was shocked and joyful.

Tie Mian Shen's iron mask was also shaved off slightly from this commotion, he called out in surprise: "This is an... Immortal Gu House?!"

Wu Yong had struck without warning, making a truly shocking move.

He did not use any immortal killer moves, he took out an Immortal Gu House from his immortal aperture.

This Immortal Gu House was not glorious or grand, it had the appearance of a bamboo building.

This was a very commonly seen type of building in Southern Border, it existed in the other four regions as well, but it was only built on mountainous terrain.

This bamboo building had two stories, made entirely out of bamboo, there were even bamboo leaves growing on the bamboos, drops of dew were dripping down from the leaves, green as jade.

Wu Yong's sleeves billowed, flying into the second story of the bamboo building.

He sat by the window, flicking his finger as the bamboo building shook, more than ten drops of jade dew fell off the roof.

At that moment, the jade dew shot out from the bamboo building at lightning speed.

Everywhere they went, clear wind blew, sweeping everything. Be it the purple thoughts or blood red tides, they were all disintegrated by the wind.

"So impressive!" Qiao Zhi Cai praised, the jade dew had flown over and resolved his crisis.

"Wu clan had three Immortal Gu Houses initially, but now they have a fourth! And this Immortal Gu House has the aura of two rank eight wind path Immortal Gu... Wu Yong had truly hidden it very deeply." Tie Mian Shen was deeply shook.

The two Gu Immortals were saved one after another, they flew into the bamboo building, standing beside Wu Yong.

"This is the Immortal Gu House that my mother constructed, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building." Wu Yong sat by the window, looking at the Gu formation outside as he explained clearly.

"Amazing! With this building, we will not lose. It is only a matter of time until we escape." Qiao Zhi Cai was overjoyed.

If Wu Yong was using Wu Du Xiu's two rank eight Immortal Gu to activate an immortal killer move, Qiao Zhi Cai would be very worried.

Because activating immortal killer moves had a chance of failure. The stronger the killer move, the greater the backlash if he failed in activating it.

But Wu Du Xiu had died, Wu Yong had only inherited these two rank eight Immortal Gu for a short amount of time.

Especially when Wu Yong was the first supreme elder of Wu clan, he had high status, how much time did he have to practise his killer moves? This was a huge problem.

But now, these two rank eight wind path Immortal Gu were used with other Gu worms to construct an Immortal Gu House!

Everyone knew that Immortal Gu Houses had fixed abilities, but they were easy to use and would not normally have backlash.

Tie Mian Shen's emotions were much more complex, he thought: "Wu clan actually had a fourth Immortal Gu House, and it is a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it is far more powerful than the first three. Each Immortal Gu House will greatly raise a clan's overall strength. With a rank eight Immortal Gu House, and some Gu Immortals, as long as they had enough immortal essence, Wu clan would basically have the equivalent of a second rank eight Gu Immortal. Wu Yong had truly concealed this deeply!"

He could not help but assess Wu Yong again in a new light.

Wu clan was not having an easy time recently, they were facing the threat of many forces around them. As the only rank eight Gu Immortal left in Wu clan, Wu Yong was busy sending out people to deal with problems, he was in an awkward state.

But as long as he used this Immortal Gu House, all his problems would be resolved, Wu clan's reputation would soar and they would become the number one force in Southern Border again without doubt, all of the other forces would stop having greedy thoughts.

But Wu Yong did not.

He had been using his own strength to deal with Wu clan's problems. He hid this Immortal Gu House very deeply, even Wu clan's Gu Immortals did not know of it.

If he was not trapped inside this purple blood river formation, nobody would be able to find out that Wu Yong actually had a fourth Immortal Gu House, and it was a rank eight Immortal Gu House at that.

"With just this, Wu Yong is definitely not inferior to his mother Wu Du Xiu! Thankfully, my Tie clan is at the northeast of Southern Border, while Wu clan is at the southwest, we are far apart. And earlier, my clan did not join in on making problems for Wu clan." Tie Mian Shen let out a breath, feeling relieved.

All of the super forces dominated an area, they had been in Southern Border for countless years.

They understood each other very clearly, each of their strengths were balanced with the amount of territory they had, it was in a deadlock.

But once Wu Du Xiu died, this balance was upset, thus, the other super clans worked together to find trouble with Wu clan.

But the moment they displayed this Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, it would replace Wu Du Xiu and suppress Southern Border once again.

Wu Yong's simply had been scheming so deeply, he had been hiding it from view. One could easily tell, the moment he took out this Immortal Gu House, the other clans would suffer, they would be met with a great defeat!

Chapter 1345: Worsening Situation, Fang Yuan Moves

The morning sun rose into the sky, it was dawn, the air was still moist and damp.

Two Hou clan Gu Immortals stood above the clouds, looking down at the canyon below them.

Golden Cloud Canyon!

This canyon was filled with mist. At night, the mist would obscure vision and had no special trait. but when the sun rises, and sunlight shines into the canyon, the mist would give out sharp golden light.

These fragments of gold light were not glaring, the mist filled this golden canyon, making it grand and imposing.

"This is Golden Cloud Canyon, it produces metal path and cloud path resources. Long ago, Wu clan had taken it away from us forcefully." A Hou clan Gu Immortal sighed: "But now, it is time to take back our assets!"

The other Hou clan Gu Immortal nodded, a faint light shining from his body.

The light lasted for a few breaths of time, after it faded, his appearance had changed, he now resembled a famous expert in the demonic path.

The Hou clan Gu Immortal beside him nodded, before rushing down towards Golden Cloud Canyon silently.

Golden Cloud Canyon was originally defended by a Wu clan Gu Immortal, but because of Wu Yong's disappearance, Fang Yuan had ordered everyone to return to Wu clan's headquarters.

This news could be concealed for a while, but it was eventually noticed by everyone.

However, Hou clan was a righteous path force, they could not attack directly. There were righteous path rules, thus, Hou clan needed an excuse. Therefore, they said that they were pursuing a demonic path Gu Immortal and charged into Golden Cloud Canyon openly.

Once they took down Golden Cloud Canyon and established that fact, it will not be easy for Wu clan to reclaim Golden Cloud Canyon.

By then, Hou clan can come up with lots of excuses, like 'we helped Wu clan defend Golden Cloud Canyon, we want some compensation', it would be a problem for Wu clan.

Coming up with excuses was the greatest ability of righteous path forces.

Unless Wu clan had superior battle strength and forced Hou clan to back off.

The demonic path expert that the Hou clan Gu Immortal transformed into flew towards the golden mist like a huge bird.

Sensing his aura, the mist inside Golden Cloud Canyon changed, metallic sounds could be heard from it, causing vibrations in the eardrums.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

At the next moment, countless blades, spears, swords, halberds, in the form of golden phantoms, shot out endlessly.

Even though the Wu clan Gu Immortal left, the resource point's Gu formation was still around.

At this moment, it was activated automatically, defending itself.

The gaze of the Hou clan Gu Immortal was stern, he called out as a strong blade qi shot down, slicing sharply. Everywhere it went, space shattered, winds were moving rapidly.

Evidently, Hou clan came prepared, he used blade qi Immortal Gu.

Wu clan's Gu formation was just a mortal Gu formation, how could it match a rank seven Gu Immortal? Not only did the countless golden phantoms shatter, even the Gu formation was completely destroyed from one attack.

At once, the golden mist in the canyon was split in the middle, a large amount of the golden mist parted as the canyon's true appearance was exposed.

The two Gu Immortals from Hou clan had heated gazes.

"Demonic path scoundrel, where are you going?" One of the Hou clan Gu Immortals shouted as he charged ahead.

...

A purple waterfall descended like a mist, it was a hundred and eighty feet tall.

Poisonous waterfall!

On a mountain close to this waterfall, there was a mortal village that Wu clan specially arranged.

"Die, die!" A large group of mortal Gu Masters charged into the mountain.

Wu clan's Gu Masters retreated, they were at their final line of defense.

Wu clan's leader, a rank four Gu Master, stood at the crossroad as he shouted at his enemies: "Your Yang clan is really despicable, you actually assaulted our Wu clan!"

"Hmph! We have been putting up with you for a long time. You have been too overbearing in occupying this place. My father and mother just wanted a Gu worm to cure their poison, but they actually died in this mountain. Today, we will settle the score!" The leading Yang clan Gu Master was still quite young, he charged into the mountain with rage and hatred.

"Damn it!" Wu clan's Gu Masters were in a defensive location, but Yang clan came prepared, they had great numbers.

Wu clan's Gu Masters were bound to lose, they could only escape from a secret cave.

Yang clan's Gu Masters defeated Wu clan, they cheered in the rubble of the village.

Above the clouds, the Yang clan Gu Immortals watching this expressed joy on their faces.

This was the area where Yang clan and Wu clan bordered. Yang clan had been planning for a long time, sending a group of Yang clan mortals here, and allowed them to live here, causing conflict to occur between them and Wu clan.

Because of this excuse, Yang clan could invade and occupy Wu clan's territory openly now.

With the righteous path's rules, these were just mortal conflicts, unless Gu Immortal seeds were killed, there were no consequences.

Poisonous waterfall was just an ordinary mortal resource point, it produced some mortal poison path Gu, it was not important to Gu Immortals.

But once this opening was made, from now on, Yang clan only needed to move forward to reach their destination, the truly valuable — Corpse Mountain!

...

Rumble!

River water raged like thunder, resounding in the ears of a Yao clan Gu Immortal.

He stood at the peak of Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian, looking at the raging red river.

Not far from here, two rivers were connected. Red dragon river and yellow dragon river, these two rivers merged together, forming a huge whirlpool that created great waves, it was extremely dangerous.

Southern Border's three rivers were not simple. Be it red dragon river, yellow dragon river, or jade dragon river, spirit springs would form in these rivers sometimes. And these spirit springs would be mixed in the river water, once they were washed away, the river water would be full of natural essence, allowing more Gu materials to be created.

Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian!

This was a very special mountain. During ancient times, a Southern Border rank eight Gu Immortal had turned into a zombie and fought against the combined forces of many super clans.

After the rank eight immortal zombie died, this place became a wasteland, it had no value.

But to think that as time passed, gradually, on the mangled corpse of this rank eight immortal zombie, due to the nourishment of the natural essence from the river, along with the aquatic plants in the river that rooted themselves, this place turned into a corpse mountain.

This corpse mountain was thousands of feet tall, there were large numbers of zombies living in it, and it produced transformation path zombie Gu, as well as qi path zombie qi Gu.

Before the headquarters of Southern Border's Zombie Alliance was exposed, they had targeted this precious area and wanted to pay a high price to buy it from Wu clan to make it their headquarters, but Wu clan rejected them.

"Zombie Alliance did not get it, but now, this belongs to my Yao clan!" The Yao clan Gu Immortal was very excited.

He looked afar, away from the river and towards the shore.

That was Wu clan's territory.

After taking over this Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian, Wu clan's territory east of red dragon river and north of yellow dragon river would be completely lost.

Yao clan took down Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian, this was like a bridgehead, they could finally start going after Wu clan's other territories.

News that Wu Yong had died spread out of nowhere.

After getting such news, several super forces colluded secretly, thus, they did not act alone this time.

Yao clan, Yang clan, and Hou clan, they were just three of these clans.

Wu clan's headquarters were in chaos.

"Damn it! These three clans are simply too daring!"

"We lost three resources at once, especially Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian, this is a huge loss. In the past, Wu clan from top to bottom spent such effort and a huge price to obtain it."

"Retaliate, we need to retaliate! We have our Immortal Gu Houses, what are we afraid of?"

Wu clan's Gu Immortals bellowed in anxiety, some were arguing endlessly, some raised their arms in objection, some were remaining silent.

More than ten days had passed since Wu Yong went missing, it was unknown whether he was dead or alive.

Wu clan had been trying to conceal this information, but like Wu Ba Chong had guessed, the mastermind had already spread news of it.

Initially, the super clans did not believe it.

Because Fang Yuan had already expected this situation, he gave out a lot of false information to mislead others.

But his actions were not normal.

Super forces were not stupid, after some observation and probing, they finally acted. The moment they did, Wu clan went into a difficult spot, they lost a lot of territory.

In the discussion hall, because Wu Yong was missing, the main seat was empty. Wu Ba Chong, who was second supreme elder, sat by the side, he was silent, quietly observing the surrounding Gu Immortals' expressions, even though he had a heavy heart, he felt a bit smug.

Especially when he looked at Wu Qiao, his lips could not help but curl up.

Because Wu Qiao was the Wu clan Gu Immortal in charge of guarding Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian. Once they lost that resource point, it was a huge loss to Wu Qiao.

Wu Qiao was solemn and had a cold expression.

Even though he sensed Wu Ba Chong's provocative gaze, he pretended not to be aware, sitting like a statue.

"Stop arguing, be quiet." Wu Ba Chong said.

This time, nobody rebuked him, the discussion hall quickly became silent.

Wu Ba Chong was very pleased at this, under the immortals' anxious gazes, he sighed: "Such a huge matter happened to Wu clan, but we still cannot make a decision, let's ask Lord Wu Yi Hai to make his decision."

Wu Qiao frowned.

The other Wu clan Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Some were unhappy with Fang Yuan, grumbling: "Such a huge matter happened to our clan, but Lord Wu Yi Hai is still staying inside the super Gu formation."

"I heard that Fairy Si Liu went there more than ten days ago. I also heard that there is a Lady White Rabbit..." The Gu Immortal who said this had vile intentions.

Wu Qiao frowned even deeper now, he wanted to speak up for Fang Yuan, but he was in a dangerous state himself, he hesitated and did not speak.

Wu clan's letter soon got to Fang Yuan.

Such a thing had happened, Fang Yuan was not surprised, he expected it.

"It seems that I cannot stay here anymore." Fang Yuan looked at the dream realm, sighing deeply.

These last days, he wanted to continue exploring dream realms.

But his luck was bad, he kept getting those absurd dream realms, there was no way to explore it.

Chapter 1346: Qiao Clan's Trouble, Rabbit's Deep Love

Of course, over these last days, Fang Yuan was not doing nothing.

The biggest batch of regretful spiders in his possession had been sold, Fang Yuan's red date immortal essence storage was no longer lacking.

As for vajra shell, Fang Yuan had completed its modification, he only needed to test it.

Because his dark path attainment level had risen to grandmaster, he successfully created an immortal killer move, extended dark concealment. This move used rank six dark limit Immortal Gu and rank seven perseverance Immortal Gu as the cores, and several hundred mortal Gu to greatly lengthen the effect of dark limit Immortal Gu.

At this time, Qiao Si Liu requested to meet him.

At Fang Yuan's will, the doors opened.

Qiao Si Liu had a grim expression, worry could be seen on her face.

She brought bad news with her.

Other than Yao clan, Hou clan, and Yang clan taking over Wu clan's territories, Ba clan and Xia clan had also moved at the same time, but against Qiao clan.

Looking at Southern Border's map, Ba clan and Xia clan were to the north of Qiao clan, they bordered Qiao clan.

Qiao clan lost their wedding dress lake and empty origin pit, they were annexed by Ba clan and Xia clan respectively.

After Qiao clan's first supreme elder, Qiao Zhi Cai, went missing, Qiao clan also did the strategy of gathering their Gu Immortals and defending their base, in anticipation of the enemy.

This made Ba clan's and Xia clan's actions very successful.

Qiao clan lost a lot just now.

Wedding dress lake and empty origin pit were resource points that were more valuable than blood tide pit.

Qiao clan was the weakest righteous path super force. After losing two resource points, Qiao clan was furious and upset.

Fang Yuan had also heard of these two resource points.

There was a folklore about this wedding dress lake in Southern Border. According to legends, a fairy in heaven weaved clothing, making her own wedding dress, whoever received it would become the husband of this fairy.

After the fairy made the wedding dress, she tossed it into this lake, and it was picked up by a fisherman who lived by the lake.

The immortal and mortal loved each other, staying inside the lake, living happily ever after.

This story was mostly fiction, but wedding dress lake had all sorts of clothing Gu. Like fire cloak Gu, water armor Gu, wood armor Gu, and so on.

In its history of being in Qiao clan's control, it had produced three wild Immortal Gu!

As for empty origin pit, it was known by the mortals living in the mountains nearby as the final resting spot, it could communicate with the immortal realm.

After the ignorant mortals died, their corpses were tossed into this pit.

Before these corpses landed, they would be torn to shreds by the space path dao marks here.

These ignorant mortals thought that the reason was because they had ascended to the immortal realm after dying.

The truth was, this place was excellent in producing space path resources. Xia clan had wanted it for a long time, and even though Qiao clan was not their match, they were backed by Wu clan.

Right now, with Qiao Zhi Cai and Wu Yong missing, this was a great opportunity, how could Xia clan miss it?

Qiao clan and Wu clan had been in an alliance for a long time, their fortunes were tied together.

Qiao clan was invaded by Ba clan and Xia clan, it was like Wu clan getting attacked.

This way, including Yao clan, Hou clan, and Yang clan, a total of five super forces were attacking Wu clan.

The situation was at its worst.

If they could not stop this, Wu clan and Qiao clan would lose even more territory later.

"I will arrange it now, Wu Qiao will bring the Immortal Gu House here and escort us back!" Fang Yuan said to Qiao Si Liu.

Qiao Si Liu nodded, this was the reason she came. With Qiao clan's predicament, Qiao Si Liu had to look for help from Fang Yuan.

Actually, because of Fang Yuan's delay, Qiao Si Liu was very unhappy already. If not for the fact that Qiao clan only had one Immortal Gu House, they would have already sent out one to bring Fang Yuan away.

"Go arrange it too, gather Qiao clan's Gu Immortals, we are leaving together." Fang Yuan said again.

Qiao Si Liu was stunned: "Together? What about here..."

"We can only give it up temporarily." Fang Yuan made up his mind, he did not hesitate.

"Then what about the Immortal Gu we used to set up this formation?" Qiao Si Liu frowned.

"We will bring them away. Otherwise, some Gu Immortals with ill intent will forcefully refine them or even destroy them. We know what these people are capable of. Excuses are too easy to find." Fang Yuan said plainly.

"Don't forget that my formation path attainment is not low. I am capable of taking out some Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan added.

Qiao Si Liu thought of Fang Yuan and Chi Shang's competition, she nodded, thinking: "Wu Yi Hai's formation path attainment is indeed not low, Chi Shang had once praised him for it."

In fact, she underestimated Fang Yuan.

Right now, his formation path attainment level was at grandmaster, he was comparable to Chi Shang.

In the past, this super Gu formation was completely indecipherable to him, he could not see anything.

But after becoming a formation path grandmaster and staying here for so long, Fang Yuan had gained a rather deep understanding of this super Gu formation.

Modifying this Gu formation was out of his ability, but taking away some Immortal Gu was possible.

After the decision was made, Qiao Si Liu called Qiao clan Gu Immortal Qiao Bo: "Pack up, when Wu clan's Immortal Gu House arrives, we will leave and return to our base."

Qiao Bo quickly acknowledged, asking in succession: "When are they coming? I need to arrange the clansmen."

Qiao Si Liu looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "No rush, I had just contacted them, it will take some time."

Qiao Bo expressed joy on his face as he left respectfully.

"Even though Wu clan's base is near Yi Tian Mountain, if they are sending an Immortal Gu House, it will take four to five days to reach here. In this case, I can do the final round of the business." Qiao Bo left and started to think.

The business he thought of was naturally the immortal opportunity business.

Qiao clan and Wu clan were in dire straits, this caused Qiao clan's and Wu clan's Gu Immortals to feel worried, the immortal opportunity business was taking a huge hit.

Two of Qiao clan's Gu Immortals were stationed to guard the super Gu formation here.

Qiao Bo was one of them, he had rank six cultivation level, when he was sent here, he begrudged the decision, but the immortal opportunity business changed his mind.

"Now that we are returning, the immortal opportunity business cannot continue, there might even be fights later. Since we are leaving anyway, I will make this a big one!" Qiao Bo gritted his teeth, making up his mind.

A day later.

Qiao Bo met with demonic path Gu Immortal Fairy Miao Yin.

"Fairy, we meet again." Qiao Bo had an excited expression, his eyes were darting around as he observed Fairy Miao Yin.

Even though Fairy Miao Yin was in the demonic path, her strength and appearance was top tier, she was one of the three great fairies of Southern Border, on par with Qiao Si Liu.

All along, Fairy Miao Yin had been entering the giant dream realm to find opportunities in the dream realm.

Even though her soul was often injured, the dream path materials that she gathered were not few.

Even though Wu clan and Qiao clan, and other super forces tried to buy these dream path materials from her, Fairy Miao Yin rejected them all without hesitation.

"Let's go in and speak." Qiao Bo said as he looked at the two Gu Immortals behind Fairy Miao Yin.

According to the rules, each business would only have one demonic cultivator or lone immortal.

But this time, because Qiao Bo was going to leave, he made this a big one and went ahead to bring in three Gu Immortals at once.

At the same time, in Wu clan's area.

Lady White Rabbit looked at Wu An: "Lord Wu An, is it true that everyone is leaving? And so urgently?"

Wu An nodded: "The situation is not looking good, I'm sure you've heard some rumors. But it is not a problem, don't worry, Wu clan will not fall. Just stay here and manage the immortal opportunity business, wait for us to return."

Lady White Rabbit pondered for a moment before asking weakly: "Before you leave, I want to meet Lord Wu Yi Hai again, is that possible?"

"This..." Wu An had a difficult expression: "Lord Wu Yi Hai is in seclusion now, he is trying to deduce an immortal killer move, he might not have time for you."

Lady White Rabbit had a sad expression: "I don't know why but I have a bad feeling, I want to meet Lord Wu Yi Hai, I just want to take a glance at him. Isn't he leaving too? I will wait here for a few days until he comes out, is that okay?"

Wu An sighed deeply.

It was obvious at a glance that Lady White Rabbit had affection towards Wu Yi Hai.

"It is a pity that the feeling is not mutual, I am afraid that in Lord Wu Yi Hai's eyes, Lady White Rabbit is just a tool, what a shame." Wu An felt some sympathy in him.

He nodded: "Alright, you can stay here, Lord Wu Yi Hai will see you after he ends his closed cultivation."

"Thank you, thank you!" Lady White Rabbit was overjoyed, she quickly thanked him profusely.

Cultivating in the secret room, Fang Yuan held a rank seven Immortal Gu.

Immortal Gu Precaution!

This Gu worm was the size of two hands, it was like a long-horned beetle with a black exoskeleton, it was very heavy. Even with Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body, he could not hold it.

But it had already been refined by Fang Yuan, it was floating in the air now as Fang Yuan observed it.

This Immortal Gu was one of the two Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan had taken after joining Wu clan as Wu Yi Hai.

As the name suggested, the Immortal Gu's effect was to protect the Gu Immortal.

It was rule path and had one weakness, when used alone, it needed some time to activate. It could only activate its effects after ten breaths of time.

Ten breaths of time was not short for Gu Immortals. Especially in intense battles, ten breaths of time was enough for a dozen round of fights, with countless attacks unleashed.

And most importantly, if a Gu Immortal sneak attacked, life and death would be decided in an instant. By then, activating precaution Immortal Gu would be too slow.

However, once precaution Immortal Gu was activated, ten breaths of time later, its defensive effect would be incredible, it was one of the top rank seven defensive Immortal Gu, it had status equal to sword escape Immortal Gu.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan had a new idea, he wanted to fuse precaution Immortal Gu into the immortal killer move vajra shell.

And now, he had already designed the killer move, he just needed to test it.

Chapter 1347: Chai Clan Has Human Smoke

He started.

The first step, Fang Yuan turned into a divination tortoise.

The second step, he started to activate a large number of mortal Gu, followed by vajra thought Immortal Gu and more mortal Gu.

The third step, and the most important one, he activated precaution Immortal Gu.

Puff!

Fang Yuan turned into a divination tortoise, spitting out a huge amount of blood. In his immortal aperture, large numbers of mortal Gu were destroyed, but thankfully, precaution Immortal Gu was sturdy and did not get damaged.

Fang Yuan's head was dizzy, his immortal killer move failed, his organs were damaged, he suffered heavy injuries.

Thankfully, he had transformed into a divination tortoise, an ancient desolate beast, he had a tough body and incredible recovery speed. If he did this with a human body, his injuries would have been worse, his organs and intestines might have disintegrated on the spot.

"Why did this happen?" Fang Yuan was dazed.

This was different from what he conceptualized.

In fact, before precaution Immortal Gu could use its power, this immortal killer move broke apart.

Fang Yuan did not expect this.

Fang Yuan had used affection Immortal Gu and other wisdom path Immortal Gu to deduce this modified immortal killer move, such a severe error should not have occurred.

This was truly a huge blow to him.

After Fang Yuan's injuries healed, he calmed down and looked at the killer move.

After several deductions, Fang Yuan was even more troubled: "There are no problems, though?"

Suddenly, he had a flash of inspiration: "I understand!"

Fang Yuan instantly understood where the problem was.

He had misunderstood precaution Immortal Gu.

When precaution Immortal Gu activated, it continued to expend red date immortal essence, but it could only unleash its power after ten breaths. It did not activate at the tenth breath, but at the eleventh breath. Because of this small mistake, the entire immortal killer move failed and Fang Yuan suffered a backlash.

"To think that the problem was here, it was truly a blind spot!"

"It seems that I need to add some time path Gu worms to make up for the time difference." Fang Yuan's time path attainment level was ordinary, it had never risen much. Because he had never encountered any time path dream realm.

However, he had Hei Fan's true inheritance and wisdom path deduction methods, it could make up for some of his weaknesses.

But because of this, the deduction could not be completed instantly.

One day passed, Fang Yuan did not rest.

Two days passed, Fang Yuan was still deducing.

Three days passed, Wu clan's Immortal Gu House had already completed most of its journey.

Fang Yuan's deduction finally had some progress.

After his qualitative advancement, his future deductions went smoothly.

Southern Border, Human Smoke Mountain Range.

This place had the most living mortals in Southern Border. Villages after villages were seen on the mountains here. On some mountain peaks, there were even several villages, they were neighbors.

This was a bountiful sight.

The population had multiplied to its limit, there were a vast number of humans here. Of course, in terms of battle strength, a Gu Immortal would be able to wipe this place out, no mortal could resist their unstoppable might.

And at the center of this mountain range, it was the political core of all the villages — Human Smoke Mountain.

The base of one of the super clans, Chai clan!

The person who created Chai clan was called Chai Fu, he had left his mark in human history.

During his era, he was the number one person in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, he cultivated fire path along with earth path, because he had gained a lot of insight from reading \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, he had a human path killer move. During his later years, he chose this place to create Chai clan, after modifying the mountain range, he created Human Smoke Mountain.

In fact, most Gu Immortal experts and great experts would read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

A true inheritance of human path was hidden within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, this was indeed the first true inheritance in the history of the Gu Master world.

It had a unique inheritance method.

Normal inheritances were like Hei Fan's true inheritance and Bai Xiang's true inheritance.

But Ren Zu's human path true inheritance was just one book, \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it was information. The profundities of human path were concealed in this information, and whatever a Gu Immortal learned would depend on their affinity and talent.

Everyone had different gains, after all, the benevolent see benevolence, the wise see wisdom. But every Immortal Venerable and Demon Venerable had their gains, and those were huge gains. For example, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had created all living being's luck and heaven and earth luck after reading \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

After Chai Fu read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, he left behind the human path method that he learned after death, passing it down to his Chai clan descendants.

Precisely so, Chai clan's development strategy was different from other super clans. Chai clan focused on increasing population, to increase the number of mortals.

As for other super forces, they basically only focused on a portion of their clansmen and allowed them to develop and grow in the five regions. These clansmen would have the bloodline of certain authoritative figures in the super force, they were also called the main bloodline.

And a portion of the people would stay inside their blessed lands or grotto-heavens and would not go outside. These people were often the branch bloodlines. Only when unexpected mishaps occur and the main bloodline dies out, or when a ruling figure dies without an inheritor, would the branch bloodlines take over.

Chai clan expanded the population, but they did not have Chai clan bloodline.

If any other clan did this, they were courting trouble. Spending great effort to nurture mortals of other surnames, with greater population, more Gu Masters would emerge among them. These Gu Masters would not have the clan's bloodline, their loyalty was greatly reduced, they had no value in being nurtured to become Gu Immortals. If they became Gu Immortals on their own, it would cause conflict between them and the main clan.

But Chai clan was different.

They nurtured so many mortals, but these mortals all had low aptitudes, there were few Gu Masters among them, not to mention Gu Immortals.

In contrast, highly talented people continuously emerged from Chai clan's own descendants, there were many who were talented enough to be nurtured into Gu Immortals.

This formed a clear contrast to the other super forces.

According to their conjectures, Chai clan's abnormal situation was likely due to the human path method that Chai Fu had left behind.

However, no matter which generation it was, even though Chai clan had lots of genius descendants, because of limited resources, these Gu Immortal seeds eventually remained as only rank four or five Gu Masters.

There was a need to talk about Southern Border's geography at this point.

Southern Border's biggest features, other than mountains, were the three great rivers.

Red dragon river, jade dragon river, and yellow dragon river, each of them passed through the whole of Southern Border, cutting it up into many segments.

Red dragon river started from the extreme northwest, moving east towards the south, all the way until Southern Border's extreme southeast.

Jade dragon river started above it, it had a downward slope if a bird's-eye view over the region was used.

Yellow dragon river had the shape of the character '几', there was a protrusion at the top, it was far more steep than jade dragon river.

Jade dragon river and yellow dragon river did not intersect, but red dragon river intersected with both jade dragon river and yellow dragon river[1].

At the point of intersection between red dragon river and yellow dragon river, it was Wu clan's territory, towards the northeast shore of the huge whirlpool there was Corpse Emperor Yu Ding Tian.

As for the intersection between red dragon river and jade dragon river, the huge whirlpool there was dozens of times as large. Natural essence was incredible dense there, at the center of the whirlpool, there were huge numbers of spirit springs, tens of thousands of them. These spirit springs were not stable, almost every breath of time, dozens would be destroyed.

Thus, a great amount of natural essence poured onto the river banks.

When Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable traveled to this place, he had once commented that throughout the whole of Southern Border, this place had the greatest density of primeval energy.

Over there, the air was filled with primeval energy, large amounts of resources were produced, on par with grotto-heavens and blessed lands.

And at this place, the bases of three super forces were gathered!

For example, red dragon river and jade dragon river formed a cross shape, with the center being the spiral whirlpool. Chai clan's Human Smoke Mountain was north of it, Ba clan was south, while Xia clan was to its east.

For the last three days, Chai clan's discussion hall had been in chaos.

Now was no exception.

Chai clan's first supreme elder sat before everyone as his gaze flickered, showing a hesitant expression.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan had sent him a letter. In the letter, Fang Yuan, who was Wu Yi Hai, represented Wu clan and was willing to work with Chai clan to attack Xia clan and Ba clan.

This was an incredibly important matter, Chai clan's first supreme elder had to gather the clan's Gu Immortals and discuss about it.

The discussion hall's chaos was due to this.

"We cannot attack Ba clan and Xia clan! Wu clan's intention is just to make use of us to get rid of their external pressure. The moment we attack, our Chai clan will have to face two super forces at once. If these two super forces ignore Wu clan and turn around to target us, we will be on the losing end, we will not be able to overturn it." A Chai clan Gu Immortal shouted loudly, standing at the center of the discussion hall.

He had just finished his words when a Gu Immortal at a corner proposed: "We can choose to attack one clan. Even though Wu clan gave the request of fighting both clans, we can negotiate about this matter. This will not determine what we do, after all."

"Sigh... the matter is severe. Our Chai clan has so many mortals around, if we fight, the other party just needs one Gu Immortal to wipe out all of our mortals, we will suffer huge losses." An elderly Gu Immortal from Chai clan sighed, he was very apprehensive.

Because of the human path method's limitation, these humans could not leave Human Smoke Mountain Range. This way, they needed an immortal Gu formation or an Immortal Gu House to defend the place.

"Precisely so, we need to fight for more resources."

"That's right! Our Chai clan's advantage is that we have a human path method to allow geniuses to appear in our descendants. But we do not have enough resources to nurture them. Once we chase away one clan or even two, we will gain a vast amount of resources, we will become the number one force in Southern Border in no time."

These were the arguments of the side that wanted to fight.

Chai clan's first supreme elder remained silent, after a while, he looked at a Gu Immortal in the hall, asking: "You Yan, tell us about your view."

[1] Yes the author's geography is incredibly messed up. Back

Chapter 1348: Easing the Situation

The discussion hall became quiet, everyone's gazes turned to this Gu Immortal.

This Gu Immortal looked young and had a normal appearance, it was not outstanding, but he was an important Gu Immortal in Chai clan, he was the trusted and capable aide of Chai clan's first supreme elder.

Chai You Yan, who was an information path Gu Immortal, thought for a while before saying: "The things I consider might be different from everyone. These last days, I have been pondering over Wu Yi Hai."

"Wu Yong went missing and is presumably dead, regardless of whether this is true or who the culprit was, Wu Yi Hai is currently the leader of Wu clan. I am thinking about his personality, and how sincere he actually is."

"We all know about Wu Yi Hai's origin. We know too little about him, he did not grow up in Southern Border after all."

"Hmm, continue." Chai clan's first supreme elder showed interest in his eyes.

Chai You Yan smiled before continuing: "Actually, we know about the information regarding Wu Yi Hai already, I will skip that. From this information, we can more or less understand this person's attitude and personality. I will mention something that everyone ignored."

"Oh? We all ignored something?"

Chai You Yan rubbed his nose: "I mean that letter. In Wu Yi Hai's letter, he wanted to ally with our clan to attack Ba clan and Xia clan. He did not choose either Ba clan or Xia clan, he chose to target them both."

"Wu clan has always acted so domineering, isn't this their usual style of doing things?" Some Chai clan Gu Immortals did not understand.

"No no no. Wu Yi Hai is different." Chai You Yan shook his head: "We can tell from how he dealt with Frosty Peak and the agreement with Mountain Moving Old Monster. His actions are similar to lone cultivators, after all, how long has it been since he returned to Wu clan?"

"Wu Yi Hai lacks the dominating disposition of Wu clan, but he has the astuteness of lone cultivators, he knows how to make agreements, from what I see, he is talented as a part of the righteous path."

"Why did he list Ba clan and Xia clan as his targets? Like what was mentioned earlier, why did he not choose one of them and seek peace with the other? Because when we ally with Wu clan, if we choose one of them to attack, would the other stay still? They would definitely work together and resist both Wu clan and us!"

Chai clan's Gu Immortals heard this and nodded, agreeing with Chai You Yan.

Chai clan, Ba clan, Xia clan, these three clans were gathered around the red and jade rivers, their relationship was complex. If one clan became strong, the other two would join up to resist it.

The three were in a power balance, restraining each other, this was also why Chai clan had never made any progress after so many years of development.

If Chai clan worked with Wu clan, this balance would shift, would Ba clan and Xia clan not cooperate?

Thus, Fang Yuan directly listed both of them as his targets. Because he knew that it was bound to happen!

"This means that Wu Yi Hai has quite good foresight. Since he suggested for us to cooperate with him, he must have made many preparations. We do not need to worry about Wu clan toying with us." Someone said.

Chai You Yan nodded: "What I want to say is, Wu Yi Hai has a lot of talent in politics. From all these details, I can see that he has a lot of sincerity in this cooperation."

"The truth is, our Chai clan needs to act."

"After developing until now, we finally suppressed Xia clan and Ba clan, it was not easy, this is the hard work of countless generations, mixed in with some luck."

"Once Ba clan or Xia clan devours more resources, their foundations would grow, our advantage will be gone."

"Of course, we need to be careful of Wu clan as well if we work together."

"As for how we will fight, and how we will restrict the extent of this battle? That will be first supreme elder's decision."

"But at the very least, we need to send some Gu Immortals to attack. We cannot let Ba clan and Xia clan expand their territories so easily, right?"

His words were met with the nodding of Chai clan's Gu Immortals.

At almost the same time.

Southern Border, Myriad Snake Mountain, Chi clan's base.

Chi clan's first supreme elder held a letter Gu and remained silent.

Chi clan was at the extreme west of Southern Border, southwest of it was Yang clan, and towards its east was Qiao clan.

Chi clan bordered on these two clans, but Yang clan was farther from its base and had a longer border with it.

Making friends with those far away and making enemies with those close by, this was a common foreign policy.

Thus, Chi clan and Yang clan had poor relationships. Yang clan's Ghost Hand Mountain was at the source of yellow dragon river, it had abundant resources and was a strategic location, Yang clan Gu Immortals mostly cultivated soul path, they had incredible battle strength and was a threat to Chi clan.

In the past, Yang clan and Chi clan had many conflicts, this had accumulated throughout history.

Towards the east of Yang clan, all the way along yellow dragon river, was Wu clan's territory.

Actually, Wu clan and Chi clan were close by. Even though they did not border each other, Qiao clan and Chi clan did.

Qiao clan was heavily supported by a Wu clan first supreme elder of a certain generation. Qiao clan was at the central area of Southern Border, bordering Ba clan, Xia clan, and Chi clan, it could even restrain the southwest Yang clan.

Chi clan and Qiao clan had conflicts, but everyone knew that Qiao clan was Wu clan's guard dog, thus, Chi clan's and Wu clan's relationship was good or bad at times, depending on the situation.

If there was one phrase to describe Chi clan's and Wu clan's relationship, ambiguous would be a rather appropriate term.

Not long ago, Chi clan had found trouble with Wu clan. But inside the super Gu formation of Yi Tian Mountain, Chi clan worked with Wu clan, creating the immortal opportunity business.

"Wu Yi Hai, you are giving me a tough problem." In his study room, Chi clan first supreme elder Chi Qu You sighed deeply.

Fang Yuan had requested to work with Chi clan and deal with Yang clan.

Chi Qu You was moved, because he knew this was a good opportunity. This chance was rare even in his lifetime.

Any force needed to grow larger. Trying to annex Yang clan's resources, even if they could not succeed, would weaken Yang clan, this was something beneficial to Chi clan no matter what.

Chi clan had a lot of spare energy for this.

Not only because Chi clan's base was located far from the action, but also because Chi clan specialized in Gu formations. By setting up many immortal Gu formations, Chi clan's base and all their resource points had incredible defense.

Chi clan had little to worry about. They also had two Immortal Gu Houses, and don't forget, Chi Qu You was a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Wu Yong had died, this news sent Southern Border into chaos.

In this chaotic situation, what would Chi clan do, Chi Qu You needed to decide quickly and resolutely!

Several days later, in the super Gu formation, Fang Yuan came out of his seclusion.

He had a bit of joy on his face.

His closed cultivation bore fruit, he had completed the deduction of vajra shell and tested it several times.

And during these few days, the situation in Southern Border had undergone a huge change.

Chai clan sent Gu Immortals to the river and showed a threatening stance. Ba clan and Xia clan had to gather a portion of their strength and defend themselves.

Chi clan's Gu Immortals directly invaded Yang clan's territory. The two clans were neighbors for so long, it was easy to find an excuse to do so.

Both sides were fighting near their mountain range.

Chi clan's great expert was very active, he brought an Immortal Gu House and attacked personally. This made Yang clan very nervous, they had to send their Immortal Gu House and many Gu Immortals to face him. Yang clan had no rank eight Gu Immortal, they were in a passive state.

Other than that, Luo clan, Tie clan, and Yi clan also made their movements.

Because Fang Yuan sent these clans letters as well. Of course, the contents were all different from Chai clan and Chi clan.

After all, these four clans were too close to each other, they were all towards the east of Southern Border.

But even so, these clans' movements had attracted the attention of Hou clan and Yao clan, they were drawn away. Because they knew that even though these clans were unlikely to strike, they were afraid of taking that chance, they had to defend against it.

As for Shang clan, this clan had always scrupulously followed neutrality, even though Fang Yuan sent a letter, they replied instantly, rejecting his suggestion.

Because of this sudden change, Wu clan's and Qiao clan's dangerous situation had become much more relaxed.

Wu clan's and Qiao clan's Gu Immortals were very shocked at this result.

Even though Fang Yuan just sent a few letters, to be able to convince super forces to act, it was not a simple thing. Especially when the letter had to be very precise on the amount of resources Wu clan was willing to give up to express their sincerity.

Fang Yuan dealt with this perfectly, it was far beyond many people's imaginations.

Very few people knew about the content of his letters, but everyone knew that these letters moved many Gu Immortals in these super forces. This allowed Wu clan and Qiao clan to have an opportunity to retaliate!

"It seems that my skills have not fallen much." In the five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan was once the leader of an organization, during the five regions chaotic war, the political situation was far more chaotic, all five regions were linked together, all sorts of deceptions, schemes, betrayal were endless.

The current political chaos was just surrounding Wu clan and Qiao clan, as well as the western part of Southern Border.

It was not too complex in Fang Yuan's opinion.

He did not need to be careful, he could directly target the problem.

"Wu clan's Immortal Gu House is finally arriving?" Fang Yuan received more information.

Originally, the Immortal Gu House was supposed to move earlier, but a mishap occurred midway and it was stalled for some time, no matter who did it or what their intention was, Fang Yuan had to wait an extra day before this Immortal Gu House arrived.

"It seems I need to leave this place now." This dream realm gave Fang Yuan an incredible boost, many things happened during this period, Fang Yuan felt a bit of unwillingness to leave this treasure.

Chapter 1349: Fang Yuan Wants To Kill White Rabbit

Fang Yuan started to settle the matters that piled up while he was in closed cultivation.

"Lady White Rabbit wants to see me? For what?" Fang Yuan asked Wu An using information path methods.

Soon, Fang Yuan understood Lady White Rabbit's intention.

"Not seeing her, get her to leave." Fang Yuan rejected mercilessly.

Wu clan's Immortal Gu House would arrive in a day.

Fang Yuan was not going to bring Lady White Rabbit with him, he needed a chess piece to stay here. Even if she was not in the super Gu formation, having one outside was fine too.

Of course this carried huge risks, after all, Lady White Rabbit's and Wu Yi Hai's 'relationship' was quite close, everyone knew about it.

But chess pieces needed to display their worth. When Fang Yuan took in Lady White Rabbit, it was not because of her beauty or love, he just wanted to extract all of her value.

"Even with one day left, I cannot waste it, I might be able to gain something in the dream realm."

But unfortunately, Fang Yuan still only met with absurd dream realms.

It was a real pity.

During this final period, he kept meeting absurd dream realms, his luck was quite bad. If they were realistic dream realms, he would at least obtain some growth.

"I heard that Qiao clan has many realistic dream realms. It is a pity... those demonic path Gu Immortals have no methods to use, but they are able to encounter realistic dream realms."

Fang Yuan could not go to Qiao clan. It was their territory, if he exposed his method of exploring dream realms, it would be a huge problem to Fang Yuan.

At this moment, Qiao clan's area.

"One more day before we leave, your dream realm exploration is going to end. Make good use of your time, also, our Qiao clan is very willing to purchase the dream path materials that you find." Qiao Bo transmitted to Fairy Miao Yin and the other demonic path Gu Immortals.

"No need for more explorations, we can end now." Fairy Miao Yin smiled at Qiao Bo.

Qiao Bo was dazed.

He had brought Fairy Miao Yin here to explore the dream realm many times, but this was the first time he saw Fairy Miao Yin smiling at him so deeply.

At once, his heart jumped, he showed a dazed expression.

But soon, his body shook.

A soft sound echoed.

Qiao Bo's pupils shrunk to pin size, he looked down at his chest.

There, a hand with sharp fingernails had pierced through his back, directly destroying his heart, a cold frost was also spreading around his injury.

"You, how dare you..." Qiao Bo did not finish his words, he lost his life and turned into an ice statue.

Qiao Bo died!

Behind him, Bai Ning Bing drew back her hand expressionlessly.

In the air, crystal shards were scattering.

Her hand was white as snow, the blood traces were all removed along with the frost.

"The time is now, let's begin." The third Gu Immortal walked out, her appearance changed as she revealed her true form.

Who else could it be but Hei Lou Lan?

"Is Lord Wu Yi Hai really unwilling to meet me?" Lady White Rabbit had teary eyes as she looked at Wu An.

Wu An sighed, shaking his head: "Leave, there is no rush, you will meet again in the future. As long as you manage the immortal opportunity business well, maybe Lord Wu Yi Hai might reward you in the future."

"Manage it well? Hehe!" Lady White Rabbit's eyes suddenly turned black, a cold light was shining in her dark eyes.

Seeing this change, Wu An became alert, he took a step back: "Lady White Rabbit, what are you doing? Don't act rashly."

Lady White Rabbit's voice changed too: "Don't talk about White Rabbit! I am not that weak fool, blindly loving this cruel and heartless man. Remember, I am Black Tigress."

"Hmph, what Black Tigress, it is time to teach you people a lesson. Even though my Wu clan is in a difficult spot, you minor characters should forget about... urgh!" Before Wu An finished his words, his angry face turned into one of extreme fear.

He found that he could not move, not only that, his body and soul were melting, turning into black water on the ground.

"What, what killer move is this? When was I hit?!"

At this time, Black Tigress' cold voice entered Wu An's ears: "Enjoy it, this was meant for Wu Yi Hai. It is a pity I did not get to see him."

Once she said that, Wu An completely melted into a puddle of black water.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Right after Wu An had died from Black Tigress' powerful killer move, the super Gu formation started to shake intensely.

The super Gu formation was under attack!

"What is going on?" The righteous path Gu Immortals here immediately reacted.

"Someone is attacking the Gu formation, they are inside the Gu formation!" Soon, Chi Gui, who was the leader of Chi clan here. found the problem and informed the righteous path Gu Immortals.

The immortals' hearts sank.

The super Gu formation had incredibly strong defense, but it was split into inside and outside. Attacking the super Gu formation from the inside and from the outside were two different situations.

Undeniably, attacking it from the inside would be much more destructive.

"The problem is at Qiao clan's area." The righteous path Gu Immortals near Qiao clan's area quickly transmitted.

"Damn it, I said that this immortal opportunity business was going to create problems. Qiao clan is toying with fire! See what happened!!" Ba Quan Feng shouted, after all, Ba clan did not participate in this immortal opportunity business.

Once he said that, many righteous path Gu Immortals went silent.

"No need to worry, even in this situation, my Chi clan ancestor had prepared against this, this super Gu formation has formations inside formations, for a total of four layers. Just these demonic path Gu Immortals cannot break our outermost layer." Chi Gui tried to raise the morale and relieve his own awkwardness. Because Chi clan was one of the instigators of the immortal opportunity business.

"That's right, they are just some rats." The righteous path Gu Immortals calmed down.

But at this moment.

Boom!

Several loud explosions occurred as the Gu formation shook again, the intensity was many times stronger than before. Many Gu worms died, quite a few Immortal Gu were destroyed.

"What is going on, what is going on?!"

Chi Gui was shocked: "They actually found our formation core? Oh no, the other party came prepared, they are not attacking abruptly."

"They are attacking from both inside and outside, the outside of the Gu formation was hit by a strong attack earlier!"

"Stop them!"

"Quickly activate the Gu formations."

"Send some people to the site, exterminate those demonic path scoundrels!"

"Did Wu clan's and Qiao clan's Gu Immortals all die? Is anyone there?!"

The righteous path Gu Immortals transmitted to each other, it was a chaotic scene.

"What is going on?" In the hall at Wu clan's area, Fang Yuan's brows were locked, he was observing the situation that had just occurred using the Gu formation.

He had just practised his killer move, the event happened too quickly, he was caught unprepared.

Information was transmitted to Fang Yuan from the Gu formation. Lady White Rabbit's transformation and the killing of Wu An, he learned about everything.

"Lady White Rabbit is a traitor, she seemed to have become another person! And her target was actually me." Fang Yuan frowned even deeper now.

He immediately decided to go ahead and kill White Rabbit to take revenge for Wu An.

Not just because of Wu Yi Hai's identity, but also because Fang Yuan needed to maintain the stability of the super Gu formation, he needed to kill Lady White Rabbit.

"To think that there was such a huge slip-up, Yi Hai, my side of the Gu formation is completely out of control, come lend me a hand!"

Qiao Si Liu transmitted to Fang Yuan a cry for help and also the scene of Bai Ning Bing killing Qiao Bo.

Receiving this information, Fang Yuan's intention of acting was dispersed!

"Bai Ning Bing? Hei Lou Lan! Why are they here? I get it, this is the act of Shadow Sect!" Fang Yuan's heart shook.

He stayed on the spot, his eyes bursting with bright light.

After discovering Shadow Sect, even though he had killing intent, his thoughts of going out vanished.

What a joke!

Shadow Sect had a rank eight existence.

Fang Yuan saw this from the battle of Reverse Flow River.

Who knew where that Purple Mountain True Monarch was. He might be close by, waiting to attack Wu Yi Hai if he came out!

"Even though I have the immortal killer move reverse flow protection seal, which can defend against rank eight existences, once I use it, my identity will be exposed. Since Shadow Sect sent Lady White Rabbit to kill me, undoubtedly, they did not discover that I am impersonating Wu Yi Hai. Otherwise, they would not send just Lady White Rabbit."

"What to do?"

Fang Yuan went into rapid contemplation.

Using his wisdom path methods, thoughts moved rapidly in Fang Yuan's mind, raging like a storm.

"Shadow Sect's intention is obvious, they want to save Spectral Soul's main body."

"Shadow Sect must have their trump cards, I need to quietly observe for now! This super Gu formation is not a joke, using this super Gu formation, we can defend against the attacks of rank eight Gu Immortals. I should not expose myself."

Fang Yuan quickly made his plan.

As for Qiao Si Liu?

You can die for all I care!

"Yi Hai, come quickly." Qiao Si Liu urged again.

Fang Yuan had a cold expression, immediately rejecting: "Hang on, I have some problems here. Wu An was murdered by Lady White Rabbit, I cannot spare this murderer!!"

"What? Be careful yourself." Qiao Si Liu was shocked, but she still gave Fang Yuan some words of concern, not knowing that he had already abandoned her in his mind.

Qiao Si Liu was facing against Fairy Miao Yin, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing.

She was a rank seven Gu Immortal, similar to Fairy Miao Yin, while Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing were rank six.

Thus, in Qiao Si Liu's perspective, the situation was not out of control. Her gaze was focused on Fairy Miao Yin: "You are all finished, the super Gu formation has already been activated, you are all trapped here, surrender now and be my clan's slave Gu Immortals, you might be able to survive."

"Hehehe." Fairy Miao Yin laughed: "Is that so?"

Chapter 1350: Grey Night Breaks The Formation

Right at this time, an intensely strong aura burst out from outside the super Gu formation.

Soon, the righteous path Gu Immortals controlling the Gu formation noticed.

"There is a strong aura ahead!"

"Such intense aura, so, so powerful! A rank eight Gu Immortal?"

The righteous path Gu Immortals were gasping.

"Is it Purple Mountain True Monarch?" Fang Yuan, who was inside the hall, watched attentively.

"No, it is not a Gu Immortal, it is an immemorial desolate beast... ah, it is actually?!"

Before he finished his words, bam—!

The entire super Gu formation was faced with an unprecedentedly intense attack.

The entire Gu formation shook intensely, the halls created inside the Gu formation were destroyed, they crumbled and disintegrated.

At once, it felt like doomsday.

The entire Gu formation was cracked open, but there were not many injuries in the righteous path Gu Immortals.

This was the difference between a Gu formation and a killer move.

Even though Gu formations were the killer moves of formation path, after a Gu formation is set up, it works based on the Gu worms and the environment. When they are destroyed, the Gu Immortal would suffer a less intense backlash.

Of course, ancient battle formations were different. Once ancient battle formations were destroyed, the Gu Immortals would suffer severe backlashes, especially the main controller of the formation.

"Cough, cough." Dust and smoke was clouding the place.

The hall that Fang Yuan was in had completely collapsed, the corners were turning back into mortal Gu, dead Gu worms poured down like rain.

A huge hole was created in the super Gu formation, the dream realm that was completely concealed earlier was now exposed.

Many righteous path Gu Immortals stood by the opening, looking outside blankly.

Over there, a huge figure was rampaging.

It was a human shaped immemorial desolate beast, it stood on both legs and had two huge monstrous claws, its hair was messy and its body was black like ink.

"Gu Immortals, so many Gu Immortals, I want to eat, I want to eat you all! After eating you, I will be closer to being human." This human shaped immemorial desolate beast growled in a low tone, extremely excited.

"This, this is..." A righteous path Gu Immortal pointed at the immemorial desolate beast, stammering in a shocked state.

"Zuo Ye Hui!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth subconsciously, feeling great pressure.

The moment he saw this immemorial desolate beast, Fang Yuan felt like he was in the dream, but the shouting of the Gu Immortals around him, the destroyed halls, and the super Gu formation that was breaking apart reminded him that this was not a dream.

Fang Yuan had not expected Zuo Ye Hui to come here!

This legendary immemorial desolate beast had caused too much suffering and deaths in Southern Border. All of the righteous path Gu Immortals in Southern Border knew about it.

With the appearance of Zuo Ye Hui, the hearts of the righteous path members wavered, their morale fell to rock bottom.

This was a powerful existence on par with rank eight Gu Immortals. Especially after the super Gu formation was destroyed, how could these righteous path rank six and seven Gu Immortals defend against it?

With their bodies?

In this huge world of the five regions, there were only two people who could resist rank eight as rank seven, they were Feng Jiu Ge and Liu Guan Yi.

"We need to hold on! Don't panic, our Gu formation has four layers! That was just the outermost fourth layer which broke. Start to move, come into the next layer of the Gu formation." At the crucial moment, Chi Gui spoke up.

He was the leader of Chi clan in this place, this super Gu formation was created by Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You, Chi Gui naturally knew some information that others did not.

As expected, the Gu formation activated and shined with a bright light. The collapsing stopped, and the outer formation was completely abandoned, a new line of defense appeared inside.

The third layer of the Gu formation appeared before Zuo Ye Hui.

It did not cover the entire dream realm, it was visible, but most of the dream realm was still concealed by the Gu formation.

The righteous path Gu Immortals quickly went inside.

Fang Yuan was not an exception.

He had to, Shadow Sect did not know about Wu Yi Hai's true identity, otherwise, Shadow Sect, which had a wisdom path rank eight Gu Immortal, would not send just Lady White Rabbit to assassinate Fang Yuan.

The enemy was in the open while he was hidden, this was a clear advantage. At the same time, Fang Yuan had another advantage, that was the Immortal Gu House.

An Immortal Gu House from Wu clan was on the way.

Most Gu formations could not move, but Immortal Gu Houses could!

And the power of Immortal Gu Houses could increase the more immortal essence was used, they could resist rank eight Gu Immortals.

With an Immortal Gu House to defend and escort him, Fang Yuan would have a greater chance to leave this place.

"But earlier, Wu clan's Immortal Gu House was delayed along the way due to an unexpected mishap, was it Shadow Sect?" Fang Yuan considered this as his thoughts turned dark.

"Tsk, so troublesome." Bai Ning Bing looked at the Gu formation's third layer of defense, frowning.

"This is hard to destroy." Hei Lou Lan sighed.

At this time, Ying Wu Xie smiled coldly, transmitting to them: "Don't worry, just dodge."

Fairy Miao Yin's, Bai Ning Bing's, and Hei Lou Lan's bodies shook as they quickly flew back and retreated.

Roar!

At the next moment, Zuo Ye Hui roared and emitted a thunderously loud wave.

Its voice burst out and created a sonic wave, pushing out the surrounding air and uprooting the trees and rocks, whipping up a storm.

Next, Zuo Ye Hui breathed in deeply, its stomach bulged up.

Its entire body expanded to double its size!

Next, it opened its bloodthirsty mouth filled with sharp teeth, and a huge beam of light shot out fiercely.

The grey colored beam of light shot out extremely quickly, in the blink of an eye, it landed on the third layer of the Gu formation.

There was a creepy silence.

The third layer of the Gu formation was hit by the grey beam of light, as it was dyed grey rapidly.

Earlier, Zuo Ye Hui had attacked the super Gu formation as well. The first few attempts were just trials, but the previous time was also the killer move grey night, together with Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, and Fairy Miao Yin, they destroyed the fourth layer of the Gu formation.

Most of the righteous path Gu Immortals did not manage to see these attacks clearly.

But this time, they witnessed it firsthand, they saw how terrifying Zuo Ye Hui was!

As if heaven and earth became still, monochrome color enveloped the place, time seemed to be moving slower.

For one breath of time.

Boom—!

Another thunderous explosion resounded in the world, the immortals' eardrums were bursting.

The entire world shook, the third layer of the Gu formation was ripped apart, as if the previous attack was going to be played out again.

The righteous path Gu Immortals were pale, they instilled their immortal essence into the Gu formation desperately.

When the tremors ended, the third layer of the Gu formation was only half destroyed, it still existed!

This was a super Gu formation personally created by rank eight Gu Immortal Chi Qu You, together with a vast number of Immortal Gu and mortal Gu from Southern Border's righteous path forces, it was displaying its power now.

It managed to block the signature move of legendary immemorial desolate beast Zuo Ye Hui!

There were no injuries or deaths among the righteous path Gu Immortals.

"I am actually still alive!" Someone almost cried from joy.

"This is Zuo Ye Hui's signature method, immortal killer move — Grey Night! We actually defended against it!!" Someone shouted loudly.

Chi Gui's forehead was full of sweat, he said: "This is the super Gu formation that my clan's first supreme elder set up, why would it be destroyed? If not for them attacking from both inside and outside earlier, the fourth layer might still be around."

"Immortal killer move grey night, it is different from the one in my dream realm, was its form changed? After so many years, grey night must have been modified. Did Zuo Ye Hui modify it? Or did it have help? Is this help from Shadow Sect? Strange! If they had Zuo Ye Hui as a tool, why did Shadow Sect not use it when they were refining sovereign immortal fetus Gu? Was it because they could not control it? Or is this all because of that rank eight Gu Immortal?" Fang Yuan fell into deep contemplation.

Fairy Miao Yin, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, they came to the super Gu formation again.

Looking at the damaged third layer of the super Gu formation, they were not shocked nor disappointed.

Because they did not come alone, there was Ying Wu Xie, as well as many demonic path Gu Immortals and lone immortals.

Shadow Sect lacked manpower, but not resources.

Normally, demonic path Gu Immortals and lone cultivators lacked cultivation resources, they would pursue resources over their whole lives.

Purple Mountain True Monarch endured the huge costs of spending resources to recruit a batch of demonic path and lone immortals.

Humans die for wealth and birds die for food, money makes the world go round.

Of course, these Southern Border Gu Immortals were not stupid, only after Zuo Ye Hui appeared and used grey night did they start to follow Ying Wu Xie and show up.

On the other hand, this showed that Shadow Sect had a good grasp on timing and human emotions.

From these demonic path and lone immortals' perspectives, not only was there the wisdom path rank eight great expert Purple Mountain True Monarch, there was also the legendary immemorial desolate beast Zuo Ye Hui, this battle was decided already, they were going to win.

"It is all as Purple Mountain True Monarch predicted, we will attack using these holes in the Gu formation. Whoever can kill enemies and expand the hole would get several times the reward!" Ying Wu Xie shouted, Shadow Sect's side started to clamor as they attacked the super Gu formation.

The righteous path side also reacted.

"Quickly, seal the hole."

"We cannot let them in."

"I need time to activate the second layer of the Gu formation, everyone, try to stall and fight for time." Chi Gui called out.

"Zuo Ye Hui has already used grey night twice, this is the limit. It needs to rest for a while, it is time to teach these demonic path scoundrels a lesson!!" Ba De shouted.

Fang Yuan squinted, he had been assessing Zuo Ye Hui, he also saw that after Zuo Ye Hui used grey night, it was in a state of exhaustion, it panted as it remained on the spot, unmoving.

This made Fang Yuan feel slightly relieved.

There were so many Southern Border Gu Immortals here, many people were familiar with history, they knew a lot about Zuo Ye Hui. After all, every time Zuo Ye Hui appeared, it would cause disaster in Southern Border, lots of Southern Border Gu Immortals would need to work together, defending against and battling it.

Southern Border's righteous path super clans had accurate information about Zuo Ye Hui from their historical records.

Chapter 1351: Chaotic Battle

"Kill!"

"Charge!"

"Block them, we need more time."

"Don't be afraid, so what if this is Zuo Ye Hui, the Gu formation is around, we can last until reinforcements arrive from our clans."

Shadow Sect attacked, while Southern Border's righteous path defended desperately.

The third layer of the Gu formation was already half destroyed, cracks could be seen everywhere, it was of little help to the righteous path Gu Immortals, a chaotic battle ensued.

Rumble...

Unceasing explosions, the collisions of wind, fire, water, and lightning, unfolded like fireworks in the sky.

There was no probing, Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves were used from the start, the battle became heated almost instantly.

"You cannot defend this place." Fairy Miao Yin smiled as she flew in the air.

Qiao Si Liu was in front of her.

Qiao Si Liu was silent, the situation had changed too quickly, earlier, the righteous path had the advantage, but now they were at a disadvantage. Even with the super Gu formation, they could only defend passively, they lost their initiative. For the righteous path Gu Immortals, their only chance was to wait for reinforcements.

"Who are you people? You can actually mobilize the legendary immemorial desolate beast Zuo Ye Hui." Qiao Si Liu asked, paying close attention.

Fairy Miao Yin laughed: "The ones to end your life."

Her killing intent rose, a crescent moon shadow appeared in her eyes.

Immortal killer move — Curved Moon!

This was a sight based attack, because the aura was completely concealed, once it was used, one would not be able to react in time, it was very difficult to guard against.

Qiao Si Liu was hit immediately.

But soon, on the surface of her dress and skin, jade green light shone. Within the faint light, long willow branches formed, it was like ribbons made of branches coiling around her, she resembled a fairy from heaven.

Swish swish swish.

The jade willow branches were not just defensive, they quickly flew towards Fairy Miao Yin with impressive mobility.

Fairy Miao Yin was stunned, she quickly retreated.

She avoided the willow branches but could not defend against the shadow below them. One of the shadows shot up like a venomous snake, slapping Fairy Miao Yin's body.

"This is... an attached move?" Fairy Miao Yin could not conceal the shock on her beautiful face.

Attached moves were like consecutive moves, split moves, and variation moves, they were special techniques in activating killer moves, they were hard to master for normal people.

What was an attached move?

Normally speaking, it meant two different immortal killer moves, one primary and one secondary. Like the willow branch attack that Qiao Si Liu used, it was the primary move. The shadows below the branches were the secondary move, attached to the primary move.

When the primary move was used, the secondary move would have a certain chance of getting activated as well, unleashing its effects.

Fairy Miao Yin did not expect that Qiao Si Liu would actually master such a difficult technique like attached move, she was caught off guard and was hit by the willow branch's shadow.

A long wound appeared as blood started to flow out.

On Fairy Miao Yin's beautiful face, it was really apparent.

Qiao Si Liu tittered: "Oh no, I lost my concentration and disfigured you. If we fight anymore, you'll no longer be on par with me in beauty."

Fairy Miao Yin snorted.

Qiao Si Liu took the initiative and attacked, there were countless jade willow branches around her, these rootless willows were formed from the killer move, they were agile and resembled dozens of long whips, lashing at Fairy Miao Yin.

The attacks became more frequent, it was like a jade storm.

Fairy Miao Yin was shrouded in whips, not only did she need to defend against the whips, she also had to guard against their shadows.

After all, a whip might come out at any time and attack Fairy Miao Yin.

Splat splat splat...

Lashing sounds were endless, even though Fairy Miao Yin was putting up her defense, her clothes were still torn by the whips.

Fairy Miao Yin retreated as she used her hands to shield herself from the willow branches.

A moment later, her clothes were torn and her snow white body was exposed, it was beautiful and alluring, men would have a nosebleed upon seeing her.

Qiao Si Liu pursued her along the way.

But good times did not last, her opponent suddenly cried out as a pair of slender hands appeared on her back.

Fairy Miao Yin had four arms now.

Her four arms defended herself as Fairy Miao Yin restored her steady position, it was easy for her to block those willows now.

Qiao Si Liu sighed to herself.

This was immortal killer move — Wondrous Hand Profound Sound, Fairy Miao Yin's signature killer move, Qiao Si Liu knew of it.

She had attacked rapidly earlier to catch Fairy Miao Yin off-guard, to maintain her pressure and prevent her from regaining her composure.

However, Qiao Si Liu's tactic failed, Fairy Miao Yin managed to use this move in the end.

Even though Fairy Miao Yin was facing huge pressure, she was not a newbie like Zhao Lian Yun, Fairy Miao Yin did not make an error, she withstood the pressure and used her killer move successfully.

With her success, the situation changed.

Qiao Si Liu slowly flew backwards, stopping her attacks and starting a battle of attrition using the damaged Gu formation as she retreated.

She had left the super Gu formation when pursuing Fairy Miao Yin, it was wise to return.

"It is my turn now, Sister Si Liu, you have to endure it." Fairy Miao Yin smiled, but her gaze was very dark.

Four hands started to move rapidly.

Her smooth, long fingers were moving in a dazzling motion.

Ding ding, dang dang...

Cling cling, clang clang...

With the movement of her fingers, sharp sounds could be heard whenever they touched.

The sounds even caused sound waves to start appearing in the surrounding air.

The sound waves were moving rapidly, with Fairy Miao Yin at the center, it quickly spread to the radius of a few hundred steps.

The damaged third layer of the Gu formation was breaking apart many times as quickly with the effect of the sound.

The sound waves appeared quickly and vanished just as quickly.

Qiao Si Liu had a solemn expression, she quickly defended herself, as willow branches surrounded her entire body.

The two were in a deadlock.

And at another hole.

Shang clan Gu Immortal Shang Guai Li crossed his arms as he stood in front of the hole, looking at Hei Lou Lan.

He had arrogance and disdain on his face: "Just a rank six Gu Immortal, you dare to attack us, you are truly courting death. I will kill you first before reinforcing my allies."

Saying this, he vanished on the spot.

At the next moment, he appeared behind Hei Lou Lan.

Next, he stretched out his right hand as it turned into a white bone claw, scratching at Hei Lou Lan's back.

Plop.

A soft sound echoed.

The white bone claw ripped apart Hei Lou Lan's defensive method, stabbing into her back as blood splattered upon impact.

Hei Lou Lan shouted in anger, turning around to retaliate.

Shang Guai Li vanished on the spot again, appearing in the damaged formation once more.

Hei Lou Lan missed her attack, she growled in anger, her expression was twisted, there were five deep wounds on her back.

Shang Guai Li mocked in disdain: "You're nothing much, I will take your life in the next hit... hmm?"

But suddenly, his expression changed.

On his white bone claw, Hei Lou Lan's flesh and blood were burning in flames.

The fire was extremely special, it grew as it burned, in the blink of an eye, it covered Shang Guai Li's entire right hand.

"You fell for it so easily." Hei Lou Lan laughed.

Immortal killer move — Flesh Blood Fire!

...

"Dragonman?" A middle aged Gu Immortal with huge nostrils, Chai Huo Xiong, was bare on his upper body, he had a wide back and waist, his body's muscles were glowing red, like he was on fire.

Every time he breathed, smoke came out of his nostrils.

He was brutish and domineering, he stood on the spot and blocked the hole in the Gu formation behind him.

"At least you are knowledgeable." Bai Ning Bing had a plain expression, she stretched out her right arm, her jade fingers were covered in frost energy, as snowflakes descended from the sky.

Boom!

A loud sound occurred around Chai Huo Xiong, the ground caved in as he shot out like a cannonball, charging towards Bai Ning Bing.

"Take this!" Chai Huo Xiong shouted in the air, large amounts of flames flew out of his nose and nose, even his pores were flaming.

In an instant, raging flames filled Bai Ning Bing's vision.

Bai Ning Bing had a cold gaze, she did not dodge, she watched as Chai Huo Xiong got closer.

Her lips curled up, she called out in excitement: "Come at me."

Before she finished her words, she charged forward!

Her body was tiny compared to Chai Huo Xiong, this was like the collision of a fly towards a flame.

Boom!

An intense explosion.

Both sides attacked and were locked in the middle, dividing this battlefield into two.

Half was flame and half was frost, they were repelling each other.

Flames flickered with the power to burn all lifeforms, while the frost solidified the earth into an icy domain, freezing all lifeforms.

Flames could not melt the frost, and the frost could not freeze the flames, there was no clear victor.

When the flames and frost vanished, two figures appeared on each end.

Bai Ning Bing stood on the spot, excitement and concentration was evident in her dragon eyes.

On the other end, the domineering Chai clan Gu Immortal took several steps back, looking at Bai Ning Bing in disbelief: "Impossible, you are only a rank six Gu Immortal!"

Bai Ning Bing smiled and her icy white teeth were exposed: "I praised you for being knowledgeable earlier, it seems that I need to... take that back!"

The moment she said 'need to', Bai Ning Bing charged ahead again, when she finished her words, she was right in front of Chai Huo Xiong.

She jumped into the sky and her right arm was raised up, she was like a deity of snow descending to the world, bringing with her an endless blizzard, her divine might was unstoppable.

Next, Bai Ning Bing's right arm slashed down at Chai Huo Xiong like a giant sharp blade!

...

"White Rabbit, you slut, die!" Wu Liao had bloodshot eyes, filled with rage and hatred.

Even though he was not on good terms with Wu An as they disliked each other, they were still Wu clan Gu Immortals.

Now that White Rabbit killed Wu An, Wu Liao attacked with hatred, wanting to avenge Wu An.

But it was a pity, Lady White Rabbit who had transformed, or rather, Black Tigress, had rank seven cultivation level, her battle strength had surged dramatically.

Wu Liao was just a rank six Gu Immortal, he could do nothing to Lady White Rabbit, instead, his own life was in danger.

"Step down Wu Liao, you are not her match." Fang Yuan blocked Wu Liao, who was going to fight, he had cold killing intent as he stood in front of Lady White Rabbit.

Chapter 1352: Fang Yuan versus Black Tigress

"Hehehe." Black Tigress had a strange laugh, her beautiful appearance looked very twisted.

Her clear innocent eyes were filled with sinister light, there were deep bags under her eyes, like she had not slept for a long time. Her eyeshadow was thick, like the wings of a black butterfly, extending from her eyes to her brows.

Even though her appearance did not change much, she had turned sinister and vicious, her demeanor had changed completely, the innocent and weak form was worlds apart from this.

"White Rabbit true inheritance... interesting." Fang Yuan's body shined in bright light.

When the light faded, Fang Yuan had turned into a huge tortoise.

Immortal killer move — Divination Tortoise Transformation!

Guh.

The rank seven formation path Gu Immortal Chi Gui coughed out a mouthful of blood.

"Damn it, damn it!" He cursed continuously, looking ahead at the fragmented corpse of the Immortal Gu floating in front of him.

This Immortal Gu was originally damaged by Zuo Ye Hui's attack.

Earlier, when Chi Gui wanted to activate the second layer of the super Gu formation, this Immortal Gu reached its limit and broke.

The Gu formation activation failed, there would be a chain reaction and cause other Immortal Gu to be damaged.

Chi Gui had to use his own body to endure the backlash of the collapsing Gu formation, in order to keep it from being destroyed.

But he got injured in the process.

"Is the injury severe?" Ba De quickly came to check.

Chi Gui swallowed the blood in his mouth, he had a pale expression like that of a dead person: "Very severe! This destroyed Immortal Gu is one of the main pillars. The second layer of the Gu formation has three hundred thousand Gu worms, but there are only four Immortal Gu of such importance. We need to find a replacement and activate the second layer of the Gu formation. This Gu formation has many linked layers, without the second layer, the first layer will not be able to activate."

After pausing for a while, Chi Gui shouted with a frantic expression: "Anyone who has earth path Immortal Gu, I need one passed to me. Now is the moment of life and death!"

Beside him, Ba Quan Feng and Ba De looked at each other helplessly.

The former was a wind path Gu Immortal, while the latter was wood path, they did not have earth path Immortal Gu.

Chi Gui had to heal his injuries, Ba Quan Feng and Ba De went to ask around.

The reason why they had to ask one by one was because he needed to try and conceal this disastrous information. After all, mental state affected battle strength, the fewer people who knew, the better.

Thankfully, among the five regions, Southern Border had the most earth path Gu Immortals.

Soon, some people spoke up, they were willing to contribute their earth path Immortal Gu.

Chi Gui had to choose, it was not easy to choose the earth path Immortal Gu, but he had to try and find the one closest to the one that was destroyed.

Chi Gui's injuries had not healed, but he could not care.

"Next, I need to deduce this and try to add that earth path Immortal Gu into this Gu formation. My safety will be in your hands."

This act was very risky, he was placing his life in the hands of others.

But Chi Gui had a determined expression, he did not hesitate.

He knew that there was no other way now, time was pressing, he needed to gamble!

Ba De had a solemn expression, nodding: "I promise that I will defend your life. Even if Zuo Ye Hui comes, he will have to step over my corpse first."

He was sincere, these were not lies. In this situation, even if Ba De had high battle strength, he could not resist Zuo Ye Hui, the battle could not be turned around.

He was not Feng Jiu Ge or Fang Yuan, who had reverse flow protection seal.

Ba De did not know that Wu clan's Immortal Gu House was on the way.

But the moment Shadow Sect attacked, he had immediately used his information path methods to inform Ba clan.

There were other Gu Immortals who did the same thing.

Defending with all they had, that was the only way for everyone to survive.

Like this, Chi Gui's attention and concentration was focused on the Gu formation. And Ba De, who had the highest battle strength, was leading the group in defending the place. With Wu clan and Qiao clan in trouble, their reputation had fallen greatly, Ba clan's Ba De became the most suitable leader.

Ba De did not let go of this chance.

As the most important person to protect Chi Gui, he stayed at the back and observed the battlefield.

All in all, the righteous path's defense was quite stable.

The righteous path Gu Immortal elites were using the damaged Gu formation, they could retreat in time.

Meanwhile, even though the demonic path Gu Immortals arrived imposingly, they lacked strong experts. It was not that Southern Border had no demonic path or lone immortal experts, but most of them had died in Yi Tian Mountain.

Even though the righteous path also suffered great losses in that battle, compared to the demonic path, the righteous path was more stable, it was easier to produce Gu Immortal experts with abundant resources.

One could imagine, unless something happened, at this rate, for the following period of time, Southern Border's righteous path would greatly suppress the demonic path and lone cultivators.

Ba De's gaze swept past Fairy Miao Yin, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing's battlefield, eventually looking at Fang Yuan.

"Wu Yi Hai." He muttered this name, feeling some emotions.

In the past, he wanted to suppress Wu Yi Hai and teach Wu clan a lesson. But now, they had to work together, Ba De had a lot of ambition, he wanted to replace Wu clan and make Ba clan flourish. But now, with this strong enemy, he was willing to work with Wu Yi Hai, he had an open mind.

Of course, this was temporary, once the crisis ended, Ba De would deal with them again.

With this event, Ba De had a huge hold on Fang Yuan. Before the mishap occurred in Wu clan and Qiao clan, Ba De had been holding himself back, he did not use the immortal opportunity business to find trouble with him. He had endured until now, there were finally results to be shown.

Black Tigress jumped around, she was very agile, evading many vajra thoughts.

After her personality changed, this former Lady White Rabbit started to use dark path methods.

Not just that, her rank six cultivation level turned to rank seven, it was simply unreasonable!

But no matter how fast she moved, she was merely a bit faster than Fang Yuan's thoughts.

Times were different now.

If this was Fang Yuan had just obtained vajra thought Immortal Gu, he might not have been able to handle Black Tigress. But now, Fang Yuan was very familiar with this move, thoughts scattered like rain, assaulting her and cooperating with each other, forming a huge web of attacks, even though Black Tigress dodged them, she was still going to be overwhelmed by the countless thoughts.

Immortal killer move — Cornered Tiger!

Realizing that she was in a disadvantage, Black Tigress' aura burst out as her toes landed lightly on the ground.

Black liquid started to spread on the ground.

A breath of time later, the water expanded to the size of a pond.

Two breaths of time later, the black water started to bubble.

Three breaths of time later, a lizard[1] with the size of a horse emerged from the black water.

This lizard was black in color and had shiny eyes, it was not real, it was made from the dark path killer move.

The lizard moved rapidly, spreading its limbs and moving like the wind, bringing Black Tigress to its back as she charged away.

Compared to Black Tigress, Fang Yuan, who had turned into a divination tortoise, looked very slow.

After he transformed, he stopped moving, he blocked the hole of the Gu formation.

Even though Fang Yuan did not move, the vajra thoughts he created were like tiny tortoise shells, they moved agilely and circulated around the divination tortoise's body with an incredible number.

Since the battle started, Fang Yuan had been using vajra shell.

The tortoise shell thoughts few rapidly, Fang Yuan had a composed plan, he first used these thoughts to defend himself before sending the new ones outside.

Black Tigress stood on top of the black lizard, she could move with ease but she gritted her teeth.

On the surface, her speed was an advantage, she had the initiative, but the truth was, she needed to get past Fang Yuan's obstruction to attack the damaged formation.

But Fang Yuan was blocking her way.

Black Tigress tried to move every which way, trying to get past Fang Yuan.

She moved around these tortoise shell thoughts and exposed vulnerability on purpose, but Fang Yuan did not fall for it, he defended himself firmly and continued to push Black Tigress out.

Fang Yuan was a bit wary of Black Tigress' trump card.

Even though Fang Yuan did not know its name, he saw how Wu An had turned into a puddle of black water after he got hit by it unknowingly.

"Black Tigress prepared that move for me."

"She wanted to meet me but I rejected her, thus she used it on Wu An."

"This means that the move has a small range, it is quite limited. Like dark assassination, even though the aura is concealed and it has great power, the flaw is evident."

Fang Yuan created more and more thoughts, the tortoise shell thoughts were moving around without any gaps, it was terrifying.

Black Tigress had to retreat, seeing so many tortoise shells, she was so angry her chest was moving up and down.

"This tortoise transformation really suits you, Lord Wu Yi Hai." She grinned, showing a cruel smile filled with killing intent.

"However, don't think my methods are just these. Take this!"

Saying so, Black Tigress opened her mouth and aimed at Fang Yuan, sticking out her tiny tongue.

Her tongue was cute and pinkish, but her lips were black like ink, it was a clear contrast of black lips and pink tongue.

Her tongue moved rapidly.

It was like a cute neighbor's daughter making a funny face.

But Fang Yuan felt a chill down his spine, he suffered a heavy injury.

He quickly turned around and looked, he saw a tiny hole on his shell.

This hole was only the size of a basin, it was nothing compared to the giant tortoise's size.

But it was very deep, the wound was spreading outwards, black smoke could be seen rising from the hole, making a cracking sound.

[1] Lizard is written as wall/corner tiger in Chinese characters Back

Chapter 1353: Tiger Lick

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

"What killer move is this?!"

"The divination tortoise's shell is the hardest thing on its body, yet it could not endure this attack."

"Even though my sovereign immortal body has the trait of non-conflicting dao marks, my tough ancient desolate beast body still suffered such injuries?"

Black Tigress' battle strength was out of Fang Yuan's expectations. Her method was peculiar and could bypass even the divination tortoise's defense.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan did not dare to hold back, he quickly used rank seven Immortal Gu Precaution.

This rule path Immortal Gu had already been added into vajra shell by Fang Yuan.

Immediately, the original vajra shell killer move stopped working, a brand new vajra shell killer move was activated.

Whoosh.

Wind was created out of nowhere, the divination tortoise's aura changed.

The brand new vajra shell killer move used a large number of time path mortal Gu, their effect was to eliminate the weakness of precaution Immortal Gu needing ten breaths of time.

Thus, once vajra shell was activated, precaution Immortal Gu's effect became active at once.

The small tortoise shell thoughts expanded and became firmer, at the same time, the divination tortoise's main body started to shine in a metallic light, it also became darker.

Black Tigress saw this and her expression changed, she licked again.

The two were far away, but Fang Yuan still suffered injuries despite the distance.

There was another hole on the tortoise shell, but this time, it was only the size of an adult's fist, the injury was light and there was no black smoke.

The wound earlier had already stopped producing black smoke, the injury was expanding very slowly.

Black Tigress snorted coldly, feeling unresigned, she muttered: "In that case, I will attack there!"

At the next moment, Fang Yuan felt his tortoise head go numb.

Immediately, pain assaulted him, there was also a numb feeling as well.

The injuries were not light.

Fang Yuan quickly placed his head into the shell.

"Damn it!" Black Tigress saw this and her eyes spewed fire from rage.

Fang Yuan was very shameless, not just his head, his limbs and tail also went into the shell.

Only the tortoise shell thoughts were still spinning and increasing in numbers, raising his defensive power and range once more.

Black Tigress licked the tortoise shell continuously, but there was little use.

She was in a predicament, there was nothing she could do to Fang Yuan.

Wu Liao healed his injuries as he watched the battle, seeing this, he broke out in sweat, he thought: "At this rate, when will Lord Wu Yi Hai be able to take revenge for Wu An, how many years would it take?"

Ba De snorted in unhappiness.

The other holes had intense battles, but Fang Yuan was calm and composed, there was little commotion.

Fang Yuan easily hid inside his shell.

He was thinking rapidly about Black Tigress' killer move.

Killer moves could be directed to targets in certain ways. For example, a fireball killer move may need to form in the hands first, before being shot out towards the target, to have any form of impact.

But where it flew, in what direction and towards what target, that would depend on the direction that the killer move was designed to move.

Wherever the move was directed towards, the fireball would fly there.

If the targeting was not impressive, the fireball would move straight, after leaving the hands, its direction could not be changed anymore.

If the targeting ability was stronger, the fireball would be able to move in a curved manner. After leaving the hands, its direction could be tweaked slightly.

And even stronger ones would have automatic homing abilities.

"Black Tigress' killer move must also have a targeting ability."

"It is formless after activation, it is not as obvious as a fireball. But it definitely has a targeting ability, because it is not a wide ranged attack, the damage is concentrated."

"Then how does it do that? By sight?"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan activated his Gu worms, creating a thick fog around the divination tortoise, surrounding it.

"What is this Wu Yi Hai trying to do? Hmph." Black Tigress was suspicious that Fang Yuan was using a new killer move, she quickly stretched out her tongue and licked towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was hit again.

"Not sight? Is it smell?"

Fang Yuan used his method again, the fog became extremely smelly.

Wu Liao who was close by to him, had a twisted expression as he quickly used his Gu worms to breathe internally.

The smell spread in the air, soon, other battlefields were looking over.

"Wu Yi Hai is actually trying to break the other party's killer move." Ba De's eyes shined, he could see Fang Yuan's motive.

He snorted as the displeasure in his heart grew.

There was usually little hope of breaking an enemy's killer move on the spot, experimentation was needed, and even if the reasoning was understood, there might not be the necessary Immortal Gu or method to counter it.

Trying to break a killer move, it would result in a drawn out battle.

"This is an emergency, but he still has the time to break the killer move? Hmph! If he has time, he should try to kill the enemy!" Ba Quan Feng expressed the unhappiness in his heart.

Ba De did not say anything, now was not the time for internal conflict.

Black Tigress hesitated for a moment, she stretched out her tongue and licked again.

Another hole appeared on Fang Yuan's shell.

Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration: "I get it, this is her sense of taste."

Normally speaking, taste was experienced through the tongue, and Gu Immortals' tongues were able to taste things from afar through Immortal Gu or killer moves, it was not hard.

"Every time she activates it, Black Tigress needs to stretch out her tongue."

"She and Shadow Sect are aligned, while Shadow Sect has food path true inheritances. Only such a non-standard path can deal such damage to my defensive divination tortoise transformation."

"Let me test it."

The divination tortoise turned red, especially the shell, it was red as molten iron.

Black Tigress licked and immediately cringed: "Argh... so hot!"

The divination tortoise's redness faded, there was a strange smell in the sky.

Black Tigress stretched out her tongue and licked, she almost puked from disgust, she frowned: "So salty!"

The divination tortoise transformation changed again.

Black Tigress stopped trying, she understood Fang Yuan's intention: "This guy! He is actually trying to counter my killer move, he is not trying to use any immortal killer moves. Damn it!!"

Black Tigress thought earlier that the divination tortoise's changes were the start of Fang Yuan's new immortal killer move.

Thus, she interfered with him time and time again, once she succeeded, Fang Yuan would suffer an intense backlash. She would have hope of passing this huge tortoise shell obstacle.

"Under such a situation, he still has time to try to deduce and counter my killer move?!" Fang Yuan's movements were not logical, the battle was so intense now, nobody had any time for this.

But precisely so, Black Tigress fell for it.

After realizing this, Black Tigress stopped using this move, she started to use other long range methods.

She punched with both fists as dark green fist qi moved around the troublesome tortoise shell thoughts, some were wiped out but some managed to land on the divination tortoise shell.

Even though the damage was little, each time the punches landed, Fang Yuan's body shook uncontrollably. Evidently, this immortal killer move had rule path Gu worms. Black Tigress was trying to prevent Fang Yuan from using an immortal killer move, it was a good strategy.

"It was taste, huh." Fang Yuan's head was still inside his shell.

Even though he had a result, it was still far from truly breaking Black Tigress' move.

Fang Yuan, however, was not in a rush.

Black Tigress could not use this move anymore, her punches were of little harm to Fang Yuan.

The original Wu Yi Hai had other methods, but they were all defensive in nature.

Black Tigress was really over-thinking it when she guarded against Fang Yuan's attacking moves, even though he had them, with this identity, he could not use them. If he tried, he would incur huge suspicions, his identity was likely to be exposed.

Thus, this battle slowed down tremendously.

Fang Yuan did not want to attack, or rather, he had no attacking moves, while Black Tigress could not go past this shell.

After a long time, there were already a hundred thousand tortoise shells around Fang Yuan.

Black Tigress felt like she was helpless, the vast number of tortoise shells made this an incredibly eye catching sight in the battlefield.

Ba De's expression became even colder, he could not help but transmit: "Wu Yi Hai, I heard you have two more transformations. Why are you still holding back? Quickly kill her and reinforce the others! Unless, you really have some relationship with this White Rabbit? You can't bear to kill her?"

Fang Yuan heard Ba De's transmissions but ignored him, pretending not to hear anything.

Ba De did not get a reply, he gritted his teeth in anger, his gaze towards Fang Yuan turned colder.

Fang Yuan was thinking about his situation.

"Shadow Sect is definitely attacking to save Spectral Soul's main body."

"They control Zuo Ye Hui, but the extent is limited, and the rank eight Gu Immortal Purple Mountain True Monarch has not shown up yet."

"The righteous path has the super Gu formation, we can hold on for a while. As long as we stall for time, reinforcements will come from all over."

"And I have reverse flow protection seal, I can resist rank eight existences, they will not be able to defeat me."

"Purple Mountain True Monarch is a wisdom path Gu Immortal, how can he not have a trump card? And these righteous path Gu Immortals are far from being desperate now."

"I should conceal my identity and wait for a chance to take action. Maybe this time, I might have some great gains!"

Fang Yuan thought about it and realized this was a great opportunity.

He had sufficient strength, but he needed to wait for the right timing.

Shadow Sect was a huge threat to him, he wanted to exterminate them all. But Fang Yuan had not succeeded in any of his attempts so far. It was not that he did not try, or that he was not determined enough, but Shadow Sect's group was made of elites and geniuses.

But now was a grand opportunity.

Chapter 1354: The Might of Hei and Bai

Fang Yuan had thought that his pursuit would have no chance, but to think that Shadow Sect personally presented Fang Yuan this great opportunity!

Because of sovereign immortal fetus Gu, Shadow Sect would not let Fang Yuan off. If Fang Yuan did not get rid of them and allowed Shadow Sect to grow further, he would end up like Ma Hong Yun in the end.

After he got rid of Shadow Sect, who would know about Fang Yuan's identity? Eliminating this biggest threat was Fang Yuan's best option, he could even get rid of the weakness of Connect Luck.

After that, he would slowly develop and cultivate using the dream realm, because of the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan had the greatest foundation in the world!

Five hundred years later, Fang Yuan would have incredible strength, be it his cultivation level, battle strength, or wealth, it would be unimaginable! (Fang Yuan does not know that the great era is already impending.)

During the five regions chaotic war, he could either take advantage of the situation for opportunities or fight with brute strength, Heavenly Court might not even be able to do anything to him.

If the situation developed well, by the time he reached rank nine, he would be one step closer to his goal of eternal life.

This was Fang Yuan's cultivation plan, it was very realistic.

Now was the best chance to get rid of Shadow Sect, how could Fang Yuan give it up?

And Shadow Sect had no idea Fang Yuan was here.

Fang Yuan was the one concealed.

Who knew that Wu Yi Hai was him? Nobody in the righteous path knew, even his 'brother' Wu Yong had no idea.

Undoubtedly, eliminating Wu Yi Hai and impersonating him to join Wu clan was a brilliant move.

Even though there was a risk, if he did not do that, how would Fang Yuan get this prime opportunity?

Fang Yuan had to make use of it.

"I might even be able to capture Spectral Soul's main body!"

"With Spectral Soul's main body, I would be able to interrogate the soul and obtain all of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's cultivation memories and experiences. All of his soul path experiences, his perspective and gains in the door of life and death, countless Gu recipes, killer moves, and secrets..."

Fang Yuan's greatest desire was lead soul into dream.

With this killer move, as well as unravel dream and guts Gu, Fang Yuan would be the number one person in this world in terms of dream realm exploration, he would have an immense advantage, the entire world would be left in the dust, even Heavenly Court!

Ding ding ding!

Sound waves could be seen as ripples all around Qiao Si Liu.

Fairy Miao Yin's arms had grown to six in number, her fingers were moving elegantly, her attacks were much more intense than before.

Qiao Si Liu, however, was able to defend herself well.

Her pupils had turned jade, her black hair had turned into willow branches that extended to her waist.

The two Southern Border fairies were still in a deadlock.

...

"Damn it, I can't block it! I need to escape!!" A demonic path Gu Immortal retreated as resolution flashed in his eyes.

Boom!

An intensely strong aura burst out from behind him.

"Cowardly rat, die!!" A righteous path Gu Immortal shouted, stretching out his hand and grabbing the demonic path Gu Immortal's head.

Next, lightning flashed and thunder roared, deep blue lightning bolts shrouded this battlefield.

The lightning flashes lasted for a moment before stopping.

The opponent that the righteous path Gu Immortal was holding onto had turned into a charred skeleton, with a barely observable human shape.

"Hmph, rat that doesn't know his limits, he dared to act arrogantly in front of me, Yi Hei Ting." The righteous path Gu Immortal relaxed the grip of his hand as the demonic path Gu Immortal's corpse fell to the ground, shattering into tiny black pieces.

...

"Everyone, your attacks are only like this?" A righteous path Gu Immortal with a slender body and tall nose bridge spoke with arrogance and disappointment.

"Don't be smug!"

"Tie clan's Tie Xin Jian, we have been suppressing you all along, you have the face to say... urgh."

The three Gu Immortals who were attacking Tie Xin Jian ridiculed him, but their expressions suddenly changed.

A strong and sharp aura burst into the sky, emitted from Tie Xin Jian's body.

The three Gu Immortals quickly moved back, feeling on guard.

Wind was blowing all around him, causing his clothes to flutter, but Tie Xin Jian had calm emotions, he shut his eyes as he said slowly: "It is useless, I have already seen all your moves, all of your weaknesses are right before me with no secrets left."

"F*ck your mother..." A Gu Immortal cursed but before he finished, his body shook intensely.

Puff puff puff.

Three sounds later, three waves of sword qi flashed, so quickly that it felt like an illusion.

Heads flew, the three Gu Immortals who were attacking Tie Xin Jian were beheaded, losing all their vitality.

...

"Hahaha!" Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly, she had severe injuries.

Shang Guai Li had rank seven cultivation level, but he looked at Hei Lou Lan with shock and wariness, he was no longer as relaxed as before.

"As expected of a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, you are a battle maniac." Shang Bu Li was unwilling to give in, but his injuries were already close to his bottom line.

"Retreat." This thought appeared in his mind.

Hei Lou Lan seemed to have noticed it as she mockingly smiled: "Where do you want to escape to?"

"What do you mean?" Shang Guai Li immediately felt something amiss, a strong sense of danger filled his heart.

Whoosh.

Flames burst out of his mouth, before spewing out of his eye sockets, ears, nose, and other orifices.

Blazing rampantly!

Instantly, Shang Guai Li was turned into a pillar of fire.

His anguished cries resounded in the battlefield before he died.

Hei Lou Lan stared with a cold expression: "So what if you are rank seven?"

...

"Quick, quick, I need more reinforcements!" Chai Huo Xiong retreated as he screamed.

Compared to his earlier demeanor, he had lost all his fighting spirit, fear and anxiety filled his eyes.

Before him, dragon lady Bai Ning Bing walked slowly, approaching him step by step.

She was extremely beautiful, it could move one's soul, but in Chai Huo Xiong's perspective, she was extremely dangerous, he wanted nothing more than to escape the battlefield.

But in this situation, at this time and place, if he tried to leave the battlefield, wouldn't he just become Zuo Ye Hui's food?

Chai Huo Xiong could only fight reluctantly.

Bai Ning Bing's battle strength was even higher than Hei Lou Lan. Because she had Bai Xiang's true inheritance, and all of the ice and snow path Immortal Gu were compatible with her Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique.

Meanwhile, even though Hei Lou Lan had the Great Strength True Martial Physique, she used fire path Immortal Gu, and the fire path methods her aunt left behind, she did not have much dao mark amplification.

Chai Huo Xiong had already requested for help once, but Bai Ning Bing killed the backup already.

Of course, Bai Ning Bing paid a price for it.

Ba De was commanding the battle, upon hearing Chai Huo Xiong's yells, his attention was drawn over.

"Tie Xin Jian, please go and help Chai Huo Xiong." Ba De thought before transmitting.

"Okay." Tie Xin Jian immediately flew into the sky, towards Bai Ning Bing.

His aura was stunning, he immediately attracted Bai Ning Bing's attention. Her dragon pupils shrunk to pin size as an immortal killer move was activated.

"My aid is here." Seeing Tie Xin Jian's figure, Chai Huo Xiong felt great joy.

But at this moment, because he relaxed his mind slightly, Bai Ning Bing noticed his weakness and her immortal killer move was unleashed.

"I want you to die!" Tie Xin Jian who was one moment late burst out with rage. He could only watch helplessly as Chai Huo Xiong turned into a popsicle, breaking apart into countless ice fragments.

Bai Ning Bing smiled but her expression was plain, she looked at Tie Xin Jian, saying calmly: "My move is called ice shatter death. Do you want to try it?"

...

"Chai Huo Xiong has been sacrificed, even though this dragon lady is rank six, her battle strength is first rate even among rank sevens." Ba De's heart sank.

He rapidly looked around the battlefield, the defensive line was still being maintained.

The righteous path had the advantage, even though they were relying on the damaged third layer of the Gu formation.

Even though there were sacrifices, Shadow Sect had even more deaths, their morale had fallen, some were wavering.

"The enemy only has four true experts. They are Lady White Rabbit, Demoness Miao Yin, the dragon lady, and that fire path rank six (Hei Lou Lan). As long as we eliminate one of them, their morale will suffer a huge blow."

Thinking of this, Ba De's attention fell on Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan had turned into a divination tortoise, he was still at the same spot with his limbs and head inside the shell. But there were already three hundred thousand tortoise shell thoughts, they swept through the battlefield, Black Tigress was pushed far away.

Ba De snorted again in anger, transmitting to Fang Yuan: "Wu Yi Hai! Stop defending, as a Wu clan Gu Immortal, do you have no courage to fight? Are you so afraid of dying? Let me tell you, you are an important person in this fight, you are the best hope to create an opening in this battle. As long as you kill Black Tigress and reinforce other areas, there will be a qualitative change, the balance will tilt towards our favor!"

Fang Yuan: "..."

The divination tortoise was like a mountain, not reacting to his words.

"Damn it, this fellow is still acting like this now, I simply cannot believe it!" Ba De gritted his teeth, feeling stifled.

"I'm done." At this moment, Chi Gui opened his eyes, he stood up from the ground with a joyful expression.

"Success?" Ba Quan Feng asked excitedly.

"Yes, I have already finished the deduction, now, we have to arrange the Gu formation and activate the second layer. This super Gu formation has greater defense as we get deeper into the layers, it is not a problem to block grey night." Chi Gui nodded.

"Good!" Ba De heard this and let out a sigh of relief.

He looked at Zuo Ye Hui, who was far away.

This legendary immemorial desolate beast was still exhausted, it did not move from its original spot, it was still breathing in deeply.

In Ba De's heart, this legendary immemorial desolate beast was the greatest worry. Most of his pressure came from it.

"The situation is favoring our righteous path." Ba De felt joy and gladness.

But Fang Yuan was far less optimistic.

"Purple Mountain True Monarch has not shown up, what is he planning?" Fang Yuan was getting more and more on edge.

Chapter 1355: Crucial Traitor

At Yi Tian Mountain's location, around the super Gu formation, while the demonic and righteous paths were fighting, another battle had come to an end.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was undamaged, it was radiating with vitality, floating silently.

The huge purple blood river formation was near the brink of collapse, the blood river was no more, only a lump of red blood was left floating around randomly in the dark purple space.

In front of Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal was trapped in a ball of wind, unable to escape, he had no choice but to surrender.

Victory was assured.

"Let me see your true identity." Wu Yong was unharmed, green light flashed across his eyes.

Immediately, the rainbow colored lights surrounding the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal vanished like clouds blown by wind, dispersing.

His true identity was exposed.

The three righteous path Gu Immortals were all stunned.

Qiao Zhi Cai stared with wide opened eyes, gasping: "Yao Geng?"

It turned out that this Seven Illusions Demon Immortal was none other than a member of a super force, Yao clan Gu Immortal Yao Geng.

He had originally fought with Wu Yi Ran over Stunning Immortal's inheritance, during the fifth time, he had died together with Wu Yi Ran.

His life tablet Gu in Yao clan had shattered, everyone thought he was dead.

But to think that he was the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal!

"Good, very good. Yao clan is actually like this." Tie Mian Shen said coldly.

Yao Geng smiled bitterly: "This is my personal action, it has nothing to do with Yao clan."

Wu Yong saw that he was defending his clan to the end, he was not as demonic as they had expected, he asked: "What made you think of the method to trap us?"

Yao Geng's smile became even more bitter: "I already have said that I am a minor character. Or rather, I am just a pawn, I was manipulated and forced to do this, my clan has nothing to do with it."

Wu Yong's expression sank slightly: "Then, the one who manipulated you is that rank eight Gu Immortal from earlier? Tell me everything about him."

Yao Geng laughed loudly, tears rolling down his face: "If I say that I do not understand that person, or rather, I have spent just about as much time with him as you, will you believe me?"

Tie Mian Shen interjected: "Is it because of the Seven Illusions true inheritance?"

Yao Geng nodded with a bitter expression.

Tie Mian Shen sighed: "To obtain the Seven Illusions true inheritance, you need to accept an information path alliance agreement. My clan analyzed and concluded that this is a trap. But what we do not understand is, there were many Seven Illusions true inheritance inheritors who did not have to execute the contents of the alliance agreement, you are the first victim."

Saying this, Wu Yong and Qiao Zhi Cai understood, they looked towards Yao Geng with a hint of pity.

"At this point, what is there to say. Winner takes all, whether you want to kill me or whatever else, it is up to you." Yao Geng sat on the ground, devoid of any fighting spirit.

"Where is that rank eight Gu Immortal?" Wu Yong asked, he felt something amiss.

Yao Geng said all that he knew: "I know as much as you do, I thought he was hiding inside the formation. Only until you found the crucial formation core and captured me did I realize that he had left long ago."

Wu Yong heard this and the bad feeling in his heart intensified.

He quickly grunted, immobilizing Yao Geng and suppressing him in the bamboo building, before using this Immortal Gu House to unleash a terrifying attack.

Rumble!

The purple blood river formation was completely destroyed, the clear sky could be seen again.

The three Gu Immortals were freed, but at this moment, before joy showed on their faces, their bodies shook.

"Oh no, so many days had passed!"

"This purple blood river formation not only has wisdom path, blood path, phantom path, and information path effects, it even has time path methods."

In this Gu formation, the three Gu Immortals' sense of time was affected, they misjudged it.

Even Wu Yong fell for it.

He had always thought that the time he spent in the purple blood river formation was not long.

But after breaking out of the Gu formation, he realized that so much time had passed.

"Oh no! It seems that the rank eight Gu Immortal was not trying to fight us to the death, he merely wanted to trap us. Don't tell me, his real motive is?" Wu Yong's heart sank, he quickly contacted his clan.

The purple blood river formation isolated them from the outside world, they could not even connect to treasure yellow heaven, not to mention their clans.

Immediately, the three immortals contracted their clans and soon, their expressions changed.

Large amounts of information entered their minds, the three immortals were stunned, to think that so many things had happened these last days!

Gu Immortals from Wu clan, Yang clan, Qiao clan, Chi clan, Chai clan, Xia clan, Ba clan and others were engaged in a chaotic battle.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's plan was to trap Wu Yong's group, creating a false image that he had died, so that Southern Border's politics would go into chaos.

He had succeeded.

Yang clan, Qiao clan, and Wu clan whipped up a storm for their own benefits.

Right when they were engaged in a battle for profits, over at the super Gu formation, large numbers of people assaulted it.

After receiving a huge amount of distress letters, the clans fell into panic.

"What is happening?"

"What guts did these demonic path Gu Immortals grow, how could they attack the super Gu formation?"

"Not just that, even a Northern Plains Gu Immortal appeared."

"Even a legendary immemorial desolate beast like Zuo Ye Hui was controlled?!"

These righteous path clans felt that it was unthinkable.

But among them, there were astute people, after realizing this fact, they quickly reacted: What happened recently could be put together as a huge shocking scheme.

The mastermind's goal was the giant dream realm!

"Go, we will go straight to the super Gu formation!" Wu Yong was resolute.

"They were actually able to cause a storm in Southern Border, I want to see who the mastermind is." Tie Mian Shen followed after.

Wu Yong had an anxious expression: "My brother is still there, I hope nothing bad happened to him."

At this crucial moment, Wu Yong still did not forget to maintain his reputation.

Qiao Zhi Cai quickly cooperated: "Lord Wu Yong, you care so much for your brother, you are truly loving towards your family and have a big heart, truly a role model of the righteous path."

Rank eight Immortal Gu House Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building tore through the sky, flying towards Yi Tian Mountain.

Chi clan first supreme elder was also doing the same thing. After receiving Chi Gui's distress letter, he immediately stopped contesting with Yang clan, he brought a Chi clan Immortal Gu House towards the super Gu formation.

Yang clan was doing the same, Hou clan, Yao clan, and Shang clan sent either Gu Immortal experts or brought their Immortal Gu Houses along.

These people did not know why Shadow Sect was attacking the super Gu formation.

Because from start to finish, they were unclear of what truly happened on Yi Tian Mountain.

They only knew some of the information that Heavenly Court purposely leaked, they knew that Heavenly Court had interfered and that the destruction of Zombie Alliance was related to the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain.

They did not know the reason for the giant dream realm's creation, or that Spectral Soul's main body was inside the dream realm.

Heavenly Court hid this information because it was afraid that some Southern Border super forces would help Spectral Soul.

Even though they did not know the reason, this did not stop the super forces from placing great emphasis on the super Gu formation.

Not only because the giant dream realm was there, but also because of Zuo Ye Hui!

This legendary immemorial desolate beast caused great losses and gave Southern Border's Gu Immortal world painful memories whenever it appeared.

Thus, Southern Border's super forces sent their people, and even Immortal Gu Houses, to deal with Zuo Ye Hui!

"Currently, even though they were attacked by surprise, they have Chi clan's Gu formation and Chi clan's Gu Immortals there, they can defend themselves for the time being." While flying, Qiao Zhi Cai said.

Tie Mian Shen was silent.

Wu Yong shook his head: "To speak the truth, I am very worried. The other party has plotted this very deeply, their pawns are extremely well selected. If Yao Geng was not exposed, who would've guessed that he was the Seven Illusions Demon Immortal? The other party could infiltrate a rank seven member of a righteous path super force, I am afraid..."

Saying this, Wu Yong stopped.

Tie Mian Shen realized as he spoke: "Afraid that they have an insider within the super Gu formation?"

...

Boom!

The sneak attack was so sudden, it caught everyone unprepared.

"Ba Quan Feng, what are you doing?!" Ba De shouted, attacking with rage.

Ba Quan Feng was sent flying with Ba De's attack, he was on the verge of death.

Ba De quickly struck and suppressed him before going towards Chi Gui.

Chi Gui was heavily injured, his face was purple-gold in color, blood flowed out of his seven orifices.

Just earlier.

His deduction succeeded, when he was at a crucial moment of activating the second layer of the Gu formation, Ba Quan Feng, who was behind him, attacked suddenly with a vicious blow.

Chi Gui greatly trusted these two Gu Immortals from Ba clan, because earlier when he deduced the Gu formation, they were guarding him wholeheartedly.

But to think that Ba Quan Feng attacked at this crucial moment.

Ba Quan Feng was just a rank six wind path Gu Immortal, while Chi Gui was a rank seven formation path Gu Immortal, he was stronger without doubt. But earlier, Chi Gui was completely focused on the Gu formation, he could not defend himself, he was hit by Ba Quan Feng when unguarded.

Chi Gui not only suffered from Ba Quan Feng's attack, the Gu formation activation failed and he suffered a huge backlash.

At the next moment, he was near death, unable to do anything anymore.

"Ba Quan Feng!!" Ba De screamed, his eyes were red, he stared at Ba Quan Feng.

If he did not witness this, he would never believe that Ba Quan Feng was a traitor of the enemy.

"Surrender, Lord Ba De, just surrender, you do not know how the enemy truly is!" Ba Quan Feng was in poor shape, his aura was weak and his expression was pale, he was close to dying.

Ba De, however, saved him from the brink of dying.

"You will not die so easily, trust me, the clan will place judgment upon you, living will be scarier than dying, you will have a fate worse than death!" Ba De gritted his teeth, hearing his words, he truly hated this traitor to the max.

Ba Quan Feng was very vicious.

Undoubtedly, his choice of timing was impeccable.

Right when they were about to succeed, he struck and destroyed the righteous path's hope.

Not only did he hurt Chi Gui, he even destroyed the newly added earth path Immortal Gu.

Without the second layer of the super Gu formation, the righteous path was bound to lose!

Chapter 1356: Fang Yuan Salvages The Situation!

"Damn it! This tortoise won't stop hiding." Black Tigress gritted her teeth.

Hundreds of thousands of tortoise shell thoughts surrounded the divination tortoise in countless layers, Black Tigress had no way of getting close, with the increasing number of tortoise shell thoughts, she was pushed farther away by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan defended like an unmovable mountain, but he did not relax his mind.

Because Purple Mountain True Monarch had not shown up yet.

Fang Yuan used his investigative methods to observe the entire place.

Fairy Miao Yin and Qiao Si Liu were two of the three current generation great fairies of Southern Border, they were fighting on par with each other, still stuck in a deadlock.

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing also displayed battle strength that shocked Fang Yuan.

Previously, when Fang Yuan was chasing them, they were still not familiar with their immortal killer moves, but now, they were extremely proficient, using them easily.

This made Fang Yuan sigh once again, Shadow Sect's foundation was truly deep. Even in this terrible state, with Shadow Sect's help, Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing still obtained such an increase in their battle strength.

If Fang Yuan did not have such gains in Reverse Flow River, and used dream realms to raise his attainment levels after coming here, the speed of his growth would definitely not match these two immortals.

However, even though Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing were strong, there were no lack of experts in the righteous path.

Tie Xin Jian and Yi Hei Ting were first rate experts among rank sevens, even though they were inferior to Wu Yu Bo, they were still able to deal with Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan.

The two pairs of Gu Immortals engaged in intense battle, thunder roared as lightning flashed, a blizzard was blowing with countless shining figures.

"However... Zuo Ye Hui has almost recovered." Fang Yuan looked at the battlefield, he did not forget about the strongest existence here.

"Wu Yi Hai, quickly return." At this moment, Ba De's words were transmitted to Fang Yuan.

"What is it?" Fang Yuan could hear something wrong from Ba De's tone, he hesitated: "I am defending the opening."

"Quickly come, we need you." Chi Gui's weak voice was also transmitted.

Fang Yuan's heart sank, he quickly entered the hole and got to the inside.

Seeing Ba Quan Feng and Chi Gui on the verge of death, Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk.

An information path Gu flew over, Fang Yuan grabbed it, instantly understanding the situation.

"Ba Quan Feng was a spy from Shadow Sect?! Shadow Sect truly is everywhere." Fang Yuan's heart jumped, his eyelids were twitching.

The situation was horrible.

The earth path Immortal Gu was destroyed too.

Just earlier, the righteous path had fallen into a hopeless situation, when Ba De had almost lost all his confidence, he heard Chi Gui say: "We still have our final hope, even though I can't do anything, there is still Wu Yi Hai. His formation path attainment is something that our clan's Chi Shang had praised, his formation path attainment level is similar to me, at formation path quasi-grandmaster. Let him in, we still can give it a try."

Ba De knew that Fang Yuan and Chi Shang had a close relationship, but this was the first time he heard confirmation from Chi clan that Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was actually so high.

Normally, Ba De would be wary and envious, but now, he was extremely glad about it, he quickly transmitted to Fang Yuan.

Precisely so, he asked Fang Yuan to come back, the opening was filled by other righteous path Gu Immortals.

"This information is known only to us, Wu Yi Hai, do you have any confidence?" Ba De had a nervous expression.

At this crucial moment, he could not spread news of this. Once everyone became disheartened and lost their morale, the righteous path would definitely lose.

"Confidence my ass." Fang Yuan cursed.

He stared at Ba Quan Feng, his eyes filled with anger.

Zuo Ye Hui would only rest for some time. Earlier, Chi Gui had already spent most of it deducing the Gu formation, Fang Yuan had less than thirty percent of the original duration left.

To deduce a way to use a new Immortal Gu for this Gu formation, in addition to countless supplementary mortal Gu, and arrange them together to form the second layer of the Gu formation, the difficulty was huge, extremely immense.

Chi Gui knew about the difficulty, thus he said they could give it a try, the hope was indeed slim.

"Even if you are not sure if you can succeed, we can only rely on you. Give it your all, if the Gu formation fails, grey night will kill us all. Don't think you can escape, Zuo Ye Hui is extremely ferocious, it is recorded in our bloody history. Our only hope is to defend ourselves using the super Gu formation." Ba De urged.

Fang Yuan was silent, rapidly thinking in his mind.

Ba De and Chi Gui did not know about Fang Yuan's true identity, but the truth was, Fang Yuan's situation was much better than theirs.

"I have reverse flow protection seal, as long as I use it, I can leave freely."

"Even if Zuo Ye Hui pursues me, I can use the five regional walls to escape from him."

"But if I do that, my true identity will be exposed, not only will I lose my opportunity here, I will be hunted by Southern Border's Gu Immortal world. Ignoring anything else, Wu Yong will become a mortal enemy!"

"I should first give it a try."

"Hmm, there is still some time, I do not have to make that final decision yet."

Fang Yuan thought of this and quickly walked to Chi Gui: "Tell me about the secrets of the Gu formation's second layer."

Chi Gui's eyes were seeing darkness, he was pale as paper. His injuries were too severe, he was barely staying awake by using his Gu worms: "Firstly, we lack an earth path Immortal Gu. This information path mortal Gu has all of the details of this super Gu formation."

After saying that, his eyes closed as he fainted.

"Damn!" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Chi Gui fainting was the icing on the cake. Even though Ba De used his methods, it was useless.

Fang Yuan almost wanted to use reverse flow protection seal and flee. In his opinion, without Chi Gui's guidance, with the need for an earth path Immortal Gu, and also the time needed to deduce the modification, there was basically no hope.

But he still looked into the contents of the information path Gu worm first.

After seeing it, Fang Yuan was staring wide-eyed, he felt extremely glad that he looked at it!

Four elements Gu formation?!

Out of his expectations, this second layer of the Gu formation was established on the concept of the four elements.

Earth, water, wind, fire, it was a Gu formation constructed of earth path, water path, wind path, and fire path Immortal Gu.

Without the earth path Gu, the three Immortal Gu of fire path, water path, and wind path were left. Earlier, Chi Gui was working hard to replenish that earth path aspect.

"Why is it so coincidental?"

"I am not very familiar with other contents of formation path, but I had deeply researched the four elements concept."

Back then, Tu Shi Cheng's training of his son in the formation path dream realm was quite traumatic to Fang Yuan.

"The four elements concept was known as an overly strict concept by later generations, even without the earth path Immortal Gu, I can use other Immortal Gu to replace it, earth path is not necessary."

"Dark path it is!"

"Dark, water, wind, fire, these are also four elements, I can definitely construct the Gu formation's second layer."

Fang Yuan was feeling firm intuition regarding this.

He believed in this.

Because he was a formation path grandmaster!

"My concept will definitely work. Furthermore... with a dark path Immortal Gu, we can also defend against grey night more effectively!"

Fang Yuan suddenly realized that his understanding of Zuo Ye Hui's signature killer move was also not small.

The reason?

Because he had entered a relevant realistic dream realm.

This dream realm was too difficult, Fang Yuan died countless times. He barely passed it using a vast number of uses of unravel dream.

Fang Yuan had experienced grey night in the dream.

Different from now, back then, Zuo Ye Hui's signature killer move was different, it was a wide ranged attack that filled the entire valley.

But now, it was a dark grey beam of light, this was a modified version.

No matter how many times it was modified, the core was still the same, grey night was still grey night.

Precisely because Fang Yuan had experienced the original grey night, he was confident of creating a super Gu formation that could defend against it.

"However... this means I will need to contribute dark limit Immortal Gu. This is my only dark path Immortal Gu."

"Dark limit Immortal Gu is very useful in concealing my identity. Should I retreat now and leave, or stay here and take a risk, to see if I can find an opportunity to benefit?"

Fang Yuan hesitated before making up his mind.

"I want to fix the Gu formation, but I do not trust anyone, take Chi Gui and Ba Quan Feng and leave me. Block anyone from getting close to me!"

Ba De knew what was important now, he said nothing, grabbing the two Gu Immortals and moving away a distance of a few hundred steps.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, turning into a divination tortoise.

A wisdom path ancient desolate beast, his transformation path dao marks turned into wisdom path, along with his wisdom path methods, Fang Yuan started to deduce.

His progress was rapid.

Because he not only had the information on the Gu formation, he also knew about the four elements Gu formation, and he was even familiar with dark limit Immortal Gu and grey night.

Roar—!

Zuo Ye Hui suddenly raised its head, growling loudly.

Shadow Sect's members had joyful expressions, quickly retreating and abandoning their enemies.

"Oh no, grey night is coming!"

"Quick, enter the Gu formation."

The righteous path Gu Immortals did not know about the truth, they thought that this was the strongest defense.

"Quicker, are you not done yet?" Ba De could not help but urge, he was the most nervous one, if Fang Yuan did not succeed, he would die.

"I'm done." Fang Yuan's huge tortoise head let out a breath of air.

Joy flashed in his eyes, dark limit Immortal Gu flew out along with many mortal Gu.

Ba De was stunned before panicking, deep fear was concealed in his voice: "This is a dark path Immortal Gu, this Gu formation needs an earth path Immortal Gu!"

"I don't have earth path Immortal Gu, I only have dark path." Fang Yuan replied unhappily.

Ba De's eyes turned, he almost wanted to hit Fang Yuan, he screamed: "Tell me if you do not have earth path Immortal Gu, I can lend to you!!"

"You know nothing, shut up!" Fang Yuan rebuked.

"You—!" Ba De had lost all hope, he was about to berate Fang Yuan when his eyes suddenly enlarged, like someone had slammed the back of his head.

Next, he was stunned to see that the second layer of the Gu formation activated, having an imposing aura that was vast as the sea.

"He actually succeeded?!" At once, Ba De felt like he had gone to heaven from hell.

He was dazed on the spot with his mouth wide open.

Qiao Si Liu and the rest arrived, seeing this peculiar scene.

Ba De lost his composure, he was in a daze, it was quite surprising.

"Ba De, what's wrong? Why are you perspiring so much?" Someone coughed and notified of this.

Chapter 1357: Controlling The Righteous Path

Ba De shuddered, when he regained his senses, his face went red as embarrassment flashed on his face for a second.

Fang Yuan concentrated on manipulating the second layer of the Gu formation, before Chi Gui fainted, he had already lent the entire Gu formation to Fang Yuan, he was now the user of the super Gu formation.

Ba Quan Feng's sneak attack, Chi Gui fainting, they all helped Fang Yuan.

"Very good, now, using the super Gu formation, I have a huge hold over others in this battle!"

It was not a waste of Fang Yuan's dark limit Immortal Gu.

This way, he had enough strength to wait for an opportunity.

Earlier, if Fang Yuan used reverse flow protection seal to escape, he would allow Shadow Sect to escape too. But now, he chose to stay and had increased control over the situation, he only had to wait for an opportunity now.

Of course, Fang Yuan did not let down his guard.

He spoke to these righteous path Gu Immortals solemnly: "Get away from me, if anyone gets close, I will consider them a traitor and expel them from the formation."

"What do you mean?" The righteous path Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan, who was vigilant, their expressions changed.

At this moment, Ba De explained for Fang Yuan: "I agree with Wu Yi Hai, nobody is to get near him. Chi Gui fainted from his injuries, it was because of the attack by traitor Ba Quan Feng!"

He told the righteous path Gu Immortals all about the incident earlier.

The righteous path Gu Immortals were all shocked, they knew now: If Fang Yuan did not salvage the formation earlier, the second layer of the Gu Immortal could not be formed, these righteous path Gu Immortals were glad about this, but were also increasingly wary of the Gu Immortals around them.

Ba De looked at Fang Yuan before managing the situation, giving his orders.

There were many righteous path Gu Immortals, Ba De could not awaken Chi Gui who had fainted, but that did not mean that the others could not.

Ba Quan Feng was also interrogated.

The other righteous path Gu Immortals rested and healed their injuries in the meantime, preparing for the intense battle ahead.

At this time, far away from the super Gu formation.

Zuo Ye Hui's aura finally became calm again.

Its huge black body was like an unmoving mountain.

It slowly raised its head and opened its mouth, breathing in deeply.

There were intense currents in the air, countless Gu worms mixed together into a complex aura, spreading outwards with explosive force.

Its body began to expand like a balloon, it had an intense aura.

When it reached its peak, it opened its mouth, as a dark grey beam of light shot out.

The beam of light was incredibly fast, it landed on the second layer of the Gu formation with the speed of lightning!

There was no sound or explosion.

It was completely silent.

But at the second layer of the Gu formation, there was also a grand, bright light. Red representing fire path, green representing wind path, blue representing water path, and black representing dark path, four colors fused together, defending against the grey beam of light.

The Gu formation was creaking.

The righteous path Gu Immortals were all nervous.

If this super Gu formation could not hold on, they would be meat on the chopping block, they might survive the attack if they were lucky, but the unlucky ones would disintegrate immediately.

Many astute people started to observe Fang Yuan's expression.

Fang Yuan was the person manipulating the Gu formation, his every action would affect their mood.

Fang Yuan's expression was calm all along, nobody could read anything from him.

But his calmness meant confidence and safety. The righteous path Gu Immortals gradually relaxed.

A while later, the dark grey beam vanished, while the colorful lights from the Gu formation's second layer also faded.

"We blocked it!"

"Hahaha..."

"Good job, Lord Wu Yi Hai!"

The righteous path Gu Immortals cheered, looking at Fang Yuan in a new light.

"I was not wrong after all, Wu Yi Hai, you saved us all." Chi Gui woke up and muttered, feeling glad.

He was in poor shape now, he still needed Fang Yuan to continue controlling the super Gu formation.

Qiao Si Liu's eyes also turned to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had saved everyone in the righteous path this time and became a hero. Qiao Si Liu did not have good feelings for Fang Yuan earlier, but now, looking at Fang Yuan who was standing straight, her heart was pounding as she has a wondrous feeling.

Immortal killer move grey night against the super Gu formation, it was the contest of spear and shield.

Eventually, the latter won and defended against this terrifying attack.

As the light faded and dust settled, Zuo Ye Hui, who was breathing roughly, looked at the super Gu formation with wide open eyes.

The dream realm was not affected.

It was huge, like a giant pot, with the bottom pointed at the sky, covering the vast land.

In the second layer of the Gu formation, Fang Yuan, Ba De, Qiao Si Liu, and the other righteous path Gu Immortals were protected. This Gu formation had lost its third and fourth layers, it could not conceal the dream realm like before, it could only shield a portion of the dream realm.

"We did not break through?!" Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest were greatly surprised, this was not what Purple Mountain True Monarch had told them.

Not long ago, they had received Purple Mountain True Monarch's transmission, he said that the Gu formation would be destroyed, they had to attack during that opportunity to secure victory.

"Chi Gui had already lost consciousness, what could be the cause." Far away, at the edge of the dream realm, Purple Mountain True Monarch sighed deeply.

This was troublesome!

They had lost the greatest opportunity, but he had no choice but to strike regardless.

Purple Mountain True Monarch, who concealed his figure, could not be detected by the others. After arriving at the dream realm, he had already prepared for a long time.

At this moment, he activated his method!

At once, the world changed colors.

Rainbow light shot into the sky beyond the clouds.

An unparalleled aura, grand and vast like a tsunami, cracked the Gu Immortals' mental fortitude, leaving them in a state of shock.

"What is going on?!" The Gu Immortals on Shadow Sect's side closed their eyes.

The super Gu formation was shaking intensely.

The righteous path Gu Immortals were all flustered: "What is going on? What killer move is this?!"

Fang Yuan's face flashed with nervousness as he announced: "This immortal killer move is not targeting us or the Gu formation, it is targeting the dream realm."

After an intense eruption, the rainbow lights did not fade away. Instead, cocoons of light were formed.

"The... the dream realm is vanishing, condensing into countless cocoons of light."

"Oh my, what method is this? It is causing such a huge commotion."

"Normal methods have no effect on the dream realm, except dream path killer moves!"

"So that's it, these demonic path Gu Immortals are after the dream realm."

The righteous path Gu Immortals called out.

Among them, one looked at Fang Yuan sinisterly: "I said that the immortal opportunity business was a bad idea! It allowed those demonic path Gu Immortals to think of an immortal killer move to make use of the dream realm. This definitely has huge benefits, otherwise, how could so many Gu Immortals disregard all consequences to attack us?"

These words made most of the righteous path Gu Immortals' expressions change.

Fang Yuan heard it and had no reaction.

Ba De snorted angrily, looking at the Xia clan Gu Immortal as he shouted: "Shut up!"

At this moment, he was still trying to sow discord with the enemy right in front of them, and most importantly, he was angering the key person, Fang Yuan, this was simply too stupid, Ba De was furious.

But at the next moment, this Xia clan Gu Immortal vanished on the spot, appearing outside the Gu formation.

"Why, why did he go out?" The righteous path Gu Immortals were stunned, they asked this.

Fang Yuan sneered as he said: "This person has ill intentions, he tried to sow discord, so I sent him outside, after all, trash can be recycled, he can probe out the enemy's ability."

"Rubbish, who gave you the authority to do this, you are disregarding our rights!"

"Quick, let our clan's Gu Immortal back in."

"Quick!"

Fang Yuan smiled coldly as the other Xia clan Gu Immortal who was screaming also vanished.

At the next moment, he appeared outside the super Gu formation, in the outside world. Looking at the huge dream realm and the flickering super Gu formation, he was stunned.

"Wu Yi Hai!" Ba De was anxious, almost jumping up: "Are you messing around on purpose?!"

Fang Yuan looked at him lightly and said: "Make a din and you will leave too."

Ba De was dumbfounded.

The other righteous path Gu Immortals: "..."

Ba De's chest was moving up and down from rage, his face was flushed red, but he spoke: "Don't forget, the Immortal Gu of all our super clans were used to create this super Gu formation!"

He was making a threat.

But Fang Yuan chuckled: "Do you think that at this moment, you can still recall your Gu worms? Haven't you noticed that you have already lost your connection to these Immortal Gu?"

The immortals' expressions changed.

Chi Gui said solemnly: "Sigh, everyone, don't bother. This was the Gu formation created by our clan's Lord Chi Qu You. Earlier, when designing this formation, to guard against traitors and prevent the Gu formation from being destroyed from the inside, the first and second layers can only be controlled by one person, others cannot interfere. Even I cannot control the Gu formation now, unless Wu Yi Hai transfers the ownership back to me again."

Saying this, Chi Gui looked at Fang Yuan sincerely and earnestly.

"Chi Gui, you are heavily injured, you have contributed too much for us, you should heal yourself now." Fang Yuan smiled coldly, crushing Chi Gui's hopes immediately.

Ba De was fuming with rage.

The immortals were also flustered.

In this situation, weren't they at Fang Yuan's mercy?

Qiao Si Liu and the others who were close to Wu clan were fine, but in Ba clan, Yao clan, Yang clan, and others, their Gu Immortals had conflict with Wu clan, their expressions were very ugly.

"Chi Qu You, this old fool!" Some people cursed in their minds.

Chi Qu You had secretly dealt a blow to these super clans, under the justification of defending this dream realm and Gu formation, to keep it safe. But because of this change of events, Chi clan lost control and an outsider took over as the person in charge.

"Don't worry, I, Wu Yi Hai, am not a person who acts without reason. In this situation, us righteous path clans need to work together through thick and thin to get through this crisis."

"My Wu clan is still number one in the righteous path, with such a situation occurring, we will definitely come forward and take on this responsibility."

Chapter 1358: Reappearance of Pure Dream Reality Seeker

"I have good news to share, my Wu clan has an Immortal Gu House secretly on the way here, to bring me back to Wu Yi Mountain. It is not far now, it is our closest reinforcement."

"As long as we work together and cooperate well, we can definitely leave unscathed, we might even do a merit for the righteous path, for everyone living in Southern Border, we will contribute greatly to this region!"

Fang Yuan spoke rapidly.

Ba De's expression turned very ugly.

Qiao Si Liu's eyes were shining, looking at Fang Yuan, her gaze did not shift, she was filled with admiration towards him.

Chi Gui had once gave Fang Yuan the information path Gu worm and told him all about the super Gu formation. Thus, when Fang Yuan realized he could control this Gu formation by himself, he decided to lead all of the righteous path Gu Immortals.

Xia clan's two Gu Immortals were unlucky people that Fang Yuan had used to assert his dominance.

After that, he gave great news regarding the Immortal Gu House.

With both the stick and carrot, he successfully got the righteous path Gu Immortals under him, becoming a force that he could manipulate.

There were no lack of elites in the righteous path, but Fang Yuan had the initiative, his advantage was too large, because of this situation, they had no choice but to obey him.

Fang Yuan's actions turned the situation around, right now, even Ba De had to listen to him.

After successfully controlling these righteous path Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan turned his attention towards the outside world.

Many cocoons of light had already formed, quietly floating in the sky.

The price for creating these light cocoons was the dream realm.

Large pieces of the dream realm vanished entirely. The originally round and intact giant dream realm now had holes in it, it was like cheese that was eaten by rats with holes all over.

More than twenty cocoons of light had formed, and more of them were gradually condensing.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan sighed: Shadow Sect's methods were truly endless. Indeed worthy of the super force created by a Demon Venerable which had a hundred thousand years of accumulation!

Crack...

At this time, waves of cracking noises could be heard from the first cocoon.

Next, cracks appeared on the light cocoon.

Bam.

The cocoon of light broke as a nude person fell out!

Before landing on the ground, Purple Mountain True Monarch, who had waited for a long time, acted rapidly.

Large numbers of Gu worms flew out and surrounded the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body, before entering their immortal aperture.

Soon, this person opened their eyes, their entire body was covered in clothing as they flew towards the edge of the dream realm without stopping.

"This?!"

The other righteous path Gu Immortals were stunned, but Fang Yuan's eyes were wide open.

"This is the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique!" Fang Yuan had seen it before, seeing it again, he was still stunned.

In the past, Ying Wu Xie had the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique.

This immortal body was a man-made extreme physique. Shadow Sect's Old Man Yan Shi had researched it for a long time, how did Purple Mountain True Monarch get a hold of this method?

Don't forget, Ying Wu Xie was still alive, and Purple Mountain True Monarch had entered the River of Time through great risks, interacting deeply with Spectral Soul's will inside the Red Lotus true inheritance.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had wanted to cooperate with Fang Yuan, but because of his low information path foundation, he rejected it.

Thus, even though Purple Mountain True Monarch knew that Fang Yuan had methods to deal with the dream realm, he could not make use of them.

He wanted to save Spectral Soul's main body, other than the super Gu formation, there was also the huge obstacle, the giant dream realm.

Fang Yuan was not helpful, thus, Purple Mountain True Monarch placed his focus on the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique.

This way, with the bulk of the dream realms vanishing, he could get to the center of the dream realm and save Spectral Soul.

"This means, the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique is created like this?"

"Shadow Sect's methods... are truly fearsome!"

Even though Fang Yuan had fought against Ying Wu Xie back then, he did not know about his origin.

After finally seeing it, Fang Yuan shouted loudly, ordering the righteous path Gu Immortals: "Quick, destroy all these cocoons! We need to kill the one who just left!!"

"What is going on?"

"Wu Yi Hai, what do you know? Tell us!"

The righteous path Gu Immortals asked.

But at the next moment, they were teleported by Fang Yuan, to the outside of the super Gu formation.

"The f*ck!"

"Not even saying a word, who does he think we are?"

"Wu Yi Hai, you are using our clan's Immortal Gu, don't go overboard!!"

Even Qiao Si Liu was sent out, this Southern Border fairy was a little dazed, she could not accept it.

Xia clan's two Gu Immortals saw that so many righteous path Gu Immortals had landed in their plight, they felt extremely satisfied, they shouted loudly to take down Wu Yi Hai.

But nobody gave them any attention. In this situation, who would dare to offend Fang Yuan, who controlled the super Gu formation?

Fang Yuan transmitted: "If you do not want to die here, listen to me. These enemies will grow stronger with time, now is the best time to eliminate them!"

While the others hesitated, Wu Liao had already listened to Fang Yuan and acted.

Next, Gu Immortals close to Wu clan including Qiao Si Liu also moved. But because Fang Yuan shifted her out along with the others, this woman, who was one of the three great fairies of Southern Border, had an ugly expression and mood.

These people acted quickly, soon, the righteous path Gu Immortals started to fight.

One one hand, Fang Yuan controlled the super Gu formation, he controlled their safety. Secondly, the righteous path forces had deep interest in exploring the dream realm. They had desire towards these immortal bodies created from the dream realm. As long as they captured one of them and researched it, their clan's dream path development would rise rapidly.

Only Xia clan's two Gu Immortals were hesitant.

But Fang Yuan did not forget them, he transmitted: "As long as you each kill a cocoon, I will spare you and let you return to the Gu formation."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals were furious, they gritted their teeth, but they had no choice! After looking at each other, they acted according to Fang Yuan's words.

Almost all the righteous path Gu Immortals had moved, killing and destroying the cocoons of light.

Only Fang Yuan stayed in the super Gu formation alone, overseeing the battle from the base, it was truly relaxing.

Strive for every second!

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies broke out of the cocoons of light as they flew out.

At the same time, when the cocoons were destroyed, the dream realms that had vanished appeared again.

"Spectral Soul's main body is inside the dream realm. Shadow Sect has planned this well, creating Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies to obscure our vision. Among these flying Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, there might be Spectral Soul's remnant soul!"

Fang Yuan stared as he controlled the super Gu formation, manipulating the battlefield intently.

This super Gu formation was built around the giant dream realm originally. Even though only the second layer of the Gu formation was active now, Fang Yuan could still control half of the battlefield, he could teleport Gu Immortals nearby.

Not only did the righteous path Gu Immortals act, Fang Yuan also manipulated the Gu formation, using its power to destroy the cocoons.

Unfortunately, this super Gu formation was built on the basis of defense, it was pitifully weak in attack, far weaker than Fang Yuan's own attacks.

"Kill!" At this moment, shouting could be heard.

With Fairy Miao Yin, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing leading, Shadow Sect's Gu Immortals had arrived.

This wave of Gu Immortals were far less in numbers, but in this complex battle situation, the disadvantage in numbers was easy to cover.

The original giant dream realm was intact, resembling a turned over pot covering the ground.

Next, because of the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies forming, large pieces of the dream realm went missing.

Some cocoons of light were destroyed by righteous path Gu Immortals, and the dream realm appeared again, but it was much smaller than before, this caused the dream realm to not be as complete as before, there was a difference.

Some of the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were killed and created a huge dream realm on the spot. Because the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies had flown away and were not at the original spots, this caused patches of dream realms to be formed outside of the original dream realm.

Don't forget, this giant dream realm itself had movement.

Thus, large patches of dream realms were all over the place, some overlapped while some were isolated, and some were only a thin line away from being connected, they were in the sky and on the ground, the terrain was truly very complicated.

When fighting here, Gu Immortals had to be very wary, they had to guard against the dream realms and could not fall into dreams.

"Creating so many Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, it must be Purple Mountain True Monarch. But where is he?"

Fang Yuan looked around using the super Gu formation, but he could not find Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Rumble!

With an intense sound, the super Gu formation burst out with power, as a shadow flew towards a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body that had just broken out of its cocoon, crashing onto it like a mountain.

Suppressed!

Without Gu worms to help them, the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body was easily suppressed, before the super Gu formation teleported them to Fang Yuan.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body stared at Fang Yuan fiercely, tied by black chains and unable to move.

Fang Yuan sized it up, his eyes shined brightly.

"Interesting, if I can capture a few more, I might be able to deduce this method of Shadow Sect and create my own Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies."

"This is the extreme physique of dream path, even though it has a short lifespan, it might be able to help me resolve huge issues in critical moments!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan searched for Purple while using the super Gu formation to capture newly formed Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

The second layer's coverage was less than half of the dream realm, while the domain he controlled was even smaller.

But cocoons of light continued to form, as Fang Yuan struck multiple times, he actually captured close to ten Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

He soon had a shocking discovery — these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies did not have rising cultivation levels as time passed. Among them, some had rank six immortal bodies while others were mortals, only a very small number had rank seven cultivation level.

Chapter 1359: Heavenly Court's Interference

Fang Yuan also found something interesting.

The time that these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies could live was inversely correlated to their cultivation level. The higher their cultivation level, the shorter the duration they could live. In contrast, those Gu Master Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies could live for two to three years, they were good research material for Fang Yuan, he had ample time to do so.

"Earlier, I was wondering why Shadow Sect did not use the method to mass produce Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies during the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain if possible."

"Now it seems, the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique that created Ying Wu Xie was not this simple."

"In order to save their main body, Shadow Sect had to use this method to create many Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, to disperse and get rid of the dream realms. They have great determination!"

Fang Yuan sighed as he realized Shadow Sect's firm and determined attitude.

Not only did Fang Yuan capture some Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, the other righteous path Gu Immortals were not stupid, they also had some captives.

These Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were the dream path fruits of Shadow Sect's research. Once anyone successfully researched on them, they would have an explosive breakthrough in the exploration of dream realms.

Shadow Sect did this without hesitation in order to save Spectral Soul's main body.

The scene was very chaotic.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was not discovered, he was still continuing to create more Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

More and more cocoons of light were starting to appear in the dream realm area.

Pieces of dream realms were cluttered together in a messy fashion, creating a complex terrain. Both the righteous path and demonic path were surrounding the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, engaging in fierce battles.

Even though Fang Yuan's side was doing their best to obstruct them, because the battlefield was too chaotic, some Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies managed to leave the battlefield amidst the confusion.

"Damn it! Spectral Soul's main body might be hiding among these bodies." Fang Yuan observed and was about to attack from afar, when suddenly!

Light that was sharp as a needle descended from the sky.

Instantly, the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body's skull was pierced.

This white light that was extremely thin was very sharp, it moved down from the skull of the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body and penetrated his entire body.

It appeared instantly and vanished just as quickly.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body that was hit was rank six.

He instantly felt that his body had no strength, he was extremely weak. He showed suspicion on his face as he raised his hand to touch the top of his head.

Next, he placed his hand in front of him and saw that there was blood mixed with brain matter.

His expression changed abruptly, there was disbelief and fear.

Next, his vision turned dark as he lost his life. His corpse fell onto the ground from the sky like a rag doll.

Instantly, blood sprayed out, bones were broken, it was almost a pile of mush, the body was completely dead.

"Hmm? Who is it?!" Fang Yuan saw this and his pupils shrunk.

He was the person in charge of the situation, among the righteous path, he was the first to observe this.

Meanwhile, on the demonic path's side, Purple Mountain True Monarch was creating cocoons of light while managing the situation.

Seeing this, he was not confused, he frowned deeply: "Heavenly Court finally acted!"

He had expected this, he had some arrangements in white heaven, Heaven Overseeing Tower was obstructed for a while.

But unfortunately, Fang Yuan salvaged the situation, Purple Mountain True Monarch's plan was greatly disrupted.

The super Gu formation and the righteous path Gu Immortals greatly hindered Purple Mountain True Monarch's plan to saving his main body.

The best timing was lost, Heaven Overseeing Tower broke free of the obstruction and finally acted, joining this huge battle.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

After several soft sounds, several small traces of white light shot out and easily killed all of the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies who tried to leave the battlefield.

Next, a grand Immortal Gu House appeared from the sky with shining light, as if a deity had descended upon the battlefield.

Such an incredible sight attracted the attention of many Gu Immortals, they quickly looked up at the sky.

A few of them were dazed, but most Gu Immortals instantly recognized Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heavenly Court's Heaven Overseeing Tower, it was too famous!

Heavenly Court?!

Almost all the Gu Immortals were intensely shocked.

Heavenly Court's imposing entrance made this chaotic battle go into even more uncertainty.

At the top of Heaven Overseeing Tower, Duke Long crossed his hand and stood upright like a tower, observing the entire battlefield.

"Spectral Soul is too devious, we cannot let a single Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body off, they need to die! Of course, these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies could just be distractions, Spectral Soul might be lurking in other Gu Immortals' bodies to escape. Thus, all of the Gu Immortals present need to be killed too, it is better to be safe than sorry!"

"Yes!" Behind Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei and the Gu Immortals she led responded in unison.

Duke Long pondered before saying: "We will kill Shadow Sect before eliminating the righteous path. But if anyone tries to leave the battlefield, no matter who, we will exterminate them!"

Heaven Overseeing Tower pressed down on the battlefield like an imposing mountain with vast power.

The chaotic battlefield froze.

Heaven Overseeing Tower had the greatest battle strength, its movement decided the flow of this battle.

The righteous path Gu Immortals' hearts were pounding.

Heavenly Court... these were Central Continent Gu Immortals, were they reinforcements?

Shadow Sect's side fell into panic.

Evidently, Heavenly Court and Shadow Sect were enemies.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim, looking at rank nine Immortal Gu House Heaven Overseeing Tower, he frowned deeply.

He had somewhat expected this to happen.

"Heavenly Court appeared again, the situation is horrible. They actually rebuilt Heaven Overseeing Tower in such a short time! I wonder how many rank eight Gu Immortals came this time!"

Heaven Overseeing Tower's appearance was a huge blow to Fang Yuan's plans.

But thankfully, Fang Yuan was inside the super Gu formation, it could defend against Heaven Overseeing Tower's might.

Fang Yuan had the experience of battling against Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Even if the strongest attack from fate Gu was used, Fang Yuan estimated that this super Gu formation could endure one attack!

Fang Yuan decided to observe for now, but Purple Mountain True Monarch could not do nothing.

He was a rank eight wisdom path Gu Immortal, how could he not have backup plans?

Purple Mountain True Monarch transmitted: "Zuo Ye Hui, according to our agreement, your enemy is here, what are you waiting for? They are from Heavenly Court!"

"Heavenly Court?!" Legendary immemorial desolate beast Zuo Ye Hui heard this as its body shuddered, intense rage and hatred could be seen in its eyes.

This rage and hatred was embedded into its soul, even after a million years, it still felt this deeply.

"Heavenly Court!!" Zuo Ye Hui roared, the sound waves burst out and swept an immense surrounding area.

Boom!

At the next moment, vast darkness burs tout from Zuo Ye Hui's body. Its body was huge to begin with, now, under the cover of the dark mist, it became increasingly terrifying.

Next, its legs bent as its body arched, it bared its teeth and stomped the ground.

Bam.

There was an intense sound, the ground shook harshly.

A huge pit was created under Zuo Ye Hui, while it shot out like an arrow, through the sky, towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heaven Overseeing Tower burst out with power, but Zuo Ye Hui was covered in dark mist, it was evidently an immortal killer move, allowing it to fly and defend itself.

Zuo Ye Hui moved like a bamboo spear or a huge meteorite, in a few breaths of time, it traveled a hundred li, arriving at Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"Hmph! Insolent fool." Duke Long snorted in disdain, his majestic body shook as his thoughts collided, Heaven Overseeing Tower burst out with an intense white light.

At once, the world turned white.

Heaven Overseeing Tower's strongest method — Fate Vanquish!

Rank nine Immortal Gu Fate's power was unrivaled.

There was no way of dodging. As long as one was not rank nine, no matter how powerful, they would lose to this move.

Light was everywhere.

White light.

Filling the world from all directions.

The Gu Immortals exposed to the light, be it righteous path or demonic path, coughed out blood. They were instantly heavily injured, most fainted on the spot.

At once, half the battlefield was cleared.

There were some Gu Immortals who were shielded by the dream realm, they were not exposed to the light and were saved.

With a loud sound, even Zuo Ye Hui could not block the attack of Fate, it crashed to the ground.

It coughed out blood, but soon, it crawled up and opened its mouth, roaring at Heaven Overseeing Tower.

In Heaven Overseeing Tower, the Central Continent Gu Immortals all had shocked expressions.

Even Duke Long was surprised.

Zuo Ye Hui did not die from fate vanquish, that was normal. It was far sturdier than normal Immortal Gu Houses, and had incredible regenerative properties.

Zuo Ye Hui was the problem of Southern Border for ages, Southern Border's Gu Immortal world had mobilized Immortal Gu Houses to kill it, but could not, they only defeated it.

But Zuo Ye Hui's injury was far less severe than Duke Long's expectations.

Gu Immortals could cultivate, so could Zuo Ye Hui. After all these years, Zuo Ye Hui had been getting stronger. Moreover, it was helped by Shadow Sect this time. Purple Mountain True Monarch purposely lent it a lot of Immortal Gu and large numbers of immortal killer moves, Zuo Ye Hui was fully armed.

Zuo Ye Hui stood up again, half of its injuries had healed.

This was a terrifying recovery speed!

It pounced at Heaven Overseeing Tower again fearlessly.

A cold light shined in Duke Long's eyes, he used fate vanquish again.

Zuo Ye Hui was hit and landed on the ground again, but soon, it stood up, even though it was injured again, it was full of vitality.

Central Continent's Gu Immortals were intensely shocked.

"This is the battle strength of a legendary immemorial desolate beast? It is truly stunning!"

"It is a bit troublesome." Fairy Zi Wei had a grim expression. Zuo Ye Hui's battle strength was out of her imagination, even though Heaven Overseeing Tower had fate vanquish, it could not be used consecutively.

After all, rank nine Immortal Gu Fate still had injuries on it.

Chapter 1360: Fang Yuan's Desperate Situation

Roar!

Zuo Ye Hui growled, this time, it flew to the sky, and stayed in midair to attack Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Duke Long sneered, activating Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Turn phantom!

Zuo Ye Hui missed its target.

The entirety of Heaven Overseeing Tower, including the Gu Immortals inside, turned phantom. Normal methods could not hit them at all.

"This is on purpose? To lure me to attack?" Purple Mountain True Monarch, who was concealed, saw this as bright light flashed in his eyes.

Shadow Sect had methods to counter the phantom form.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch did not act against the phantom Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Because he was not Spectral Soul's main body, he did not have all the Immortal Gu needed to counter the phantom form. Even if he used them, against Heaven Overseeing Tower, it was too inefficient.

"He did not act?" Duke Long thought to himself.

In the past, during the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Spectral Soul had sealed the phantom Heaven Overseeing Tower and prevented it from returning to solid.

Duke Long had specially prepared well against this killer move, but Purple Mountain True Monarch was really patient, he did not do anything.

Duke Long controlled the phantom Heaven Overseeing Tower and tried to get closer to the dream realm.

Once the huge Heaven Overseeing Tower entered the dream realm, it started to fade from its phantom form, some Gu worms by the fringe were devoured by the dream realm.

"Phantom methods are useless too." Duke Long's heart shook, bringing Heaven Overseeing Tower away from the dream realm.

This was the first time Duke Long was seeing an actual dream realm.

This was something related to Great Dream Immortal Venerable, Duke Long was quite surprised.

Even though Heaven Overseeing Tower was in phantom form, the dream realm still devoured a corner of it. The Central Continent Gu Immortals in Heaven Overseeing Tower were quickly trying to repair it.

"Without any dream path methods, even Heaven Overseeing Tower will get lost inside the dream realm." Duke Long concluded.

One skill to dominate the world!

Back then, Ying Wu Xie with Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique could use lead soul into dream killer move and directly make Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord go to sleep.

Evidently, even the powerful rank nine Immortal Gu House could not defend against the might of dream path.

Unless it was an Immortal Gu House with dream path Immortal Gu, normal Immortal Gu Houses would get lost in the dream realm without resistance.

"This means, this battlefield is not good for Heaven Overseeing Tower to fight. Heaven Overseeing Tower is too big, it is far less agile than Gu Immortals fighting alone." Duke Long looked at the growling Zuo Ye Hui as light flashed in his eyes.

At this moment, Heaven Overseeing Tower returned to solid form as Zuo Ye Hui chased after it.

Heaven Overseeing Tower turned and accelerated, rushing towards a dream realm.

Zuo Ye Hui flew in the sky, moving even more quickly, its huge body was like a black cloud, winds were wild as it moved towards Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"Oh no!" Purple Mountain True Monarch saw this and quickly stopped it.

A mystical light flew out and landed on Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heaven Overseeing Tower's speed slowed, it became illusory as ripples appeared, like it was the surface of water.

"Fake?" Zuo Ye Hui quickly stopped.

It almost went into the dream realm.

The dream realm was incredibly dangerous to Zuo Ye Hui as well.

Behind it, the real Heaven Overseeing Tower appeared.

"Hehehe." Duke Long stood at the top of the tower, his dragon eyes looking coldly at a certain place.

Purple Mountain True Monarch sighed, knowing that this was a trap.

Duke Long was seemingly trying to trap Zuo Ye Hui, but the truth was, he wanted to find out Purple Mountain True Monarch's location.

But even if Purple Mountain True Monarch knew of Duke Long's plans, he had no choice but to act.

Because Zuo Ye Hui was too valuable of a fighting force, it could not be lost, Shadow Sect needed it to defend against Heaven Overseeing Tower.

"Lingering split soul of Spectral Soul, hmph, I will kill him. Fairy Zi Wei, go deal with that super Gu formation and kill Fang Yuan. The others will control Heaven Overseeing Tower and leave this place. Zuo Ye Hui will surely follow, I do not need success, I just do not want failure." Duke Long ordered, as everyone responded.

With the roar of a dragon, Duke Long turned into a mystical light and charged at Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Meanwhile, Fairy Zi Wei charged at the super Gu formation.

Heaven Overseeing Tower brought the Central Continent Gu Immortals and flew into the sky, leaving the battlefield.

Zuo Ye Hui looked at Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, and finally, Heaven Overseeing Tower.

It knew that it was highly restricted in this battlefield because of its size, and because it liked to move around fast.

Meanwhile, Heaven Overseeing Tower had an aura that it detested, and was the symbol of Heaven Overseeing Tower, it had a deep desire to destroy this tower.

Duke Long flew in the sky, turning into a phantom shadow as he appeared before Purple Mountain True Monarch instantly.

He had a tall and majestic body, the dragon horn on his head was sharp and imposing, his dragon pupils revealed dominance and indifference.

Boom boom boom!

Purple Mountain True Monarch fought Duke Long.

A few breaths later, Purple Mountain True Monarch could not fight on par with him, he had to run away.

"You will die today." Duke Long roared, chasing relentlessly.

In the super Gu formation, Fang Yuan was breaking out in cold sweat.

He realized that he had fallen into a trap!

"Heaven's will! It was actually hiding in... no, rather than that..." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to pin size, sweat poured down his face.

At this moment, Fairy Zi Wei had already arrived in front of the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan calmed himself down, activating the super Gu formation and defending against this enemy.

"This Gu formation is not bad." Fairy Zi Wei's eyes shined with purple light, she observed the super Gu formation and nodded: "It is a pity, there is a flaw, these Gu worms are of different sources, the user of the Gu formation is borrowing other people's Immortal Gu, but this can be used by me."

As she said that, she raised her right hand, which was holding an Immortal Gu House.

Star Constellation Chessboard!

This Immortal Gu House was personally created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it was possibly the smallest Immortal Gu House in the world.

When the chessboard was activated, it changed into crystal starlight that filled the sky.

Starlight moved around like fireflies, surrounding Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei's human body was assimilated by this starlight, turning into starlight and joining them.

The starlight expanded slightly, pouncing at the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan was already vigilantly waiting, he activated the Gu formation and attacked the starlight.

But the starlight completely ignored the Gu formation's attack, it started to infiltrate the super Gu formation.

Originally, this super Gu formation was shining in four profound colors of red, green, blue, and black. But now, with the invasion of the starlight, these four lights weakened as starlight mixed in, Fang Yuan felt a sense of sluggishness from the super Gu formation.

"Fang Yuan, you were an otherworldly demon chosen by heaven's will and tasked to save the people of this world. Even though you destroyed Shadow Sect's heaven defying plan, you took a wrong step and betrayed the righteous path, entering the demonic path and becoming enemies with the world. If you admit your mistake now and surrender, I will leave you with a complete corpse, I will make a biography for you after death so that your name will go down in history as a lesson for the future."

At this time, Fairy Zi Wei's voice came from the super Gu formation.

Fang Yuan laughed as he said: "This is truly an incredible scheme by heaven's will!"

As he said that, he tried to activate the super Gu formation.

The Gu formation was still under his control, but it was getting incredibly hard to use, some mortal Gu by the fringe were vanishing from Fang Yuan's control.

Evidently, Fairy Zi Wei was fighting with him over the control of this super Gu formation.

"Stubborn fool." Fairy Zi Wei had a cold voice, seeing Fang Yuan's struggle, she put in more effort.

The starlight shining in the super Gu formation became brighter.

"Heavenly Court knows my identity, this proves my conjecture."

"I cannot take back dark limit Immortal Gu anymore, as time passes, the super Gu formation will go under Heavenly Court's control."

"What do I do? Do I discard the super Gu formation and activate reverse flow protection seal to escape?"

"No!"

"Heavenly Court has fought with me before, they definitely know about reverse flow protection seal."

"Since they want to eliminate both me and Shadow Sect, how could they not consider the element of reverse flow protection seal?"

"Heavenly Court wants to see me rely solely on this move. If my killer move is broken, I will face a backlash, I will lose all my battle strength and even die immediately!"

"What should I do?"

Thoughts moved in Fang Yuan's mind like a huge storm was brewing.

It was a desperate situation.

Fang Yuan thought of how he could leave the battlefield.

There was no way!

He could not otherwise escape. His only hope was reverse flow protection seal.

"Should I bet that Heavenly Court has no method against reverse flow protection seal?"

Fang Yuan had a bitter expression.

He knew that the chances were slim in this regard.

As for the upper extreme heavenly eagle?

Fang Yuan did not have heavenly crystals, the upper extreme heavenly eagle could not become an immemorial desolate beast.

Even if he had a lot of heavenly crystals, an immemorial desolate beast upper extreme heavenly eagle may not be under his control.

The upper extreme heavenly eagle was prideful and only submitted to strong experts, there was a huge chance of betrayal. Just that slight relationship it had with Fang Yuan was fragile and unreliable.

"There are two ways of stalling." Fang Yuan thought of two methods.

The first was to bring out Reverse Flow River and placed himself inside like a fortress.

The second was to put himself in his immortal aperture, placing in Southern Border and closing his immortal aperture's entrance shut.

But both methods only stalled for time, they could not change the situation.

If Fang Yuan used these methods, he would be giving up the initiative.

This was very dangerous.

The only hope in these two methods letting Fang Yuan escape was Southern Border's righteous path reinforcements.

If Southern Border's Gu Immortals could repel Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan might be able to escape.

But Heavenly Court was not stupid or weak.

The overall strength of Southern Border's righteous path was definitely stronger than the group from Central Continent that was here. But whether the reinforcements could handle Heaven Overseeing Tower and Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, that was uncertain.

Even if they won and Heavenly Court was chased away, could Fang Yuan continue to be Wu Yi Hai?

How could that be possible!

Since Heavenly Court knew his identity, they just needed a few words to get Southern Border to turn on Fang Yuan.

Wu Yi Hai's identity could not last if the entire Southern Border righteous path was investigating it.

Chapter 1361: Purple Mountain True Monarch versus Duke Long

Swish, swish!

Killing intent surged, two figures flew rapidly between dream realms.

Purple Mountain True Monarch against Duke Long!

They were extremely fast, like meteors in the sky, but they were incredibly agile like snakes.

Boom boom boom!

As both sides fought, explosions could be heard.

Waves of air currents crashed imposingly, but after getting to any dream realm, they dissipated.

The two rank eight Gu Immortals fought, one was a first generation split soul of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, having cultivated for a hundred thousand years. The other was unknown in history, but was a legend of Heavenly Court, having quasi-rank nine power.

Undeniably, the fight between these two was the core and essence of this battle of the giant dream realm battle, and was the most intense.

Heaven Overseeing Tower and Zuo Ye Hui collided, it was far less important than the fight between those two.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes flickered with crystal purple light, his arms were stretched out as small rocks resembling charcoal appeared around his body.

The rocks flew out and became larger in the air, the surface of the rocks burned with raging red flames.

Thousands of fiery rocks charged at Duke Long like a meteorite storm.

Duke Long took the attack head on, not dodging.

As the fiery rocks hit his body, he was surrounded by a light resembling a cloud.

The cloud light did not move, but soon, Duke Long found that a fire was burning inside his mind.

His thoughts were moving, but the fire was burning up these thoughts.

The cloud light needed to be maintained by Duke Long, thoughts about it were constantly created. Now that they were burned, this defense was gone.

The fiery rocks thus landed harshly on Duke Long's body.

At once, there were loud sounds as fiery rocks landed on Duke Long's muscular and tall iron-like body, like eggs, these fiery rocks broke and shattered, exploding as sparks poured out along with rock fragments.

Duke Long continued to charge, his body had a terrifying accumulation of dao marks, he also had defensive methods similar to Bi Chen Tian's wood armor and Fang Yuan's ghostly concealment.

His aura was shocking, like a wild dragon in human form, he endured Purple Mountain True Monarch's attacks as he moved unceasingly.

His dragon eyes were cold and indifferent, Duke Long had no expression except a cold look.

He did not frown, Purple Mountain True Monarch's immortal killer move seemed like a gust of wind, harmless and weak.

Duke Long had a very powerful disposition, Purple Mountain True Monarch was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he focused on his tactic, he retreated as he fought.

The fiery rocks could do nothing to Duke Long, but Purple Mountain True Monarch was smirking.

He stretched out his left index finger, pointing at Duke Long who was chasing after him.

Immediately, flowers bloomed.

On Duke Long's body, countless flowers grew out of nowhere.

Fresh flowers blossomed, thousands of them covered Duke Long's body.

Duke Long had a strong body with shocking defense, but when the flowers bloomed, his expression finally changed.

"Consecutive move."

For the first time, Duke Long stopped his chase as he floated in the air.

Even though he was flying at a rapid speed, he could immediately stop moving, anyone would sigh at his amazing movement method, and his incredibly strong physique.

The flowers were blooming at an increasing rate on Duke Long's body.

The petals were tender and fragile, but they were a huge problem to Duke Long.

Duke Long stretched out his right hand, he grabbed into a fist and after a while, opened his hand.

Poof.

With an explosive sound, his right hand burst out with countless faint pale air currents.

These air currents were like threads flying in the sky, circulating around Duke Long's entire body continuously.

Waves of air currents were like sharp blades, getting rid of the flowers on his body.

At once, flower petals floated in the air, as these flowers were eradicated.

The air currents seemed weak, but were extremely sharp, after a few breaths of time, the flowers on Duke Long were all wiped out.

Purple Mountain True Monarch saw this and his pupils shrunk.

Duke Long's killer move was incredible sharp, it was not about the mass of the air currents, but the technique involved in manipulating them that was extremely profound.

Originally, this was a method to deal with enemies, but Duke Long controlled it for use on himself. If he was careless, he would get injured.

But Duke Long was proficient and daring, he was extremely confident in this move, he could use it like moving his fingers, many of the air currents grazed his skin and clothing, but he was completely unharmed, he had complete control of his actions, it was truly superb.

However, with this amount of time, Purple Mountain True Monarch was ready with his move.

Immortal killer moves had difficulties in activation. If Zhao Lian Yun was in Purple Mountain True Monarch's position, she might likely fail her activation of the killer move.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch was incredibly experienced and resolute, he used this chance without doubt.

An immortal killer move was activated.

Illusions appeared, surrounding Purple Mountain True Monarch, there were dozens of purple light illusions.

These illusions were still increasing, one turned into four while four turned into ten, they formed into a huge army.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's true body was concealed as the purple light illusion army charged at Duke Long.

Duke Long snorted coldly, his right hand turned into a dragon claw as he waved.

Claw marks appeared in the air out of nowhere, they were several meters long, everywhere they went, purple light illusions collapsed.

Next, Duke Long's left hand also turned into a dragon claw, he slashed at another area as the marks extended, almost creating wounds in space.

The purple light illusions were quickly eradicated, Duke Long's dragon eyes shined as a mystical light surrounded a secluded space.

Purple Mountain True Monarch knew that his location was exposed, he came out.

Both sides were standing in the air, with the backdrop of countless messy dream realms, they were a thousand steps apart.

"It seems that after such a long time of sleeping, you're still able to keep up with the times." Purple Mountain True Monarch said plainly, he was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, his long robe was fluttering as his purple hair swayed, his gaze was focused and he was in his top condition.

"I practised a bit recently. The times are always changing, there were too many geniuses in the last million years, there are simply too many new incredible methods now." Duke Long sighed.

He sighed before continuing: "Alright, enough with these petty tricks, the probing is over, let's use our real methods now."

Purple Mountain True Monarch smiled, nodding: "Indeed."

At the next moment, both of them collided like two flashes of lightning.

Boom boom boom...

Dazzling rainbow lights shone like fireworks, when used, the surrounding dream realms became even more illusory and enchanting.

"These two fellows, seriously..." Fang Yuan was observing the battlefield with the super Gu formation.

After observing Purple Mountain True Monarch's and Duke Long's fight, Fang Yuan was speechless.

"Both of them are rank eight Gu Immortals, and not ordinary ones at that, they are simply too strong!"

"Normally speaking, when Gu Immortals first fight, they would use mortal Gu and mortal killer moves. Only when they fight seriously will they use Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves. But these two directly used immortal killer moves to probe each other."

"These two have at least great grandmaster attainment level. Be it the fiery rocks, flowers, or the air currents and cloud light, they are all mimicry of other paths."

"If I do not use reverse flow protection seal, I would lose terribly in one move."

"So intense!"

"The two of them are fighting with greater intensity now, their firepower has increased!"

Information was very important to Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan used the super Gu formation to observe them, he had huge gains.

Be it Purple Mountain True Monarch or Duke Long, Fang Yuan was not their match. Even if he used reverse flow protection seal, he would only passively take a beating.

As a matter of fact, during the battle of Northern Plains' Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan was able to escape because of the chaotic situation.

Eventually, Fang Yuan used the regional wall to escape from dog tail life extending ferret Mao Li Qiu.

"With my own strength, it is hard to escape from such a situation, hope is slim!" Fang Yuan's frown deepened.

At this moment, his expression changed.

It turned out that in his immortal aperture, an information path Gu worm brought words from Wu Yong.

"Wu Yong did not die, Qiao Zhi Cai and Tie Mian Shen are alive too, they are only trapped for the time being. They are trying to get here with an Immortal Gu House!"

Wu Yong told Fang Yuan to hold on and hold onto his life, it was fine even if he escaped.

He even told Fang Yuan that Chi clan's first supreme elder, Chi Qu You, was also bringing an Immortal Gu House here as backup, but he was still farther away than Wu Yong.

Not just the two of them, the other super forces also sent their Immortal Gu Houses.

Southern Border's righteous path super clans were in conflict, but after hearing Wu Yong's words about the giant dream realm's situation, they immediately went into ceasefire and worked together, gathering and moving towards the giant dream realm.

Looking at the entirety of Southern Border from a bird's eye view, Yi Tian Mountain was at the center of Southern Border towards the west, while the super forces were scattered in all directions, all heading towards the center.

Fang Yuan had a complex expression.

If he was Wu Yi Hai, upon hearing this, he would be overjoyed and have improved morale.

But he was not.

He was Fang Yuan.

Once Southern Border's reinforcements came, Heavenly Court would expose his identity, chaos would ensue, Fang Yuan would be all alone.

"As for Wu Yong..." Fang Yuan sighed.

This brother, his biggest backer, would turn into an extremely strong enemy chasing after him in the future.

Fang Yuan killed the real Wu Yi Hai, even if Wu Yong did not care about his brother and did not want revenge, because of his righteous path status, he needed to take revenge and kill Fang Yuan.

One could say, Fang Yuan and Wu Yong had an unresolvable conflict.

"Wu clan actually had another Immortal Gu House! Wu Yong was really good at concealing himself. But even though he is very fast, as the closest reinforcement around, he still needs at least a day to get here."

Fang Yuan rapidly calculated.

When the reinforcements arrived and Heavenly Court exposed Fang Yuan's identity, would he be able to escape amidst the chaos?

Chapter 1362: For Now... Cooperate

Hope was slim.

It was a chaotic three-way battle now.

Heavenly Court's forces were number one.

Shadow Sect was number two because of their rank eight battle strengths, Purple Mountain True Monarch and Zuo Ye Hui.

Southern Border's righteous path forces were third, even with the super Gu formation, it was stationary and even Fairy Zi Wei's Star Constellation Chessboard could infiltrate it.

As for Fang Yuan, he was a Southern Border righteous path member on the surface, but the truth was, he was closer to Shadow Sect's side, he was a unique person.

Based on the battle situation, Heavenly Court and Southern Border's righteous path were attacking Shadow Sect.

Shadow Sect was unable to rival Heavenly Court, now that they were attacked by another side, they were in the worst position.

"One day, it takes at least one day to get here."

"In this current situation, if the situation continues like this, I cannot hold on until then."

"Moreover, once Shadow Sect falls, Heavenly Court and Southern Border's righteous path would deal with me, the traitor, together."

"Shadow Sect's loss is just one aspect, this super Gu formation is also unable to hold on for a day!"

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze, he looked at this super Gu formation worriedly.

Because of Chi Qu You's design, this super Gu formation's second layer could only be controlled by one person, others were useless. Thus, even if Fang Yuan intended to recall the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals, they were unable to resist Fairy Zi Wei's invasion.

Moreover, Fang Yuan's identity was a problem.

If these Southern Border Gu Immortals learned about Fang Yuan's true identity from Heavenly Court, regardless of whether they believed it or not, or whatever action they take, it meant there would be unknown danger for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had naturally thought of the first layer of the Gu formation.

This super Gu formation had four layers, Fang Yuan was only controlling the second layer, there was still a first layer.

If Fairy Zi Wei succeeded, Fang Yuan would destroy the second layer of the Gu formation, in theory, he could activate the first layer and resist her.

But, according to Chi Gui's information path Gu worm, the user of this first layer must be a Chi clan Gu Immortal.

This was Chi Qu You's personal arrangement, from his perspective, he naturally placed his clan's benefits first.

The first layer of the Gu formation had many ways to detect identities, Fang Yuan could disguise himself if it was bloodline.

But unfortunately for him.

One of the methods was about life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu.

Fang Yuan did not leave any life tablet Gu or soul lantern Gu in Chi clan.

Regarding this, Fang Yuan could only sigh, he cursed helplessly in his mind: "Chi Qu You, this old dog!"

A rank eight Gu Immortal, how could he be simple?

When Chi Qu You designed it, he naturally did not think of this complex situation. But now, it was Fang Yuan's greatest restriction. It was like a dead end, Fang Yuan was getting closer and closer to it.

But Chi Qu You's move was undoubtedly the best one he could have made.

It was a huge assurance to Chi clan.

Fang Yuan had to ensure that Chi clan's Gu Immortals did not die out completely, especially Chi Gui, if anything dangerous happened, he needed to teleport him back using the super Gu formation.

With Chi Gui, there would be the first layer of the Gu formation.

As for what attitude Chi Gui would have and how he would treat Fang Yuan, it was a mystery.

Unless he was completely helpless, Fang Yuan would not make use of Chi Gui.

The situation was complex, three sides were fighting, Fang Yuan had a special status, even though he was in the Southern Border righteous path camp, it was not reliable.

There were too many variables now.

He was using wisdom path methods too.

Fang Yuan's mind was full of churning thoughts, his brain was going to emit smoke at this rate!

How could he escape?

This was an unsolved problem.

"Spring Autumn Cicada?" A thought appeared in Fang Yuan's mind before he denied the possibility.

He could not use Spring Autumn Cicada no matter what.

Heaven's will was inside it, the risk of failure was nearly certain.

A few times, Fang Yuan was able to rebirth successfully because of the secret help of heaven's will. But now, he was standing on the opposite side, heaven's will wanted to eradicate him.

Using Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth in this situation was simply deluding himself!

The heaven's will in Spring Autumn Cicada would directly kill him.

Using Spring Autumn Cicada was suicide!

Unless he used Shadow Sect's method to reverse refine it. But now, how could Fang Yuan find time for that?

"Wait, no!"

"I can use time path methods to accelerate the time of my immortal aperture. This way, I can give up the super Gu formation and hide inside my immortal aperture, to refine Spring Autumn Cicada."

"No, this won't do, there are calamities and tribulations."

"If I accelerate the immortal aperture's time, calamities and tribulations will descend, heaven's will would control them and make it much more difficult."

"And my time path attainment level is too low, I have no guarantee in this, to successfully purify Spring Autumn Cicada under such restrictions."

"And this method requires me to give up the super Gu formation, it is simply an idiotic way of crippling myself."

This would not do.

Fate was too vicious, as if there was no way to survive.

But Fang Yuan did not give up.

He continued to persevere.

His determination did not waver, even though his pressure was intense, even though Fairy Zi Wei had not stopped her invasion of the super Gu formation.

Persevere!

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with vigor, he was not afraid, he was very calm in his mind.

This was not his first desperate situation, in fact, he had many such encounters.

In this world, cultivating and fighting for one's life, no matter what choices one made, there were risks involved.

Once one started moving up, like climbing a mountain, how could there be gains and growth without any risks?

Even the powerful Old Ancestor Xue Hu, the number one battle strength in Northern Plains (publicly), had taken a risk, causing Snowy Mountain, hundreds of years of his hard work, to be destroyed. His plan of refining Fortune Rivalling Heaven completely failed, Reverse Flow River was taken away, and even his wife, Lady Wan Shou, was injured.

Or look at Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, Bi Chen Tian and Wei Ling Yang, these rank eight great experts, they were such high and mighty existences. But in the end, they died in another region, even their ruined corpses were lost, unable to return home.

And Sword Immortal Bo Qing, as well as Feng Jiu Ge, who died from attacking Lang Ya blessed land back in the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life...

Fang Yuan was not Ma Hong Yun, he was not the child of luck, compared to everyone above, he was extremely ordinary.

In fact, Ma Hong Yun died too, even with Fortune Rivalling Heaven's protection.

Heaven and earth were impartial, treating all beings as pawns. No matter how talented one was, or how extraordinary the Gu Immortal was, in this world, they were just a life form, ordinary and simple, they were all treated equally.

His five hundred years of experience, compared to heaven and earth, what could it amount to?

His experience and deep schemes were just the result of having experienced the callous nature of this world, and having understood the ways of human minds.

Humans had limits, who had never made a mistake? Even rank nine venerables were no exception, even Ren Zu was deceived by wisdom Gu.

Conversely, heaven's will was vast, it controlled the situation, the power of heaven and earth was limitless.

Defying heaven as a human, how hard was that!

Such feelings were not just in Fang Yuan's heart.

Ying Wu Xie felt very similarly.

He was fighting.

His enemy was a rank seven righteous path Gu Immortal, at this moment, the rank six immortal zombie Ying Wu Xie had the disadvantage.

Even though he had incredible immortal killer moves, his opponent was so strong, Ying Wu Xie was just barely able to stay on par with him.

After an intense chaotic battle, Ying Wu Xie was left to fight alone, the situation was dangerous.

Soul beast summoning!

Ying Wu Xie unleashed his immortal killer move, three ancient soul beasts surrounded his body again.

But his enemy, a Xia clan rank seven Gu Immortal, laughed mockingly.

Not long ago, when he first faced the soul beast summoning killer move, he was flustered.

But now, after gaining experience, the Xia clan Gu Immortal found a way to counter the ancient soul beasts.

Using the dream realms.

Ancient soul beasts had low intelligence, with just some schemes, the Xia clan Gu Immortal was able to lure these soul beasts towards dream realms.

Once the soul entered the dream realm, they were meat on the chopping block.

Soul beasts were souls that became solid bodies.

Making full use of the battlefield was part of the qualities that made up a Gu Immortal's battle strength.

Soon, the ancient soul beasts that Ying Wu Xie painstakingly summoned were dealt with by the Xia clan Gu Immortal.

Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly on the inside, he could not get free, he had to rely on external help now.

But at this moment, his expression froze, he received Sixth Hair's letter — Fang Yuan wanted to cooperate with Shadow Sect!

Ever since Purple Mountain True Monarch awakened and took over control, he had contacted Fang Yuan, asking to work together.

Unfortunately, Fang Yuan had been wary of Shadow Sect's information path methods, even though they had their respective needs, they did not make any progress in cooperation.

Ying Wu Xie did not expect that Fang Yuan would seek cooperation with Shadow Sect now.

"It's too late!" The bitterness in Ying Wu Xie's heart intensified.

Too late.

It was too late.

He did not know where Fang Yuan was, but Shadow Sect had already started the mission to save the main body!

Sixth Hair transmitted that Fang Yuan needed an information path Gu worm to communicate with Ying Wu Xie.

Fang Yuan could not interact with Shadow Sect directly, they needed Sixth Hair as the middleman.

This was because communication information path Gu came in pairs.

This way, clues to each others' whereabouts were left behind. It was easy to deduce their locations from this.

"Give it to him." Ying Wu Xie thought and did not reject it.

Next, Fang Yuan's voice resounded in Ying Wu Xie's mind: "You are in a sorry state, Ying Wu Xie, the Xia clan immortal is about to kill you. What about lead soul into dream? Aren't you using it?"

Ying Wu Xie heard these words and his eyes widened, he was extremely shocked.

"Fang Yuan!" He transmitted: "You are here in this battlefield?"

"What do you think?" Fang Yuan chuckled: "Stop using soul beast summoning randomly, you have already used it three times, the effect is getting worse, you are only increasing the risk and wasting your immortal essence."

Ying Wu Xie shook: "Fang Yuan, you are here indeed! Damn it, you actually made your way in, since when? Wait, is my opponent you?!"

"If that was me, you would be dead already. Enough idle chatter, let's..." Fang Yuan paused: "Cooperate!"

Chapter 1363: Biggest Traitor in Southern Border's Righteous Path

"Cooperation?"

Hearing Fang Yuan's suggestion, a complex expression appeared on Ying Wu Xie's face uncontrollably.

Fang Yuan's and Shadow Sect's relationship was very intertwined and complex.

As a half otherworldly demon, Fang Yuan was once heaven's will's tool, sent back to destroy Shadow Sect's plan in a last ditch attempt.

Fang Yuan, who successfully obtained the sovereign immortal aperture, was enemies with Shadow Sect, they were at a complete conflict.

During the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Shadow Sect lost entirely, they wanted to tear Fang Yuan to pieces.

But Fang Yuan made good use of his time, and the advantage of the sovereign immortal body to get stronger, he started to hunt Ying Wu Xie and gang.

If Ying Wu Xie and the others did not have a good grasp of time or excellent methods to escape, they would have died at Fang Yuan's hands already.

After the battle of Reverse Flow River, Fang Yuan was already able to match rank eight Gu Immortals.

Shadow Sect was now led by Purple Mountain True Monarch, they changed their tactics, seeking cooperation with Fang Yuan. This was a crucial turning point in their relationship.

Precisely because of this, at this moment, when Fang Yuan initiated the cooperation, Ying Wu Xie nodded, replying: "Then let's work together."

Ying Wu Xie was not against working together.

Or rather, he was once against and hated the idea when Purple Mountain True Monarch mentioned it, he did not understand why.

But people change.

If this was during the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Ying Wu Xie was new to life, he knew nothing, he would not consider working with his enemy.

When Shadow Sect was strong, Fang Yuan was weak as an ant, Ying Wu Xie would never work with Fang Yuan.

After losing in Yi Tian Mountain, Ying Wu Xie hated Fang Yuan, there was no way for them to cooperate. Ying Wu Xie only wanted to regain Shadow Sect's former glory.

But as Fang Yuan grew stronger and went after Ying Wu Xie multiple times, Ying Wu Xie started to feel deep wariness in his heart. Recently, when Fang Yuan chased them to Northern Plains, other than wariness, Ying Wu Xie also felt fear towards Fang Yuan.

After the battle of Reverse Flow River, Ying Wu Xie developed a new emotion towards Fang Yuan.

That was — admiration.

Fang Yuan did what Ying Wu Xie was unable to do, he was truly worthy of being chosen by heaven's will to return to the past and disrupt Shadow Sect's plans.

"It is not that I am not strong, but that my enemy is Fang Yuan!" Ying Wu Xie had such a thought and realized that his losses were not that unacceptable.

"How are we going to cooperate? I can't hang on anymore." Ying Wu Xie said directly.

Fang Yuan frowned, Ying Wu Xie had a very direct attitude, Fang Yuan was slightly surprised.

"Of course I will help you people first, Heavenly Court is too strong, there is only hope if we work together." Fang Yuan sighed, transmitting to the Xia clan Gu Immortal who was fighting Ying Wu Xie.

"Retreat? Why must I retreat? I already know about my enemy's weaknesses, I can win this." The Xia clan Gu Immortal was very confused.

"A Yao clan Gu Immortal is in great danger, you need to help him. Quickly go, I am overseeing the entire battlefield, how can you understand the big picture like me?" Fang Yuan said without politeness.

The Xia clan Gu Immortal was very unhappy, but because of Wu Yi Hai's status, and the fact that he was in control of the super Gu formation, he snorted in his mind before leaving.

"How are you going to help me? Quickly do something!" Ying Wu Xie urged, but suddenly, his eyes widened as he looked at his opponent in shock, he retreated while having a discontent gaze at Ying Wu Xie, rapidly flying away.

"Stop making a fuss, I already helped you." Fang Yuan said at an appropriate timing.

Ying Wu Xie heart shook, asking: "Didn't you say that was not you?! Is he one of your subordinates?"

"Enough pointless chatter, tell me, what is Shadow Sect's plan? Don't tell me you have no backup plans." Fang Yuan immediately asked.

Ying Wu Xie smiled bitterly, replying: "Of course we do, our backup is me."

Rumble!

An intense explosion occurred, from the raging air currents, Purple Mountain True Monarch flew out of the endless profound lights as he charged down.

"Why are you escaping? Fight me!" Behind him, Duke Long chased.

His long hair was fluttering, his muscular body had changed, not only were his dragon horns sharper and longer now, his hands had turned into dragon claws, his dragon tail was waving behind him, his skin was covered with a layer of dragon scales.

Purple Mountain True Monarch looked pathetic, but his gaze was clear like water.

"Duke Long, history states that he cultivated qi path primarily, but because of his lacking lifespan, he also cultivated transformation path." Purple Mountain True Monarch analyzed in his mind.

"Just his transformation path methods are already so powerful, as expected of someone on par with Bo Qing."

"Let him try this move."

Thinking of this, Purple Mountain True Monarch's body shook, he turned around agilely, flying upwards.

At the same time, his ten fingers fluttered like he was playing a zither.

Swish swish swish...

And endless stream of purple starlight specks shot out of his fingers, piercing through space and attacking Duke Long.

These starlight specks were extremely dazzling, not only were they fast, they flew in the air with a trail of light behind them, it was extremely beautiful.

Duke Long grunted, he felt that these purple starlight specks were not simple.

He quickly used his attacking methods against them.

But these purple starlight specks were very agile, they quickly dodged Duke Long's attacks as they aimed directly at him.

Duke Long saw this and praised in his mind: "As expected of a wisdom path cultivator, his immortal killer moves are agile and nimble, especially this move, it is extremely refined. I cannot compare to him in this aspect."

Wisdom path Gu Immortals had endless thoughts, they were most skilled in controlling immortal killer moves, and creating attacks of varying styles.

"Why must I get bogged down? It is wiser to make use of my advantages." Duke Long ignored these purple starlight specks, using his powerful defense to take on the starlight specks and charging ahead fearlessly.

Seeing this, mysterious light shined in Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes.

"He finally fell into my trap."

It turned out that his move had a hidden effect. Upon contact with any immortal killer move, it would transmit some fragmented information to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Countless fragmented pieces of information would combine and expose the secrets of the immortal killer move.

With enough information, Purple Mountain True Monarch would be able to target Duke Long's defensive method and retaliate against it.

Duke Long's offensive approach after confirming the power of the purple starlight specks suited Purple Mountain True Monarch's tactic.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had always been feeling troubled by Duke Long's defense. After getting enough information, Purple Mountain True Monarch used a new immortal killer move.

He pushed with both palms as large amounts of cloud mist appeared, blocking Duke Long from advancing.

Duke Long's dragon eyes flickered with sharp light, after looking at it, he instantly saw the power of this immortal killer move.

He laughed heartily as he charged into the purple mist.

Instantly, he lost his sense of direction entirely.

Duke Long immediately stopped, staying motionless as he opened his mouth, emitting a loud dragon roar.

The dragon roar reverberated in the entire area, the purple mist became thinner until it faded away.

Duke Long saw Purple Mountain True Monarch again, he was still retreating, attempting to pull away from Duke Long.

Duke Long laughed, his figure vanished and appeared before Purple Mountain True Monarch instantly!

"Eat my fist." Duke Long shouted loudly, striking with his right fist directly.

This was not an immortal killer move.

In such a short time, Duke Long had to maintain his concentration on his various defensive killer moves, he did not activate any other immortal killer moves.

But with his physical toughness, his normal fist had incredible offensive power.

Bam.

Purple Mountain True Monarch could not dodge in time, he was directly hit by Duke Long's fist.

But his chest that was punched flickered with profound light, his body was basically unharmed.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had incredible defensive methods too.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was uninjured from Duke Long's punch, he even used the force of the fist to accelerate his retreat backwards.

But at the next moment, Duke Long appeared beside Purple Mountain True Monarch again, punching.

Bam.

The same scene appeared again, but Duke Long chased relentlessly, no matter where Purple Mountain True Monarch flew to, he could instantly teleport over and punch with his fists.

Duke Long's punches rained down endlessly, countless fist shadows enshrouded Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was like a rubber ball, thrown around by Duke Long constantly, he was taking a beating without being able to retaliate.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was flickering with profound light, defending against Duke Long's fists.

Soon, Duke Long's punches were no longer so simple.

Chaotic dragon fist!

An immortal killer move was activated.

But the effect was low.

Duke Long thought: "My chaotic dragon fist will cause the thoughts in my enemy's mind to become chaotic if it hits. With a flurry of punches, my opponents will not be able to think, they will only take hits passively. But this effect does not appear on him at all."

At Duke Long's level, he can already achieve the traits of other paths. Duke Long's transformation path killer move had wisdom path effects.

But when it was used on a wisdom path Gu Immortal, Purple Mountain True Monarch, it was simply child's play.

Duke Long could punch his other enemies with death with chaotic dragon fist, but against Purple Mountain True Monarch, he only had the upper hand.

While Duke Long was probing Purple Mountain True Monarch's wisdom path attainment, Purple Mountain True Monarch was also analyzing Duke Long.

Even though he was taking hits, he was calm in his mind, with no hint of panic.

Wisdom path had three aspects, thoughts, wills, and emotions. Purple Mountain True Monarch had methods to eliminate his negative emotions in battle.

"Duke Long's movement is evidently an immortal killer move, allowing him to teleport continuously."

"Inside his dragon eyes, there is another immortal killer move with powerful investigative effects."

"With my initial deduction, his teleportation does not depend on where he looks. Don't tell me..."

Chapter 1364: Duke Long Enters Dream

At the next moment, Purple Mountain True Monarch snapped his fingers.

An immortal killer move was used, purple halo spread to the range of thousands of steps.

Duke Long's figure came to a stop, he could no longer use teleportation to get close to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

"He saw through it, that reaction speed is really fast... wisdom path Gu Immortals are as troublesome as always." Duke Long stopped his attacks, sighing.

His movement killer move was used with the dragon roar earlier.

Wherever the dragon roar reached, he could teleport over using the killer move.

But there was a time limit.

Purple Mountain True Monarch saw through this and used his wisdom path methods to mimic the effect of sound path, cleansing his surroundings.

Duke Long's movement method could no longer be used, it was ineffective.

"In that case, try this move." Duke Long opened his mouth in the air.

Two teeth fell out, they grew larger with the moving wind.

In an instant, his two teeth became snow-white dragon fangs that resembled curved blades.

Duke Long breathed in deeply and after a few breaths of time, used his immortal killer move —

Spiraling dragon fang!

Two snow-white dragon fangs shot out rapidly, the speed far surpassed Purple Mountain True Monarch, rapidly approaching him.

The two curved dragon fang blades spiraled around Purple Mountain True Monarch, each time they hit, there was a dazzling sharp light on Purple Mountain True Monarch's body.

"Trying to use this method to restrain me?"

"Dragon fangs... they are solid, this is different from normal killer moves."

Purple Mountain True Monarch felt his pressure intensifying.

The power of the dragon fangs was no small matter, Purple Mountain True Monarch quickly realized that he had to deal with this immortal killer move!

...

"Lord Purple has already used his personal methods, but he is still suppressed by Duke Long." Ying Wu Xie flew as he observed Purple Mountain True Monarch's and Duke Long's battle.

He had a good angle of the battle, in this complex battlefield, he could actually watch the battle of two rank eight Gu Immortals.

At the moment, the two were still probing.

Evidently, Duke Long was stronger than Purple Mountain True Monarch.

In terms of battle strength, Duke Long was on par with Bo Qing, Purple Mountain True Monarch was naturally weaker. Even though the latter actually had peak rank eight battle strength!

"Lord Purple's strength will continue to weaken, because he is constantly using the immortal killer move to create more defective Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and clear the dream realm. During this process, he would need to split his own soul, it is extremely painful!"

Ying Wu Xie watched with worry.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was not Duke Long's match to begin with, but he still had to create Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies now. By the time Purple Mountain True Monarch's methods were fully understood by Duke Long, he would lose.

"Quick, quick, quick!" Ying Wu Xie urged himself.

He would not tell this to Fang Yuan of course.

Even though they were working together, they did not set any information path agreements, Ying Wu Xie did not trust Fang Yuan fully.

But if they wanted to set an agreement, the situation did not allow them to, and even if they could, Fang Yuan would not do it.

Both sides wanted to cooperate, but they did not trust each other. But because of the enemy, Heavenly Court, they had to work together!

"Found it, towards your southeast, there is a cocoon of light about to form, get there quickly." At this time, Fang Yuan transmitted.

Ying Wu Xie looked in that direction and felt hesitant.

If he followed Fang Yuan's instructions, he had to get deep into the territory of Southern Border's righteous path. There were many Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals there.

Was Fang Yuan reliable? Was this a trap?

Ying Wu Xie could not help but hesitate.

"If I wanted to harm you, you would have died earlier." Fang Yuan transmitted, as if he knew what Ying Wu Xie was thinking.

Ying Wu Xie had to admit that Fang Yuan was right, but he thought: "Maybe Fang Yuan doesn't want me dead, and wants to capture me alive? If he wants to capture me, he would need to make arrangements, is there a Gu formation or a battlefield killer move there?"

But this time, Ying Wu Xie shook his head, no longer hesitating.

He wanted to gamble.

At this moment, he had to gamble!

Following Fang Yuan's instructions, he flew.

Soon, he saw a Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortal.

"Damn it!" Ying Wu Xie's heart jumped.

The Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortal also found him.

But when he was about to pounce on Ying Wu Xie, his face changed, after hesitating, he flew away with a complex expression.

"Why did that happen?!" Ying Wu Xie was shocked.

This was the second time.

Was he also Fang Yuan's subordinate?

If so, why did he had that expression, he strangely looked unwilling and slightly angry?

Ying Wu Xie was getting more confused.

He continued to move forward and met with the third person, and then a fourth. The two Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals he met also left him alone.

This was naturally Fang Yuan's manipulation.

Using the excuse of the big picture, he sent all those Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals away with simple reasons.

For example, 'that place needs you more', 'an ally is in danger, if you do not go, they will die', and 'ignore that rank six immortal zombie, I have sent others to deal with him ahead'...

All sorts of reasons allowed Ying Wu Xie to move unhindered.

Nobody would expect Wu Yi Hai to work with Shadow Sect.

Among the righteous path Gu Immortals in Southern Border, who would think of that?

At this time, Heavenly Court had not yet exposed Fang Yuan's true identity.

With Fang Yuan's help, Ying Wu Xie got closer to his destination.

"Hmm? There is actually a cocoon of light here?" Rank seven expert Yi Hei Ting had a sudden discovery.

His body flickered with lightning, bringing his body towards the cocoon.

"Stop it!" Ying Wu Xie who had just arrived suddenly shouted out loud.

Yi Hei Ting felt strange: "Who is this? He actually made it here!"

Ying Wu Xie's yell did not disrupt him, he was already very close to the light cocoon, he was about to succeed.

But at the next moment, Yi Hei Ting's vision changed.

He was forcefully teleported by the super Gu formation.

"Lord Wu Yi Hai! I was about to..." Yi Hei Ting realized this and suddenly bellowed.

He was truly a hindrance rather than help! He was clearly about to succeed!

"I know, but another place needs you more. Don't worry, I have already noticed the enemy by the cocoon, I will deal with it." Fang Yuan interrupted Yi Hei Ting's words.

Yi Hei Ting wanted to say more, but his vision changed, he was teleported out again to another place.

"This Wu Yi Hai, he thinks he can use me as a pawn because he controls the Gu formation? Hmph!" Yi Hei Ting was extremely unhappy, but he did not suspect Fang Yuan's true intentions.

Fang Yuan did not randomly teleport him, because around him, there was a Southern Border Gu Immortal about to die from Fairy Miao Yin.

Yi Hei Ting quickly entered the battle, forgetting about the displeasure towards Fang Yuan.

Ying Wu Xie felt like he was in a dream!

Seeing that Yi Hei Ting was about to succeed, he almost despaired.

But at the next moment, he went from hell to heaven, this change was too sudden, he was overjoyed.

Ying Wu Xie was a little dazed.

But when he came to his senses, he contacted Fang Yuan with his information path Gu worm, crying out: "You, you actually control the entire super Gu formation! What is your current identity?"

Fang Yuan knew this could not be concealed, he exposed it: "Who else? I am currently Wu Yi Hai."

Ying Wu Xie heard this, his eyes almost popped out.

This answer was too stunning, since when and what methods did Fang Yuan use to get to this position?

After accepting this fact, Ying Wu Xie understood everything.

No wonder those Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals gave way to him, Ying Wu Xie thought that their expressions were rather funny now.

But soon, he felt some worry.

"Fang Yuan has unravel dream, staying here for so long without any detection, he definitely has a huge scheme! He definitely made great gains!"

"So close. If not for Lord Purple's plan to catch the righteous path off guard, Fang Yuan might have been able to continue staying here for a long time, it would be a huge problem for Shadow Sect."

Ying Wu Xie's emotions were changing, from shock to realization and to worry, he finally reached the cocoon of light.

"This aura! A rank seven cocoon." Ying Wu Xie was excited.

"How can I choose wrongly? What are you waiting for?" Fang Yuan laughed.

Ying Wu Xie nodded, using his immortal killer move.

This killer move took effect rapidly, in an instant, the cocoon that had not formed yet stabilized completely and took shape.

Ying Wu Xie's soul and Gu worms entered the cocoon of light.

Meanwhile, his rank six immortal zombie body was abandoned.

The cocoon of light broke apart as a rank seven Ying Wu Xie appeared!

"Don't resist, I will send you off." Fang Yuan's voice entered Ying Wu Xie's mind again.

At the next moment, Ying Wu Xie was teleported away, watching Duke Long and Purple Mountain True Monarch's battle again.

Without hesitation, Ying Wu Xie used his trump card.

Immortal killer move — Lead Soul Into Dream!

"Urgh!" Duke Long's expression changed, in an instant, he was dragged into a dream.

At the next moment, he lost contact with the outside world.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was stunned: "What is going on? A scheme?"

But next, he received Ying Wu Xie's transmission: "I am here, Lord Purple, I am a rank seven dream path Gu Immortal now!"

"Good." Purple Mountain True Monarch was overjoyed, this trump card was finally activated.

"After some hurdles, I obtained this immortal body due to Fang Yuan's help. He is currently acting as Wu Yi Hai, he is controlling the super Gu formation of Southern Border's righteous path, he wants to cooperate with you."

"Oh?!" Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes shined brightly: "Excellent, send my information path Gu worm to him, we need to talk."

With Fang Yuan and Shadow Sect starting their cooperation, the situation finally appeared to be turning around!

Chapter 1365: Star Constellation Heaven's Will Appears

Duke Long entered a dream!

Ying Wu Xie had a rank seven immortal body, he burst out with great strength, changing the battle situation between two rank eight Gu Immortals.

Duke Long fell into a dream realm and could not escape.

Purple Mountain True Monarch used this great chance to retaliate.

Rumble...

Explosions continued unceasingly, but countless dragon shadows appeared on Duke Long's body, there were also countless dragon-shaped tattoos moving around his skin.

"Such an amazing defensive killer move..." Purple Mountain True Monarch could not do anything to Duke Long for the time being.

Similar to Purple Mountain True Monarch, Duke Long had a lot of defensive methods, among them were incredibly useful killer moves. These killer moves were like the wood armor that Bi Chen Tian was so proud of.

This type of killer move turned into dao marks and became engraved on the Gu Immortal's body. They were normally dormant, but when attacked, they would activate themselves and would not need any thoughts for manipulation, only using immortal essence.

This was somewhat like Fang Yuan's ghostly concealment.

Ghostly concealment was a top-tier killer move created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. But this move was much more refined than Bi Chen Tian's wood armor, or Duke Long's and Purple Mountain True Monarch's defensive methods.

Because ghostly concealment not only melded with oneself and had an active effect all the time, most importantly, it did not cost any of the Gu Immortal's immortal essence.

A killer move that was active permanently without using any immortal essence.

This was a supreme method of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable! From the perspective of Central Continent's ten great sects and Fang Yuan, it was unthinkable, they had no way of understanding such a mystical method.

Swish swish!

Two white lights were spiraling and landing on Purple Mountain True Monarch's body.

It was the spiraling dragon fang killer move that Duke Long had used earlier.

After the two flashes of light burst out, the two dragon fangs met with no success, but they still circled around Purple Mountain True Monarch, ready for an opportunity.

"This killer move also needs no manipulation from the Gu Immortal? Troublesome." Purple Mountain True Monarch frowned slightly.

"But thankfully, I have been keeping purple thought perception starlight activated!" Purple Mountain True Monarch let out a loud shout as countless starlight specks emerged from the pores of his body.

Starlight specks flew around Duke Long, they gathered, shooting at Duke Long's layers of defense and being broken continuously.

But soon, all sorts of information was transmitted into Purple Mountain True Monarch's mind.

"Quickly kill him!" Ying Wu Xie observed the battle from afar, calling out in his mind.

In the super Gu formation, Fang Yuan was also watching Purple Mountain True Monarch's battle closely.

"Truly unrepentant!"

"Fallen demon, you are beyond saving!"

Fairy Zi Wei's voice could be heard from the super Gu formation again. Fang Yuan had helped Ying Wu Xie and indirectly caused Duke Long to enter his dream, Fairy Zi Wei saw all of these.

"However, if you think Lord Duke Long will fail because of this, you are completely wrong."

Saying this, Fairy Zi Wei actually laughed: "I need to thank you, the many times you used the super Gu formation allowed me to see many of the operations of the super Gu formation, haven't you noticed that you are gradually losing control of this super Gu formation?"

"Your invasion speed is getting faster, but there is no need to try and bluff me." Fang Yuan sneered.

Fairy Zi Wei was dazed: "Hmm?"

"Even though you people came here imposingly, your true battle strength is only at this level." Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly.

"The truth is, as long as another rank eight Gu Immortal like you shows up, you would be able to sweep the battlefield. Unfortunately, Heaven Overseeing Tower did not send anyone else."

"Instead, you had to come here secretly to invade the super Gu formation, and Duke Long had to go battle personally."

"Even though you know my true identity, you have not exposed me, my identity is still a secret."

"Other than having no evidence, your intention is to use the strength of Southern Border's righteous path to deal with Shadow Sect, right?"

"And also, there is another reason, even if you expose my identity and convince Southern Border's righteous path, this super Gu formation will still be in my control. This crucial point will not change because of my identity."

"You came to the super Gu formation in order to get this huge bargaining chip too."

"All these show that your Heavenly Court is putting up a false front, your rank eight battle strength is lacking."

Fairy Zi Wei went silent.

She recalled the scene a few days ago.

Back then, she was researching Star Constellation Chessboard.

This Immortal Gu House had always been in Heavenly Court's treasury, after Duke Long woke up, he had the authority to take it out and let Fairy Zi Wei use it.

After interacting with and using it, Fairy Zi Wei felt the supreme brilliance of this Immortal Gu House.

"This Immortal Gu House was indeed the wisdom path Immortal Gu House created by Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, it could actually allow my deduction ability to rise by many times."

Thinking of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, Fairy Zi Wei had a look of admiration.

Her wisdom path deduction ability was originally amazing. Now that it grew by several times, Fairy Zi Wei felt as if this was an illusion of her being the number one wisdom path immortal in the current world.

"It is a pity that even though my deductions are more powerful now, I still need crucial information. The clues are too few, it is hard to make deductions." Fairy Zi Wei had a dim gaze.

She thought about earlier, when Central Continent's Gu Immortals were pursued by Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Longevity Heaven, they managed to conceal the clues and prevent Fairy Zi Wei from deducing the location of where the Central Continent Gu Immortals were trapped. The reinforcements thus had no place to go and could not be sent.

She also thought about Fang Yuan, all along, Heavenly Court had been trying to kill this person.

But they lacked the clues to him.

When deducing, because Fang Yuan had preventive measures, he could always hold out and get informed of the deductions.

Thus, Fang Yuan's whereabouts were not in Heavenly Court's grasp.

Fairy Zi Wei sighed eerily.

But right at this moment, the Star Constellation Chessboard in her hands started to absorb her immortal essence and activated on its own.

A lump of heaven's will gushed out of Star Constellation Chessboard, floating in the air and turning into Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's appearance.

Seeing this, Fairy Zi Wei was extremely shocked.

Star Constellation Chessboard was the possession of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but she had died long ago. Fairy Zi Wei was able to control this Immortal Gu House now, she was merely borrowing it.

"Zi Wei, this is Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, why are you not paying respects?" Duke Long arrived and stood behind Fairy Zi Wei.

"But this is heaven's will." Fairy Zi Wei was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, she could naturally tell what this will was.

"Of course this is heaven's will. You are too young, you do not know this secret. Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had assimilated with heaven's will long ago. Even though her body is gone, her will resides in the world of the five regions, she is one with heaven and earth!" Duke Long exposed some truly terrifying secrets.

Fairy Zi Wei was in a daze, feeling unparalleled shock.

"This means Star Constellation Immortal Venerable achieved eternal life? If heaven's will is Lady Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, then wouldn't the entire world be on Heavenly Court's side?"

But Duke Long shook his head: "You should say, Heavenly Court is on the side of heaven's will. After assimilating with heaven's will, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable is no longer herself. This was a major and selfless sacrifice! Back then, for the sake of humanity, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable sacrificed herself to modify heaven's will. Since then, heaven's will gained the form of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but it is still heaven's will in essence."

Fairy Zi Wei's gaze flickered, she was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, she immediately understood.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had sacrificed herself for the entire human race, she assimilated with heaven's will.

The core of heaven's will did not change, but some things were modified by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. For example, the form that it took, and maybe... a hint of human-like concern towards Heavenly Court?"

This was perhaps the reason why Heavenly Court followed and executed the will of heaven, and after countless eons, it was still standing strong!

"The great era is coming, the five regions will become one, destiny has already reached a crucial point." Star Constellation heaven's will spoke while stretching out her right hand.

On her right hand, a lump of heaven's will flew out and floated in the air, turning into the form of Southern Border's super Gu formation.

"Here."

"A crucial battle is about to unfold, the result of this battle will affect the entire world."

"Spectral Soul Demon Venerable is extremely weak, all of Shadow Sect will be gathered here, Fang Yuan is disguised as Wu Yi Hai, mixing in with Southern Border's righteous path."

"These are a bunch of fate defying people, the source of all chaos and turmoil. Eliminating them will help towards the repairing of fate Immortal Gu."

"However, Heavenly Court will only allow the two of you to fight this time."

Star Constellation heaven's will said plainly.

"Why?" Fairy Zi Wei did not understand.

Heavenly Court had very deep foundations, earlier in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, they had found out too late, and the awakened Heavenly Court rank eight Gu Immortals were not enough to turn the situation around.

But now that they had the reminder of Star Constellation heaven's will, time was ample, Heavenly Court had lots of time to prepare. Heavenly Court could totally gather its power and crush the enemies.

But Star Constellation heaven's will told Fairy Zi Wei and Duke Long that only the two of them could go.

"This is something fated to happen."

"After the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, the uncertainties of luck have greatly decreased. Now that fate Immortal Gu is recovering, fate is regaining control of the world."

"You will undoubtedly win this time."

"Do not bother the hibernating Gu Immortals in Heavenly Court, they serve a greater purpose. Heavenly Court's foundation cannot be weakened further, otherwise, the consequences will be severe."

"Bring Heaven Overseeing Tower and Star Constellation Chessboard, the Gu Immortals of Central Continent's ten great sects should not be mobilized unnecessarily. Keep in mind to preserve their lives, in the next ten years, Heaven Overseeing Tower will need even more rank eight Gu Immortals to hibernate. Remember, remember this."

...

Star Constellation heaven's will gave them many instructions.

Fairy Zi Wei obtained a lot of information, but she became much more confused now.

She found out that even though she was a member of Heavenly Court, she, in fact, knew too little about it.

Such a huge organization had deep foundations, but it could not use them recklessly like she had imagined before.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were hibernating, other than to extend their lifespan, there seemed to be an even greater purpose.

Chapter 1366: Duke Long Awakens

Heavenly Court had its concerns, but what these concerns were, Star Constellation heaven's will did not state clearly.

After saying everything, Star Constellation heaven's will vanished into thin air.

"Oh Zi Wei, don't look at me. Even though I have lived longer, I do not know as many secrets as you think I do. I'll tell you the truth, this is only the second time I've seen Star Constellation heaven's will appear on its own." Duke Long sighed deeply.

After pausing for a while, he continued: "We need to believe in Star Constellation heaven's will and do as she says. We will definitely win this time, this is our fate!"

Duke Long's unwavering determination rubbed off on Fairy Zi Wei.

In Heavenly Court's actions later, it went according to Star Constellation heaven's will's instructions, Duke Long and the rest did not defy her.

While Heaven Overseeing Tower moved in white heaven, it was obstructed by Purple Mountain True Monarch's methods. It was carrying Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei, and other Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects, joining in this crucial battle.

Fang Yuan's analysis was correct.

Even though he did not understand why Heavenly Court refused to send more Gu Immortals, this did not stop him from seeing through this detail.

Precisely so, Fang Yuan made the decision to use the super Gu formation to help Ying Wu Xie and affect the battle between Duke Long and Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Using treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan successfully obtained an information path Gu worm from Ying Wu Xie.

This information path Gu worm allowed him to talk directly to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Fang Yuan helped Ying Wu Xie so as to gain Shadow Sect's initial trust, otherwise, how could he get this Gu worm?

This Gu worm and Purple Mountain True Monarch had a close relationship, with it, he would have a crucial clue and would be able to deduce matters on Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Thus, these Gu worms were usually kept very closely to oneself.

Only in this situation would Purple Mountain True Monarch give this information path Gu worm to Fang Yuan.

During normal times, they would definitely need to set an information path alliance agreement.

After getting the information path Gu worm, Purple Mountain True Monarch contacted Fang Yuan and said: "Fang Yuan, I need to thank you. Purple Mountain True Monarch is a great title, thanks for bestowing it, I like it."

Fang Yuan did not expect that the lie he used to deceive Tai Bai Yun Sheng would become reality one day.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had well honed interpersonal skills, once he said that, the relationship between him and Fang Yuan became much closer.

Fang Yuan laughed: "Then I'll call you Purple Mountain True Monarch. You have already felt my sincerity, we are working together, I am not the only one putting in effort. Now, it is time for your side of the deal."

Purple Mountain True Monarch attacked Duke Long fiercely while answering: "Okay, what do you want?"

He knew what strength Fang Yuan had, but in this crucial moment, he did not hesitate at all.

Fang Yuan answered: "Heavenly crystals! I want a large amount of heavenly crystals!"

Heavenly crystals were too hard to obtain. Even though they were sold in treasure yellow heaven, they were rare and in small quantities, Fang Yuan's needs were not satisfied.

But Shadow Sect had them.

Fang Yuan did not doubt that.

Even though Shadow Sect was greatly damaged and lost a lot, it did not lack resources. Fang Yuan could see this during his pursuit of Ying Wu Xie and gang.

As expected, Purple Mountain True Monarch answered: "Okay, I have a lot of heavenly crystals, they can be given to you to express my sincerity."

"You want heavenly crystals to nurture the upper extreme heavenly eagle?"

"This is a sound idea, reverse flow protection seal cannot be used recklessly. But even if you turn the upper extreme heavenly eagle into a true immemorial desolate beast, you might not be able to control it, I know about your enslavement path method."

"But don't worry, I have a method for you to control the upper extreme heavenly eagle."

Purple Mountain True Monarch's words made Fang Yuan overjoyed and also incredibly amazed.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was very generous, he gave up the heavenly crystals to gain Fang Yuan's support without hesitation.

He was already in a passive state, thus, when he said his later words, the method to control upper extreme heavenly eagle, he lured Fang Yuan. This was turning his position from passive to active.

As expected of a rank eight wisdom path Gu Immortal, his words were filled with wisdom, Fang Yuan felt the aura of an intense opponent.

Fang Yuan was silent before saying: "Adding in another method to control the upper extreme heavenly eagle is fine. But now, I have something more important to do!"

He said that as if he had some way to control the upper extreme heavenly eagle himself.

This way, Purple Mountain True Monarch's bargaining chip was not as significant.

Purple Mountain True Monarch smiled: "What is more important?"

"That is, both of us need to enter a ceasefire now!" Fang Yuan said.

Shadow Sect would benefit from this matter, it was good for Fang Yuan too, only Heavenly Court would not stand to gain from it.

Immediately, Purple Mountain True Monarch gave his orders, recalling the Gu Immortals of Shadow Sect.

Fang Yuan also sent orders, even though the Southern Border Gu Immortals did not understand it, due to Wu Yi Hai's identity and his control of the Gu formation, they listened to him.

Both sides began to separate.

Shadow Sect had many losses, only Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, Fairy Miao Yin and so on were left.

Over at Southern Border, even though there were losses, they were not significant, their numbers were not lacking.

However, Shadow Sect's Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies were still breaking out of the cocoons, the numbers were increasing as the dream realm continued to weaken and vanish.

This situation was the worst for Heavenly Court.

"The difference in strength between both sides is shrinking, now, what will Heavenly Court do?" Fang Yuan was vigilant against Heavenly Court's actions.

Duke Long was still sleeping, while Fairy Zi Wei was increasing her speed of taking over the super Gu formation.

Heaven Overseeing Tower was still entangled with Zuo Ye Hui.

Boom!

Zuo Ye Hui raised its left claw and jumped up, slamming Heaven Overseeing Tower to the ground.

Heaven Overseeing Tower flickered with white light, being undamaged.

Zuo Ye Hui opened its mouth and let out grey night.

Heaven Overseeing Tower used fate vanquish again.

The two killer moves faced off, grey night vanished in the white light as Zuo Ye Hui was pushed away with broken bones and tendons.

But almost instantly, it used an immortal killer move and its injuries vanished.

Regaining its peak condition, Zuo Ye Hui growled again and attacked Heaven Overseeing Tower with fury and hatred.

There was a sigh in Heaven Overseeing Tower, before it flew into the sky.

Zuo Ye Hui had its flying killer move too, it flew into the sky and chased after Heaven Overseeing Tower.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals in the tower had nervous and anxious expressions.

"Damn it! This immemorial desolate beast is too sturdy, it is able to use killer moves, Heaven Overseeing Tower cannot deal with it in a short time."

"What do we do? Lord Duke Long was targeted and fell into a dream realm, being attacked by the rank eight demon."

"We need to go! We need to send reinforcements to Lord Duke Long, if this goes on, it will not be good."

"But Lord Duke Long instructed before leaving that we need to stay inside Heaven Overseeing Tower, we cannot move rashly."

"Times are different now."

"There are rank eight Gu Immortals among us, now that Lord Duke Long is in danger, he has lost control of the battle. If we do not help him, Lord Duke Long will be in danger."

After a short discussion, Heaven Overseeing Tower attacked, temporarily pushing Zuo Ye Hui back and creating a chance.

Two Central Continent Gu Immortals took the chance to fly out of Heaven Overseeing Tower and move towards Duke Long.

"Hahaha, two rats came out!" Zuo Ye Hui laughed, a sinister light shining in its bestial eyes.

It opened its bloodthirsty mouth.

The two Central Continent Gu Immortals' bodies shook, as if they had encountered a predator, they felt an incredible danger and could not control themselves.

Crack!

Zuo Ye Hui shut its mouth, even though it was far from these two Central Continent Gu Immortals, when its teeth connected, it was as if it had bitten these two Central Continent Gu Immortals.

Blood flowed out of its mouth.

At the same time, the two Central Continent Gu Immortals were spurting out blood, they were covered in terrifying wounds, their organs were punctured, their entire bodies looked completely deformed.

"This is a food path killer move! It is hard to defend against."

"Zuo Ye Hui has human intelligence, it knows how to use the tactic of targeting an enemy's weakness."

"Quick, bring the two back."

Heaven Overseeing Tower quickly tried to save them, and because the two Central Continent rank eights had methods to help themselves, they narrowly escaped death and were not eaten by Zuo Ye Hui.

After escaping that danger, the Central Continent Gu Immortals realized the terrifying power of Zuo Ye Hui!

"Indeed worthy of a legendary immemorial desolate beast, the beast that Reckless Savage left behind!"

"But this way, how can we save Lord Duke Long?"

"Bring Heaven Overseeing Tower in."

"It is too dangerous. If we are sent into a dream realm, we will lose Heaven Overseeing Tower, can any of us bear that responsibility?"

While Central Continent's Gu Immortals were discussing, Duke Long was in the greatest danger he had ever been in.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's methods were finally working, he broke through Duke Long's defenses.

"Break!" Purple Mountain True Monarch flew to Duke Long and spat out some purple gas.

This mystical breath landed on Duke Long and dissolved all of his defenses.

Immortal killer move — Brilliant Will Dissolution!

"Die!" Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes shined with bright purple light, he used his killer move on Duke Long.

But at this moment, Duke Long opened his eyes.

Boom!

There was a thunderous explosion.

Purple Mountain True Monarch flew out from the dust and smoke as Duke Long stood on the spot.

He had woken up.

"How could he escape so quickly?" Ying Wu Xie was greatly shocked, he quickly used lead soul into dream.

Purple Mountain True Monarch had a bad feeling, Duke Long had woken up at a very coincidental time, he wanted to stop Ying Wu Xie, but it was too late.

Duke Long vanished instantly and Ying Wu Xie received the backlash of the killer move.

He had fallen into the dream himself!

"This move seems to be called lead soul into dream? It is a good move. If I had more time, I would be able to decipher its profundity." Duke Long spoke.

As the vigilant appearance of Purple Mountain True Monarch was reflected in his cold dragon eyes, Duke Long continued speaking: "As for you, if your methods are only at this level, you will not be able to handle my next move."

"Because this was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable!"

Duke Long cultivated qi path primarily and transformation path secondarily. At this moment, he was finally going to use his true methods!

Chapter 1367: Triple Qi Retraction

After Duke Long said that, his aura changed abruptly.

He had just forced Purple Mountain True Monarch back, and caused Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream to be ineffective, his aura was overwhelming, he was like a giant dragon soaring into the sky.

But now, it was decreasing.

'Decrease' was not an appropriate word.

It was condensing and solidifying.

His overwhelming aura earlier was condensing now, in a few breaths' time, Duke Long's shocking aura was completely concealed. He was like a deep abyss, unfathomable and mysterious.

Purple Mountain True Monarch acted like he was facing a strong foe.

He could sense that Duke Long in this condition was much more dangerous than Duke Long with overwhelming aura!

Roar!

Duke Long opened his mouth and roared.

Next, he vanished entirely on the spot.

"Oh no!" Purple Mountain True Monarch's heart sank.

Duke Long was doing the same thing again.

He had once used this method to teleport to Purple Mountain True Monarch and use chaotic dragon fist, suppressing Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Ordinary Gu Immortals would not be able to react even if they knew about Duke Long's intention. But Purple Mountain True Monarch was different, he cultivated wisdom path, he could think rapidly.

Almost at the same time as Duke Long roared, Purple Mountain True Monarch finished thinking and reacted.

In their earlier combat, Purple Mountain True Monarch had seen through the secret of Duke Long's teleportation, at this moment, he used the same method again, eradicating the sound of the dragon's roar around him.

Indeed, at the next moment, Duke Long stopped moving, he reappeared in front of Purple Mountain True Monarch.

But this time, he did not succeed in getting close, he was still several hundred steps away from Purple Mountain True Monarch.

But to Duke Long, this was enough distance.

"Human qi retraction!" He shouted, waving at Purple Mountain True Monarch.

His movement was very ordinary, like a friend waving to another friend.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch suffered a huge blow.

A huge amount of human qi gushed out of his body and flew towards Duke Long uncontrollably.

In the blink of an eye, it entered Duke Long's palm and vanished!

After losing such a huge amount of human qi, Purple Mountain True Monarch's eye sockets sank in, his expression turned pale and his bright purple hair became dull, he felt an intense feeling of weakness in his head and throughout his entire body.

Deep within Purple Mountain True Monarch's eyes, a mysterious light of shock could be seen. When he heard Duke Long's shout, he thought of a famous qi path killer move.

Triple qi retraction!

This killer move was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, it had two very well known traits.

The first was that it was very difficult to learn.

This killer move was incredibly complex and used a lot of Gu worms, they were used interchangeably with countless steps, even wisdom path Gu Immortals would have a headache in attempting it.

The second was that the risks were huge.

Because this killer move was very complex, when Gu Immortals used it and made a mistake, the huge backlash would be inflicted on them.

If the killer move succeeded and could not hit the enemy, this killer move would return and harm the user.

Triple qi retraction had incredibly terrifying power.

The explanation started at the process of immortal ascension.

When humans underwent immortal ascension, there were three qi involved — heaven qi, earth qi, and human qi.

When Gu Masters cultivate from rank one to rank five, they would accumulate human qi in this process. When they undergo ascension, they would take in heaven and earth qi, the three qi would become one and the Gu Master would concentrate in controlling them, tossing their vital Gu in and creating the immortal aperture through an explosion.

The more human qi the Gu Master had, the more heaven and earth qi they would be able to fuse, and the higher the grade of the immortal aperture they would get.

Normally speaking, the ten extreme physiques meant incredibly abundant human qi, far beyond normal people. Or perhaps a Gu Master could make accumulations by themselves, regardless of what path, as long as one had grandmaster attainment level, their human qi would be very abundant.

After creating the immortal aperture, be it cultivation or managing the immortal aperture, Gu Immortals had to keep a balance between the three qi.

Heaven qi, earth qi, human qi, not one of the three could be lacking and break the balance.

Like Fang Yuan, after getting a secluded domain of heaven and earth like Reverse Flow River, the heaven and earth qi expenditure of the sovereign immortal aperture became extremely high. Thus, he had to place his immortal aperture often to take in heaven and earth qi of the outside world, to replenish himself and maintain balance.

Regarding the three qi, no matter which Gu Immortal or Venerable, they could not be careless about it.

In the world of the five regions, heaven and earth qi varied. If Gu Immortals who were not native took in foreign heaven and earth qi, their immortal apertures would suffer great losses, even though they could do that in an emergency situation, it could not happen a lot of times.

When Gu Immortals die, blessed lands would form. For example, in Luo Po Valley, many Central Continent Gu Immortals died in the battlefield, their immortal apertures became blessed lands in Northern Plains, but because they took in heaven and earth qi of another region, the foundation and resources inside the blessed lands were greatly damaged.

All of these explanations served to prove a point: Heaven, earth and human qi, they were incredibly important to the immortal aperture and Gu Immortals. Any imbalance would cause great damage to the immortal aperture.

And this immortal killer move, triple qi retraction, targeted this point, it directly attacked the foundation of the immortal aperture.

It was the combination of a consecutive move and variation move. Thus, the Gu Immortal who used this killer move had to be extremely skilled.

Triple qi retraction had three styles.

The first style, human qi retraction. After the target was hit, they would lose a lot of human qi, their foundation would fall. of course, if the target had no human qi, like a desolate beast, this move would have no effect.

The second style, earth qi retraction. If hit, the Gu Immortal's immortal aperture would be drained of earth qi, with a severe loss of earth qi, the three qi would completely be out of balance, the immortal aperture would be in grave danger.

The third style, heaven qi retraction. This would extract heaven qi, if a person was hit by all three moves, their immortal aperture would break apart instantly.

Purple Mountain True Monarch retreated.

He was already hit by human qi retraction. If he was hit by earth qi retraction too, the disadvantage would be too severe.

Even though Purple Mountain True Monarch knew about this move, this was his first time seeing it, he could not see through it in this short period.

This move was too complex, the more complex a move was, even though it was more difficult to use in battle, it was also harder for opponents to unravel.

After all, everything had advantages and disadvantages.

Purple Mountain True Monarch could not resolve it, he could only use his methods as he created countless clones.

At once, hundreds of Purple Mountain True Monarchs flew out randomly.

At the same time, his main body vanished.

Triple qi retraction was powerful, but if it could not hit, it was useless.

However, Duke Long was unmoved, he was completely prepared for Purple Mountain True Monarch's response.

Next, he laughed coldly as his voice spread throughout the battlefield, even though he was not loud: "It is too late, Purple Mountain True Monarch, you were hit by human qi retraction, there is no way for you to dodge the next two styles, you can only endure it!"

"Come, earth qi retraction." Duke Long paused before waving again.

He was not trying to deceive him.

Duke Long's waving motion was not in the right direction, and he did not make any investigations, he had no idea where Purple Mountain True Monarch was now, but he was still hit instantly.

Purple Mountain True Monarch was greatly shocked!

A vast amount of earth qi flew out of his immortal aperture, raging on like a storm towards Duke Long's palm, before vanishing without a trace.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's immortal aperture was greatly damaged, his foundations were crippled and his three qi had lost balance long ago, his immortal aperture was going to break apart in a few breaths' time.

At this moment, one final choice was presented to Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Placing his aperture.

Placing his aperture here.

This way, he could take in heaven and earth qi to regain balance.

But Purple Mountain True Monarch gave up on this option immediately.

This was a horrible idea!

Once Purple Mountain True Monarch placed his aperture, his main body would be stuck in his immortal aperture, he would leave the battlefield immediately and lose all initiative.

And most importantly, the immortal aperture could only take in heaven and earth qi by opening the entrance.

A passage was necessary.

And outside, Duke Long was waiting for him.

If this immortal aperture's entrance opened, Duke Long would charge in and easily deal great damage to the immortal aperture. Furthermore, he could fight or retreat at will, while Purple Mountain True Monarch would be trapped inside his immortal aperture.

"Even if I place my aperture and replenish my earth qi, the balance was long since lost due to my lack of human qi. I do not have the human path methods needed to replenish human qi, I can only buy large numbers of humans or variant humans."

Countless thoughts flashed inside Purple Mountain True Monarch's mind.

In a short time, he made his choice!

He stretched out his arm and grabbed at his stomach, before an eerie purple light shined in his hand, as his hand pulled away from his stomach slowly.

With his movement, the immortal aperture was taken out.

Seeing this, Fang Yuan felt a familiar feeling in his mind.

He thought of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had a fire path method that could take someone else's immortal aperture.

This move left a deep impression on Fang Yuan.

"How does Purple Mountain True Monarch know this?" Fang Yuan was a little puzzled but he soon understood.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was a member of Zombie Alliance to begin with, and Hei Lou Lan was firmly controlled by Shadow Sect, it was not strange for Purple Mountain True Monarch to know this method.

All the paths in the world, with a deep enough attainment, could mimic other paths and achieve their effects.

Purple Mountain True Monarch's move was evidently a wisdom path method, it could also be that he created it himself and it had nothing to do with Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Purple Mountain True Monarch took out his immortal aperture and placed it in the outside world.

The immortal aperture's entrance opened and began to take in earth qi.

But this grotto-heaven had little hope of salvation, even if the earth qi was regained, human qi was too lacking.

Seeing Purple Mountain True Monarch's resolution, Duke Long was slightly shocked, a look of admiration flashed on his face for a moment.

Chapter 1368: Capturing Spectral Soul

Purple Mountain True Monarch lost his immortal aperture, he lost his cultivation foundation. Without his immortal aperture, his future was bleak.

Forget about the future, even now, after his immortal aperture left his body, he lost a huge amount of dao marks.

Even though he kept most of the Gu worms and immortal essence with him, without the amplification of dao marks, his battle strength fell to rock bottom.

This was something he had no other way to deal with.

If his heaven qi was extracted, Purple Mountain True Monarch's immortal aperture would break apart, the winds of assimilation will blow and he would be in even greater danger of losing his life.

Triple qi retraction was simply too incredible.

It directly targeted the Gu Immortal's foundation, even the great Purple Mountain True Monarch had to discard his own immortal aperture. It was like an Iron Palm[1] martial arts expert breaking his own two arms!

Fang Yuan watched this, filled with shock.

Throughout history, there were only ten who became venerables.

Anything related to these ten existences could become extraordinary.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's formless hand was like this, so was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's reincarnation battlefield, and so was Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's triple qi retraction.

"What can we do?!" Fang Yuan thought hard on how to change the situation.

There was nothing he could do.

He could only feel glad now.

Glad that Purple Mountain True Monarch had already given him all the heavenly crystals earlier.

While manipulating the super Gu formation and resisting Fairy Zi Wei, he started to nurture the upper extreme heavenly eagle. He had a lot of heavenly crystals now, far more than the heavenly crystal eagle nest earlier, even if the upper extreme heavenly eagle became an immemorial desolate beast, the same thing would not happen again, it would not starve to death.

"Indeed worthy of Duke Long." Purple Mountain True Monarch spoke, expressing his admiration towards Duke Long.

Duke Long was too powerful.

He definitely had quasi-rank nine battle strength.

Against ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals, he could crush them. Only people like Purple Mountain True Monarch, at the peak of rank eight, and being one of the original split souls of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, having cultivated for a hundred thousand years, had the foundation and qualifications to challenge him.

But after dozens of rounds, after Duke Long's probing ended, he realized that Purple Mountain True Monarch had no true way of countering him, so he started to use his qi path trump card.

Triple qi retraction was incredibly powerful, but such a strong killer move would leave the user in horrible condition if it was countered. It was like lifting a rock and smashing it on one's own head!

Thus, any Gu Immortal would be very careful with such a killer move.

Like how Fang Yuan would rather nurture the upper extreme heavenly eagle than use reverse flow protection seal.

"In this battle, I am bullying a junior, if you were not someone who is defying fate, we might be able to sit down and have a nice conversation. After all, in this world, there are too few people who can register my interest."

"However, I believe that in the near future, the entire world will brighten up, it will become incredibly exciting."

"And I will be the person to unveil this great new era!"

Duke Long sighed, starting to chase after Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Purple Mountain True Monarch fought and retreated, he was completely suppressed.

He was hit by the first two styles of triple qi retraction, his battle strength fell drastically, he was not Duke Long's match originally, the situation was worse now.

Duke Long's attacks were powerful and unceasing, at this moment, he surpassed Purple Mountain True Monarch in every aspect.

Purple Mountain True Monarch could only hold on desperately while trying to use the killer move to create Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, but he had no choice other than to stop it.

Ying Wu Xie was still stuck in a dream realm, the other Gu Immortals only watched helplessly.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, having a heavy heart.

He quickly looked around the battlefield, Duke Long had a great advantage, Purple Mountain True Monarch was a lost cause. The only way now was to target the enemy's weakness to salvage the situation.

However, Duke Long had predicted this when he sent his forces. All of the people he sent out were powerful beings.

Ignoring Duke Long, Fairy Zi Wei had Star Constellation Chessboard, while Heaven Overseeing Tower was tough as a fortress, even though Zuo Ye Hui was attacking, it could only damage the exterior.

There were many Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals, but they could not interfere in a battle of such intensity.

"Oh no!"

"This cannot go on."

"Once Purple Mountain True Monarch loses, the entire battle will tilt in Heavenly Court's favor."

"By then, there will be too little hope for me to escape!"

"Should I retreat now?"

"Should I take a gamble on whether Heavenly Court has already found a way to counter reverse flow protection seal?"

Fang Yuan could not help but hesitate.

This was something hard to decide on.

But at this time, the battle between Purple Mountain True Monarch and Duke Long had a new development.

A blessed land's entrance suddenly opened, as a huge soul beast army appeared from within.

Purple Mountain True Monarch relied on these soul beasts to block Duke Long's attacks as he retreated into the blessed land.

"This is Shadow Sect's blessed land!"

Fang Yuan saw this as his eyes shined brightly, flashing with dazzling light.

During the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Shadow Sect's blessed land was moved here by Shadow Sect. Shadow Sect's blessed land contained the door of life and death, Spectral Soul had emerged from it to resist the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, unleashing his great power and killing Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, Heaven Overseeing Tower was destroyed and sovereign immortal fetus Gu was refined.

After the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Shadow Sect met with failure as Fang Yuan snatched the fruits of their labor. The dream realm covered the entire place and Shadow Sect's blessed land had to shut its entrance, defending from the outside.

Purple Mountain True Monarch led Shadow Sect here and had been using his killer move to turn dream realms into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

After trying hard, unknowingly, the blessed land was freed, as the surrounding dream realms were removed.

Thus, the entrance of Shadow Sect's blessed land could open again.

There were countless soul beasts inside the door of life and death, they were all mobilized now to attack Duke Long.

These soul beasts were of a massive scale, there were countless desolate beasts, with many ancient desolate beasts and even immemorial desolate beasts among them.

The soul beast army disregarded sacrifices, attacking Duke Long in a suicidal manner.

Purple Mountain True Monarch passed through the immortal aperture's entrance with the help of the soul beasts, entering Shadow Sect's blessed land.

The appearance of the soul beast army did not turn the situation around, it only gave Purple Mountain True Monarch some time to regain his footing.

"Fang Yuan, let out your upper extreme heavenly eagle, what are you waiting for?" At the same time, Purple Mountain True Monarch continued to ask Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snickered.

This was already the fiftieth time he had asked.

Ever since he was hit by the qi path killer move, he had been urging Fang Yuan to no avail. The upper extreme heavenly eagle was his final trump card, even if it was uncontrollable, he could let it out to cause chaos.

How could he release it according to Purple Mountain True Monarch's words?

"Charge in, this blessed land is Shadow Sect's base camp." Fang Yuan thought, he wanted to see Duke Long enter the blessed land and fight to the death with Shadow Sect. He wanted Shadow Sect's blessed land to be full of traps, so that Duke Long could meet with trouble.

But Duke Long did not pursue him, he stopped his movement.

Fang Yuan was disappointed, while Purple Mountain True Monarch was slightly flustered.

Duke Long's lips curled upwards, for the first time, he showed a natural smile.

He suddenly turned around, charging somewhere with the speed of lightning.

"You finally decided to come out? Spectral Soul!" He shouted, attacking as air currents raged, turning into a huge claw that grabbed at an area in the soul beast army.

"He found out!" Purple Mountain True Monarch felt like he had fallen into an icy river.

From the soul beast army, a human shaped soul emerged, he did not evade Duke Long, he attacked.

Boom!

Even the powerful Duke Long was sent flying, while that human shaped soul remained unmoved.

"Hahaha." Duke Long spat out blood but he laughed: "Spectral Soul, you are truly at your weakest."

"Damn it!" Purple Mountain True Monarch quickly charged ahead, trying to reinforce him, panic showed on his face for the first time.

Fang Yuan saw this and finally understood everything.

"Shadow Sect is truly cunning!"

"Purple Mountain True Monarch created a huge amount of Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, seemingly wanting to let Spectral Soul escape, but this was all a distraction."

"His true intention was to let out the soul beast army for Spectral Soul to devour and strengthen himself."

Spectral Soul had the supreme method of devouring souls, that was the only way he could recover his strength rapidly, he might even be able to help Purple Mountain True Monarch defeat Duke Long!

But all this was predicted by Duke Long in advance.

Duke Long attacked while Spectral Soul was still weak, Purple Mountain True Monarch had to intervene.

"Too late!" Duke Long laughed, stretching his arms as his dragon claws tore through space, forcing Purple Mountain True Monarch to retreat.

Duke Long attacked Spectral Soul again, air currents raged like dragons, entangling with Spectral Soul's main body.

Spectral Soul's main body was originally very powerful, it was considered a quasi-rank nine immemorial soul beast, it could even use Gu worms and the immortal essence he had left behind in his lifetime.

But after the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Spectral Soul only had a trace of his remnant soul left.

And this trace of his remnant soul was surrounded by dream realms, constantly consumed.

The human shaped soul roared, forcefully defending against Duke Long's methods.

Duke Long's dragon eyes shined with intense fighting spirit: "You want to resist me?"

"Oh Spectral Soul, if you were still a rank nine, I would avoid you at all costs, I would escape to the ends of the world."

"But now, you are just a remnant soul. Your Gu worms and immortal essence are not with you."

"I have been waiting for you for a long time!"

"I'll tell you the truth, I am here to capture and imprison you within Heavenly Court. So that the entire world will understand the supreme might and glory of my Heavenly Court!!"

The human shaped soul was still struggling, while Purple Mountain True Monarch attacked Duke Long like he had gone mad.

Duke Long defended against the latter easily while he looked at the human shaped soul.

He said arrogantly: "Still going to struggle pointlessly?"

"In the past, even Red Lotus Demon Venerable was stopped by me!"

"Now, surrender to me!!"

As he said that, Spectral Soul's main body was unable to defend against Duke Long's methods, he was trapped by a cage created from countless air currents.

Like what Duke Long had said, he actually managed to capture Spectral Soul's main soul body!

[1] One of the 72 arts of Shaolin. Back

Chapter 1369: Elder Brother, Quickly Lend Me Immortal Gu

Seeing this, Fang Yuan could not help but stare with wide eyes.

A rank nine venerable, with overwhelming prestige that flowed into every Gu Master's and Gu Immortal's heart, like a river of fame.

But now, Fang Yuan saw that Spectral Soul was actually captured by a rank eight Gu Immortal.

"As a matter of fact, who is this Duke Long? He is actually so strong!"

"However, thinking about it, Spectral Soul had died long ago, this is only his soul remaining."

"If his soul was in top condition, Duke Long would not be able to take him down. But unfortunately, Spectral Soul had resisted the tribulations and made great sacrifices to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu. Even though he succeeded and forced back Heaven Overseeing Tower, the result of his hard work was taken by me, Shadow Sect only had some remnant forces remaining while Zombie Alliance was wiped out, their losses were severe."

"And his own soul was depleted until only a trace was left in Yi Tian Mountain. After falling into the dream realm and being weakened for so long, it is already unthinkable that he could last this long."

Fang Yuan thought about himself, if his soul was thrown into such a massive dream realm, weakened and depleted by it, without using any dream path killer moves, he would only be able to last for a few days.

Even though Spectral Soul only had a trace of his soul left, the quality was superb, he could endure such a long period of time, even now, he could still struggle.

It was not strange that Duke Long could capture him.

After all, Duke Long was strong while Spectral Soul was currently weak.

Spectral Soul's era was over!

He had once slaughtered the world and his demonic might spread over the five regions and two heavens, it was a chaotic time period.

In his life, he was invincible in the world, he was the strongest being alive, and had the greatest status in heaven and earth.

However, time flowed like water, he eventually died.

After death, and with the appearance of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's influence was greatly reduced, peace and blessings were brought to this world.

Even after Spectral Soul died, he was not resigned to failure.

He built Shadow Sect and Zombie Alliance, attempting to defy heaven again.

Sword Immortal Bo Qing was his first attempt, but he only managed to become a pseudo-Immortal Venerable, and his corpse sank into Falling Heavenly River.

Sovereign immortal fetus Gu was his second attempt, but the world schemed against him, his hard work of a hundred thousand years was taken away by Fang Yuan.

The failure of Yi Tian Mountain and Spectral Soul's terrible loss had consumed all of his foundation. But with just Shadow Sect's remnant forces, he still whipped up a storm.

Until now, Spectral Soul failed completely and was captured by Heavenly Court's Duke Long.

"The great era is coming, antiques like myself should quietly lie down and stop trying to become the main characters of the current era. Oh Spectral Soul, your era is long gone."

Duke Long sighed as he stretched out his hand, air currents moved and carried Spectral Soul as it entered his phantom aperture.

"Ah—!" Purple Mountain True Monarch screamed at the sky, his eyes were bloodshot.

Seeing how Spectral Soul had fallen into captivity, he almost went crazy.

Even the main body was captured, all hope was lost.

A complete loss!

But Purple Mountain True Monarch was a wisdom path Gu Immortal after all, he held in the urge to seek out Duke Long for a suicidal attack.

That would truly be giving up!

He breathed in deeply and moved towards a deeper part of Shadow Sect's blessed land.

"Running? Why do you think you're going?" Duke Long floated in the air, his dragon eyes looked towards Purple Mountain True Monarch with a cold gaze.

The entrance of Shadow Sect's blessed land closed, and the soul beast army stopped charging out, they returned to defend it.

Duke Long laughed arrogantly, he turned around to look at the super Gu formation and saw that Fairy Zi Wei was making good progress, he aimed at the location of Shadow Sect's blessed land and used an immortal killer move —

Dragon Gate!

This dragon gate was majestic and huge, there were two red pillars by the side with a dragon coiling around each of them, their dragon claws were holding up the top of the gate, firm as a mountain. There were flickering dragon scales and two tough dragon bodies. The dragon bodies coiled around the huge pillars, as the dragons' upper bodies looked at each other, the dragon mouths were open with a dragon pearl in each of them, shining like radiant suns, forming a scene of two dragons and two pearls.

The dragon gate opened, the interior of Shadow Sect's blessed land could be seen.

This immortal killer move, dragon gate, could forcefully open blessed lands!

Duke Long laughed, stepping in as the dragon gate closed, before vanishing.

There was an intense battle in the blessed land, but there was no commotion outside, the entire battlefield fell into a peculiar silence.

But it could be easily imagined that Shadow Sect's blessed land was definitely not peaceful, with Duke Long inside, the soul beast army was definitely attacking him endlessly!

"What do we do?" Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Suddenly, they realized that they had no enemies left.

Purple Mountain True Monarch against Duke Long, they were inside Shadow Sect's blessed land. Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, Ying Wu Xie, and the rest were hiding inside the dream realms with the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies.

The only things moving in the battlefield were soul beasts.

Countless soul beasts were rampaging the battlefield.

A portion of them were inside dream realms, unable to escape, they were quickly dissolved by the dream realms.

Most of the soul beasts saw the dangers of the dream realms and escaped due to their survival instincts.

Soul beasts could hunt for all lifeforms with souls and devour them to strengthen themselves.

Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals quickly became the targets of these soul beasts, even though they did not want to fight.

"Wu Yi Hai, quickly send us into the Gu formation." The Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals quickly requested.

They did not want to leave.

Because now, Shadow Sect lost, Heavenly Court was likely to win. And Heavenly Court had not shown any killing intent towards Southern Border's righteous path.

Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals subconsciously thought that Heavenly Court was on their side.

After all, they were all in the righteous path, one was Central Continent's righteous path, and the other was Southern Border's righteous path.

Of course, there was also another important element that affected their judgment.

The dream realm.

This dream realm might be extremely scattered now, but from the perspectives of Southern Border's Gu Immortals, it was their resource, it belonged to them.

Furthermore, they had witnessed the battle between Duke Long and Purple Mountain True Monarch, as well as Spectral Soul's main body, they finally experienced some of the hidden details of the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain.

The huge secret of a rank nine venerable was here, there might be a fortuitous encounter, who would want to leave?

This was Southern Border's super Gu formation, and all sorts of reinforcements from the super clans were rapidly getting closer.

As for Heaven Overseeing Tower and Zuo Ye Hui, they were still fighting, with both sides in a deadlock.

Fang Yuan ordered: "Everyone, work hard to kill these soul beasts! Our reinforcements are coming closer. These soul beasts were sent by the enemy, killing them is weakening the enemy. If we let these soul beasts leave, there would be a huge problem, this is the responsibility of the righteous path!"

These words made sense, but the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals did not listen to him.

"Aren't the reinforcements arriving? Let them handle it."

"That's right, I am so tired, I need to rest."

"Even if we are not injured currently, our immortal essence expenditure was huge, we need to save up our battle strength and not waste it."

Fang Yuan snorted: "I'm telling you to go, enough nonsense."

Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals scolded and cursed, but Fang Yuan ignored them.

He was doing something very exciting.

That was asking Wu clan for help.

"Quick, it is very dangerous here, the situation is very complex, quickly send the Gu worms I need over with treasure yellow heaven!"

"No worries, I will bear all the cost myself."

"Why do I want bloodline Immortal Gu? I need to use it in the super Gu formation and increase its power!"

"It is difficult because I am borrowing so many Immortal Gu? Why are you troubled? This is not my first time borrowing Gu!"

"What? Borrowing Immortal Gu in Wu clan's internal treasury requires the first supreme elder's approval?"

Fang Yuan contacted Wu Yong.

"Elder brother, quickly lend me a hand!"

Wu Yong was controlling the Immortal Gu House and rapidly moving, hearing his brother's words, he replied: "What happened? What help do you need?"

"I am sure you know about the situation, brother, I am controlling the super Gu formation now. This is a great opportunity! It can allow our Wu clan to control this resource point and suppress the other clans, we will be free from our difficult situation!" Fang Yuan spoke sincerely.

Wu Yong was silent for a moment.

This battlefield was not sealed, Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals could communicate with their clans using information path methods.

Over at Wu clan, they only had Fang Yuan and Wu Liao, along with Qiao clan's Gu Immortals.

Thus, all of the reinforcements were familiar with the battlefield's situation, Wu Yong was no exception.

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan salvaged the situation and took over Chi Gui's spot in the super Gu formation, Wu Yong naturally knew about this.

When he first heard it, he was a little surprised, he did not expect his own brother to have such a strong formation path attainment. But Wu Yong quickly accepted it.

Why?

Because earlier, Fang Yuan had competed with Chi Shang in terms of formation path, among them, Qiao Si Liu was involved, rumors about them had caused a commotion in Southern Border for some time.

Fang Yuan exposed his formation path attainment, everyone was shocked about it, but because of that, everyone could accept this result easily.

If Wu Yi Hai were a Gu Immortal born and bred in Southern Border, he would face great suspicion. The great thing was, Wu Yi Hai came from Eastern Sea, the Southern Border Gu Immortals did not know much about him.

Therefore, Fang Yuan had ample room to act and perform.

Wu Yong heard Fang Yuan's words: He could use reputation restriction Immortal Gu to reinforce the super Gu formation and gain more benefits for Wu clan.

He hesitated.

But his hesitation had no suspicion in it.

He believed Fang Yuan.

He had not suspected that Wu Yi Hai was an impostor from the very start.

His hesitation was about how reliable Fang Yuan's plan was, and how successful it could be? If the chances of success were low, and if they failed, what would Wu clan's political situation become?

These were all things that Wu Yong had to consider, as a person in power, he needed to have foresight, he could not focus solely on immediate benefits.

Chapter 1370: Shadow Sect's New Leader?!

Wu Yong's hesitation did not last long, he quickly decided to act according to Fang Yuan's plan.

This was a great opportunity!

It was a good chance for Wu clan.

Wu Yong had been defending Wu clan and resisting the challenges sent by all the other clans earlier, it was quite a tough time, he did not want to face it again.

And he also understood, as long as he, as a rank eight Gu Immortal, did not die, Wu clan would have enough foundation in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, they would never truly fall!

Lend him!

Fang Yuan wants reputation restriction Immortal Gu, he will get to borrow it.

Bloodline Immortal Gu?

Lent.

But his action was not blindly decided.

Wu Yong and Wu clan's Gu Immortals listened to the reasons for Fang Yuan's borrowing. If there was any inconsistencies or illogical points, they would retort and reject him.

Such vigilance was the tradition of all the super forces.

Immortal Gu were unique, any Immortal Gu, even rank six, counted as the foundation of a super force.

Immortal Gu could not be lent out easily!

Fang Yuan had to make up logical reasons in this short time period, it was not easy.

But eventually, he still borrowed six Immortal Gu!

"Six Immortal Gu is about enough, if we lend more, do you have enough immortal essence to use them?" Wu Yong rejected Fang Yuan's request in a nice manner.

Six Immortal Gu lent to one person, it was a huge risk.

Not that Wu clan suspected Wu Yi Hai's identity, but if anything happened to him, these Immortal Gu would be lost, it would be a huge loss to Wu clan's foundation.

Never put all your eggs into one basket, everyone understood this logic.

Fang Yuan sighed deeply: "Oh! Brother, your reminder is true, I do not have much red date immortal essence left. Brother, lend me some immortal essence stones, I need to replenish my immortal essence!"

He decided to get some more benefits.

Wu Yong did not hesitate, he approved of it. An emperor has no use for hungry soldiers, without immortal essence, all those Immortal Gu were useless. After lending out so many Immortal Gu, they had to make sure they were used properly, right?

Fang Yuan obtained a hundred thousand immortal essence stones.

Wu clan was a super force indeed, this showed their tremendous foundation.

"Use it sparingly."

"The immortal essence stones and Immortal Gu are all lent to you, remember to be vigilant and careful!"

Wu Yong told Fang Yuan concernedly.

Fang Yuan quickly acknowledged it.

Immortal Gu and immortal essence stones were transmitted over through treasure yellow heaven rapidly into Fang Yuan's hands.

Treasure yellow heaven went into a commotion!

Once Fang Yuan obtained them, he quickly turned the immortal essence stones into his immortal essence, while tossing those six Immortal Gu into Reverse Flow River.

Suppressed entirely!

After this battle, Wu Yi Hai's identity would definitely be exposed.

Just a few words from Heavenly Court would attract sufficient suspicion. Fang Yuan could not pass intense investigations, just soul searching or checking his immortal aperture would expose him.

Thus, before running, he had to dig out the last bit of benefits possible!

"It is a huge pity I could not borrow any Immortal Gu House." Fang Yuan pursed his lips, even though he scammed Wu clan to this extent, he was not fully satisfied.

For any super force, Immortal Gu Houses had much greater significance than Immortal Gu.

They could not be lent out to Fang Yuan no matter what!

Similar to nuclear weapons on Earth, they were the last resorts of certain countries, they could not be lent out.

Unless Fang Yuan became someone like Wu Yong who had the greatest authority in Wu clan, then nobody would say anything about him having an Immortal Gu House.

Like how Hei Cheng borrowed Dark Prison due to the four Hei tribe supreme elders being forced to stay together as a result of cultivating Green City Rampage and being unable to go out alone. Hei Cheng only managed to gain his authority as a result of this.

If Fang Yuan asked to borrow Immortal Gu House, Wu Yong's first thought would be: "My brother wants to borrow an Immortal Gu House, after this battle, if he does not return it, and uses this Immortal Gu House together with Qiao clan's help to resist me, what would I do?"

Also, Immortal Gu Houses could not be completely sent over using treasure yellow heaven.

Immortal Gu Houses were Gu formations, nobody could use Gu formations or killer moves in treasure yellow heaven.

Thus, to send an Immortal Gu House over, it had to be split apart, but reconstructing an Immortal Gu House was very difficult.

Immortal Gu Houses were the apex of formation path, to create an Immortal Gu House, even if one knew about the steps involved, a formation path Gu Immortal still needed to focus entirely and put in hard work.

Any carelessness and the creation would fail, this was similar to setting up a formation, the Gu Immortal would face a backlash and the Gu formation and Immortal Gu House would also end in the same result.

The risks were too great, lending Fang Yuan so many Immortal Gu and immortal essence stones was Wu clan's limit.

This was also due to Fang Yuan being Wu Yong's brother, and the fact that he had contributed a lot to Wu clan recently. If not for Frosty Peak, Moon Bowl, and Mount Snail, Fang Yuan would not be able to borrow it.

Fang Yuan was profiting on the side, watching Shadow Sect and Heavenly Court go against each other while he reaped benefits.

Even though he tried very hard, the situation did not go according to his wishes, Heavenly Court's Duke Long was too powerful, beyond his imagination.

Shadow Sect lost and Heavenly Court won, this was basically assured.

Even Spectral Soul's main body had been captured, if Shadow Sect had any other methods, they already would have been used up.

Speaking of which, Shadow Sect's foundation was truly deep. It was a pity that their losses were too severe on Yi Tian Mountain when they tried to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu!

The loss was too great, they were unable to recover.

On their last breaths, they were still faced with Fang Yuan's pursuit, they could not develop properly.

"But I have captured Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, and gained a lot of heavenly crystals, the upper extreme heavenly eagle is currently being nurtured. And now, I scammed six Immortal Gu and a hundred thousand immortal essence stones from Wu clan, my gains are actually huge!"

Fang Yuan was good at reaping benefits.

Until this point, he did not fight to the death, he did not put in much effort, but his gains were still stunning.

"Unfortunately, dark limit Immortal Gu cannot be retrieved, I cannot take it out recklessly now, if the Gu formation breaks apart, I will need to face Fairy Zi Wei."

"There is also another problem, that is Wu clan's alliance agreement. I joined Wu clan and underwent an agreement, there is also the life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, they are still inside Wu clan's ancestral hall!"

This final problem gave Fang Yuan a headache.

The reason why he scammed six Immortal Gu was for this problem as well. If Wu clan used this relationship to try and harm Fang Yuan, he could use the six Wu clan Immortal Gu that he possessed to negotiate with them on that basis.

A great chess player would need to plan multiple steps ahead when making a move.

Even though Fang Yuan was still stuck in the battlefield now, he was planning for the future.

"Demonic path members are truly insidious and greedy beyond hope. Even before death, you are still scamming others. Oh Fang Yuan, your crimes are too severe, you will die today without doubt! Forget about running away, because with me around, you have no hope of escaping." At this time, Fairy Zi Wei's voice resounded from the super Gu formation.

Fairy Zi Wei must have known about the matter of Fang Yuan borrowing Immortal Gu and immortal essence stones from Wu clan.

There was no helping it, treasure yellow heaven was like this, it was an open market, any transaction could be exposed easily.

How could Heavenly Court not have methods to observe treasure yellow heaven and keep it under surveillance?

Fang Yuan sneered: "This is the result of Heavenly Court not exposing me earlier. It seems that you have no conclusive proof. Actually, even if you do, so what? Will Wu clan believe you? Will Southern Border's Gu Immortal world believe you abruptly? They will only believe in what they have verified themselves. These righteous path forces are like this, any sort of matter would be a political scheme in their eyes."

Fairy Zi Wei was silent, she did not speak.

She understood thoroughly that Fang Yuan was completely immersed into the demonic path, his mind was firm and determined, words could not sway him.

Fairy Zi Wei chose not to waste her effort on pointless attempts.

Her speed in invading the super Gu formation became quicker now.

Fang Yuan's expression changed, realizing that this was bad.

At this rate, even if the upper extreme heavenly eagle matured, it would be too late. The super Gu formation would break apart in advance.

He had the information path reputation restriction Immortal Gu now.

His plan was to use this Immortal Gu to control the upper extreme heavenly eagle.

But Fang Yuan did not have much confidence in this.

Because the upper extreme heavenly eagle was an immemorial desolate beast, it had rank eight battle strength, while reputation restriction Immortal Gu was just rank seven. The only thing that gave Fang Yuan hope was that he indeed had strong reputation, he could hopefully use it to allow reputation restriction Immortal Gu to display incredible power.

If it did not work, he would need to release the rampaging upper extreme heavenly eagle and create chaos, to find a chance to escape.

The battlefield was divided into four parts now.

The first and most crucial area was the battle between Purple Mountain True Monarch and Duke Long. They were fighting inside Shadow Sect's blessed land, the situation was unknown, but Duke Long had the advantage, it was highly likely that he would emerge victorious.

The second area was Heaven Overseeing Tower and Zuo Ye Hui, they were unable to defeat each other. Both sides were injured now, even with Zuo Ye Hui's incredible recovery speed, it was still covered in wounds, Heaven Overseeing Tower's edges were also breaking apart, it was no longer as grand as before.

The third area was the fight between the Southern Border Gu Immortals and soul beasts, nothing much was happening.

The fourth area was Fairy Zi Wei's and Fang Yuan's fight over the super Gu formation's control. This battlefield was the most secretive, even the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals were kept in the dark.

In Fang Yuan's opinion, it was a foregone conclusion, Heavenly Court was sure to win. In this situation, he could only escape and his plan of fishing for benefits was over.

But Fang Yuan was an old demon, even if he was about to be defeated, his gains were tremendous.

"Now, it is time to see if I can escape!"

Right when Fang Yuan was working hard on this goal, he received Purple Mountain True Monarch's words: "Fang Yuan, can we continue to cooperate?"

Fang Yuan's interest was roused: "Of course."

"Hehehe, very good, I was not wrong about you!"

"I will entrust everything to you. My Immortal Gu, my killer moves, my experiences... and you will not need to bear any responsibility or task."

"Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, White Rabbit, Miao Yin and Sixth Hair, they will all be your subordinates!"

"From now onwards, you will be the leader of Shadow Sect!"